<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3078</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweden ends ID checks on Denmark travelers imposed as migration peaked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which reddit app is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In that case GDP would be ~5-10% lower 

What model are you basing that on, and over what time period? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? Because you didn't get bombed in WW2 as hard as we did and so you had a very easy time to recover?

No...? Because the benefits of EU membership are significant in Poland, and have been evaluated by the Polish government. Poland had further to go and has done so quickly because EU membership offered things like stability for political institutions and access to a large market. Poland had institutional issues during and after the transition from communism that the UK hasn't had to deal with, it is a much greater beneficiary (rightly..) of development funding and so sees a large positive benefit in cash terms as well as political, social and economic.  That's very different from the situation in the UK for obvious reasons.  

I'm not suggesting that the UK didn't see benefits from the EU, but they fall far short of the benefits that Poland saw.

Nobody knows, if we could manage better on our own and maybe we would have rebuilt most of our infrastructure faster without any ""help"" from the EU.

I have no idea what you are talking about here now.. Neither the UK, nor Poland had help from the EU in rebuilding after WWII if that's what you are referencing, both went through some modernisation whilst in the EU (and both went through some before membership too for that matter..) but Poland was in a far worse state on joining than the UK was and it saw significant benefits in a reasonably short period of time...

True, like the fact that we got a bit of money for rebuilding parts of our highway routes? But what about the point of a free market. NOBODY knows, if we maybe had a way better situation right now, if we produced more stuff IN our country and don't import most stuff. NOBODY knows if it wasn't smarter to just trade with a few partners and export only in these.

You can create scenario's where Poland does better outside of the EU than inside it, not massively credibly, but I suppose you could.. The point however is that Poland has seen significant benefits from EU membership, it's much harder to argue that Poland could have done better outside, because it has done very well in the EU. 

If you can see in alternative realities

I can't, and I'm not suggesting I can. What I can see however are the benefits that the UK, and Poland get from the EU and look at the costs and note that Poland has some massive benefits that the UK doesn't have and so it's harder to argue that EU membership is not a good thing for Poland...

Trump was criticized by people like you (that already know what will happen in the future, apparently) that he want's to limit the trades with other countries and instead produce most wares in his own country.

Not sure what Trump has to do with anything.. but if your point is around whether limiting trade, or enabling trade is a good thing, then broadly I'd agree with the school of thought that trade is broadly beneficial to a country..

If it fails = People say: Hah, told ya. Trump has no idea what's doing. If it's good = People say: Hah, should have done that in the past 20 years already. See? It works!


Again, not sure why Trump is relevant.

We are talking about benefits of EU membership, the Polish government have looked at that over the last decade and outlined the improvements that Poland has seen, and the benefits that Poland feels it has had as a result of EU membership.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brexit: Theresa May says she'll be 'bloody difficult' to Juncker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't say that without knowing where we would currently stand if there was no EU, but I understand that this is how UK plebs try to argue..

You can argue the balance of benefits and costs though.. It's easier to do that for the UK than it is for Poland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen it from 'the rest of the EU' either, apart from possibly in this sub. Not to mention that the EU can't force Ireland to put border posts in anyway, at most it can increase checks between Ireland and the rest of the EU if it really wanted to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're putting a lot of effort into arguing an incredibly minor point

I'm really not putting a lot of effort into anything, other than pointing out that it's really not ironic for some people in Northern Ireland to identify as British as you suggest.. Because frankly it's a daft position to present.

As to your link, it's lovely, well done you for posting it, but it really isn't relevant is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State seeks to impose religious rules in Egypt's North Sinai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State seeks to impose religious rules in Egypt's North Sinai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously!?

Last I checked, Northern Ireland was part of 'The United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland' and people from the UK (often used as a short term for the above..) are often referred to, and often refer to themselves as British.

You are creating a distinction that doesn't exist unless you start defining things narrowly by geography..

Moreover, even if they lived in Gibraltar, or even Germany if they were born to a Welsh mother and a French father but identified as 'British' surely that's fine and perfectly unironic..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think the EU should just give unconditional bailouts? That's cute. 

Where did I say that? I said that the conditions attached to the various stages of the bailout were problematic, not that the bailout should have been unconditional.

Greece didn't have to accept the EU bailout, they had a choice. They could have instead faced the consequences of their own borrowing and economy. They didn't, they chose a bailout.

Indeed, they were faced with two pretty nasty choices and tool the one they felt was less damaging.  That doesn't mean that the choice they took wasn't problematic, or that the choices offered were the only ones that could have been offered.  

Again you seem to think you can blame the EU for Greece's borrowing. I don't see how. The EU didn't force borrowing on Greece.

No, I don't, and I certainly haven't said so. I do however see an issue in how the bailout was structured and have a problem with the various priorities that were attached to the stability of the Euro, the Greek economy and the impact that continues to have.

 "Chose to", not "had to", because they felt the alternative was worse.

'Had to' to prevent the alternative that they felt was worse.  That doesn't change the substance of the point at all though.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're part of the UK. That's the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland. 

Indeed, and it gets shortened variously to UK, GB and Britain, as you are well aware, and the people who live there are often referred to as British.  Why then would it be ironic for people in Northern Ireland to Identify as British?

You might as well whinge that someone corrects you when you say Northern Ireland is part of England.

Except obviously that that is wrong and not accepted shorthand for the UK, and quite annoying for a large number of people in say, Northern Ireland.

It really shouldn't be surprising, and it certainly isn't ironic that some significant number of people in Northern Ireland identify as British. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I.. I must confess. I'm not used to talking to normal people on here. Not sure what to do next.

I could insult you in some way if it helps..

All in though, it's going to be really quite interesting to see how this all continues to develops, assuming no-one does anything irrational or incredibly stupid (and then it'll still be interesting, just in a less fun way..).

Anyway, have a nice one.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given it's part of Britain not really... I don't think people who are British are identifying purely with the geography, but rather with the country that 'Britain' is shorthand for.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue isn't the bail out, it's the conditions that have been attached to the various bail out stages.  Greece is between a rock and a hard place, and some of the 'rock' aspect is essentially of the EU's making, the result has been pretty nasty for people and businesses in Greece, and at times at the expense of financial institutions that presented a systemic risk to the rest of the Eurozone if they weren't supported (indirectly, via bail outs to Greece..). 

It isn't just an issue in Greece (although it is amplified by the Euro..), it's essentially a much more problematic playing out of the same issue we saw in other countries, where governments had to prop up banks rather than leaving them to fail on the back of poor lending decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd have to order them if I want them from the bank.. 

That said, I bought my second^^1 car cash, and took 1500 out in 50 notes.. I've never felt quite so paranoid, I'm sure everyone could tell.

^^1 I bought my first car with cash too, but at 250 a roll of 20's worked out.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Kaczynski doesn't like then he should leave the EU.

Is this the default now... You can't disagree with stuff, you have to leave? Usually backed up by 'we pay you!', which starts to sound a lot like 'we thought we'd bought you' after a while.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This debate is actually not really Brexit related and has gone on for a long time beforehand.

I'm aware, it has been rumbling on for quite a long time, and it's one area where the UK has been quite active. It has however been pulled out as a stick a few times, it's not as though there hasn't been a refrain from some areas (Again, since before the UK voted to leave the EU) that clearing should occur within the Eurozone (never mind the EU..). 

Basically, if the EU wants to force Euro clearing from the UK, it will be violating an ECJ ruling, and will likely need to rescind equivalence for a lot of other countries that handle Euro clearing too.

Yeah, and the EU likely won't because it'd be (as you point out) detrimental to the Euro more generally.  It's not like it hasn't been tried before, so we know what the impact would likely be.  

The concern really is around how the EU approaches these draft proposals and develops them, there is a lot of pressure from the likes of France to take a more protectionist approach (and IIRC France had exchange controls on the Franc up until 1990..) without the balancing effect of the UK, although in this area Germany is fairly sane too so...

It's widely known in the market that coordinated central bank buying has long supported the euro at its weakest points over the past few years. If that confidence goes, then all bets are off.

Yeah, and no-one in the EU wants to cut themselves off from international markets whether directly or indirectly as a result of regulation, the direction of travel (and as with MIFID..) is in the other direction.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is balance. Yes there was and is a brain drain, but there is also investment in Poland (which is now labelled by some as exploitative, when that certainly isn't the case in most instances). The question is whether the balance is right, so membership and participation in the EU is net positive for the member state in question. Obviously that is different depending on the state, but for Poland, it seems to a net positive (based on what the Polish government has said, and what others have said).  

That could change in the future, it could change for other member states, but right now it'd be pretty hard to suggest that the EU has been anything other than beneficial to Poland to at least some degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's quite a bit harder to paint EU membership as a bad thing for Poland than it is for say the UK, but the Polish government does do a nice job of looking at it fairly regularly [see here](http://www.msz.gov.pl/en/foreign_policy/foreign_economic_policy/costs_and_benefits/). Some of those reports are well worth reading, and far from uncritical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends heavily on the way that oversight occurs, the suggestion that the move would end up "forcing UK operators to either relocate or be policed by European authorities." is quite a lot stronger than the US approach, but essentially you are right, it's a continuation of a story that has veered from the EU pulling Euro clearing into the Eurozone to the EU revamping oversight provisions. And as you point out, MIFID II is going to be quite positive generally for third countries and obviously helpful in terms of simplifying regulatory approaches..

Not a non-story though, the drafts are important, as is the approach being taken to risk.  It's probably also interesting in a political context (nothing in a vacuum and all that..).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah cheers, didn't see that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poland outraged after Macron comments on Le Pen and Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK manufacturing growth spikes to three-year high in April </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree on it being a much larger risk.

Fair enough, but I would then ask what risk the UK poses to the EU that is much greater than the Euro taking a step on clearing that would be perceived as internationally hostile.  Although we can leave that there if you prefer (But I am seriously intrigued as what risk you see coming from the UK..). 

Apart from this and from Gibraltar, what's your take on a trade deal between the UK and the EU?

A mutually beneficial deal would be.. beneficial, and entirely possible. It'd be better to do it sooner rather than later given the current convergence on regulations and I think the EU and UK would both benefit from a continued push on the international level that maintains standards and regulatory approaches.

Although I do think the UK approach has been better and a good influence on the EU more widely.  [See this from the Government Office for science](https://www.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/381905/14-1190a-innovation-managing-risk-report.pdf), specifically (although the whole thing is worth reading..):

*...there are two fundamental confusions that bedevil debate on several important regulatory topics, particularly within Europe. The first is the
way in which the notions of hazard and risk are differently embedded in national modes of policymaking. This is why it is so important that we share a common understanding of the distinctions between hazard, risk, and vulnerability.*

*The second is a drift of interpretation of the precautionary principle from what was, in effect, a holding position pending further evidence, to what is now effectively a stop sign. To be meaningful, the precautionary principle requires a rational response to uncertainty (as distinct from risk.)*

On what basis should it be build?

On areas of mutual interest. We have a lot of overlapping interests, even outside of a political union. The UK would be looking for a looser, and so likely less comprehensive arrangement when compared to the single market, but one that is as comprehensive as possible within the political limitations that the EU is working under..

Like the customs union (preventing the UK from doing other deals)?

It seems reasonably clear that the UK is leaving both the Single Market and the Customs union, largely that is about ensuring that the UK is as free to trade with the rest of the world as is possible, presumably at least in part to counterbalance the loss of the very deep integration it had as part of the EU.

The EU said the 4 freedom are inseparable, so a full trade deal like the current one can't happen

Indeed, and that's a shame given the UK can't agree to the 4 freedoms (or rather, the principle of the four freedoms, there are still issues within the single market, some of which happen to be very important to the UK on services..). That on its own means that the UK will be looking for an FTA rather than being integrated into the single market.

How far from that full trade deal should it be?

That depends on what the EU and UK can agree on really..

Regarding the 60B sum the UK agreed to pay, should it be repaid? Should it be part of the negotiation?

The UK hasn't agreed to pay 60B AFAIKT.  That said, it seems clear that the UK has obligations, including financial ones to the EU, and the EU will likely also be seen to have financial obligations to the UK, so I'd assume a negotiated figure could be identified and paid by the UK.  That should be part of the exit negotiations of course.

I'd probably say that in terms of the negotiations, the exit and trade terms are somewhat distinct, there is some overlap, but they should be negotiated separately. There is no real reason why there can't be some concurrency though.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible, but extremely unlikely given you'd then create issues not only with unionists in Northern Ireland, but pretty much every nationalist and unionist in the other parts of the UK too. IIRC even the advice currently on carrying some ID causes some people to get upset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pelosi: I could be 'helpful' to Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Erdogan says Turkey has nothing to discuss with EU unless new accession chapters opened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Erdogan says Turkey has nothing to discuss with EU unless new accession chapters opened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the UK want to undermine the peace process then they'll answer for it obviously.

Anyone who does so will, and frankly should answer for it.

Right now though, neither the Irish government, the UK government or the EU seem keen on causing any issues, imposing a border or otherwise messing with the CTA or rights that Irish and UK citizens have in either country.

So the issue is non-existent until someone acts either in bad faith, or takes the piss by trying to use the issue for leverage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five countries sit on 90 percent of cash injected by ECB: study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five countries sit on 90 percent of cash injected by ECB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German minister in pre-election dispute over 'dominant culture' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swiss spy agency defends practices after German arrest in tax case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on lad, lets not create new conspiracy theories for people to latch on to.. Especially not whilst there is an Argentinian pope in the Vatican, it'll get out of hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because the EU says something, doesn't mean the EU will get that in the negotiations though. The reason the UK is saying things that are contradictory to the EU position, is because the UK position is contradictory to the EU position. Oh and if there isn't compromise, then neither the UK, nor the EU position is going to end up reflecting reality, because the UK will end up leaving without a deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK leaving the EU isn't an existential threat to the EU though, so whilst you are absolutely right that the continued existence of the EU is a benefit, it isn't at issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think everyone has already been reasonably clear, the UK and Ireland included, that no-one wants to put up border posts, and you are absolutely right, anyone who decides that they need to put them in will spend most of their time looking over their shoulder, so it seems somewhat unlikely on that point alone.

For anyone looking for a united Ireland, the deal between the UK and the EU is going to be pretty important.  There isn't any need for a roll back of the progress made over the last few decades in Ireland, the only way that happens is if someone tries to use Ireland, or the North as leverage, which I think neither the UK nor Irish governments would do, but I guess we'll see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I see it, the options are to either figure this out, or to become irrelevant in the world.

Somewhat. But I agree with the premise, however in the run up to the UK's referendum I've come to the conclusion that I don't think the EU will figure that out. It's not getting any better at the moment and frankly, once the UK leaves I can see things becoming more problematic not less, especially if weight is seen to shift more toward Germany and France.

You're right about that, but just technically. You've also got FN and PVV euroskepticism. But what the Dutch elections demonstrated is not just that these kinds of views are generally minority views which depend on foreign support to make any traction significant whatsoever, but that an even minimal counteracting of of foreign material support, such as that recommended by the AIVD was sufficient to restore the organically-occurring political minority status of Dutch euroskepticism.

I don't mean simply euroscepticism from the likes of the FN or PVV, I mean disagreements between member state governments about the role, priorities and scope of the EU. You have countries that aren't on board in terms of defence, other countries that have issues around migrant policy, other countries that are poorly served by the management of the Euro and so disagree about the direction and scope of reforms, and a whole slew of other minor and major issues.  Now in the past, say 3 years ago, I'd have said fine, that'll get worked out over time and you'll end up with a consensus that works. Now I'm not sure that is possible at all, not just because of the differences in opinion, but because there is a disconnect between popular positions, government positions, the EU position and what is actually needed to fix some of the issues the EU faces.  It's not insurmountable by any means, but I don't see there being a lot of appetite to try and tackle it from those who can.  

In essence it seems a lot of people are wary of pushing anything, in case it breaks something.  At the same time, others are building new stuff, but not on solid foundations, which means that after a certain point, people get wary of pushing to fix the foundations, because it might break something...

 The first thing that europe needs to do to get its house in order is to fix its economic institutions in such a way as that european stability can actually be had. And to a certain extend, it'll mean telling the Germans to STFU on the economic front, if we want to see europe-wide progress on things like monetary policy and institutional crisis response mechanisms.

IMO, everything will need to start on the economic front.

You probably aren't wrong, although I'm not sure that you have to start with the institutions around the Euro (and frankly, without the EU you are going to get massive pushback from non-Eurozone countries if further attempts are made to use EU institutions and mechanisms to support the Euro..). I'd argue that the first thing the EU has to do is come up with a vision for itself (one, not several options..) that member states buy into. That way the reform has an intended aim, rather than the current situation where you have several different states looking at several different aims.

Maybe agreement on a multi-speed EU has to happen first, but even that seems quite a long way from being likely given the objections raised last month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not a power grab. This is sensible risk management.

It's not sensible risk management, it introduces a much larger risk than the one you are suggesting might come from the UK (which is generally seen very much as the opposite of a risk, which is a factor in why it has the position it does in finance).

If you try to force Euro clearing to happen in the EU (unlike every other reserve currency on the planet, including the dollar and the pound for that matter..) you make it less attractive, if you do so on the back of essentially a protectionist, political argument, it becomes even less so.  Would you want to trade using the Euro if the EU can arbitrarily fuck around with you? Probably not.  Not to mention you'd end up with massive secondary markets springing up anyway, so it'd do little to solve whatever problem the EU is trying to solve and do everything to reduce confidence in the Euro as a reserve currency.

You are right that it isn't a power grab though, the ECB and EU can legislate and regulate however they want, that is within their control, it'd be unwise, potentially harmful and somewhat pointless, but it's not really a power grab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The has the resources to do so (both economic/industrial and manpower/expertise). It's just a question of organizing and coordinating it more than anything else.

It goes a bit beyond that, it's about whether member states are willing to cede control in various areas to the EU. That's actually quite hard, especially when you get into areas of competing interests and national positions.

We'll see. TBF, British (and specifically Torry) skepticism has been a major roadblock to the deepening of europe. Europe's liberals have been claiming for some time now that w/o that kind of obstructionism, we'd have a more organized europe by now.

So we'll see how far this gets.

The problem there is that it isn't uniquely British scepticism (and frankly, the issue is broader than Tory scepticism..), it's arguably the difference between seeing trade as a priority and seeing the political project as a priority. That's where the clash between deeper integration and expansion occurs too. The UK is far from unique in being more pro expansion than integration.

Of course there is an opportunity for change now, as the UK leaves the political settlement is going to change, but I honestly don't think that in quite a few areas, there is enough consensus for real moves forward and a real risk of steps being taken that aren't build on a solid foundation, leading to a crisis further down the road again, it seems to be a bit of a pattern, especially where the EU is pushing things for which there isn't broad public support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In that case, My feeling is that Guy Verhofstat's suggestion that the EU should actually finally develop some serious operational capacity on the world stage might get taken more seriously.

It might, but most of the proposals seem to be presented as ways that member states can reduce costs by working through the EU rather than creating new capabilities or capacity. It seems less about doing more, and more about having the EU do, or at least appear to do it.

And if we took capacity-building when it comes to intra-EU economic affairs, or international/military affairs more seriously, the attractiveness of membership would look very different.

That's very true, the real question is whether the EU can deliver. I ended up voting leave because I don't think the EU is capable of the reform needed to support what you are suggesting (and in other areas). Essentially I think you'll end up with a cludge that doesn't work very well, quite possibly one that creates more problems that it solves and that is quite dangerous if you are talking about defence and foreign affairs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it has.. Sure, some people seem intent on equating any act of violence with terrorism, but it doesn't seem like a very accepted definition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does, but the EU also runs a lot of it's own little projects in that areas, often in parallel with NATO and other organisations, so the UK ceasing to be involved on that side will make it harder for the EU to act, although that'll likely just mean more contributions from France and other EU members.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brussels set for power grab on London euro-clearing market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is anyone surprised the UK and EU do not agree about Brexit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brexit: UK 'will not enter into briefing war' with EC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brexit: UK 'will not enter into briefing war' with EC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brexit: UK 'will not enter into briefing war' with EC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not in most cases, usually has a political or ideological dimension, most of the school shootings you see tend not to have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shootout leaves eight dead near Mexico's Los Cabos tourist hub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. issues travel alert for Europe, citing threat of terrorist attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the identity theft, but the apparently complex process to deal with it. Where I've had issues with a business account in the past (which generally have poorer protections than individual ones) I've had the money back immediately and been able to resolve the issue fairly rapidly between a couple of emails and a phone call. I certainly didn't have to go into a branch to sign anything or have to wait for a period for transactions to be reversed.   The Identity theft protections on my personal account are (At least on paper) pretty strong, again, with immediate repayment of any money and essentially the burden on the bank to solve the problem in relation to their stuff.  That might be because my bank has reasonable protections in place to prevent someone moving or withdrawing money without a card+pin, passwords or a secure dongle etc.. but the idea that my bank would be an issue if I suffered from identity theft seems a bit bizarre (others, like say any companies that someone had set up contracts with can be harder of course).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU would not survive Le Pen presidency, French PM says in newspaper column </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you cannot do is to play the enforceability card

Right.. But we don't have a full conversation, or any context, just an extract. I doubt very much that Davis went in with 'well you can't make us pay!' and that we are only getting a very small aspect, of one view of a conversation.  That was my point.

Well, this was the Economist - not really a bastion of the Radical Left.

Nor is the Times.. I'm not saying that this is some leftist conspiracy, I'm saying that the media across the board aren't exactly trying to present a nuanced picture.

And - while this may well be a "strategic" leak - I do not think even for a second that its contents are false, as it would just be too easy to disprove everything.

I doubt it's false, but I'm also willing to bet its not complete in any sense and that it fails to accurately portray the discussions that were had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The exchange wasn't leaked by the UK government to be fair, and there are valid questions about the enforceability of 'debt' that isn't agreed.  It doesn't take much context to turn the exchange from being a Junker 'burn' of an incompetent, to something very different.  I don't think it betrays utter incompetence, bordering on stupidity, I think it's a slanted presentation of a serious issue to which there are no terribly easy answers.

My point again though is that Davis isn't an idiot, Junker presumably isn't either, both have differing positions, and both the UK government and various parts of the EU seem intent on pointing out that the other side has no idea what they are doing.  Some of the more amusing presentations of that (via the Guardian, Independent, and Times in the UK in the very least) are so one sided it's almost laughable. The EU side takes their negotiating positions as absolute fact and any notion that the UK might have different positions as idiotic and some on the UK side seem keen to take EU negotiating positions as 'threats'.. In either case, they are negotiating positions, not facts, or threats, they will move..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, but the hassle/stress of someone getting your info, using a fake debit card, overdrawing your account, having to take off work to sign papers for it, waiting on the bank to credit you back, and dealing with any disputes, I could see how some people wouldn't want to.

To be honest, reading this makes me wonder what the fuck is wrong with your banks.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone who can't think who it was.. it was you.

On that note... Once, when I was duty driver, I did make myself a brew in the guardroom without asking if anyone else wanted one. I essentially spent the next 5 nights driving and making tea.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wanted to have an EU willing to give the UK conditions that all other members did not have, on account of the UK sense of superiority.

Not so much on account of a UK sense of superiority, but on the basis that it would be better for the UK (oh, and the concessions he was after weren't all UK specific..). That's sort of the job of the government.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Davis seems to be a monumental idiot, totally out of his depth. 

The problem is that he isn't. I've spoken to him a few time (albeit on civil rights issues and extradition, not the EU) and he certainly isn't an idiot. That was before he was a minister, and as a minister he obviously has access to rather a lot of information and decent briefings. I seriously doubt that he is under briefed, or that the UK civil service is providing weirdly skewed information either.

I'd be really careful about assuming anyone, on the 'other side' to your position (or mine..) is an idiot, if they are doing something that looks like it might be harmful, my first question would be whether that position is subject to movement, likely to be used as leverage somewhere else, or whether from their perspective, it doesn't look as damaging as the alternatives.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Supreme Court sides with Venezuela over oil rigs claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my Nougat update today and, after setting the default launcher to the google launcher (because that's what I had before..) I haven't noticed any major differences so far. I disable notifications on the lock screen so no idea about how or whether that works properly, but rotation works as expected.  I did lose a clock and calendar widget though, and I think there has been a subtle font change that I don't really like, but I'll tweak it.

Biggest annoyance so far is the truecaller dialler, but I can swap that out too..  So, so far, not too bad given there was a solid reason for the change, but I'll wait to see what happens in terms of battery life before I'm entirely happy.

Edit: Some updates. The bluetooth kept crapping out as I was driving today, that's never happened before (losing connection to the car and coming back again 10-15s later), and It randomly rebooted too.  Not happy with that, but I'll have a closer look as to what is going on.

Edit: Further. No more reboots and the bluetooth seems fine now for extended periods.. Might have just been teething problems (I've done one full reboot now) but it all seems happy, reasonably fast and stable and battery life seems OK too..
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much appreciated. Ta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't see it. Cheers! (Have you got a link? reddit search being crap and I was looking for the discussion..). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cameron didn't want a brexit either, he essentially wanted to have an EU that the UK would have fewer issues with, and felt that without that eurosceptisism would rise in the UK..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pretty important point. Almost everyone thinks the EU needs reform, but that reform comes in a million different forms some diametrically opposed to others.  We saw that in the EU referendum in the UK, both on the remain and the leave side, it's not exactly surprising that it's a reasonably common refrain.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Airways tied up and offloaded 'diabetic passenger' at remote military base over business class row </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Airways tied up and offloaded 'diabetic passenger' at remote military base over business class row </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but it'd have to be a pretty bad deal.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at the outer border, which is the point.

Yes at the outer border, and of the customs union, not the EU border at that, you can have goods enter the customs union via Turkey and not be inspected at all (entry based on the paperwork submitted and agreed, tariffs paid etc.. before they hit the border).

And if it doesn't want to it would have to make sure it doesn't happen, haha. And its fellow EU member states would have to insist.

On that basis any EU country could allow whatever goods it wanted into the EU via their ports given there are no internal borders.. 

All those things and checks, unless Northern Ireland is planning to accept EU regulations.

It's not and the UK won't be putting up a border, and nor will Ireland, and the EU won't demand it.. Again, this has been pretty well covered, there are lots of ways around it, the EU seems keen on that (from its own negotiating documents) so does everyone else.

Seriously, it doesn't feel like we're past "no border because don't want" here.

The thing with countries is that if they don't want something, they can generally not have it. Between the EU, Ireland and the UK, I'm really not sure who you think is going to impose a hard border..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely the question is how you'd make it workable. If we had a referendum on the terms (which would presumably have to be an accept/don't accept of whatever is negotiated with the EU) what happens if the answer is no? The clock runs out on the negotiations and we go from whatever the government and EU put together to no deal at all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where?

Lots of land borders, hell, including the EU for traffic passing through the EU rather than destined for the EU.. Electronic manifests, container weights, 'bonded' or otherwise approved secure warehousing etc..  The point being that if Ireland wanted to allow dubious goods into the EU it could anyway, by virtue of having a coast. As it is it can be managed and sensibly, with the usual precautions against smuggling and obviously all the usual things, like rules about standards and so forth apply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's natural and just part of the normal bureaucracy for ports and airports, but there's a land border between Ireland and Northern Ireland. Once the stuff is off the ship, you have a much harder time tracking it. It could be delivered to a destination in Northern Ireland and have no guarantee that it is not repacked and doesn't end up in Ireland or the rest of the EU later on. So, you could either deny entry at an Northern Irish port or do additional checks when stuff is shipped from Ireland to the rest of the EU.

Right now stuff comes across land borders without being checked at every port and border.

 I don't think it's going to be easy to find an agreement there.

If you put a border between the UK and Ireland, some Irish people are going to start blowing things up. Quite possibly not just in the UK, so there's that.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right now we have remote storage but is there remote processing to the same degree?

Arguably yes, anything that is heavy on the server side is arguably remote processing (so my accounting app, that takes a photo of a receipt, ocr's it and adds it to a ledger etc.. or youtube when it handles the conversion of your video on upload and lets you edit etc..). There are a whole host of things where you pass the heavy lifting off on to something else, even things like web based document editing (docs..) could quite easily pull processing server side if there was a need.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see that the old woolly jumper might be a more british term, but I'm reasonably sure jacket is fairly universal..  I was tempted to use kagoule instead, but it doesn't really work in context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't call it a gimmick, if my smart phone is powerful enough to do most of what I need a desktop PC to do, why not just have monitor/keyboard/mouse terminal set-up at my desk and save a bunch of money?

Because mostly it won't be. It'll be usable, but you'd probably be better off with a cheap laptop and a cheap phone than a PC replacement phone.

 And then I don't have to worry about transferring files if I don't want to, they would all stay on one device that I always carry around.

See my other comment on this - the direction of travel is to have your data and services, calendar, email etc.. available anywhere, from anything, formatted for that device and so on.  We don't have to worry about having the right data on the right device anymore (I don't like using 3rd party services, but even I can get at anything I want, on any device, from the NAS at my house..). 

And as I said in the other comment, it's great that people are still looking at this, but I don't think the problems that we found 5 years ago have obvious solutions yet, and the world has moved in a very different direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right to a certain extent.. But the direction of travel has been somewhat in the other direction.

Rather than thinking about your PC or phone, or tablet or whatever, the direction has been to think about the data and applications that you use. So you can have a computer, a phone, a smart watch, a tablet etc.. and access all the stuff on your google/microsoft drive, use web apps and so on.  You don't need to use the same device, because you can have your data and applications (and music, video, photos etc..) delivered to whatever device you want, wherever you are. 

You aren't using your tiny PC to connect to your home PC, you are using both to connect to well optimised services geared toward their capabilities..

Why would you disconnect your phone from a display and keyboard at home rather than say, using your smart TV, or a cheap computer (or your voice activated gadget that can read and write to your calendar, notes, blog... etc.) to do the same thing. 

And again, that's sort of true now, I can control my PC from my laptop, manage navigation and routes that will be displayed on my phone from my PC. I can set alarms on my smart wrist band thing from my phone, or set them on my PC. I can view documents, emails, social media messages and so on on my tablet, PC, or phone, all optimised for the display and performance.

And I can do it without having to try and compromise (scaling my dual monitors onto a single phone display? Not thanks, and whilst we are at it, why do I need a 6 inch display on my phone?)..

Trying to make one device that does lots of things well in a modular fashion has been tried lots of times and it does involve compromose. It usually falls down either because you have an underpowered device (and your phone is still under-powered even compared to a cheap sub-notebook..) or you need lots of (often proprietary) bits to plug into it to make it work.  

And of course there is a temptation to create a UI for an OS that will work across everything (see windows 10, Unity, or KDE's current attempt at plasma across small devices..) which so far has been more hit than miss.

Given that these days we have very mobile and portable data it's easier to see computers, phones and all that other guff as simple terminals (with their displays and interfaces geared toward their use cases) but not to a particular server (your PC at home) but to your data.

Now you might be able to sell a PC/phone thing as a way of not buying two devices, but frankly the savings aren't there. I can buy a phone for 99 and a laptop for 199, both perfectly capable of fulfilling their roles and have way more computing power than a phone for 399 that compromises in both areas (likely on battery life or heat in its phone role, and performance in its desktop role), and you aren't saving anything...

That's not to say people shouldn't keep playing with this idea (like I said, I found it very interesting when I was playing around with it..) but I doubt it's going anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right.. But at the time it was pretty solid, and very quick. I could type a document on it, browse the web and so on without many issues, the point was that the novelty of hooking it up to a monitor and a keyboard was just that a novelty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're working for Elon Musk, the goals of his companies are to further the prosperity of mankind not to line the pockets of employees.

And yet still subject to the same rules as anyone else. He can't undercut the minimum wage, employee protections or anything else because he claims the moral high ground in terms of his companies objectives..

Maybe you could ask Grohmann why he paid them 75% of the going rate.

I was under the impression (and I might be wrong..) that the issue is pay for more hours because of the increased operational tempo with the model 3 production, but again, that might be wrong. I think it's also the case that the company was grown to accommodate the new work when Tesla bought the firm and so reached the point where there were enough employees to trigger the application of the collectively agreed wages.  The point to note in either case is that Grohmann is now having issues recruiting, as well as the problems with the union.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, it was nice to be able to do (I demoed it a few times, I think I watched a film or two too) but it wasn't practical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are on android, you can cast your screen (buy a cheap chromecast) and use a bluetooth keyboard. That'll even work on a monitor with the relevant inputs. It's painful though.. By all means give it a go, I spent a long time playing with various embedded linuxes on odd hardware before android was a thing, with the idea of having a 'real' pocket computer, but the end results were generally less appealing than the other options (and at that point it was a Thinkpad X41 Tablet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read it again.. (and it came earlier this year, I even got the summer duvet out, today.. the heating is on again..) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 80.6 fareneagles apparently. Means nothing to me though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you can do that now, and almost no-one does because it's actually incredibly unwieldy and you are better off with almost any other option (tablet with a keyboard, laptop etc..). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But like he said, that union has a vested interest in the carbon industry which Tesla is trying to put out of business. Maybe Grohmann workers need another union which shares Tesla's environmental goals.

The union disagrees and frankly it's not up to the employer which union the employees decide to be members of.. 

I mean it's taking the piss really, can you imagine any other large employer getting away with that? 'Oh no, the unions doesn't have our interests at heart, so we don't want people to be a part of it', no shit. The union has its members interests at heart, and you are in a fight with the union not because it's doing something you don't like, but because you aren't paying the relevant amount to staff...

I mean, how exactly does paying 75% of the usual rate fit into the whole 'they don't share our values' thing anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me a single example outside of the EU. Well, maybe there are examples, I don't know, but only if there are similar common regulations involved as in the single market. You see, goods and people that are rightfully in one member state of the EU have the right to enter all other states.

Well. there's the common travel area that exists between the UK and Ireland (and predates the EU..), the  Nordic Passport Union also predates the EU, but if you'd like some other examples, there's Russia and Belarus, India and Nepal too, and lots of places with very weak border controls without the kind of integration the EU has too...

That's why Schengen works at all, the passport checks at the inner borders where useless by then anyway, for the individual exceptions Schengen introduced increased cooperation of the national authorities, border checks where delegated to the EU outer border. At the Schengen outer border, all you need to do is prove that you're an EU citizen.

Right.. but the UK and Ireland have external borders that are managed (by virtue of being an island) and cooperate on visas (as part of the CTA) outside of Schengen.  So if you arrive in the UK now, even though the UK and Ireland are not in Schengen, you can go to Ireland and the reverse is true too.

Schengen is about how you manage your borders, it shows that with the appropriate external controls you can do whatever you want with your internal borders, and it has nothing to do with free movement (a Chinese person can get a Schengen visa, but won't have the right to reside or work for example..). The same would be true in Ireland and the UK. It doesn't matter if a Canaidan national can cross the border into the UK, because they will have gone through an Irish airport anyway, same goes for an American entering Ireland from the UK.  In neither case would they have any special rights to work...

Outside of the EU, British goods and people have no automatic right to enter the EU, and the only way to be sure is to stop trucks at the border. Either to see what's in there or to check if the paper work says it's ok to enter. There is no other way to know what's in this truck.

Yeah.. So you use the various tools we have now to track consignments and containers between ports and trucks. Everything else is smuggling anyway, and we have to (and do..) deal with that already between the UK and Ireland and indeed between EU countries in Schengen.  The idea that you absolutely need a fence to stop it is a little archaic given we have goods that arrive from say Taiwan, go through the Netherlands and are then shipped to various places around the globe.

The agreements between the UK and Ireland will definitely have to be part of the Brexit negotiations, because Ireland can not ignore its obligations towards the EU, and the single market can not have a hole of the size of Ireland in its borders.

They don't have to ignore their obligations, they can meet them without a hard border.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We don't have to worry about that until about the middle three days of August.

That's not fair, we have that one random day in March where the freezing aftermath allows everyone to quip 'well, that was summer then' and that one day in October where everyone is caught off guard in jumpers and jackets even though it is inexplicably 27 degrees and sunny suddenly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huge correlation between the two.

There is a correlation between people going to university, and people being smart. There is not a correlation between being smart and going to university, or rather that correlation weakens significantly as you go further back. It's not a small difference either, if you look at the numbers we've gone from 3.5 per 10k of population getting a first degree in 1950, compared to 65 per 10k of population in 2016. That compounds rather rapidly, and the  university admission numbers accelerated after 1997, it's not a gradual increase.

To put it another way, more people graduated in 2016 than did between 1950 and 1960... By a really large margin.

One begets the other. Take two people of the same intelligence, one goes to university and gets a job which involves a lot of thought and research. The other goes straight from school to a factory job. After forty years, the first one will be more intelligent than the second.

What if you take two people, one goes to university, the other does an apprenticeship, or trains as an accountant? The point is that university access has massively increased in the last few years. In isolation it is not a great data point, especially given that for a huge number of jobs, requirements for a degree are very recent too. Someone getting a computer science degree, or an English literature degree now isn't necessarily any more intelligent than someone who has spent the last 10 years as a programmer, or as a writer.  

The 'educated' numbers are skewed massively because we've entirely changed our approach to higher education.

If you take say social class as a guide, instead of age or level of education, it reduces the amount of skew by quite a bit:

AB went 59% for remain, C1 closer to 52% C2 went 62% for leave and DE 54% leave. So that C1 class is almost 50/50 split, even though it includes professionals and junior management..  In fact the DE grouping which would be your factory worker, (Semi-skilled and unskilled manual workers) were less likely to vote leave than skilled manual workers..

Compare that to the point about 70% of degree holders voting remain and 70% or those with no qualifications voting leave which seems to correlate far more closely with age (under 34 vs over 55's..) than with anything else..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schengen? really? I don't know what specific type of border you are thinking of ... I can not look inside your head, but I want to stress one last time: after the UK left the EU and the single market, as the standard option, there's going to be an EU outer border between Ireland and Norther Ireland.

There will be a border, in the same way that there currently is a border. A point where the UK ends and Ireland begins, where UK law applies, and where Irish law applies. What there won't be are checkpoints, a fence, or a major barrier.  The reasons for that are the agreements that the UK currently has with Ireland, the GFA, and because there is no need for one, the Irish and UK governments don't want one, and no-one can impose one..

 Then it is Ireland's duty to regulate all traffic of goods and people between that border to meet the rules of the single market.

Indeed, and the UK will want to regulate all traffic of goods and people too. Happily, that can be done without a hard border, as it is done elsewhere. And that is what the UK and Ireland will likely work to achieve, likely with the support of the EU..

You dived into a comment chain about the need for a hard border, there isn't going to be one. There will be a border, there will be customs and immigration processes, but there aren't going to be walls and checkpoints dividing the Island of Ireland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I am just going to respond to this part, as it is the easiest: The UK-EU border is not an EU outer border at this point, there's freedom of movement of goods and people across that border. 

Yes.. but it is a border. The UK isn't in Schengen so there are passport controls and so on. The border exists in reality not just as an administrative boundary.

The EU/UK border right now is nothing like it will be after Brexit is finalized.

For the most part the border itself won't change, the customs process will and obviously immigration processes will too, and the rights people have one way or the other (Whether it's in terms of goods or people) will be different and managed differently. 

The only way that there is not going to be one of the three borders (EU/Ireland, Northern Ireland/Ireland, Northern Ireland/UK) is when the UK remains a full member of the single market, which is very unlikely, otherwise the UK would enjoy full freedom of movement as a non-EU-member. 

The UK is not going to be in the single market, but there is still no requirement for a hard border and no interest from those who would have to put one in place. Customs and immigration controls can be managed without a hard border, and likely will be between the UK and Ireland.

People going on about "not wanting a border" is not going to change a thing, this is a matter of international law.

What is a matter of 'international law'? As a country, you don't have to put in a border if you don't want to, you certainly don't have to put in place a particular type of border.  How you enforce your border and customs controls is down to the country in question.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "it hasn't got updates" is perfectly correct English

I don't think it is, under either the UK or US conventions, at least not if the intention is to say that it has not been updated, rather than saying that it currently doesn't have updates available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure it would be to be honest. I had an N900 (that could dock with a monitor and run a non-windows desktop OS..) and it was a gimmick at best. By the time you need a monitor and a keyboard, you are better off with either a laptop, or a desktop, especially given how easy it is to have data available across devices now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2015 election was the only one in recent history where Eurosceptics got a worse result

Except that both Labour and the Conservatives have been essentially pro-EU parties for quite a long time now.. Less mainstream positions (which an anti-EU position, and an extremely pro-EU position would both be) don't fare well under FPTP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next battleground: An aging Great Lakes pipeline stirs new protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next battleground: An aging Great Lakes pipeline stirs new protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next battleground: An aging Great Lakes pipeline stirs new protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sudden collapse of Alitalia would be a shock to Italy's economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You are right, the union wanted a 30% wage rise considered industry standard and Tesla responded offering shares to workers betting on the fact that there will be another 10x increase in the next 5-10 years.

Until very recently Germany didn't have a minimum wage, instead it had minimum wages set by collective bargaining agreements instead. Now it has a mix (a federal minimum and the agreements, both enforceable by law). That's important to consider here. Germany does business in a very different way to a lot of countries and, as a result unions have quite a bit of clout (and they will have within anything Tesla does). Tesla can't really ignore that, you can't just offer shares instead, or some other benefit, you actually have to pay people.  What's more is that IG Metall is threatening strike action, which is something German unions do extremely rarely.

If you look at the German press (from say, 4 days ago), the issue that Grohmann has now is that it has more work than it has employees, and it can't hire people because it isn't pay the going rate. Moreover, there is a feeling that the push to set aside non-Tesla work, and essentially reduce the customer base is threatening the long term viability of Grohmann, that again doesn't really do anyone any favours in hiring (Germany being somewhere where people still generally look for a career with one employer, especially in this area).  That's compounded by Tesla's takeover of Grohmann having also led to the resignation of the founders of the company.. Essentially, the trust in the firm is, to a certain extent, shot.

Now the Tesla response is intended to head that off. Tesla are offering a raise, plus a share offer to  cover one half of the issues, and the promise of no redundancies over the next 5 years to suggest stability, but in not engaging with the union Musk is seen as making a major mistake in such a unionised area. It's worth noting that both the company works council and the union aren't happy with the offer and at the moment the issue seems to be that the offer of negotiations is being ignored by Tesla.

If you look at the statements by the union, the current issue around strike action is around the fact that it could harm Grohmann customers and employees given the wider situation. They seem keen to avoid it, but if Tesla don't negotiate, they don't seem to have a lot of options left, ignoring the company's own works council and the union aren't great ways to expand those options either..


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has President Trump said about your country in his first 100 days? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Marines back in Helmand as Afghanistan 'stalemate' continues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The workers concerns were entitled but after Elon Musk addressed the issue with the letter above most of the workers canceled the plans to unionize.

Which workers? Unless I've missed something, I'm reasonably sure that the ones at Grohmann Engineering are already unionised and that one of the issues recently was pay at 30% below the union rate.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah believe what you want. 

I'll look at the situation and come to a conclusion based on what we know. You can do that, or you can believe what you want..

You will get a Free-trade agreement and still be asked for your thoughts on every matters in Brussels.

The UK will likely get an FTA, it won't be asked for it's thoughts on every matter that the EU discusses in Brussels... It will however have influence given that the UK and EU still want to work together on issues of mutual interest..

You just refuse to understand what everybody has been saying to you for the last 6 months. And even tho Merkel said it clearly 2 days ago : Britain is wasting time with Brexit delusions.

No.. I don't. It's clear that the UK will not have rights equal to those member states have once it leaves the European Union. To a certain extent the UK doesn't want to have equal rights as member states.  The UK doesn't want to be part of the political project, the current government is looking to take the UK out of the single market.. That's two big sets of 'rights' that the UK won't have.

What you seem to be doing is taking what Merkel is saying and utterly misunderstanding it. The UK won't have the same rights, or more rights in the context of the EU as an EU member, of course it won't. But it's not going away, it won't suddenly be irrelevant, especially in those areas where the UK is particularly capable and influential..  The UK is leaving the EU, not seceding from the world. If there are any delusions here, they are your suggestions that the UK won't have any influence in Europe, of course it will. It did before the EU existed and it will for a long time after it has left too.

And none of that is counter to what Merkel has said, whether you take the snippets reported in the media or listen to what she is saying in German in the context of EU and Germany domestic politics..



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are absolutely right, but the point is education, not intelligence. Older people were somewhat more likely to vote leave, so if you throw in that access to university has massively increased in recent years and so if you are younger you are *vastly* more likely to have had the opportunity to go to university, it becomes less a 'stupid' vs 'smart' and more a critique of access to tertiary education in the UK.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each block has its own legislation on its ground.

And every country not in a trading block, or without a specific agreement where there is bilateral agreement... The UK will have to comply with EU rules and US rules, and Chinese rules etc.  And of course the EU, US and China will have to comply with UK rules.  We can put in place FTA's to reduce and remove barriers where it makes sense of course.

Yeah you're leaving the EU, not NATO so you're still supposed to contribute to it as you were. 

And the UK will, the point is that means you continue to have cooperation and coordination in areas that are important to the UK and EU.  That said, it won't be until the EU decides to go fully federal and combine it's defence (and there is still a lot of objection to that within the EU, even without the UK) that the takes a leading position in NATO. Until then the UK's position doesn't really change at all.  After all, the UK still has very deep defence ties with the US, above and beyond what other EU members have by quite a long way and that really doesn't look like it'll change. 

But other than that, the UK's influence in EU matters is over. You won't be able to block any kind of European Task Force, of services integrations and all the others things the UK was stalling for the last decade.

Yeah, or course. The UK is leaving. It won't be able to block anything that the EU agrees to do. On the other side of that, the UK also won't be taking part in them or contributing financially either. That's the point of leaving.. But the UK isn't the only party that has been less than enthusiastic, the UK leaving doesn't solve the problems the EU has in areas where it requires unanimity, it simply reduces the opposition.

Why would the EU cares about the UK once it's out? 

Because it's still the largest non-EU regional power in Europe and that's relevant to the EU?

What the EU become is no longer your concern really.

Of course it is, it's still relevant to the UK's interests, and the UK is relevant to the EU's interests.  The UK will be outside of the EU, it won't be part of the political project, but it will still be a major trading partner, a defence partner and of course another country that the EU will want to work with as much as the UK wants to work with it..  From everything from trade, to trade sanctions, the UK is pretty relevant to the EU (as the EU is to the UK..).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK block on EU spending infuriates Brussels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 12:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 12:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> France and Germany have now more power than ever to go wherever they want to go from now on.

France and Germany now have the power to cooperate with 25 other nations in some areas of competency. The EU isn't some German-Franco empire and as we have seen time and time again, both France and Germany only have so much leverage across the EU.  The UK will be the largest regional power that isn't part of the EU, arguably the single largest regional power bar the EU if you consider, military, economic and social factors together.

That alone will mean that the EU will be interested.

In the end, you'll have zero MPs in Brussels and you will be put aside of all Europeans projects.

The whole point is to have zero MEPs in Brussels, leaving the political project is basically the whole aim. But that doesn't mean that the UK will have zero influence.

As to projects, sure the UK will leave many the EU ones, not so much the European ones but it'll likely depend on which projects. I'm sure the UK will still participate in some (there are plenty of non-EU countries involved in quite a few of those projects after all).

You won't have a say in any of the EU legislation that you will still have to comply in order to do business with the EU.

We will only have to comply with some EU legislation, in much the same way that Germany has to comply with US legislation when it deals with the US, or France has to comply with Brazilian legislation when it deals with Brazil.  The UK isn't going to turn into Norway, or Switzerland, where the EU can legislate on issues that are broadly domestic..

But yeah, for the camera and shit : "great, deep, respectfull, Mickey Mouse cooperation". Right. Delusion much.

The UK has a slew of non-EU bilateral cooperation agreements in areas not covered by the EU competencies with EU states now. The EU is keen to keep the UK on board for policing, intelligence and a range of other issues, the UK will continue to cooperate via NATO and various other frameworks..  So no, it's not delusion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 11:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you know, there's going to be a border between the UK and the EU. Goods and people passing that border need to be properly registered, import restrictions met, trade taxes levied and so on ...

There is going to be a border in the same way that there is a border now between the UK and the EU generally, between the UK and Ireland there is almost no chance of being a hard border though. None of the parties involved want one, and there are other ways to deal with the movement of goods etc..

That there is no border at all and British goods and people can just pass into the EU, as if it was still a member, is not an option.

You do realise that just crossing a border is just one part of importing something, or emigrating..? There are lots of ways to track goods, and manage people crossing a border, especially when you are talking about the border on an Island.

The EU doesn't want a border, the UK doesn't, and Ireland doesn't. No-one can impose one on the UK and Ireland either so.. There isn't likely to be a border. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you need a hard border between the UK and Ireland to control immigration? Irish people can settle in the UK anyway and anyone else doesn't get any additional rights just because there isn't a border (in much the same way as someone from say, the US or Indonesia entering Schengen doesn't suddenly have the right to live there).. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to be anymore.

Of course we do. The UK doesn't want to be part of the EU's political project, but we still have an interest in ensuring that the EU is stable, both economically and socially.  That's before we get into things like defence cooperation through NATO and bilaterally and all the other little things that we work together on as a group of nations (often well beyond the EU).

there will have zero voice for the UK in Brussels and all the drama will be over.

The UK won't be part of the EU, it's not going into seclusion. The UK will have diplomatic representation in the EU in much the same way that the EU will have in the UK, and no doubt there are lots of areas where our cooperation will be both broad and deep.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah well you're not saying anything but random drunkar babbling. 

It may be that your lack of understanding as to how the EU works, and where the balance is between the EP and members is leaving you a little confused.

The EU is a democratic Union where each country has Mps depending on the number of their population.

Right.. But the European Parliament (Where those MEP's sit) can only act within the competencies granted to it by the member states, via the treaties. If you want to extend those, you need agreement from the member states, the level of agreement required depends on the kind of extension. You can't 'force' a member state to agree to hand over competencies, and you can't introduce legislation on some matters without the consent of member states.

You're trying to play the "let's divide them" when you obviouly couldn't care less about the Netherlands. I mean, you don't even care about N.I. or Scotland's vote why would you care about a foreign country.

Not at all. I'm saying that where previously the UK has worked with the likes of the Netherlands on a common interest within the EU, the UK leaving only weakens the dissenting view, it doesn't eliminate it. And of course in some areas, a single dissenting voice is enough to prevent further action (although there is always enhanced cooperation available to those states that want to make use of it).

I would be concerned however if the EU could force through an expansion or major reform of it's institutions without consent, that would be a bad thing for all involved, which I'm sure you'd agree.  After all, the EU is a grouping of sovereign states, not a federation.

IDK if the Brexit makes you brits petty or if you were already petty and that made you vote for it.

I honestly don't see what you see as petty here, I hope the EU does manage to carry out the reform and integration that it wants. It would be beneficial for the region and provide stability. I'd rather not see that forced on members who don't want it though, and happily in many areas that isn't possible anyway, so the EU will have to continue to form a consensus.

Surely that's a good thing all round, rather than your suggestion that the EU could simply force the Netherlands or Ireland to accede to whatever demands are made because they are too small to protect their interests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany has free tuition for (almost) all students, so does France (again, not quite free) and the Nordics IIRC, Argentina is essentially fee free too and you'll find similar situations with public universities in a number of countries, as long as you are resident. I doubt you'll find many countries that offer free tuition specifically to former members of the US military though, I mean.. why would they?

Oh and how would Germany be being more patriotic than the US, by providing free education to former foreign military personnel? I'm reasonably sure it wouldn't be seen as patriotic if the US offered former German soldiers free education.

It's not about patriotism, it's about less profit focused higher education systems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's nowhere near enough to block anything in Brussels. 

Depends on the issue and how the various vote allocations are reassigned, and it's not just Ireland and the Netherlands in any case.  Not to mention that you'll end up with a slew of new EU political problems if you think the EU can simply cast side the views of whole members, especially whole members that have large economies and are net contributors to the EU budget.

The idea that the Netherlands, as a whole can be disregarded is a pretty major problem I'd have thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK want a hard border

The UK have said they don't. Ireland have said they don't. And the EU seems to be saying that they don't... The UK and Ireland have existing agreements (as you well know..) that deal with working in the UK and Ireland for their respective nationals, that doesn't have a wider impact on EU nationals so it shouldn't be an issue, we'll see in the negotiations of course, but I can't see why it would be and apparently almost no-one else does either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's significant in that the random briefs, leaks and statements from various parts of the EU are now a coherent position that has been agreed upon.  It obviously doesn't have any greater significance until we start negotiating and those positions are eroded, built upon, challenged and so on, and we get an idea of what the actual exit looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has always been angry, the target of the anger just changes depending on who is seen to be disparaging about the EU. I mean, in the run up to the referendum we went through several tranches of anger and ridicule, but the UK has hardly been alone in that. Germany got a little during the refugee crisis, Greece was the enemy for a period when they looked like they might not just lie down and take it, currently the V4 countries are getting a bit of a kicking, Austrians nearly got one over the presidential election and if the election in France looked to be going differently (As unlikely as that would have been) no doubt French commentators would have been sneered at.  It's the usual thing of seeing people who hold a different position as a threat, and the voicing of that position as an attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't frustration turn internal towards the British political establishment post Brexit?

Probably (and hopefuly) yes. There will be a period where it isn't (as there is a period after every General election where everything is the last government fault, regardless of what caused it), but over a relatively short period of time it should mean the UK government being held responsible for things that opposition parties can actually do something about if they are elected.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A different IRA to be fair, but yeah, some people aren't going to quit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those already shifted.

No they haven't. There has been some proposals in terms of mitigating the direct impact of the UK leaving, but nothing about the political implications. There ares till major philosophical differences in quite a few areas between Germany, France and others that were at least partially mitigated by the UK (and more recently with the results blamed on the UK's position or intransigence..).

It's going to be really interesting to see how the EU deals with some of the upcoming issues it faces and with things like whatever replaces TTIP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it's the UK which pushed for always more enlargement

The UK pushed for enlargement, rather than integration broadly because the UK valued the trade benefits over the political project... 

The EU will function properly at last, the UK was stalling it from its membership

The EU still needs reform, without the UK it might be able to carry out more of that reform (maybe not, the UK wasn't alone in opposition, and treaty change still requires unanimity..) but the UK's exit won't fix the issues on its own, and it will introduce some minor new issues, especially amongst the other member states who worked with the UK and have positions closer to that of the UK than say France and Germany.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's obviously not a thing, Hungary and Poland want to be in the EU and the UK doesn't. I'm sure there'd be more functional swaps, just not ones that keep the UK in the club.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you see France's relationship with the EU changing over the next decade or so?

In the context of the EU, in what areas do you see priorities for reform, and what kind of reform would you be looking to support or initiate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU 27 agree Brexit negotiating stance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU 27 agree Brexit negotiating stance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to order a study on abuses of U.S. trade agreements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla recruiting engineers in Mexico for California plant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they have your car^1, your phone, your wallet, why not your glucose levels.

^1 *So many completely insecure ODBII bluetooth dongles discoverable in traffic these days..* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, a BBC article on the paper is available [here, with a readable, but slightly less precise.. title](http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-39746027) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smartphone-controlled optogenetically engineered cells enable semiautomatic glucose homeostasis in diabetic mice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea crisis: North test-fires ballistic missile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump pledges fealty to NRA gun lobby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet we've always been in that situation. I mean Christ, we essentially burn a religiously motivated 'terrorist' in effigy every 5th of November because we foiled a plot over 400 years ago.  It'd be nice not to have to need to, but terrorism is old and it's not going away, in 25 years it'll still be there, it may be different causes, different perpetrators, different methods but it'll still be a thing, and we'll still have to detect and disrupt the threats posed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea that somehow Theresa May being totally unopposed is going to help Brexit negotiations meanwhile is just complete fucking nonsensical fantasy.

Partly true, partly not. The argument is that the bigger her majority, the less internal opposition she has to deal with, and the less leverage the EU has in using the UK's own domestic opposition to undermine the negotiating position of the government.

So, arguably it is true, but for anyone who doesn't want the government to be able to act essentially unilaterally, that obviously isn't a good thing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was she by any chance a Baby Boomer?

I'd have assumed between 35 and 50 at the absolute top end, so not that generation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. That seems a sensible explanation for that error on my part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know. But I actually thought you were right on more than one level. Just take it as a compliment, you may have been trying to hide it, but I saw the depth, nay, the love in your comment.  Well done I say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, and those kind of events sometimes seem to attract people with some interesting views on the world, but usually the reveal themselves in long, well meaning, often somewhat disturbing polemics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDR: Woman tries to take all the mugs being given away by a community group at a civil liberties event, gets told no, leaves in a huff.

Although come on mate, that's barely 700 words.. Would an audio version be more helpful perhaps, someone could do the voices.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, just from that article she sounds fairly reasonable. Even the drug courier (and I suppose benefit fraud..) bits aren't net negatives. People make stupid decisions when they need money, she did, apparently recognised it and managed to salvage the positives, combine that with leaving home at 16 and she does come across as someone who has faced a few challenges and overcome them, not perfectly, but hey. That's not a bad thing.  Granted she went on to start and drop out of a few courses, but seems to have finished teacher training at college.

So, going purely on this one article, given its student politics, she seems more normal than many of the people you hear about. That probably does make her a representative NUS president.


^Of ^course ^there ^is ^a ^good ^chance ^that ^someone ^is ^going ^dig ^up ^something ^outrageous ^that ^she ^has ^said ^or ^done ^to ^undermine ^that ^point, ^but ^hey. ^For ^now ^I'll ^take ^it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had something similar (almost) happen a year and a bit ago when I was running a little stall where we were giving away random merch to people we were speaking to, all on behalf of a tiny community advocacy group, at a civil liberties convention (think small, a few speakers, a few workshops and maybe 1000 people). The stall had the usual stuff, pens, posters, mugs, wrist bands, caps, small USB sticks and some T-shirts IIRC and lots of brochures style information for people to get a better idea of what the group did and so on. 

There were about three of us chatting to people, getting contact details, some donations, and I think there was a petition involved, but that may have been a different event.. Anyway, our little table was covered in promotional material, we'd been at it for a few hours but the event was still quite busy, all in all a good day. 

As I'm talking to a guy I see a woman walk over pick up one of the leaflets and read though it, so as I finish I pop over to her and ask if there is anything she'd like to know or if she's happy reading and she stops, looks up and asks how much our mugs are. 

Now normally people would ask about a specific thing in the leaflets, or ask about the stuff that the group did, occasionally they'd ask for a specific one of the posters or similar but I don't think anyone had asked about pricing for the bits we were giving away.  I replied with something along the lines of 'oh, those? we aren't selling them, were giving them away to people who are interested!' and I hand her a mug. She pops it in her bag and goes back to reading.

At that point I step away and let her read, there was another guy who wanted to chat about something and she seemed more interested in the literature so I let her get on with it.  About two minutes later I look across the table again and she's putting all of the mugs we've got on the table in her bag. 

Now it wasn't a small amount, I think about a dozen, maybe a few more, full sized coffee mugs in a variety of colours. I was a tiny bit taken aback so I sort of watched in fascination for maybe 15 seconds as she tries to pack these mugs into a bag that's already basically full of them..  10 seconds in she bends down and grabs the box of extra mugs that we have sat under the table (maybe another 10-12 mugs..) and starts to try and arrange the mugs she can't get into her handbag into the box..

At that point I went over again and asked her what she was doing and the conversation wend something like:

Me:  Excuse me, you can't take all of those..

Her: Why? You said they were free!?

Me: I said we were giving them away to people.. But if you take them all we won't have any left to give. 

Her: If they are free then I can take them, you can't stop me if they don't cost anything.

Me: ... No, we are giving them away, we aren't letting anyone take as many of them as they'd like.

Her (sounding really quite indignant): Well I don't see the difference and you said they were free. 

Me: The difference is that I haven't said you can have all of those. Could you put them back please?

Her: I don't see why I should..

And she puts the box on the table, takes maybe 3 of the many mugs she's stuffed in her bag onto the table and stalks off.  I'm half bemused, half annoyed and entirely bemused about the whole thing but hey, stuff happens.

About 15 minutes later one of the event organisers, looking a bit confused, collars me and asks what had happened. Apparently she'd tried to complain to one of their event staff that we were engaged in false advertising by saying we were giving away mugs for free and then not letting her take as many as she needed.  Apparently she felt that she was entitled to some money for her trouble, in part because she'd had to leave around 20 mugs that she valued at at least 1 a piece behind due to our actions.. Needless to say she didn't get any (never mind anything else, it was a free event..) and apparently left in a bit of a huff.

edit: *TLDR: Woman tries to take all the mugs being given away by a community group at a civil liberties event, gets told no, leaves in a huff.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swap Sinn Fin for the SNP then. Between them, they show two different approaches (absenteeism, vs opposition) that people with views that go directly against the existence of something (the UK as a union including their member country..) can use in support of their aims... That is comparable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is the school of thought that above all else, the money is best in my pocket. It might look mildly better on the balance sheet, it might give you a good buzz but in terms of relationships its shite.  I've worked for small organisations in the past where I've taken the approach of paying suppliers in full, as early as is reasonable (essentially pay on invoice, rather than sitting on it). Oddly enough you end up with decent relationships, more room to talk about discounts, you can get things done that you can't where you don't have that relationship (especially getting people to rush a job for you..). Almost inevitably at some point or another down the line, someone decides that paying suppliers in 30 days, or 90 days is better, often trying to haggle at that point for additional discount... Then I inevitably get a call from someone at the company asking if they know why X supplier is suddenly not offering them the same discounts, or how I got Y supplier to provide something in 72 hours without a huge markup instead of the usual 7 days and whether I'd talk to them (the answer to which is.. no, your relationship, if you've screwed it up I'm not putting mine on the line..).

It's daft. Goodwill is valuable, yes there are at times good reasons to hold payment, but be up front about it, and if you have the service or product and it's right, and you have the agreed price, pay it. Keeping the cash on your books for an extra month or two really isn't worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's generally a little difficult to take a country to court over the actions of its secret intelligence services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The argument is that they aren't getting either under the current approach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK has unions for journalists though.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd take the Tagesschau over BBC News 10 out of 10 times.

I watch both, they tend to be pretty much on a par in terms of quality, if you are comparing the Tagesschau with a News bulletin. The difference tends to be the focus (with the Tagesschau covering more German specific news 
etc.. obviously). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is, although there is a slight issue in that the UK is Canada's largest trading partner in the EU at the moment by quite a long way and is on its way out of the EU. Not that that diminishes opportunity within the rest of the EU, and it's likely that Canada and the UK will build on their relationship when the UK can, but it's another set of complications.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's academic now frankly.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's reasonable, but I think the argument is that something short of EU membership will reduce those economic issues whilst opening up EU trade to some degree at least, hence the argument some people are making about Scotland not joining the EU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Chinese one has both IIRC, the UK one.. I can't remember where that ended up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as we'd become a net recipient of membership funds..

I think all the more reasonable suggestions that I've seen would mean that an independent Scotland would be a (small) net contributor to the EU, not a net recipient of funds, I think your farmers would be better off via agricultural funding, but if Scotland were a net contributor that's obviously just a movement of Scottish funding around anyway and then ring-fenced for farming by the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is: Islam. Atatrk managed to make a democratic state, how well is that working out?

Indonesia? Egypt managed for a while too.. If you have a state set up to separate religion from political power it's entirely possible. If you can go from Nazism to democracy, you can have democracy in a Muslim majority country.

Nope, I don't care. We have a moral responsibility to not piss away what took generations to build. 

The generations that built that were the ones who thought these issues were important.  The whole point of the refugee conventions was to prevent the horrors that very mobile European and Jewish people (amongst others) experienced after all. Of course your values are entirely up to you, I just don't see them as justifiable, or the threat that you present as credible.

Yes it is. It's clear as day that continuing current policies will end in civil war.

No, it's not.

I'm moving to the US for this reason

Good luck with that.

So it is true. Glad I was able to correct that misconception.

What misconception? You suggested that migrants get more than nationals, they don't they get nothing, refugees (a smaller subset of the people who have moved to Europe) get the same at most, if their claims are valid.. That's not a correction, that's a changing of the goalposts.

This is a completely irrational feelz based policy. 

Yes, you are right, suggesting that maybe not pulling people out of the sea when made aware that they are drowning is just me being a woolly bleeding heart, it's all about he feelz...

More people die because you're giving them an incentive to take the risk.

So turn them around after pulling them out of the sea. The point is that letting them die doesn't equate to granting them residency and giving them a house.

t's neither. It's rational. Your policy prescriptions are daft and immoral because not only do more people die at sea, you will also piss away all the progress attained by pushing Europe into civil war. 

Europe is not going to enter into a civil war though is it? I mean.. come on...

Now, I realise that most people are stupid and will continue to vote for idiots until it is too late, which is why I'm out.

See, what I don't get is how, if you think Europe is heading toward civil war, you think the US is somehow a safer option.. But hey.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hey, if it works..](http://www.royalnavy.mod.uk/-/media/royal-navy-responsive/images/units-and-equipment/ships-and-surface-fleet/aircraft-carriers/queen-elizabeth/hms-queen-elizabeth-masthead.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was confident of a remain victory which looking at the polls even at the time he shouldn't have been. The main reason that it happened was because of in fighting within his party and not because of the public demand. Having high public support was just a bonus.


I think he was excessively confident, but as you point out, the decision was necessary because of the issues it was causing him, even within his own party, and because other parties (including the Lib Dems) were using as a stick to beat him, and of course there was public demand too.  That does suggest it was the right decision though.  He may have been unhappy with the outcome, but the reasons for holding the referendum remain fairly sensible.

I think that it was, referendums are seldomly ever a good idea and there wasn't that much consideration put into it, in order to make it as reflective as possible. Referendums debatably show the public mood at the time so if people change their mind it is pretty hard to do the changes that have been done.

I'd somewhat agree with you. I think they are only sensible on matters of governance (so independence, changing voting systems, significant treaties with political implications etc..), that's why they are so rare. EU membership however does seem to fall into that category, and a very clear question, which again, the EU referendum had, is the right approach.

I can't speak for anyone else but I didn't support it as long as it was announced. 

No, but you would have been in a minority in the UK.

Referendums tend to be or at least were quite popular in general it just was that this one was more in the limelight. Having an EU referendum is pretty popular in other EU countries as well, 53% of French people support having a referendum on the EU, while only 33% of them want to leave, both articles are in French BTW.

And that goes for most referendums, people want a say, it doesn't mean that they all want the same result. That's perfectly reasonable. You have to take into account that not only was there support in the polls for a referendum, but also support in Parliament (The commons voted 544 to 53 in favour of holding a referendum, those 53 nays all coming from the SNP..).

Yes there was.

What exactly? People wanted a referendum, the government wanted a referendum, the opposition voted for a referendum, even the Lib Dems did. The issue doesn't seem to be that there are regrets that a referendum was held, but that a referendum was held and that remain lost.

It made existing divisions even deeper, referendums by its very nature are divisive. They force people to take sides on an issue, especially an issue as complex as the the EU.

It made some people take sides for the vote, but it broadly illuminated an existing split. The UK didn't suddenly become vastly more divided as a people, although as people informed themselves they took positions for and against a political question. Then we had the result, and the country is broadly coalescing around that, and no doubt with the focus shifting on the how, rather than the if, that will continue.

It didn't happen by accident or because culturally the British are opposed to the EU. If there is going to be constant negative reporting of something. Don't be surprised that the public have a negative opinion of it. Many of their problems aren't caused by the EU as such they are still going to be unhappy after it has happened.

Except that the UK has been, generally, very lukewarm on the EU since joining. There is vastly less support for the political project. We can try to make out that this is all a media conspiracy, but that really doesn't make a huge amount of sense, there have been long standing political divisions, opposition to various aspects of the EU and negative media reporting.. If anything, the result of the referendum shows that a significant fraction of the population, across party lines, were perfectly able to balance their priorities and come to a very different view from the remainder. 

It's easier to blame the media than it is to look at why people might reject the EU, I understand that, but it doesn't give a full picture at all.

You don't know what exactly will happen in the future. The referendum in 1975 was more clear cut than the last one yet a small minority campaigned to leave, until they could convince a small majority to vote that way. Most people got on their lives for those 40 odd years, yet it still happened.

Of course not, but joining the EU now is very different than joining the EEC in 1973, many of the things that the UK had opt outs on likely wouldn't be opt-outable of so you'd not only have to convince people that EU membership was the right move, but also defend against the suggestion that the UK would lose the pound, have to join Schengen and potentially a whole raft of other things that are genuinely unpopular in the UK (like an EU Army etc..).  Not to mention that they'd have to convince the EU that they should take the UK as a member.

Maybe in 40 years things will change, but I seriously doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's no way that his plan only adds $200 billion to the deficit 

Agreed, but the corporate tax changes seem to be around that sort of area, the suggested changes to income tax will presumably dwarf that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Credit = popular awareness = willingness to fund (in democratic state).

Right... But ESA can promote itself too, just because NASA claimed credit for something doesn't mean ESA has to shut up and say nothing.  And again, is stopping cooperation with NASA a reasonable response?

From your own country (with the british flag), I bet there wasn't a lot of popular awareness about what the EU actually did for the U.K. and now you have the brexit predicament thanks to it. 

I'd argue that there was quite a bit of awareness of what the EU did, just that a small majority of people felt that it wasn't worth the downsides of membership, or the compromises involved. That has very little to do with credit going to the EU, and everything to do with what people think of things that actually were, largely, down to EU membership.

We don't want people to vote away funding for space exploration and leave it all to Trump and Putin.

Right, so ESA needs to promote what it does, ending cooperation with NASA which is what the parent proposed doesn't exactly deal with that in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thatcher was similar, she tended to avoid public confrontation. And we all remember this

It's a classic failure to communicate what 'danger to our ships' means, followed by some quite dismissing comments that just don't come across terribly well.  Take this particular argument, the course of the Belgrano is public now (not sure if it was at the time) and it clearly wasn't 'sailing away' but rather loitering outside of the exclusion zone and changing heading somewhat regularly (although not directly into the exclusion zone AFAIKT).  The questioner does a wonderful job of repeating 'sailing away' and Thatcher fails to properly respond to that specific accusation and essentially argues that she knows better so that should be enough.  

We've moved a long way on since then of course in terms of communications.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be surprised if he shows regret for what was such a terrible decision.

It was a decision that led to a result that went against his expectations, but it wasn't a terrible decision in and of itself. Having a referendum on EU membership was entirely reasonable and popular (Even among people who later voted remain). The outcome is also not terrible, it might turn out to be, I doubt it, but it certainly isn't yet and doesn't look like it will be.

I can understand him regretting the campaign, regretting the approach to the referendum even regretting standing down when he did, but there is little to regret in deciding to hold the referendum in the first place.

It didn't have to poison British politics but was escalated in such a way that it did and the referendum didn't put it to bed. If anything it created even deeper divisions.

It hasn't created deeper divisions, it has illuminated divisions that were already there, and kicked off a process that will likely heal them to a large extent.  Being in the EU was a sore spot for a lot of people for a long time, one that got rubbed every time anything they didn't like happened, being outside of the EU isn't going to have the same impact on those who voted remain even if only because being outside of the EU will not be as visible as being in it is.

Give it a few years and the current remain/leave split will disappear, a small minority will no doubt campaign to join the EU, but it will be a very small minority, most people will just get on with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there must be TV debates, then run 10+ of them, each targeting a different part of the population, or focusing on specific areas.

Run 650 of them, we have local TV stations and I'm sure a lot of local candidates would love that kind of exposure and reach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One useful thing that national debates do is force every party to present a single, consistent vision for governance to the people.

That's true, but it also backfires when they present something that they can't back up with the rest of their party, and generally they don't get called out on it if it is their view.

In regular campaigning the party candidate for Clacton can be giving one kind of spin to his constituents whilst the party candidate for Kensington can be telling a completely different lie. 

And in the real world, the party candidate for Clacton can take a completely different view and promote different issues than the party candidate for Kensington. That's sort of my point, my MP is anti-nuclear weapons, his party has a pro-nuclear weapons policy but the party leader is anti-nuclear weapons. If positions on nuclear weapons were incredibly important to me in terms of my vote (and they are to some extent) how do the debates help me figure out what that mess means? More to the point, someone who doesn't know what their MPs position is, or the party position, may not get the best position from a televised debate, especially if where a leader and party differ, or an issue is controversial, they do the usual thing of giving vague replies.

The debates are one of the few ways in which we can force parties to sell everybody the same deal, not tailored deceptions.

Indeed, but manifesto documents do it just as effectively which removes the issue of personalities and whether you like the look or sound of someone.

 It doesn't stop them lying to us, but it at least limits them to one lie on each issue, and one that can be publicly fact checked by the broadcaster.

Hold on, it doesn't limit them to one lie each either, they still get to send out different material in each constituency and campaign differently in different areas.. About all it does is ensure they have a nice generic country wide argument that they can use as a backdrop too.

Sure the debates shouldn't be the only thing we judge our votes on (and they aren't!) but they are definitely a useful anchor as we attempt to process all the bullshit.

Yeah, I think candidate debates are but that leaders debates create more skew than they eliminate, and that's before we get into the candidates and parties that aren't represented at all in them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok your first post was discussing the economy as a whole

My first comment was about the corporate tax (as in, what the article is about), not a wider tax plan though, hence the figures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm willing to bet that the vast majority of people will still only see highlights and out of context snippets. Granted now people will watch the whole thing than a campaign speech at an event, but that still doesn't deal with the issue of it essentially being a presidential style event in a very much not presidential system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... In aware of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would we only consider a single piece of a tax plan when discussing its impact?

Because we are in /r/Entrepeneur in a thread that is specifically about reducing the Corporate income tax rate to 15%... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and there are lots of smart people too. The 'general public' as a grouping that includes a lot of different people with a lot of different views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back of a fag packet calculations on the corporate rates (as that's what the article is about rather than the wider tax plan..), and over a year not a decade. The articles you link seem to include multiple proposed cuts (not just corporate tax) and over longer periods.

Corporate income tax brings in about $250-300bn a year, so even if you eliminated all of it, and factor in growth and inflation, you aren't going to get anywhere near a trillion dollars in a year any time soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, that's fair enough. It just annoys me sometimes when people try to create false equivalencies that imply a particular outcome that simply doesn't make sense when you are talking about a state that can print money.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have, and I also know 'people' in general, most people aren't interested in politics for the sake of politics (which is probably a good thing) and are more focused on what they think they want out of the country. That doesn't make them morons. Or maybe I'm unique and living in a relatively moron free bubble, or indeed I'm a moron and haven't noticed).. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's certainly one part of it, but he has also taken positions that much of the Party doesn't necessarily stand for and failed to bring the party along (which comes back to the PLP to some degree).  It feels like as leader, he has placed electoral success behind an ideological position that is less popular, and so hasn't been able to show support from the middle ground, which in turn has caused problems for the PLP, many of whose voters fall into that middle ground.

It comes back to the notion that in an FPTP world, the Labour party, like the Tory part is essentially a large coalition. Corbyn hasn't been able to bring all of those factions into line behind him, and it's costing him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if Scotland does go for independence, there is a good chance that they'd fall short of joining the EU in any case (opting for a position closer to the EU than the UK is aiming for, but short of full membership given the complications with everything else). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't Unionism, British Nationalism?

Somewhat, but it rather depends. I suppose if you call unionism nationalism, you could also call remain voters in the GE European nationalists, but that doesn't really fit either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is arguably more annoying because whether you support independence or not, the utter lack of a political process that even edges in that direction is a bit dire given the sentiment in the region. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the general public are morons, we must not forget this.

They really aren't, and I'd argue that TV debates are at least partially a case of people feeling the need to treat them as though they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would increase the deficit from 500bn to about 700bn, you'd have to define 'bankrupt the country' in some new way (not that I'm saying it's a good idea, just that at this point US debt is massive to make any comparisons to bankruptcy a bit daft, especially as the US can pay to maintain its debt). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're talking EU here. 

We are talking about elected assemblies that include people who don't support their countries or regions membership in the entity that the assembly is part of.  So in the case of UKIP and the EP, they don't want the UK in the EU, but are representing people in an EU body, and the SNP don't want Scotland in the UK, but are representing people in a UK body.

 I don't see a parallel to Scotlands goal to get rid of Westminster domination.

Scotland wanting to leave the UK, is, on the face of it similar to the UK wanting to leave the EU. The SNP and UKIP both want the bit of what they represent not to be part of the larger body that they have elected seats in the parliaments of..

Apparently, Westminster seems to be ok with Brexit while at the same time holding on to Scotland. How does that fit into your narrative?

I really don't see how it is relevant.. Westminster is OK with Brexit and authorised a Scottish independence referendum a couple of years ago and will no doubt do so again in the not so distant future. Last I checked there hasn't been a unilateral independence declaration from Scotland, or indeed a majority supporting independence, so at the moment Scotland is very much still voluntarily part of the UK, as it has essentially always been. But what does that have to do with Some MP's in Westminster wanting an Independent Scotland? or MEPs not wanting their member state to be part of the EU?

The point is that you can be elected to a body even if you don't want that body to exist, there is nothing particularly wrong with that, after all, if you are elected, it would seem quite a few other people agree with your view too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tories never shy away from saying how terrible everything WOULD be if labour were in charge, but for some reason labour don't seem that focused on how terrible things ARE. I normally disagree with this approach but I think swathes of the general public are so accepting of the offered scapegoats that they don't realise (or choose to ignore) there are people making decisions that are leading to all the issues around them.

Frankly I'm a bit sick of this from both sides, I'd much rather have some positive messaging (and not just 'we will defeat *bad thing*') but hey, we'll see if that is even possible in this election. 

So many people have such huge problems with Corbyn that at this point they should put at least some time into the 'better of two evils' approach. Sadly I'm not sure Corbyn has the self-awareness to really grasp this somehow.

Yeah.. pretty much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that Whataboutism? I'm saying that in both cases it's fine, not that it's fine in one case because it happens somewhere else.  The SNP representing their constituents in Westminster, whilst advocating for Scottish independence is fine, as is a UKIP MEP representing their constituents in the European Parliament and advocating an exit from the EU.

So do you think the SNP shouldn't take their seats in Westminster (some Northern Irish MP's don't for example)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk, Corbyn has seemed much stronger than May to me recently.

To be honest, he's always seemed principled and and strong on his positions and priorities. The problem for me is that I agree with about half of them and have real issues with the other half. 

Now, a lot of the Labour policy discussions that have been had have been broadly positive, but it doesn't always feel like Corbyn is entirely interested in them (based on what comes out of the party and social media as much as anything else), and on the areas where I support the party position essentially in apparent opposition to Corbyn there are real problems. The two don't balance each other out nicely either. So at that point, as a Labour member the message is horribly mixed, for the average person I can imagine it's a bit worse...

 but I think putting them next to each other in a situation other than PMQs could have some real impact on people's view of May.

Honestly I don't think even electorally, ignoring anything else, that would be helpful. The worst possible thing would be the expectations of May being dropped as far as they are now, and then having a debate that gives Corbyn the opportunity to say something stupid, probably in opposition to the party, likely on an issue lots of people care about, and likely in a way that he then ends up trying to roll back...

Because really it's bloody terrifying that her government might be given such a huge majority at such an important time.

It really, really is.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's insane.. Just looking at the posted *highest* prices for a endometrial ablation, if you did it privately in the UK (so not on the NHS.. not endorsing abusive medical tourism..), you'd pay less than $13k to fly to the UK, stay in a hotel for a period, pay for the entire treatment and fly back.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pay $60+ for 15 down .75 up and it's the fastest thing where i live. :(

Shit...

I pay about $75 for 50 down and 5 up, a phone line with unlimited calls and cheap international (some free IIRC..) and two mobile phones (SIM only..) that have data, unlimited data and an absurd amount of talk time.  The US system really needs reform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Several' football arrests over Tax probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Several' football arrests over HMRC probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After that you don't pay for the internet anymore hence the "free"

Ah, that is a decent idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah you could be right that it might not change much, but I still think some people would benefit from seeing some actual unedited coverage of Corbyn.

Ha, I'd like Labour to do well in this election, so I'm honestly not sure if they should. Although at least if they do get some, then maybe we avoid the after election struggle of whether we should continue down the current route regardless of electoral results, or find something that actually works..

and I agree entirely that we shouldn't be focused on the leaders so much, it's really terrible. I would probably prefer politics to be entirely anonymous and purely policy led but the problems with that obviously make it a ridiculous idea.

In an ideal world, you could get rid of parties (I think that was the intention in the US at one point..) and make it all about policy, but.. well, we are a long way from that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say that the point here is that "nation has not spoken" by any means.

It has 'spoken' in so far as it speaks on anything. The whole point of holding a referendum was because it was an issue that crossed party lines, where there was discontent and Parliament wanted guidance from the electorate. They got it...

And with the tight results of the public consultation (with no legal value) the only out-come should be thorough parliamentary debate possibly followed by election where the politicians would present their program regarding the brexit - so the new parliament would get the mandate to go further.

Why? I mean, apart from the fact that there was parliamentary debate, and a parliamentary vote based on the public consultation (the UK is leaving because Parliament allowed the PM to trigger A50, not directly because of the referendum...) and of course there will be a general election now too. 
 An election which will almost certainly return a massive majority for the Government, and even if it didn't, the opposition parties are all also supporting the view that the UK should now leave the EU.

Finally the adoption of measures of the constitutional magnitude (as invoking art 50) should follow the UK constitution

They do, in so far as the UK constitution and conventions exist. We even had a supreme court decision on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't think they do. If you think back to the various elections before TV debates, there was an element (especially with Blair) of it, but it was less than the 'Clegg' factor in 2010 or massive focus on the likes of Farage and Bennet in 2015. If you go back a little further it becomes even less pronounced and you see groups of 'leading' people from the parties as more important. Fewer people attend hustings too of course, and campaign material has become more and more focused on national and leadership figures than local issues and candidates..  But I'd argue the TV debates solidified that and took it even further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the bigger issue is the media. 

No, it's not. The bigger problem is that Corbyn and the party are both doing a really bad job when it comes to the media. The party are in a position where even when there are successes to be had, they aren't being properly presented, it's an absolute shit show in that regard. The print media isn't neutral in the UK, it has never been but the last few years have been particularly bad (and Ed had similar issues, albeit not to the same degree, so did Brown for that matter). It's not as though Cameron didn't have issues with the media either, the difference was the level of competence shown in managing narratives and presenting things.

Now I get that Corbyn wanted to do things differently, but he failed miserably in that regard, even a lot of the Labour/Corbyn social media efforts are incredibly poor. You can't simply shift the blame to the media.

As to Ed, he was presented as less electable, but the Miliband Labour party  was nowhere near the territory that the party under Corbyn is in now.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also holds quite a few positions that are unpopular, as well has having had massive problems showing he can lead the Labour party, that's not all some media creation, it has come from the Labour party and has been obvious (between the no confidence votes, difficulty in filling Shadow cabinet posts, resignations and leadership challenges). The unelectable bit isn't tripe, he's actively unpopular with a large segment of the population, to the point where his leadership is putting off people who would normally vote labour (and that is evidenced in the polls, the party's own campaigning and anecdotally..). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's true that it doesn't fit, but it's also the case that a great deal of people don't have problems with Corbyn's policies but some notion that he is a weak personality.

Right, but if we were a little less focused on presidential style debates and personality that might matter less. The team around Corbyn have been focusing everything on him, rather than Labour as a part for a long time now, and unfortunately that really hasn't helped. May isn't seen in isolation in the same way, that means that even through she isn't a great speaker, she is seen as being able to manage and that's more where the whole notion of 'good PM/bad PM' material seems to come from. If we were dealing with that on both sides, things might be a little better.

that too doesn't fit, and a TV debate can show the people that make these judgements that they shouldn't eat up everything the press gives them. not everyone has an active interest in politics, but many of them still vote.

I'm honestly not sure that a TV debate would change the views people have of Corbyn because it's not filtered through the media in some other way.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And an even smaller proportion (using the same method..) voted to remain. That's broadly the point isn't it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> slow but "free" internet, it was like $300 hookup or $25 a month for a year.

If you are paying $300/y or $25/mo it's hardly free... (In fact it's about what you'd pay for a semi-decent internet connection in places like the UK) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
