<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4858</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 09:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americans, killing more Americans than Al Qaeda (and ISIS and Abu  Sayef and any other Jihadist group) since 2000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither is necessary just ignore it and don't recognise the concept. There is no reason for the secular state to engage religious groupings on anything other than its own terms. In fact the concept itself, like quite a lot of religion, is demonstrably false and only really exists to bind together against an imagined other. It is no different to the medieval and later ideas of Christendom. Fine if calling for Jihad (Crusade) against Infidel (Heathen) but the minute it is just them in a room the unity shatters and relatively minor points of doctrine can mean the difference between life and death.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are plenty. And plenty of British : Turks, Iraqis, African origin Muslims etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh its the mid 2000s all over again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is stupid to allow the creation of Muslim as an identity and individual demographic. What does a Somalian's experience have to do with a Malaysian's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a lot of Afghan men living in Afghanistan are gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You assume they want to avoid conflict. I think NK must be top of the list for a nice distracting war, totally justifiable because they do say crazy things, actually have WMDs and slave camps for lots of their population. It will either be Iran or NK but Trump is going to have a war with someone. Because it will automatically boost the economy and allow him to exert more direct control and call any opposition un-american and traitors etc. It will also happen soon. He knows he only has 4 years, so 1 year to ramp up the hate, 1 year to prepare for invasion, 1 year for actual war then campaign for re-election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA truly doesn't realize how quickly it could drop out of the driving seat. Other countries are more populous, make more stuff and the bulk of the science is done by foreigners. American exceptionalism was based on the opposite of isolation, it was based on global war/trade and massive government spending and strategic planning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you take back your street beggars please they are a scam and annoying. Thanks, Western Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All posturing and pre negotiation tactics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally someone talking sense! Preach! MAGA! edit : irony, thought i was responding to /s comment. Also if I try to go to america in the next 3 years I totally meant the comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/2925337/vienna-austria-new-years-gang-rape-sex-attack-iraq-asylum-seekers-accused/    

http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-4253226/Asylum-seekers-charged-gang-rape-NOT-deported.html    

http://metro.co.uk/2017/02/23/family-of-nine-gang-raped-drunk-woman-for-two-hours-as-she-pleaded-for-them-to-stop-6465784/

It happened. And you know the Mirror is a left wing paper? The real question is why it is ignored by "respectable" news media. I see the trend now is to deny every story. The accused have literally been in court, one confessed and they have comments from the named prosecutor and named judge. 

You are right to fact check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the brothel is closed and now the girls are working in parks and alleys in the cold getting STIs and murdered but at least the privileged can feel like they tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine Iraqi asylum seekers from same family 'gang-raped German teacher for hours' on New Year's Eve in Vienna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe there was an honor code not to do disreputable things while on the scholarship program like fucking a drunk chick at a party in a bathroom 2 up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do these numbers support my view? I don't know whether to shout fake numbers or call you racist for identifying "foreign" doctors.../s What should I say? What stance should I take? Wait let me check my fb for what to think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what I was replying to and certainly what I meant was not about getting to London but increasing infrastructure/transport spend in the North and the regions so business can relocate from London and people can move, bypassing the need for London growth at all. Not increasing the links to London but the links between northern cities. My mention of HS2 might have confused that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree plus the risk of it turning the north into feeder dormitory towns for London is horrific. Similar problems happened in Europe after building mega rail projects. Not sure what the solution is perhaps increasing property prices and increasing social unrest from the unemployed in cheap government subsidized  accommodation will see the middle levels (everyone on 30 - 80k) leave London and head to nicer more balanced parts of the UK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billions being spent on HS2 and the liberalisation of flying between the regions where many many people fly from north to south means it isn't that bad. Plus if you travel at the right times (not commuter time) driving is very easy fast and cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why imposition of US healthcare rather than Germany, Swedish or French? Most of Europe operates private insurance topping up state insurance, several have minor charges for GP visits etc and many have strict qualification criteria and ID cards to ensure treatment is only paid for citizens. All of which have been suggested for the NHS and rejected by public opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 09:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of European healthcare systems include things that would be unacceptable to people in the UK if introduced to the NHS. 

For example France has an ID card system to prove who you are and that you are eligible for treatment, Sweden charges a small amount for GP visits, Germany refunds the bulk of treatment costs and then the rest is refunded by private insurance etc etc all of these things were suggested for the NHS and each time cries of "evil Tories" "facsists" are screamed until nothing can be done. All at the same time as everyone saying UK NHS is dying and should be more like the wonderful European systems.

Don't disagree with you about there being a variety of solutions but  my point is that some change is required and the reason that the Tories don't get hammered on the NHS very successfully is that the other parties know the public will only allow minor tinkering but at the same time not allow massive tax increases to put billions more into the NHS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For USA reditors this is like being a teacher and complaining you can't buy a house in NY or beside Google. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter who is in power, there are massive problems with demographics and how much people are prepared to pay. Council's liability to legacy council pensions also limits their operational budgets creating problems. 

No one in the UK could fund the NHS properly, as the problems affect the entire developed world. The reason there is no real opposition to the Tories is that all the others have seen the books and realise they would probably be doing a variation of the same. Hint, there are areas of the UK that have self governed for a long time now and are not doing anything that different or having much better results. Edit : Sentence structure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or to keep it UK the "glassing" in London when a girl is verbally harassed. Viral outrage then finally announced as social experiment etc http://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/footage-shows-stranger-smash-bottle-6728834 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related to, Bill Fucking Murray !?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And make people clean their shoes and freak out about any tents being brought in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't his twitter and he isn't Capt America either. I would have expected a journalist from a respected newspaper to do some background and probe a bit. I have learnt more from 10 randoms posting on a reddit forum than a newspaper worth millions paying the journalist thousands per year. Why has no one in the media done a simple twitter check and said oh look someone from the same country with the same name is a muslim activist super critical of USA policy perhaps the real story is over zealous/incompetent/pointless security checks. But they just let it play out and people are getting worked up over half a story. Now the other guy even says he is not the welsh teacher on twitter. So the media is still lying by omission telling half a story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be wrong because you are talking about race as if it literally exists outside of USA and blacks vs whites, there is no other discourse allowed only the USA black white paradigm. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 11:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A not THE UK police chief. One who is trying to get career profile or a public profile for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 11:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winners!!! Big winners!!! NOT losers. Winners!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This kind of reporting is as bullshit as the one sided fox news narratives. Why do Indy and guardian have to omit things that don't support their narratives just means I can't trust them for the rest of their stories. They would have more of a point if they said Muslim activist who advocates whatever and is critical of USA foreign policy is denied entry to USA where is the free speech etc. BUt they went all out for the rage yet more clickbait from grown up media that should know better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only there was a titanium ultralight chair I could buy so I can be really ultralight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edinburgh also old and built up spent about 100 million per mile on a single tram line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The videos from Canadians being shouted at by some fuck wit border guard are crazy. The cop (a hero in his own mind keeping USA safe just like his brother flag wearers like Delta and SEALS) going off on one about how the stop terrorists on a daily basis coming in from Canada! Just total bullshit, he even looks like he believes his own lies. All because this guy was going to the mall with his family and didn't worship the cop power structure and expected to be treated as a human being.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct and especially worrying when you find out there is very little comparison between top pay and actual 
performance of companies. Several activist shareholders/funds now challenge crazy top pay and it is probably only a matter of time before limits/controls on top salaries become imposed, either by shareholders or in some places like Europe by governments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or admit they are gay and not kid themselves, they should just fuck their bro dude, he probably wants the same thing. He probably gets off to gay porn because they work their lats harder and definition etc no homo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got an old early 90s Muddy Fox courier comp frame and forks, stripped 9 spd deore from a Scott hardtail and bought new shimano wheels. It is awesome and have toured Uk end to end with it fully loaded tent etc. Handled well and nice to ride. Now it is used as a commuter. It is great fun doing a build and a great way to learn, one day it will go to Africa.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were welcomed, people really did not like Sadaam but they allowed chaos to take over for too long and really did not know what they were going to do and had ZERO plan for after the war. They made most of the police/army unemployed and destroyed the civil infrastructure. Look at Basra in the south a city of 1.5 million with no water, power, limited medical capability and then asked 5-6000 troops to maintain order and rebuild. To put that into context that is about half the number of police that a similar sized area in UK (fully functioning civil society, light, power, food etc) might have.   

The local powers in the region saw the reality on the ground and exploited it for the own gain so Iran effectively took over southern Iraq through its control of politicians and street militias which controlled the police. Further north the Sunni population feared Iranian influence and whole chunks of Sadaam's intelligence and SF machine went underground creating AQ linked groups and the precursors to ISIS. These Sunni groups may or may not have got support from some gulf state wealthy people to counter Iran/Syria axis. 

In the planning phase anyone who had a brain and said you will need more troops for occupation/rebuilding was sacked and by the time it was clear that the whole thing was a disaster everyone responsible had promoted clear of blame/joined the private sector or retired with their power and cash intact. Many Generals and politicians like Cheney, Rumsfeld, Blair.

In short they did not shape their plans to reality they expected reality to conform to their plans. There is no evidence at all they have learned. Plans for Libya went the same way and suggested plans for Syria and training forces etc were fantasy. Trump/Hilary bs aside the most sensible part of Trump's campaign was questioning the constant spend of American blood and cash on other peoples wars but even now that seems to have gone out the window.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen that documentary it is know in US Intel circles as Team America. Fuck Yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly you have not heard of Afghanistan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 10:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at Piers's attempt to break into America and his anti gun stance. Everyone in UK was happy he left, shame he is back. NOw he just picks and chooses his stance to get publicity sometimes right sometimes left just depends what will get him the most social media traction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 10:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-3806018/Ex-husband-Labour-s-domestic-abuse-Minister-nightmares-attack-divorce.html

The Labour minster for equality was actually cautioned for domestic violence against her husband so all things are definitely not equal. And apparently it was the mans fault for "tension". PP in full effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chu-Ko-Nu when you have the great wall is particularly good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.theguardian.com/world/2011/mar/30/onagawa-tsunami-refugees-nuclear-plant
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yanosuke_Hirai
http://www.oregonlive.com/opinion/index.ssf/2012/08/how_tenacity_a_wall_saved_a_ja.html

The trained engineer executive who noticed the "folk" memory and historical warning stones and insisted the sea wall was high enough to withstand historical tsunamis and the cooling system would still work as the sea receded. He put good engineering above short term profit (unlike Fukashima company) and saved his company and Japan billions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, people are just anti change but then constantly whine about the current situation. Can you imagine the outrage if new pump storage hydro was to be built, people would be living in trees and burying themselves to save the hills etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do keep up, you are slightly behind the current outrage curve. But A + for effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But environmentalists oppose the barrage because of the impact on the coast and sealife and would not let it be built. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 10:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take it you mean Iran will give them a bomb? Do you agree with the current ramping up tension and trying to start a war with Iran? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 10:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> India Pakistan is a potential. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 09:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was reading this looking for a comment on Brent Spar. Even some of the environmental groups agreed it would probably have been better to pump it out then sink it deep but they only said this after they had raised such outrage, protests, fire bombings in Germany etc. http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/c6108ee0-62fc-11db-8faa-0000779e2340.html?ft_site=falcon desktop=true

http://www.independent.co.uk/news/greenpeaces-brent-spar-apology-1599647.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much black and white propaganda, good vs evil etc which is fine trying to teach children morals and the difference between right and wrong but as an adult you should be able to see consequences and understand nuance. I cant think of any country whose diplomats talk about "seeing who has our back" and "taking names", fucking clowns. 

I wonder how many Americans saw the new Star Wars movie saw the death star and Imperial troops and realised "gee that is us" or how many saw the cool rebels and thought "yeah that is us fighting for freedom".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think quite a few voters forgave him for being a dick when they believed he said America should stop fighting wars for other people and promoted a more isolationist stance for USA. Turns out that was bullshit too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I bet if they had touched a judge they would be in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but it feels right and goes along with everything else so it just fits so must be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The land of Lybia and the fabled realm of Tunesia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no doubt that the average Syrian was better off before the recent civil war. The war has displaced millions, created chaos and many many dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The proper bolongnese spaghetti sauce is made with carrots which is why some bastardized versions suggest you put in ketchup. The ketchup (loaded with sugar) is just adding the sweetness that carrots should have added not the "tomatoyness" of the ketchup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also remember the SNP love in with Trump when he was golfing with their leaders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should grow up. Turn up stay silent, don't stand etc but attend and show some respect to the American people and country even if he is a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So nice to hear these examples of normal human behaviour where normal people don't freak out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good and I hope that some of the people he persecuted sue him for damages he deserves to be ruined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't give a shit about reality and was purely anti- establishment taking any case he could construct if it was against the MOD. I don't believe lawyers like him believe anything objectively and probably convince themselves that the truth is purely argument won in court, which is a view but not one I share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump will be gone in a few years and it will take longer than his presidency to get out of EU and start signing trade deals. But that is diplomacy and looking longer ahead than the next tweet or soundbite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 10:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep much better if Japan had achieved dominance over SE Asia, would have gone well for Australia. But yeah people like Bannon talking about war like it is a sport or fun political strategy and not even worth trying to avoid are sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it was true the last thing you want is a collapsed Iran. JESUS CHRIST HAVE WE LEARNT NOTHING FROM CREATING VACUMS IN MUSLIM COUNTRIES!!!!!!!! It is not good for anyone, anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did the right thing, peaceful protests need to stop themselves being used by extremists who usually have a different agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you need to show some leadership reign in the hyperbolic idiots calling Trump literally Hitler, defend free speech and civil argument and self police non violent protests.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually that is probably the aim of the people behind the protest to provoke over reaction by the state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have forgotten what extremism actually is and that left wing extremism can literally mean kill the rich ie anyone you label as worthy of death. Smashing the state is an end goal to rebuild it how you want it. Look at the Spanish civil war and the slaughter between different left wing or anarchist factions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, people get that much jail time for cutting peoples throats in UK hope he learns though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zealot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 10:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must keep the wierding modules. Edit : And they must keep the awesome non newtonian blocky shield armour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the evidence points to the opposite that they look at Muslims first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even better massive crowd in silence all turn their back to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily he is now elevated to a powerful position on the NSC instead of career military and intelligence officers. Reading his statement he is mad. Even if you believed what he said that Jihadists and ISIS will eventually be pitched against "the west" you have to ask what his end game is. Work with the Islamic world to destroy this ideology or provoke the Islamic world to conflict forcing them to choose sides? Also there are nowadays many Islamic American citizen how will he fight their inherent Islamism? Will he attempt to force conversions, exile? I think they have a year or so of this level of crazy before the grown ups in the deep state of USA "make changes". Because the end point of his thinking will be internment camps for people against Trump and it won't be long before they are wanting to change the constitution for their own ends and a lot of oath keeper types will find themselves on the wrong side of team Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not wrong for some of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republican voters supported Trump but the majority of the GOP machine did not. Given his actions are at odds with established political norms like gutting the NSC and having ambassadors talking about having backs and taking names, how long before the GOP begins to act against him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican voters supported Trump but the majority of the GOP machine did not. Given his actions are at odds with established political norms like gutting the NSC and having ambassadors talking about having backs and taking names, how long before the GOP begins to act against him? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take it back to the 9/11 twin towers everything after that is like being in an alternate timeline with incredibly odd decisions being made. Like invading Iraq and trying to find an excuse to bomb Iran, welcoming fb and google and handing over our id and privacy to corporations willingly. The total political christian domination of GOP. If you brought the founding fathers back they would explode that everything they tried to avoid has happened, oligarchy, religious politics, information tyranny, becoming the worlds policeman, constant war etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delta force. Navy Seals. The Rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The vet isn't Scottish. EDIT : The vet isn't by ANY definition Scottish. Stop peddling inaccuracies because they feel good and half the bullshit will go away. She was born in Iran, only has Iranian nationality, grew up in Italy and joined Glasgow University as a  resident in veterinary anaesthesia in November 2015. It is stupid to deny her transit visa but there are real facts and bending them to fit feels created the Trump/Hillary nightmare. Downvoters feel free to explain how she is Scottish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweden? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get more affluent family next time. Stay in the nice parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think online fund raising go to 5k last time i looked so she is doind very well out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 14:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tAlPwnkQURg

"Crack? Crack, Super Hans?"
"Relax. It's not Blue Peter. I'm just having a relaxing smoke of crack" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 13:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iranian living in Glasgow. Still crazy that her transit visa to connect to a flight out of USA was blocked but in the article it does say she can't fly out of mexico, panama, cuba etc because she would need a proper visa for those countries too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming from an ambassador this is more embarrassing than anything Trump has done and is barely at the level of minor corporate politics let alone high end stuff. USA is about to be outmaneuvered by skilled diplomacy that is playing a longer game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 11:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The axle of Elvis. I suppose for Russia is better than being the axis of evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And 4 kids, black lab and Land Rover/Range Rover but it is ok because they recycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ban all wood burning stoves inside the city. The smoke particulates are a real problem and at least cars and vans are doing something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not a steer then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
