<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8631</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard? Well blake would have appreciated that before  he died-.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just use it for nosleep. We need you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was quick! O.o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Second Part! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Will Either Face a Gruesome Death or Make Half a Million (Part 2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [DAY 1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66373g/i_will_either_face_a_gruesome_death_or_make_half/)

When I woke up this morning the image of Codys open eye sockets flashed in my mind. I looked around the room and everyone was already awake. Blake and Elise looked completely normal but Allison was shaking and looked completely pale. I asked her if she was okay. She looked at me with eyes filled with torment before throwing up all over her bed. Blake jumped out of his bed and ran to Allison and started to pat her on the back. She shook him off and said, Im fine. Just, please. Dont touch me. Im sure you would rather touch pretty boy over there anyways. 

Blake stood up from his bed. He opened his mouth but immediately closed it again when Elijah walked into our room. After a small cough, Elijah looked down at us and said, Its time for breakfast. Get dressed. Allison you um. You take a shower. It smells disgusting in here. Allison put her hand out towards Elijah and asked, Do you have any. ugh. Any heroin? I need it. I cant go on without it. Please. Can you help me? Elijah scoffed and told her to wait in the room. Elise went into the restroom to change her clothes while Blake and I changed in the room. Allison had her face on the pillow the entire time. 

Right as I finished dressing, Elijah walked back into the room and threw a small spoon with brown tar on it, a lighter, and a needle on Allisons bed before walking back out. I didnt want to watch her do that again so I followed Elijah out of the room. We walked into the kitchen and saw two pieces of toast on each plate and a jar of grape jelly sitting in the middle of the table. I took a seat and quietly ate. Blake and Elise came out a couple minutes after I did and started eating. 

When I finished my breakfast I got up and walked into the living room. Elijah was sitting on the couch staring out the window. I sat next to him and asked, So when are we starting today? Elijah let out a quiet sigh and said, We start in 6 hours. Relax until then. Meditate if you do that shit. You do any drugs? I thought for a second and asked, Shit. I want some cigarettes and the harshest drink youve got. Elijah looked at me for a second before laughing and slapped me on my back. He got up from his chair and walked out the front door. A couple minutes later, he came back with a thermos and a carton of Marlboro Smooths. I gratefully took them from his hands and sat back on the couch.

I ripped open the carton and took out a pack of cigs. I dont know about you, but no matter how stressful anything is. A cigarette somehow takes the edge off. It makes you think that no matter what situation you are in. You have a chance of getting through whatever you find yourself in. Right as I put the cigarette in my mouth Elijah lit it for me. I sat back on the couch and opened the thermos. Took a sip and felt the liquid go down my throat and produce a feeling of warmth and comfort instantaneously. 

I closed my eyes for what felt like a second, but Elijah was shaking me and telling me to wake up. I groggily opened my eyes and grunted in response. The thermos bottle was still in my hand. Holding back throw up, I put the thermos bottle down and saw that half of it was gone. After a couple of deep breaths, I got up from the couch and walked into the room. The other three were sitting on their bed staring at a simple white table that was just placed in the middle of the room. Elijah walked up into the room and up to the table and said, Well guys. Its time. Im going to use my phone to record you guys tonight. He tapped on his phone a couple of times before pointing the camera towards us. 

He let out a whistle and one of the men dressed in all black walked into the room and set four knives on top of the table. Elijah pointed the camera towards the knives and said, Alright guys walk up to the table and grab a knife. Once you pick a knife walk back to your bed with it and sit down. I got up from the bed and grabbed a knife along with the others and walked back to my bed. Elijah turned his phone around and I could see his face fill the screen along with **42683 viewers** written on the top right of the screen. He let out a dramatic breath before saying, Okay guys. The game has begun. Do what your gut tells you to do! Show the world who you truly are. 

He stood in the corner and pointed the camera back at us. 


We all stared at each other dumbly for what felt like an eternity. Elise was gripping her knife extra hard as she stared each of us down. Allison was sitting in the middle of her bed. Clutching the knife with both of her hands. Blake had his head hung down low. He was barely holding on to his knife. I started to look back at Allison, but Blake let out a huge sob. I looked back at him and saw him staring at Elijah. Tears were dripping down his face. He grabbed his knife and with a shout lunged towards Elise. Her eyes were wide and her body was still as Blake plunged a knife deep into her left shoulder. A scream erupted from her mouth as she tried to push Blake off of her. He took the knife out of her shoulder and started to bring it back down on her when Elijah grabbed him and threw him on the ground. Elijahs helper ran up to Blake and kicked the knife out of his hand. Blake tried to get back up, but the man pushed him back on the ground and tied up his wrists tightly with rope. 

Elijah nodded at the man and walked up to Blake and held him down. The man then walked up to each of us and took the knives from us. 

Once he gathered all of the knives he grabbed Blake by his hair and sat him on his bed. Elijah grinned at Blake while he pointed the camera towards him and said, Well that was awfully quick. Blake. Blake. Blake. Were you mad? What made you stab poor little Elise? What did she do to you? Huh? Made fun of you for liking mens butt? Blake looked up at him and stared him down. Elijah let out a small laugh before saying, Well honestly. I dont really give a fuck. You proved that lust wasnt your only fault, and because of your little hissy fit. You lost. He turned the camera back towards him and said, Okay. I have chosen two people to give my lovely assistants instructions on how we should end Blakes life.

He whistled towards the door and his other helper walked in and helped the other man carry Blake and placed him on the table. 

Elijah then looked at us and said, Open up your laptops so you can see that commands that come on the screen. I opened up my laptop and instantly saw Blakes face fill the screen. 

The first command came on the screen. 

**I want you to chop off his hands.**

One of the men grabbed a knife out of the bag while the other held Blakes hands down on the table. The man quickly brought down the knife down and the sound of bones crunching against sharpened metal followed by a loud thud as the knife landed on the table filled the room. Blake didnt scream. He just looked at the bloody stub that was once his right hand. Before Blake even took his eyes off his severed hand the man sliced off his other hand. 

I tried turning my head away to avoid watching anymore but I couldnt move. I wanted to help him, but I knew it would only end up with me giving up my life. I looked back on the screen as the next command came up.

**Stab him in the stomach and shove one of his severed hands inside.**

I managed to look away right after the man stabbed him in the midsection. He was whimpering but it soon became screams of pure agony. It took all of my willpower to look away. I thought it was over when the room became quiet, but I felt someone tapping on my shoulder. I looked up and saw Elijah standing next to me. He pointed at the screen and I looked at the next command.

**Get Jared. I want him to slice a chunk of Blakes thigh off and take a bite off of it. He must chew it and swallow.**

I had to reread it several times before I could even comprehend what I was supposed to do. Elijah grabbed my arm and led me up to the table. Blake was lying down on the table almost completely still. He was slowly blinking as I took the knife from the man. 

This is where I doubted everything about me. I thought I would never be the person that would be able to mutilate a person, eat a chunk of human meat, or do it without hesitation, but within seconds I was shoving Blakes severed thigh flesh in between my lips. I took a decent sized bite out of it and soon my mouth filled with the taste of salt and copper. I gagged a little, but I kept chewing until I managed to get it into a texture I could swallow. 

Elijah gave me a small tap on the middle of my back before saying, Okay guys. Last request and we are done for the night.

It only took a couple of seconds for the last command to pop up. 

**Let Jared see my face. Let him see my face as I watch him stab Blake 5 times in the chest.**

Elijah let out a sigh and clicked on the profile that sent out the last command. It showed a picture of when I was 7. I wanted to scream but I held it in. Elijah then turned on the feed to the persons camera and saw myself looking at my mother and father. They were smiling at me and my mother cleared her throat before saying, Well what are you waiting for. This is your chance. Your only chance to finally bring us happiness. You were always such a pussy, but Im glad you finally decided to do something ballsy. Pick up that knife and make mommy and daddy proud. 

Without hesitation, I stabbed Blake in the chest. I didnt stop at 5. I kept going. I couldnt stop. I was sobbing and I didnt want to kill him off, but he wasnt the one that was in my mind while I stabbed him. I thought about how amazing it would be to stab my parents. Over and over again. 

I snapped out of my moment of lunacy and looked down at the table. Blakes chest was nearly gashed completely open. I dropped the knife back on the table and walked back to my bed.

Its been 3 hours since I ended Blakes life and made a new mission for myself. 

I needed to win. I needed to stab my parents as many times as I stabbed Blake. They deserved the death I gave him. I dont care about the money anymore. I needed to get revenge on my parents. The pieces of shit that kicked me out of the house when I refused to kill my grandpa so that they could get what he left for them. The ones that refused to give me a single cent when I called them and told them I was starving.

The ones that told me that the only way for me to go back home was if I killed my [grandfather.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's not possible. anything past 6 months cannot be downvoted. i just checked. you only have one post within the last 6 months. Try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is the first time i did it, and it is something i wanted to do. I'm sorry but I'm the one that is spending hours upon hours creating stories for people. 

If you don't like it move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> too bad :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't really spice things up, but I think on the weekly posts if you added in the nosleep rules as well it would benefit the community. A lot of new readers on mobile will not know what they are commenting is against the rules so if it was at the top of the page it would reduce a lot of the "rule-breaking" comments!

just a suggestion :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^OHHHHHHH Making History </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such hatred:) good day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Number 1 MOVIE IN AMERICA

**Coming Soon** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm. Imma let you find it while you get downvoted :) while i face the next challenge i can think about what a fool you are :) thank you for this entertainment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the rules. Read the rules. Read the rules. Read the rules. Read the rules.


P.s. read the rules. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY HEY HEY. get back on the table </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and if they track it down they will create a powerful enemy. but ^They ^can ^try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly do too. You read the first couple of sentences and commented. It's obvious because I explain how I can post on here. Try reading. It's fun and it avoids making you look foolish with non witty comments that provide zero benefits to the other commenters :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you read the whole thing? About how we were given laptops. We can use it for whatever we want?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh thank you very much :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh he's saying that the loser of each contest will do a show. like the last one did. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is kind of like the 2nd day now. I can interact with them, but they are all quiet. Maybe I can try to get them to talk to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the one I wrote in the story. America. Nashville, Tennessee. I feel like half of you guys didn't even read it. Just tried to look for something to find a plot hole in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The graphics card isn't good enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does that cost money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i am doing the first two and will try to do the last </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have to stay inside. I can use the laptop to do a couple of things, but mostly youtube and reddit right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not allowed to. You can see or watch it if you get an invitation and you pay the 50k unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh well I started posting on r/NoSleep but they have other writing communities here. I would link to my Facebook Author Page at the bottom of each story! I'm at around 1800-1900 followers. That's after 3 months of having my facebook page up and running.

For the publisher. NoSleep has a great publishing company that sort of works with them. Once you get a decent following and a good story line they will contact you! Or you can contact them. Just PM me and I will let you know specifics!

P.S. When I was young my dream job was to be an entomologist XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly same thing for me, but I just started to write and write and write. Now after 5 months of writing I am publishing my first book and have a decent following on facebook! It's a lot of fun and will keep your mind alert as you look around the office looking for things to inspire your next story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thereeeee it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends how long I last. I could die today, tomorrow, or i could win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " I just hope it doesn't stretch beyond 4 or 5 episodes." this was the part i was referring to XD because you know me. Somehow I make other series connect to it and then next thing you know. BAM 17 parts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> definitely not mine lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here stands a legend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well tooooooo bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have the coke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really isn't mentioned for being so big.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it really isn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant believe so many people are fussing over this small detail of the story when people are dying for entertainment, but gotta find something to poke a hole in our experiences. So here. 

3.99 for lm menthol bolds(cigs) 2 for 3 dollar gatorades. 3 sandwiches for 1.49 a piece. After tax i still have some change left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk why this has anything to do with the story to make it crucial but here .

3.99 for lm menthol bolds(cigs) 2 for 3 dollar gatorades. 3 sandwiches for 1.49 a piece. After tax i still have some change left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like i said nashville,tennessee. 3.99 for lm menthol bolds(cigs) 2 for 3 dollar gatorades. 3 sandwiches for 1.49 a piece. After tax i still have some change left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read it? They gave us a laptop for us to use........ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thank you :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. One of my favorite stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I need all the luck I can get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope i can finish it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The cost to watch is 50k. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And piss off the viewers? No.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another series? about a dark web for rich people </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Will Either Face a Gruesome Death or Make Half a Million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, my name is Jared and I am homeless. Well. I was homeless. Im now fighting for my life. How did I find myself in that predicament? Well, I chose to. Why? Because I want to win half a million dollars.

Last Night, I was walking around the streets of downtown Nashville. I finished the day off with around thirteen dollars in my pocket. Im not homeless because I had shit luck. Im homeless because I was a stubborn twenty-year-old trying to make it out on my own. I had family waiting for me back home, but I wasnt ready to crawl back to my family yet. Like I said, Im a stubborn guy. I would rather die than beg my parents to take me back. 

With the thirteen dollars I had in my pocket I could buy two gatorades, three ham and cheese sandwiches, and a pack of smokes. I was on the way to my usual convenience store when a man got out of the back seat of a Bentley and walked up to me. He was casually dressed in a t-shirt and jeans but I knew that the clothes he wore cost a small fortune. As he stuck out his hand towards me he said, Hey bud my name is Elijah and I would like to buy you some dinner. You look hungry. I shook his hand and asked him, Why? I have a little bit of money. I can buy my own dinner. 

He chuckled and said, Well. It looks like you havent had a decent meal in ages. Tell you what. I have way too much money and I like helping out people less fortunate. Ill get you some dinner and we can talk. If you dont like what I say I will personally go to any hotel of your choice and get you a room for 3 months. That sound fair?

I thought about it for a second before nodding my head nervously at him. He put his arm around my shoulder and led me into his car. He didnt take me anywhere really fancy. Just the local steakhouse and we took our seat at the back of the restaurant. He ordered a salad and I ordered a t-bone steak. The first half of the meal was silent. He wasnt really eating, just kept staring into the salad and moving around pieces of lettuce with his fork. 

The silence was broken when he put down his fork and let out a small cough. I looked back up at him with a large chunk of steak in my mouth and he softly asked, I have an opportunity for you. I swallowed what was in my mouth and asked, What kind of opportunity? Like a job? He gave me a small smile and said, Yeah. Well. Kind of. Let me be completely honest with you. I see you as a strong willed person. Suicide is the last thing on your mind, and that is what I am looking for. I have been watching you for the last three days. Keep in mind. This is an opportunity for you to make half a million dollars. That should be enough for you to be happy for a very long time.

Half curious and half disturbed, I put down my fork and asked, What do you mean you watched me for three days? What do I have to do to make the money? How do I know you even have that much money?  

After taking a deep breath, he got up from his chair and sat next to me. He leaned his face towards my ear and whispered, Five people go in. One person leaves. This is for a, hm, lets just say its a show. People from all over the world pay fifty grand to watch you guys like its a reality tv show. Of course, people will die and it might be you, but if you win. You get to take home five hundred grand. No strings attached. 

I scooted away from him and pushed the meal away from me. He started to speak again but I held my hand up and told him to let me think. 

I know. Money isnt everything, but this was an opportunity for me. Probably a once in a lifetime opportunity. I knew the probabilities pointed to an early grave for me, but I just couldnt lose this chance. 

A chance to finally prove to my family that I was fully self-capable.

I looked back at him and said, Im in. When do we start? 

He clapped his hands together and said, Well we need to head out now. I will drive you to our private airplane. Erm. Im going to have to blindfold you when we get in the car, but the contest starts the day after tomorrow.

When he got up from his chair I got up and followed him to his car. He grabbed a blindfold from the front passenger seat and handed it to me. I covered my eyes up and sat back. After a couple of minutes, I felt the car start up and he put something in my hand and said, Take this pill. Itll knock you right out. I shrugged my shoulders and threw the pill into my mouth and swallowed it. As the car started to speed up I slowly drifted off. 

I woke up and felt a small pain inside of my ear. Once I managed to stand up I rubbed my eyes and looked around. Within a couple of seconds, I knew I was on a plane. There were two other guys and two women sleeping on their chairs. I sat back down on my seat and stared out the window. I noticed that it was the morning now. We were descending, but all I could see was the ocean. After a couple of minutes, the plane started to descend quickly. I looked out the window and saw an endless amount of trees. As the plane started to quickly go down I sat back in my seat and braced myself. I was completely convinced that we were about to crash into the trees, but as the plane touched down on the ground I saw that we were in a small clearing. 

The plane came to a stop and a door opened from the back of the plane. Elijah came out and walked to the front of the plane. I looked around and saw that everyone else was awake. He looked at all of us for a second before saying, Alright. Let me see if I can remember. Jared, Blake, Cody, Allison, and Elise. Did I get that right? We all nodded and he smiled before continuing, Okay follow me out of the plane and I will lead you guys to your room. The contest starts tomorrow. We have a computer for each of you to use. You can call out for help if youd like too, but it wont help. You see. We are now on an island that is not traceable. Plus, if you get found you wont win the money! So. The nights are your time. The daytime is entertainment time. Your only objective is to not be the last one to finish the challenge. The last one to complete the challenge will provide our lovely viewers with whatever they request.

He snapped his fingers at us and we all got up and followed him out of the plane and saw a small house in front of us. I started to panic, but I reminded myself that this is what I wanted. 

A chance to either prove myself or die. 

I was the first one to walk into the house and looked around. It was a small house with worn down hardwood floors, blue wall paint that was chipping with age, and a kitchen with surprisingly new appliances. The only thing in the living room was a small brown couch. I walked past the kitchen and into the only bedroom in the house. It was a larger room than I expected. There were five small beds with a laptop on each bed. The others walked up to the room and quietly picked out their bed. I chose the one closest to the door. 

Elijah walked into the room and said, I lied. The contest starts today. Open your laptop and turn it on. There will be a window that pops up. If you turn off your laptop or turn off the screen you instantly lose. He closed the door and I grabbed my laptop and booted it on. When the home screen came up a window came up almost immediately. 

The window was completely white for a second before it showed a footage of Blake walking into a store and groping a mans ass before running out of the store. We all looked at him and chuckled while he started to grow pale. The next clip showed Allison sitting in an alley shoving a needle into her arm and slowly injecting herself. I looked at her, but she looked away from all of us. Next, it showed Elise breaking into a house. She walked up to the sleeping man on the couch and she grabbed her pocketknife and sunk it into his throat. She proceeded to stab him 4 more times before running around his house and grabbing whatever valuable thing she saw. When her clip ended none of us looked at her. We didnt want to see a person witnessing a murder they committed. 

Right as they showed me on the screen I knew what it was. It was from two days ago. I was in the convenience store I always went into. A woman walked into the store and I dont know what came over me, but she was beautiful. She was wearing a very short skirt and a white shirt that prominently revealed her nipples when under the right light. I reached into my pants and pleasured myself. Right as I climaxed I looked up and saw that she was staring at me in disgust. I gave her a small nod before running out the store. I heard a couple of chuckles coming from the others, but the only thought that was running through my head was how they managed to get that filmed. 

Right as the next clip came up I heard Cody yell out, Fuck that. What the fuck. You show pussy ass shit for everyone else. Why the fuck you show me doing this shit? I looked back at the screen and saw Cody speaking to an old woman. They were laughing together while sitting on a park bench. She handed him a picture and I saw Codys face instantly turn sour. He started to yell at her and grab her by the shoulder. She tried pushing off of him, but he then put his hands around his throat and started to squeeze. She tried to get out of his grip, but she became still and he let go of her throat and ran away. The screen zoomed in on the picture. It was of Cody, the woman, and a man. I love you son, but please know that your daddy loved you just as much. 

Cody slammed his laptop shut and started to scream at us, Dont fucking judge me. I loved my mom, but she always backed up that filthy bitch. He fucking did shit to me man. He didnt love me. He was a piece of shit.

Elijah came into the room with two other men dressed in all black. The two men dressed in black picked up Cody and took him outside. Elijah stayed in the room and said, Keep the laptops on and stay on the screen you were looking at. Watch Codys punishment so that you may know what happens when you lose.

The screen came back live and I saw the two men standing behind Cody. He was sobbing and pleading for his life. It was the first time I saw a truly broken man. It took all of my willpower to not shut my laptop off right then.

Messages started to pop up on the bottom of the screen. 

The first one said, Take his eyes out. I dont want him to see what we will do to him next.

I saw Codys eyes glance down at the screen and he started to scream. The man on the right nodded his head and grabbed a rusty spoon from the table behind him. The other man held on to Codys face to keep it steady while the other guy scooped his eyes out. 

The next message said, I want you to cut off three of his fingers and shove it down his throat. The man put down the spoon and grabbed a kitchen knife. While the other man held on to Codys hand I looked away from the screen. The sound of bones crunching vibrated my eardrums. I looked back at the screen and saw Codys scream halting and changing to gagging as three of his fingers were shoved down his throat. 

The man that held the knife said, One last request. Make this one fatal.

The last message said, Stab him in the head 14 times. Keep stabbing even if he dies. 

The man nodded his head and put the kitchen knife down and picked up a pocket knife. 

Cody started to whisper, Please. Please. Just let me go back. I wont tell anyone about this. I just want to go back. I just His pleading ended when the knife entered and exited his head with forceful stabs. 

After the man stabbed Cody for the fourteenth time the screen blacked out and closed out. 

Elijah looked at all of us for a couple of seconds before saying, I will let you guys know when it is lunch time. The next challenge starts tomorrow. Prepare yourselves. Today was a cake walk. 

Im not asking for help. I know I will probably die, but I want to finish this out. That is why I am not posting this on my facebook or alerting anyone I know. People are paying 50 grand to watch this, but I figure I might as well entertain you with the written version. 

One down. [Three more to go.] 

[For Day Two] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66ally/i_will_either_face_a_gruesome_death_or_make_half/)




  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [this one?] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/50cx47/for_years_weve_defended_you_now_we_need_you_to/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is awesome to hear! Glad you enjoy them and party smart! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha thank you very much. It's honestly the whole Life is Beta series along with 12 unread stories! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure when to be completely honest :/

But on amazon! Hopefully it'll be soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just submitted in my first book :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you XD lmfao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drugs, Doors, and Far Too Many Arms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The soft sound the rain makes when it hits the window next to my face has helped me calm down just a little, but I am still a nervous wreck. 

I have been straight edge my whole life. Never drank a drop of alcohol, took a drag out of a cigarette, or taken any type of illegal drugs, but the past couple of months have been stressful. Two months ago, I smoked my first cigarette and loved how relaxed my body felt and how light my head was. Two weeks after that I drank my first beer with my three roommates (Jay, Richard, and Peter). The taste of it was terrible, but once I started to feel a buzz I grew to appreciate the taste of the lukewarm PBR.

Over the course of the next 45 days I continued to smoke cigarettes and drink beer, but I really never crossed that line. They tried to pressure me into trying some of the drugs they managed to find, but I just never really had an interest until Jay brought home some coke three days ago.

He was smiling from ear to ear when he dropped the sack full of yellowish-white powder on the table in front of me. With a bit more excitement than usual Jay looked at me and said, Okay. You wont do acid, weed, or shrooms, but you gotta try coke at least once. Just do one small line, and I will never ask you to try another drug again. 

I tried telling him I wasnt interested, but he ignored me and used his credit card to take out some coke from the bag. He then crushed it with the back of his card and spread them out into two small identical lines. I sighed and sat down on the ground next to him while he pulled out a crisp twenty dollar bill. While I stared down at the lines I saw Jays face lean in close to mine as he stuck the rolled up bill into his nose and snorted up the first line. 

He rubbed his nose and handed me the bill. With a sigh, I stuck it in my nose and snorted the second line. 

From the second the powder went up my nose I felt a rush of excitement. I wasnt addicted right off the bat, but damn, I really wanted to do another line. Jay laughed when he saw my face and asked, So Im guessing you like it. Just toss me 40 and I can give you half of the bag. Just dont go doing it all at once. That line I gave you. Do one that size, but dont do more than 3 in an hour. Gets a bit risky after that.

Without hesitation, I grabbed my wallet out of my pocket and tossed him 40 dollars and eagerly watched him scoop up half of the powder and put it into an empty Altoids tin. He handed the tin to me and I took it into my room and put it on my desk. 

Over the next two days I went through it all. When I asked Jay when he was getting some more he laughed and said about a week from now. I tried to not look disappointed but he gave me a solid pat on my shoulder and said he was heading out to pick up some molly. I gave him a nod and walked back into my room.

I sat on my bed and played around on my phone for a couple of minutes. My eyes started to droop after a couple of minutes so I just leaned against my headboard and closed my eyes. It only felt like a couple seconds passed by but I woke up to Jay shaking me awake and Richard and Peter standing by my door laughing about how I was drooling. 

With a groan I wiped off the drool from the side of my mouth and slowly got up. As soon as I stood up Jay grabbed my wrist and dragged me into the living room. I tried to ask him what was going on, but I already knew why they were so excited. When we got to the living room I sat on the couch and Jay threw a pill on my lap. I picked it up and looked at it. It was a clear capsule filled about a quarter of the way with pink powder. 

Feeling a bit weird about the pill I asked Jay what molly was supposed to do. Jay opened his mouth but Richard cut him off and said, Dude. Shit is wild. It takes about 20 minutes to hit, but when it does you feel like everything around you is amazing. You want to touch shit and you want to talk. Shit. I even called a couple of girls to come over in 30 minutes. They want some too. I was still a bit confused, but at the mention of girls I got a bit excited and popped the pill in my mouth. 

Within 2 minutes Jay stood up and said, Yo. This shit isnt right. Im already feeling shit and it doesnt feel right. I dont know. Rich. you alright bud? Youre fucking pale right now. He looked at me and started to scream, Dude. Youre foaming out of your mouth. What the fuck is going on?

He was right. I was foaming out of my mouth. Right after I took the pill I started to feel bile come up from my throat. I tried swallowing it down but it only made it come up stronger out of my throat. I couldnt breathe. I tried punching my throat but the foam kept coming out of my mouth. With my last couple of breaths, I looked around the room and saw the other three were lying completely still with the same foam spewing out of their mouths.

It might not be the same for everyone, but right as I died I found myself standing in the middle of a massive room. The floor and the ceiling were made up of gray concrete blocks. The walls were completely covered with thousands of doors. There was a hand on each of the door knobs, and every hand and arm led to one creature standing in the middle of the floor. It was pure black with arms that were completely white. Its head nearly touched the roof that my eyes could barely see. The face was almost invisible to my eye, but that wasnt the source of oddity. It was the arms that started from the bottom of its body to what seemed like the chest area.

The room was completely crowded by other people trudging along the room while some walked up to the creature and tugged on an arm. The creature would then retract its rubbery arm back and scoop the person towards the door the arm was on. 

I didnt know where the doors led to, but I wanted to look around the room and try to find my roommates. 

I walked around the room for what felt like an eternity, but no matter what I saw inside of the room I could not find any kind of answer. I tried talking to the others, but the few that actually talked back to me were as clueless as I was. I watched people walk through the doors but even the same door showed different results; it would go from sounds of melodious harps while they walked through with smiles on their faces to getting grabbed by a lumpy blue arm that ripped the person in half before dragging the person inside one half at a time. 

I finally found my three roommates after walking for what felt like an eternity. They were all sitting together towards the middle of the room. When I walked up to them Peter gave me a small smile and said, You ready to choose your destiny? Confused, I asked him, What do you mean choose my destiny? Peter pointed towards the creature and said, Choose an arm. That is what will lead you to where you are supposed to go.

I gave him a nod and asked, So whos going first? Richard said, Fuck it before grabbing an arm and waited for the hand to grab him. When the creature grabbed him and took him to the door he opened it and instantly the sound of sobbing filled the room. He looked scared as he walked through and the door closed slowly behind him. 

Jay looked at me with a look of worry before walking up to the creature. He nervously grabbed an arm and waited for the arm to grab him up. Right as he was grabbed up by the arm he looked at me and shouted, Up! When he opened the door he stood in front of a high pitched scream filled the room. I could see him shaking as two purple hands shot out of the door and grabbed him. They tore open his mid-section and drug him into the door with his intestines dragging behind him. 

Peter tapped my shoulder and I looked at him. After taking a deep breath he said, Im going to try to climb as high as I can. Go when I go. When I get to a spot I cant reach up climb on top of me and keep going up as high as high as you can. Right after he said the last word he started to climb on the arms of the creature. I followed him.

The arms I climbed up felt like dry jello. The whole time I climbed up I saw the bottom of Peters shoe. Right as we got to the top of the stomach area I noticed I was climbing on top of Peter. I managed to get my feet on his shoulder before I saw the hand of the creature grabbing Peter by the shoulder. I looked up and saw the next arm right above my head. I grabbed it and continued to climb up. Right as I got to the neck area I noticed that the creature did not have a face. It was covered in arms.

Right as I got to the arm at the very top I waited for the arm to grab me. It picked me up and took me to a door placed on the ceiling. I closed my eyes, opened the door and took a step through the door. I woke back up on the couch coughing up the remainder of the foam lodged into my throat. My roommates are all dead. I checked their pulses. 

Before I call 911 and tell them about the death of my three roommates I wanted to write this out to you guys. This may not be the same to everyone, but if you find yourself in a place where the only option is to give up your soul. 

[Look up.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did the same thing to life is beta! Four series and 2 one offs! Start a new series and blow people's minds with the connection! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely shorten the title. It is reaching the realm of summarizing the story. Which would call for removal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WELL IT'S MY ABSOLUTE FAVORITE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry. A lot of other NoSleep writers despise the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write for yourself. Not everything will get popular, but you never know what will gain more attention outside of Nosleep. We have had stories that don't even hit 200 upvotes but cause a stir on the internet or in towns. 

If you don't find it scary at all. Chances are others won't either. If you feel a tingle of fear while writing it. It is probably scary for the readers. I'm definitely not a veteran by any means, but I love writing and i'm closing in on 5 months writing here. Just stay consistent. Use your main reddit account and have fun! It's amazing when a story takes off and you can witness the comments pummeling in. Get involved with the commentors :) It makes it that much more real for them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But to say you find my skills marvelous actually makes me feel dirty. I'm well within part of nosleep. So if you insult nosleep as a whole you are insulting everything within nosleep. 

Instead of slamming other writers (Which yes. You did.) Send them a pm. Instead of calling yourself a prolific writer. Humble down and see yourself as an equal. Instead of ranting of negative feedback. Own that shit. I have written many flops, but I own it. Appreciate every aspect of the community you want to write in. 

Nosleep is a community. Get involved. Help others and they will help you. Insult them and you will start to get more and more negative feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( dont destroy me plz. I waz jus tryna halp :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait but i have a cult though ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying? Trying? Define trying... 

Do i spend 2 to 3 hours a day while having a kid and working a salary job to entertain readers? Yes

Do i try to think up of stories that are unique with as little tropes as possible? Yes.

Do i keep writing even when self entitiled assholes slam down on my work week after week? Yes.

Does almost every other established writer do the same thing as i do? Yes.

Do you? No. You're just ranting about upvotes in the most petty way possible. You are slamming down fellow writers so you can feel better about your sophomoric stories. So sit down. Relax. Drink your favorite drink and try. Try to be part of the community of writers that help each other. Try to write stories instead of rants on the OOC. 

Most of all. Try to not be an **asshole.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 700 upvotes will not be your peak. Buckling down and biting the bullet would be to continuously write new stories. Making a sequel is more of taking the easy way out. 

Plus, if it has been more than a week since the original. Expect it to be around 20 to 25 percent of what you got on the original.

If you need help let me know by pm. I will do anything i can to help you push out more stories. 

As a newer author myself. I want others to feel the awesome feeling of surpassing more upvotes than you thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmmmmm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Life Without Love.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Am Not Allowed To Fall in Love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may want to roll your eyes after the next sentence but just hear me out. My name is Dave, I am nineteen years old, and I know I will never have another relationship or get married.

You see, around five years ago I just went through my first and only break up. I told my friends I dumped her for a hotter chick, but the truth was. She dumped me for my step-sister, but how was I supposed to tell my friends that? Thats about the most embarrassing thing ever. My step-sister, who was a year younger than me, managed to steal my girlfriend.

Of course, my mother knew about it and was more than supportive to my sister, but she still felt bad for me. She came into my room and put 50 dollars in my hand and asked if I wanted her to drop me off at the mall for a couple of hours. I slowly nodded my head and started to get ready. 

On the way to the mall, I texted my 5 friends and told them to join me. My mother tried talking to me while we drove there, but I just silently stared out the window. When we pulled up to the entrance to the mall I got out of the car and slowly walked in. Before my mom drove off she yelled out, I love you, Dave! I glared her down until she drove away. 

I was there for two hours by myself. None of my friends texted back and I was getting ready to call my mother to pick me up when I saw the prettiest girl I have ever seen. I dont know what came over me. When she walked past me I started to follow her. She looked at me and gave me a smirk before turning around and planting the most passionate kiss I have ever felt in my life. My arms were flailing for a couple of seconds before the feel of her lips, the light coconut scent of her hair, and the warmth of her embrace made me lose track of everything. My arms matched her embrace and I was truly happier than I have ever felt in my life. It felt like days flew by before she pulled away from the kiss. 

She gave me a short laugh before asking, If you liked that. Why not just go ahead and promise to be mine forever? I was a teenager and my teenage hormones were bouncing all over my body. I didnt care how weird her question was. After taking a deep breath I asked, How do I do that? She grabbed my hand and asked, Just say yes and I will do whatever needs to be done. Without a second thought, I answered with a quick, Yes. I want that.  

She gave me a smile before her body started to melt. I shrieked and tried to jump back but my hand was stuck to whatever she had become. Soon she became a puddle. A puddle of flesh that surrounded me. 

Slowly, the liquid started to rise from the ground, and slither up my leg. I tried to slap it away but it easily avoided me and continued to crawl up. I tried yelling but my throat wasnt responding. Instead, I found myself sitting on the bench with my mouth wide open. Whenever I wanted to struggle my own body fought against my urges and kept me still until the liquid started to pour into my mouth. 

The taste of copper filled my mouth and I started to gag, but the liquid kept flowing down my throat. After around 10 to 15 seconds the remaining liquid went into my mouth and I regained control of my body.  

I called my mother and told her to pick me up before I ran into the restroom and tried to puke whatever was inside me out. I threw up my lunch and even part of my breakfast, but the liquid girl stayed inside of me. 

For the next couple of months, I monitored myself, but nothing seemed to be out of the ordinary. It still annoyed me seeing my sister making out with my ex but I got over it. For some reason, I was actually a little bit happier than I normally was. I was a lot more outgoing; I started to excel in all of my classes and quickly became one of the more popular kids in my freshmen class.  

Of course, this drew the attention to several girls, which I did not mind. I wasnt really interested, but out of nowhere, a girl named Molly caught my eye. She was shorter than average, blonde, and completely perfect to me. We started to spend more and more time together. I asked her out about a month later, and to my delight, she said yes. That was almost the best day of my life. 

That night, while I was lying on my bed thinking about how hard I fell for Molly I felt something rise out of my throat. 

I quickly closed my mouth and tried to swallow it back down, but the taste of copper came out of my mouth and a small glob of liquid bounced out of my mouth. I jumped out of bed, turned on the lights and looked around the room, but I couldnt find anything there. 

After looking around for a while, I became too tired and fell back asleep. The next morning when I woke up I got ready and my mother drove me to school. When I got to school I noticed something was off. Kids were acting normally until they were stopped by a teacher in the front of the school. They turned around and started to walk back to the car they were dropped off in. I ran up to a kid that was in my History class and asked him what was going on. 

He shrugged and said, They said someone died in our school. I asked him if he knew who it was, but he just shrugged his shoulders again and walked back to his car. Later on, while I was watching the news Mollys face popped up on the screen. I dropped the remote on the floor and continued to stare at the screen and hear about what happened to her. She was found in the middle of my first classroom. She had an envelope in her hand. They were investigating all of the tapes, but all they saw was her stopping in the middle of the class and grabbing at her throat. She fell to the ground and squirmed around for a couple of seconds before her movement stopped entirely.

It took me over 2 years to get over the death of Molly, but for some reason, I felt like I was never truly alone. 

I tried dating another girl, Grace, about three years ago, but I was never really into the relationship. She really tried to make the relationship work, but something inside of me was pulling me away from her. After several months of seeing her suffer I wanted to cut it off with her, but when I walked up to her to break up with her the next day I froze in my steps. This was the girl that really went through months of torture to make me fall in love with her, and I really did start to love the girl. The love that I havent felt since meeting Molly.

I walked up to her and grabbed her close to me before planting a kiss on her cheek. I whispered I love you into her ear and for the first time. She truly looked happy.

The day flew by. After school, we walked around the school parking lot for hours and talked about everything important and stuff that was completely trivial. I loved every single second of it. 

When I got home, I immediately started to text her and we talked until around 1 AM. Right as I put my phone on my side table and started to drift off I felt nauseous. I tried with all of my strength to hold it back, but no matter how much I tried I felt the same taste of copper come out of my mouth. Right as a cup full of goo expelled out of my mouth I jumped right on the spot I thought it landed on but it was gone. 

I tried texting Grace to be careful, but I started to feel the liquid come out of my mouth again. I started choking and tried to grab whatever was in my throat with my fingers but before I put my fingers in my mouth I felt it rush out of my throat. 

It was the girl that I saw at the mall. I tried reasoning with her, but she raised her hand and a blur flashed across my face. I woke up the next morning to a bunch of texts on my phone. They were all about Grace. She was dead. She was found in her room. I called her brother, John, on the phone and through sobs, he described out how he found her. She was lying on her bed. He hands were around her neck. Her face was completely blue. Her neck had several gashes. Her blood surrounded her dead body. He swore up and down that he saw a pinkish liquid coming out of her mouth. 

She was the last one I fell in love with. I have tried everything I can to stay out of the way of anyone I felt like I had a chance of falling in love with. Sometimes I wake up in the middle of the night and see the girl I saw at the mall. The girl that is now a permanent part of me. No matter how many times I have seen her I can not describe what she looks like. All I know is that she is everything I desire in a woman. 

Like I said. I tried really hard to stay out of the way of love, but just the other day, I met a girl. Her name is Amber. I helped her study for her communications exam. She gave me her number and we are going out to a movie. I hope I dont [fall in love.](https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okayyyyyyyyyyyyyy WE GOT IT THE FIRST TIME. 

Jk. 

RIP Karma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh thank you so much :c it blows my mind getting compliments gahhhh, but I know you can do it!

Just read Migraines :) very well written! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's along the same lines of practice, but be consistent. Write for at least 2 hours a day. It becomes second nature to you after that. 

Try to find inspiration from normal things and twist it up as much as you can. and what u/EtTuTortilla said. I actually don't use the restroom until I have my story written out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potato checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause mass hysteria

Make the next war of the worlds

Well minus the death and stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final Part of the New Series! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Pieces of Candy Ruined my Life - Final Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/64ygus/five_pieces_of_candy_ruined_my_life_part_1/)

I woke up in the middle of the night to the sound of my phone buzzing. With a groan, I reached over and grabbed my phone and blinked a couple of times to adjust my eyes to the bright led screen. It was a text from a number I didnt know. Still shaken up from the visit earlier by my family members, I slowly tapped on the screen and opened up the text.

*Not sure what Im doing, but here goes. Im the girl at the front counter. Kathy.  I just cant get your face out of my head and its driving me crazy. God. This is so weird but. and I swear. This isnt like what I usually do, but can I come up to your room?*

Pleasantly surprised by the text I replied back and told her yes and went to the restroom to make sure I didnt have any noticeable bed head. As soon as I looked at the mirror I had to do a double-take. I was far better looking than I originally was. My face was completely symmetrical and my body was in perfect shape. There wasnt an ounce of fat visible on my body. The last thing I noticed my clothes were now too small on me. 

In the middle of trying to find another outfit, I heard a soft knock outside of my door. I looked out the peephole and saw a very nervous looking girl standing outside. After a couple of deep breaths, I slowly opened the door and gave her a little smile. 

Slightly stuttering she muttered out, Y-youre the guy that just checked in, but you look a lit-little different. I laughed and told her that I was just a bit tired when I first checked in. She gave me a nervous smile and. Well. You know what we did. I really dont want to give you THAT much information.

She started to fall asleep on my arm after we finished, but I slowly shook her awake and told her that she should leave. After a couple of protesting grunts, she got up and started to get dressed. I told her she was more than welcome to contact me at any time, but she just gave me a chuckle in response. After she put on her shirt she turned to me and the moment I saw her face I knew I was fucked. 

She was still chuckling but her face was scrunched up from what seemed like various emotions running through her. I got up from bed to ask her what was wrong, but she pushed me back on the bed and pointed at me. She was trying to say something but she let out a loud sob while giving me a smile. I looked away for a second and looked back at her right as she started to laugh while her face was fixed into a frown filled with sorrow. Tears were dripping down her face as she continued to fall into a more and more intense laughing fit. I tried to help her, but every time I got close she would just push me back down. 

I know it was just a smaller woman acting completely bat shit crazy, but I was completely scared out of my mind. I closed my eyes and covered my ears. After a couple of minutes, I heard the sound stop. With caution, I slowly turned my body around and saw that she had stopped moving. Without a second thought, I called 911 and reported a death in my room. They told me to wait there, but I couldnt handle it anymore. 

I ran out of the hotel and caught the first cab. He asked me where I wanted to go and I quickly said, Raleigh.  He looked back at me and asked, You know how much thats gonna be right? Thats about an hour and a half drive. I gave him a nod and leaned back into the chair. He shrugged his shoulders and started to drive. 

The driver was quiet for the first five minutes so I started to daydream about being back at home with my family. My thoughts were disrupted by the sound of the driver coughing. I looked up and his eyes met mine before he asked me, Now dont get me wrong, but damn man. You are about the best looking guy I have ever seen in my life. Do you model? When I didnt reply back to him he just kept talking to me about how handsome I was. 

Around 30 minutes later he chuckled and said, Hell. If I was into dudes I would be all over you. I let out a nervous laugh and said, Thanks, man. It was silent for a little longer before the driver stopped the car and parked it in the middle of the highway. I started to ask him what was wrong, but he just turned around and asked me, How about this. You give me some pleasure with that pretty mouth of yours and Ill just give you the ride for free. He gave me a mischievous smile while putting out his hand urging me to shake it. 

Shocked, I looked at him for a couple of seconds before replying back, Im okay man. I just need to get to Raleigh. Ive had a rough day. He gave me a nod and turned around and continued to drive. He was completely silent for the rest of the ride. 

As we got into the first rest area past the Welcome to Raleigh sign I handed the driver two hundred dollars and told him to keep the change. He grunted thanks and I got out of the car. While I walked up to the building I heard him calling after me. I turned around and saw the taxi driver holding a gun to his head. He yelled out before pulling the trigger, If I cant have you. I dont want to live. Its not worth it. As the sound of the gun went off, I ran into the rest area and sat on the ground next to an outlet for the next 2 hours. Trying to think of someone to contact, but I already knew I did not have anyone else I could trust. 

After I charged up my phone I walked out to the street where the bus stop was and silently waited with the others. 

That is when an unbearable heat started to come from my pocket. I reached in and took out the candy and threw it on the ground, but they wouldnt leave my hand. I tried everything from shaking to scraping it on the ground but nothing worked. 

I should have been in pain, but all I could feel was raw anger. Anger that was building up since everything started to go to shit and the good looks that I never asked for. I wanted to be ugly again. I just wanted my life back. 

The bus came and I sat in the middle of the bus. I didnt know where I was going but I knew I had to be on this bus. I dont know why, but there was something I just had to do. 

I finally figured it out after the fifth stop. A happy little shit got on the bus. He looked around and saw that the only available seat was next to mine. He walked up to me and asked me if he could sit, but I spat back, Cant you just stand? He shrugged and jumped over me and took a seat by the window. I dont know why, but all of my anger was directed at him for the rest of the ride. I kept digging my elbows into his ribs as well as accidentally stepping on his foot. Right as he started to ask me to stop hitting him I experienced the worst smell of my life. It was coming from his mouth. I gagged and said, Cant you take care of your breath before talking to someone? 

He became quiet and stared out the window. The candy started to get cold and I took them out of my pocket. I ate one, but there was still five in my pocket. There wasnt any time to second guess myself. When the bus got to the last stop I threw the candy on the guys lap and rushed off of the bus. 

Im in a hotel now. The candy has not returned. Im still good looking, but people are not freaking out or killing themselves over me. Its a fresh start for me now. Hopefully, the next guy will figure out what he [has to do.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i think the mods removed it :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait.... We arent allowed to maul??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hurray! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh forgot to sign it.

Love,

Your friendly neighborhood nosleep writer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeahhhh. don't open that shit. next thing you know you're staring into the soulless eyes of dolls staring back at you. You start to slowly close the door when one of the dolls catches your eye.

It looked almost exactly like the little sister that went missing just 2 weeks ago. The sister that never seemed to get along with your girlfriend. 

You walk into the closet and take a closer look at the doll, your heart stops for a second. The skin. You've felt it before. It was the same skin that held your hand when you walked around the mall when you were little. The same skin that embraced you when you were dumped by your first love.

You slowly close back the door and put the padlock back on. You turn around, and there is your girlfriend. smiling at you, but not the smile you're used to. lips slightly curved upwards in the shape of the bloody knife she holds in her hand.

tldr: rip op </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man. Just. That man blows my mind so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yoooo. So down. Pm me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing is Truly Innocent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Pieces of Candy Ruined my Life [Part 1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever had something simple ruin your entire life? 
 
Im talking about something so minuscule that you would never have guessed that anything terrible could ever occur from said item. 
 
For me, 5 small pieces of hard candy did just that. 
 
This morning, I was running late, but managed to get ready and caught the bus before it drove away. Panting and sweating, I walked to the middle of the bus and sat down next to an older woman. I plugged in my headphones, leaned back, and started to enjoy the beginning of my 40-minute ride until I felt a sharp finger jab me on my side. I yelped and looked over at the old woman. She was looking at me with the most disgusted look possible. She started to say something so I took my headphones off and said, Excuse me?
 
With an agitated sigh, she cleared her throat and said, If youre going to sing along with your music please make sure you brush your teeth in the morning. I can smell your breath all the way over here. The people behind me started snickering and I muttered a half-hearted apology before plugging my headphones back in. 
 
Twenty minutes go by and the woman gets off and squeezes by me. Before she starts walking towards the door she reached into her pocket and threw 5 pieces of candy at me. Annoyed, I tossed them under my seat and just looked out the window until the bus arrived at my spot. 
 
Oh. Before I forget, let me introduce myself. My name is Simon and I am a waiter at a seafood restaurant. I am 28 years old and I live at my parents house. They dont really mind. I pay my share of rent as well as buy my own groceries. I come back home at reasonable hours, and I was never one to start any type of trouble. I do have the money saved up to move out and get my apartment, but there really is no reason. I have enough space in my room, I have never had a serious relationship, and Im pretty sure I never will. Not trying to be negative or anything. Just truthful. Im fucking ugly. Not your average ugly. I am the guy that actually creeps you out just by looking at you.
 
Horribly misshapen teeth, eyes that look like they are about to pop out any moment, acne all across my face as well as neck area, and hair that is already half balding is just the beginning of my physical flaws. Not trying to sound clich, but I do have a great personality. That is why I am so good at being a waiter. 
 
I love my job. It wasnt my dream job, but it is gradually becoming something that I am very passionate about. My tips are always great and I get to meet a lot of people from around our city. Most are nice, but of course, there are some people who are rude throughout their entire meal and refuse to tip. Its just all part of the job. The good always makes up for the bad luckily.
 
So, back to what started happening 2 days ago. I got off the bus and started to walk towards the restaurant, Crackin Crabs, and felt something rub against my jeans. I dug into my pocket and pulled out the five pieces of candy the lady handed me. Curious, I put the rest of the candy back in my pocket except one and held it up to my face. It was orange and had a clear plastic covering over it. Shrugging, I opened up the wrapper and popped the candy into my mouth. 
 
It may sound really dumb for me to say this, but holy shit, that candy was the best tasting candy I ever ate. It was orange flavored, but there was so much more depth to the taste. The strong aroma of a peeled orange enveloped my mouth. This is kind of awkward and embarrassing to say, but I puckered up my mouth and sucked as hard as I could. Before I knew it, the rest of the candy dissolved from my mouth and flowed down my throat. 
 
Disappointed about the candys early dismissal, I walked into the restaurant, clocked in, and started to work. It started off normally, but gradually I started to notice the other workers staring at me. Not of disgust but of genuine curiosity. I didnt really know why they were staring at me until a customer I was serving asked me, Man. I mean this in the straightest way possible. You are about the best looking guy I have ever seen! I gave him a laugh and rushed to the restroom. 
 
The reflection looking back at me was me, but not really me. It was a perfect version of me. Teeth were completely straight, hair was styled perfectly, my face was crystal clear of any imperfections, and the rest of my body looked to be much more fit. Curious, I lifted up my shirt and saw that my slight pudge was now an immaculate six pack. Everything on my body was completely defined. I looked down my pants and gave a little chuckle when I saw the unexpected growth.
 
Should I have been curious about what happened? Absolutely, but put yourself in my shoes. This was the first lucky thing that really happened to me. I was finally confident to talk to people, and I was finally somewhat happy.
 
With confidence, I walked through the door and worked the rest of my shift. As I was grabbing my jacket from the break room a cook that recently laughed in my face after I asked her out on a date, Janet, nervously walked up to me and asked me if I needed a ride. I gave her a smile and told her I was fine. 
 
After giving her a nod, I started to walk towards the bus stop when I heard someone scream out, No! I quickly turned around and saw Janet running full speed at me. Panicking, I took off running and didnt stop until I got in the middle of the others waiting on the bus.
 
She didnt stop running until she tried grabbing me, but the other people started to push her off of me. The whole time she kept yelling, **You cant look like that. Youre not supposed to look like that.** She grabbed a knife from her back pocket and tried to throw it at me but luckily they had her down on the ground. They all tried to fight for the knife, but in the end, she managed to grab the knife with both of her hands before plunging it into her chest repeatedly.
 
The cops came about 15 minutes later. They kept asking me how I knew her and why she would do that, but I kept telling them the same thing. I dont know. After going back and forth for about 40 minutes they told me to not leave the area and they would contact me if they had any other questions. I gave them a slow nod and they left. The bus ride was the longest ride of my life. I finally acknowledged that my good looks did not come out of luck. It was something else. The candy, but why did the old woman give me the candy? 
 
The bus came to a stop and I looked up and saw that it was my stop. I got off and walked up to my house. When I walked in I noticed that my parents were asleep on the living room couch. They did that every night. 
 
I started walking up the stairs when I heard my dad wake up and ask, Now what the fuck do you think youre doing here? 
 
Confused, I looked at him and asked, What do you mean dad? Im just going to my room. I have to wake up early tomorrow for work.
 
With a grunt, he got off of his couch and walked up to me. I stood still but flinched when he raised his hand at me. Instead of hitting me, he just grabbed me by the shoulder and threw me out the front door. As he closed it I heard him yell out, Dont you think you can ever come back in here you evil piece of shit. You hear me? I hate you. You are worthless and you will never be anything. Go kill yourself, because sooner than later. We will come kill you.
 
I was confused as well as hurt. My father always treated me well. He was the last person I ever thought would say he hated me. Im in a hotel now, I got a free room. The woman in the front counter blushed while telling me that she will cover the cost for me. Flattered I gave her my number and went to my room. After just 2 hours in my room, I am scared shitless. 
 
In the middle of writing this out to you guys, I started to hear several familiar voices call out my name. I got up from my bed and looked out my window. Everyone I loved, my uncle, aunt, father, mother, and my 2 best friends, Matt and Stephen, were staring up into my window. I stuck my head out the window and asked them what they wanted, but they kept staring up at me. My mother had a knife in her hand and rubbed it against my fathers back. My uncle rose up his gun and I ducked out of the way. I sat there shuddering. They were all looking at me with a look of absolute hatred. 
 
I grabbed the rest of the candy and tried to get rid of it, but it keeps coming back to me. I threw it out my window, flushed it down the toilet, threw it out of my door and down the hall, and even tried melting them with my lighter. Nothing works. The candy and the wrapping around it will not melt or truly disappear. 
 
I dont want to eat the rest of the candy. I already have the people I love outside trying to kill me. I didnt want to do it, but I ended up calling the cops. After I told them the address to the building and said I was just filing a noise complaint I hung up the phone. By the time they arrived at the hotel and walked to the spot I described everyone was gone.  So please guys. Im scared. Im stuck with these fucking demonic candies, and I just really wish I never [ate the first one.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)
 

[Part Two] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/655txx/five_pieces_of_candy_ruined_my_life_final_update/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *she </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/demons_dance_alone with the Aunt Carol Series.

u/iia with Amy's Wish and Roo

u/grindhorse with Serious Moonlight 

u/deadnspread with Count to 10 and it will go Away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> god. there is nothing more scary then being stalked by things you can't see:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is really strong and at times really really obnoxious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's always nice to have some sort of item to identify as a good luck charm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't help it. 

Keep scratching my face.

Must make sure it's still there D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The online quiz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandmother is dead, and it is all because I was dumb enough to do one of those dumb You Are a 90s Kid If You Can Correctly Answer at Least 8 Questions! on Facebook.

 I have never been one to do any of those, but I was bored and the only gateway out of my grandmothers boring house was my grandmothers computer.  

Before I continue, let me introduce myself. My name is Joshua Griffin and I just turned eighteen two days ago. My parents almost never had time for me. They were hardly at home when they were in the US, but for 9 months out of the year, they had to go to Italy and manage the company they set up there. I asked them several times why we couldnt just move to Italy, but they wanted to make sure I went to Dartmouth just like my mother and father did. 

Theyre busy people and I get it. Sometimes it would make me sad, but it also gave me a lot more freedom to enjoy my childhood a lot more than most people. They made a decent amount of money; we had our own cooks, our own cleaners, and a person that made sure I was home before 11 pm. I never got in trouble with the law and have always tried to be the best son possible whenever my parents were home. 

After I graduated high school I told my parents I wanted a year off from studying and they were more than understanding. They still sent me money every month to get whatever I needed. 

Two days ago, Harold, our cook, woke me up and told me I only had about 3 hours before I had to be on my flight. I sighed and got out of bed. I got dressed, ate the breakfast he prepared for me and walked out to the car that was waiting to take me to the airport. 

Fast forward 7 hours. I am getting out of the cab and walked up to the front door of my grandmothers house. I knocked on the door and heard her slowly walking up to the door. When she opened the door she gave me a huge smile and gave me a kiss on my cheek. I sheepishly grin at her and ask her how shes been. For the next 40 minutes, I sat next to her on the couch and listened to her rant about how the damn computer refused to work. I laughed and asked her if I could take a look at it.

With a wave of her hand, she said, Go ahead. Just dont break the damn thing even more. I chuckled and walked up to the desk on the far right corner of her living room. Sat at the chair and booted the computer up. 

I turned around and asked her what was wrong with it and she snorted before saying, As soon as I turn the thing on. I get all of these advertisements. They keep telling me what new cream I should buy and pills to grow out something I dont even have. I let out a laugh and asked her if she had anything important on the computer. After she told me that there was nothing on there she needed to keep I unplugged the Ethernet cable and let it fully boot up. 

It was windows 10 so I easily restored the computer to factory settings and plugged the ethernet cable back in before it rebooted. My grandmother walked up behind me when the setup screen came up and gave me a pat on the back while saying, Thank you. Now I can finally check my e-mails without seeing a penis on the screen. 

Right as I finished setting the computer up she told me to come into the kitchen. When I walked in I let out a deep breath. She remembered it was my birthday. A cake was in the middle of the table, and surrounding it was my favorite dishes. I could tell worked hard making the pot roast, baked potato, creamed corn, and deviled eggs.

After filling my stomach with the best meal Ive had in years, I helped my grandma clean up the kitchen and she went to bed around 7:30 pm.

I sat on the couch and watched a couple of Netflix shows, but before I knew it my phone died and I was met with complete darkness. I thought about walking around, but I was feeling a bit lazy so I walked up to her computer and browsed around my Facebook page. It was all the usual stuff. Clickbait lists, friends complaining about politics or whatever, and little videos that tried to make you feel guilty enough to like and share their page. I started to get bored so I went started to close out of the page when something caught my eye.

 You Are a 90s Kid If You Can Correctly Answer at Least 8 Questions! More out of curiosity than anything I clicked on the link and was taken to a bright and colorful page. I scrolled up and down the page and noticed that all of the questions were on one page. There werent any annoying ads so I started answering the first couple of questions.

It started innocently with somewhat fun questions.

Pics of tv shows where you have to guess what show it was from, little toys that were popular, and snacks that only 90s kids ate on a near daily basis. 

After I answered the 10th question I clicked the submit button on the bottom and saw I got 3 out of 10 questions right. 

Slightly entertained, I looked around the page. 

There were several other quizzes on there, but none of them really seemed that fun until I saw something that drew the blood out of my face. 

How Well Do You Know Joshua Griffins Life? The words were on a little icon with a photo of my senior photo. 

Nervously, I clicked the link and it took me to a page with just three questions. 

**What did Josh shoot and kill when he was 15?**

**What did Josh Griffin do to the 21-year-old cook?**

**Does Josh get off on the thought of both memories from the two previous questions?**

Terrified, I tried closing out of the window but a window popped up. It said, Close out the window before answering the questions will result in punishment. Rethink the decision you are about to make.

I didnt want anyone to die so I tried answering the questions.

For the first question, I typed in.

*My older brother. He was trying to kill my parents to inherit their money.*

For the second question, I typed in.

*I threatened her job and everything about her whenever I had the chance, I wanted her to feel as replaceable as possible. She got depressed after a couple of months but I didnt care. People were just an item to me. She ended up hanging herself.*

For the last question, I stared at it for a while before simply typing in, No,

Both of the windows closed down after I submitted in the list. I shut the computer off and walked to the room next to my grandmothers. Throughout the night I could hear her snoring. She was always a loud sleeper. I fell asleep shortly after checking the time and seeing that it was 3 in the morning. The next time I woke up I didnt hear the sound of my grandmothers snore. 

Worried, I got out of bed and checked the time. 

10:15 am.

I quickly got out of bed and went to check up on her but only saw the carcass of what held my grandmothers soul. Her hand was limply off the side of the bed and her head was bent at an impossible angle on top of her chest. 

Gulping down the buildup of saliva and fear, I shuffled towards her and saw that she was dead.

Her eyes that shone like a lighthouse in the middle of the dark seas now illuminated a reflection of a dying candle in the middle of the forest. On the middle of her forehead, there was a series of cuts strategically placed to create a sentence, **One Chance for Truth.**

I will admit it. I get off at the thought of my brothers dead body lying in a puddle of blood. I get off at the thought of how the cooks body flew back and forth with the wind. 

Im a fucked up guy, but my grandmother wasnt. She was an angel caught in the crossfire of the wicked. I want to tell everyone about what I did. The sins I have committed daily, but I will start with you guys. A place that doesnt know who I really am. A place that will never know how messed up I really am. My name is Joshua Griffin and I am the guy that doesn't regret the lives I took, but the [life of my grandmother I lost.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)






 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yo. before this gets removed. I went to rossview too XD class of 2011 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brother Love Only Goes So Far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Whole Town Hates My Brother </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Matthew and I want to trust my brother, Daniel. He has always been there for me, but he is making it impossible for me now.

As I lie on my bed and slowly type out what has been going on for my whole life I hear my brother slowly whispering to himself, Just take me back to The Lodge. Take me back home. 

We had a pretty normal life growing up in our small town. If you are wondering where we are located, the most I can say as of right now is that we are in Clarksville, Tennessee. Right off of Exit 11. When you get off on the exit you take a left and you will see a heavily wooded section. Drive about half a mile and park your car on the road and walk into the woods. About 2 to 3 miles you will see a sign for Elkview. 

We have a population of around 200 and, of course, everyone knows everyone. We have our own schools, our own doctor, cops, and 5 shops that supplied us with everything that we needed. 

I had an average life of a kid that grew up in Elkview. I went to school all 8 years, fulfilled my 32 hours of work a week while I went to school, and had my 30 minutes of free time with the other kids. I worked at the local grocery store. My job the entire time I worked there was to restock the items that were taken from the bins that surrounded our store. People would come in. Scan the buckets on the ground and take the food they needed before handing the guy at the front one of their vouchers and walking out. We were each given two vouchers a month for each store in our town. Each trip we could take up to 20 items. The doctor was available for whenever we needed him along with our local cop. 

We could go to the doctor or cop as many times as we needed, but any type of false alarm we were punished. We would also get punished if we tried sneaking out more than 20 items on a voucher visit, or breaking any of the 10 commandments stated by the Bible. 

The punishment was always the same. The sinner would stand in the middle of the center point of our town and five randomly selected people would get the honor to throw a rock as hard as they could at the person. This was to beat the devil out of the person. I have been there for 36 stonings. Only 12 people walked away alive. One of them being Daniel. 

He was never the same after the stoning. 

He would still do everything he was supposed to, but whenever we were alone in our room he would sit on his bed and stare at the wall. Softly whispering to himself. 

Sometimes at night, I would see him walking out of the room. Quietly muttering to himself, They will pay. They will learn what is real. They will figure out the truth. Every time I saw him walk outside of our room a dead body would be found in the entrance of our town by one of our guards the next morning. They werent from our town, but it was hard to tell at first glance. The bodies were mutilated and chopped up. It was to the point to where a couple of our elders had to piece them together to make sure they werent anyone that we knew. When pieced together, they were almost always older people with thin layers of worn down clothing. They smelled far worse than death, and none of them ever had anything to identify them. 

I wasnt dumb. I knew it was Daniel getting revenge for the stoning, but I didnt turn him in. I loved him far too much. He was my brother, but it didnt take long for the others to start pointing their judgmental fingers at Daniel. 

He was sent off to The Lodge (a mental hospital about 20 minutes away from us) instead of another stoning because our forgiving pastor allowed him to choose the alternative. 

Daniel was gone for 6 months and our town started to go back to normal. Until he came back. Within 5 days of his arrival bodies started appearing at our entrance. That is when they called the sheriff to our town and they took Daniel away for 3 days. He came back with a smile on his face. A smile that showed the satisfaction of fooling a whole entire time. 

I wanted to stop trusting him, but no matter what, a part of me still clung on to the fact that even the police couldnt find any substantial evidence that he was to blame for the murders of the 21 mutilated bodies. 

Yesterday, was the day I saw, for the first time, parts of a human body lying on the steps that led to the front door of our house, My father was standing by me when I opened the door and as soon as he looked around for a second he yelled out, Stephanie, come out here! My mother came out and let out a short gasp before getting on her phone and called the priest. When he came out here he asked to speak to my brother. Daniel came out of our room and slowly walked down the stairs.

The priest pointed towards the woods that surrounded us. Daniel gave a short nod and they walked into the woods. They were gone for 4 hours. I impatiently waited at the front steps. When I saw Daniels head poking out of the woods I got up to my feet and ran up to him. As I got close to him, I noticed how his expression stayed in the same blank expression. I grabbed his arm as soon as I got to them and led him into our house.

Daniel has been whispering the same thing over and over again.

Just take me back to The Lodge. Take me back home. 

A soft chant entered into our room. A perfectly synchronized group of voices saying, Let your will be done oh Lord. Your will is our mission, oh Lord. Curious, I sat up on my bed and leaned closer to the window. The distant sound of screams hit my eardrums and I made the split decision to go investigate.

I walked out of our room while he was turned away from me. As I quietly opened the door and slid out, I heard Daniel cry out, Matthew. Be careful. The truth will ruin you. You will become like me. Blamed for murders happening in our town. You will be known as a sinner. You will never be accepted ever again. I looked at him one last time before closing the door and sneaking out of our house. 

I followed the noise of the chants and found myself standing behind the local bakery shop. I looked at the center of our town. There was the seal that was there since the beginning of the town, a man holding up a plate full of fruit on each of his hands, along with every adult that lived in our town. In the middle of them were our 4 elders. They spoke out in perfect unison as each of them stared into different parts of the crowd, 

I started listening as soon as the elders started to speak again. 

**This is the last time we say this. Daniel must go. He knows too much. We have sent out people to bring the homeless to our town. We have chopped them up and left them in the entrance to our town, but our youth refuse to believe that Daniel is evil. If they do not believe our town will die. We must get them to believe. They must believe that Daniel is evil and that they must never try to leave the sanctuary we have created for them.**

They were silent and everyone started to walk away from the crowd. 

Without any type of hesitation, I ran back home as fast as I could. 

I managed to get back home before the front door opened back up and I heard whispers coming from my mother and father. They were talking about ways to get rid of Daniel, but they ended up arguing. 

Five minutes later, I heard the sound of my father snoring from their bedroom. 

I am writing to you guys. I tried looking up ways to get support in this type of situation. NoSleep was one of the first things to come up and it has the biggest type of following. Im lost on here. I have only used the internet for my studies, but this may be my only chance at any type of help. Please. If you have any type of suggestions. 

Please [let me know.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not heard of the book. Reccommended reading? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heaven. It is Real, but What is it really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 300 Years Of Heaven Was a Punishment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Nathan, and I came back after living in Heaven for exactly 300 years. I am sure a lot of people would be curious as to how that felt so let me start from how I got there. 

I tried to be a good person, but my horrible temper always got in the way. It was to the point to where I no longer had friends. My family stopped talking to me, including my own mother, father, and two sisters. I was only 21 years old, but I was truly alone. I tried to blame everyone around me, but I knew, deep down, that it was my own fault. 

Enough of my sob story. 

Let me tell you how I died.

I got off of my shift at the local grocery store and was walking back home. On the way home, a man walked up to me and asked, Hey man, could you spare some cash? I lost my job a couple of days ago and I need to get some type of food for my kids. He pointed at a hungry boy and girl sitting behind him, but I scoffed and said, Not that hard to get a job. Why did you even procreate when youre fucking trash? 

I gave him a quick chuckle and walked past him when I felt pain erupt from my lower back. The next couple of seconds were filled with a knife plunging into my chest. I dont know when I blacked out, but the next thing I remember was opening my eyes and seeing a woman sitting close to my head and saying, Stay calm. Were almost there. Stay with-. I blacked out again and before I knew it I was met by a sense of absolute peace. 

Before I opened my eyes, I knew I was floating. When I opened my eyes I saw myself floating through a fog of memories. 

Through the fog, I could see myself yelling and cussing out my parents a year ago before storming out of their house. That was the last time I saw them. The next thing I saw was the time I was pulled over by the cops with my best friend since we were 6, Brad. He was there for me whenever I needed someone the most, but I took advantage of that. When a cop pulled us over I took out the 7 grams of coke out of my pocket and threw it on the car seat behind me. 

Brad looked at me with pleading eyes while the cops cuffed him, but I acted oblivious to everything.

I closed my eyes again and did not open them until I felt solid ground under my feet. With a deep sigh, I opened my eyes and saw around 20 to 30 people standing in front of me. I looked down and saw that we were standing on a clear glass of some sort. When I looked back up I saw that I was next in line. I rushed up to a man that stood in front of the largest gate I have ever seen in my life. The gate was simple, but it looked to be made of solid gold. After ogling at the gate for a couple of seconds I looked down at the man in front of me. He was maybe a little over 4 feet tall, poorly maintained facial hair that covered half of his face, and eyes filled with sadness and disappointment. 

I opened my mouth to ask him who he was, but before I could get a sound out he spoke in a raspy voice, Nathan Cliff, enter through the gates. Although I was confused, I rushed through the gates and looked around. A road paved with gold, bodies made of solid light walking around everywhere, and other people walking around with dreamy expressions on their faces. 

Besides the people that walked around me, everything around me was a mixture of absolutely pure light. Something far brighter and crisper than anything I have ever seen. The only thing that stuck out like a sore thumb was a man dressed in all red with a piece of paper. Written on the piece of the paper was the date. Somehow, whenever the man flipped the paper over it gave the date of the next day, and an endless swarm of people surrounded the man. 

The first 50 years passed by quickly. I met a lot of other people, we talked about our lives, but I quickly became bored. You can only talk to so many people before their lives start sounding the same. We never grew hungry, tired, or thirsty, but it never ended my cravings. I wanted to get a good nights rest. I wanted to eat just one carrot and savor all of the taste. I wanted to quench a thirst with a cool glass of water, but all we had was each other and those damn angels that never said a word to anyone. 

For the next 110 years, I reflected back on my life. It may seem like a long time to think about 21 years of life, but you can learn a lot more about your life just by revisiting the same memory thousands of times. You learn to see things in more than just your perspective, in ways much more than the words said. 

It took me 160 years to finally snap. I dont know what came over me, but I wanted to leave this place. I wanted to go to hell. Anything would be better than here. 

This is when everything around me started to fall apart. 

It started with me walking up to the bodies of light we called the angels. I tried talking to them, but they never responded back to a word I said. When I truly became desperate, I tried to attack them in any way possible, but anything I struck them with would just go through them. With every attempt, they just looked at them and said the same thing. Keep searching. Keep walking. For you will find the answer.

Eighty years have gone by since then, and all I have done was failed attempts of attacking other angels as well as asking everyone else if they knew what the answer was. Everything was a failure. I started to give up hope, but I started on the longest journey of my life. I turned around and started running as fast as I could. 

I would still see the man flip the sign over and tell us what the next day was. It was annoying at times, but it was really the only thing that kept me from going insane. 

55 years go by. 

It is now my 295th year in Heaven, and I started to see the gate I walked through three lifetimes ago. 

Three years of constant running and I dont feel like Im any closer, but the scenery around me changes. I am now surrounded by body parts and blood lying all around where I run. I came across a couple of heads, and whenever I see each one I stop running and asking them what happened. Each of them said the same exact thing, Dont look for the truth. The truth wont help you. Endure the punishment. It only gets worse from here. I started to get scared. Not just scared for my life. This was far more. I was scared for my soul. The part that will never die. The part that will suffer for all eternity. No matter how bad we were cut up, sliced open, or just cut into dozens of pieces like the people around me now, I would not be able to leave. This was a punishment that will never end.

After three years of running and hearing the same thing over and over again, I started to second guess myself, but I needed to know. It was beyond curiosity. I was trying to get out of the eternal suffering I ended up in. 

Two years later and the start of my 300th year I approached the gates. I walked up to the man that stood in the front of the gate and fell to my knees, a defeated man. He looked at me with the same eyes that were filled with disappointment and sadness before saying, Nathan Cliff. Poor Nathan Cliff. 

I begged him to let me out. To let me leave, but he simply said back, Learn the truth and you may leave. 

In between heavy breaths of panic, I replied back, They told me you would tell me the truth. Or that I would find the truth on my way here.

He simply said back, You know the truth.

I said the first thing in my mind Is this Hell?

He chuckled and said, No. You are in Heaven, but what makes you think Heaven is for the good? You left the paradise created by God. The paradise ruined by us. We can blame the devil all we want, but we are the ones that continue to do wrong. Do you think Lucifer continues to spread his lies to the people when the lies are spread for him?

I wanted to argue with him, but deep down I knew that was the truth. Humans are truly what ruined the world God made us. Lucifer may have tempted us, but we are the ones that truly ruined it. 

I woke back up and saw the woman that was talking to me before I lived through the scariest experience of my life. 

She calmly said, Dont worry. Youre back now. Dont go on us. Were almost there.

I knew she was mostly saying it for herself, but I gave her my best attempt of a nod. She put the defibrillator back down and we were silent for the rest of the ride. 

Im in the hospital now. 

I learned that I was dead for 45 seconds. 45 seconds that created exactly 300 years for me. 

Im on my phone now. The doctors are done treating me. Pain is still erupting all over my body, but man does it feel good. I have a tray of food in front of me. 

Carrot sticks that I never liked, but it is bursting with flavor for me. Water that is quenching my parched throat, and after I post this experience to you guys I am going to enjoy a [good nights rest.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First one to figure it out. I applaud you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to be nice and just say that you are entitled to your own opinion, but after reading your own comments I'm just going to leave this mass of words that do not contribute to the conversation. 

Much like your mini ranting session is to NoSleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude... Stop lol i understand. After the 3rd time you said it. No need to continue.... Especially when noone is listening except me....... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh for some reason I REALLY Like the Glen guy XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just go back to commenting on r/funny with LoL on every single comment. or just keep talking about how Trump is worse than cancer or aids.

ps. I really don't care if you stopped reading. LoL

LoL

LoL

LoL

LoL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no just stop reading. especially if you automatically bounced to the bottom of the screen to criticize lol...

i mean i was trapped. I couldn't leave. nothing worked. what would you do? sit on the floor an jack off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man i really gotta give SSS and LoS for being such active subreddits. I love both to death.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it moderated by anyone consistently on NoSleep? Maybe that would increase traffic somewhat. 

On mobile so haven't checked the moderator list yet lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/63t4jo/i_am_responsible_for_the_death_of_nine_students/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
