<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nosleep Stories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complete list of stories posted to the sub r/nosleep by u/subject374.

Ordered from least to most upvotes, *Score as of 04/27/17*

-----

**Single Part**

[She is My Eternal Inspiration](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yayg0/she_is_my_eternal_inspiration/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Perfection](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/53qec1/perfection/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[I Witnessed A Murder That I Didn't See](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5z4ovi/i_witnessed_a_murder_that_i_didnt_see/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[My Dog Won't Stop Barking](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6665tg/my_dog_wont_stop_barking/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[For The First Time In My Life I Wish I Had Said No](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zgx5d/for_the_first_time_in_my_life_i_wish_i_had_said_no/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[We Learn From Experience](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/618ite/we_learn_from_experience/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[I'll Never Take City Transit Again](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5vfqhf/ill_never_take_city_transit_again/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[I've Been Speaking With My Shower Head](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/64g5ks/ive_been_speaking_with_my_shower_head/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[It All Started With A Game of Would You Rather](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/63vpqt/it_all_started_with_a_game_of_would_you_rather/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Strange Things Happen in Louisiana](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/62qvct/strange_things_happen_in_louisiana/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[I Thought It Was An April Fools Joke](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/643jli/i_thought_it_was_an_april_fools_joke/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[My Daughter Loves Playing Games With Me](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yx900/my_daughter_loves_playing_games_with_me/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Best Kept Family Secret](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5xl8oz/best_kept_family_secret/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Perhaps I Took My Gambling Habit Too Far](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/624rej/perhaps_i_took_my_gambling_habit_too_far/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[My Children Never Lied](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/592px2/my_children_never_lied/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[I Was Almost in The Lucky 47 Club](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61oydb/i_was_almost_in_the_lucky_47_club/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Our Home Inspector Overlooked The Walls](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66psez/our_home_inspector_overlooked_the_walls/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Mr Cooke's Last Chemistry Class](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60epj1/mr_cookes_last_chemistry_class/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Don't Use Dove Lotion](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66f7sa/dont_use_dove_lotion/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[I Tried to Force My Husband Into Losing Weight](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zrocn/i_tried_to_force_my_husband_into_losing_weight/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[You Don't Do That To Family](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5xtytg/you_dont_do_that_to_family/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[How To Drive A Boy Crazy](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ux2ut/how_to_drive_a_boy_crazy/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Not Your Average Sibling Rivalry](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5x5cpc/not_your_average_sibling_rivalry/?ref=share ref_source=link)

-----

**"Series"**

Suicide Town [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yi7eo/suicide_town/?ref=share ref_source=link) and [Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yp9sf/suicide_town_part_2/?ref=share ref_source=link)

Population Control [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/545jly/population_control/?ref=share ref_source=link) and [Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5mk1q0/missing_post_population_control_part_2/?ref=share ref_source=link)

My Sister Didn't Exist Until I Found Her Journal [P1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zys6i/my_sister_didnt_exist_until_i_found_her_journal/?ref=share ref_source=link), [P2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60niox/my_sister_didnt_exist_until_i_found_her_journal/?ref=share ref_source=link), [P3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61ihg4/my_sister_didnt_exist_until_i_found_her_journal/?ref=share ref_source=link)

Good Shade: (Anthology - *can be read as single parts*)

* [Meet Tyler](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6104g9/the_good_shade_hotel/?ref=share ref_source=link)

* [Hotel Holiday](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61xh3y/our_hotel_celebrates_the_strangest_holidays/?ref=share ref_source=link)

* [Delivery](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/649wuc/a_delivery_to_the_good_shade_hotel/?ref=share ref_source=link)

* [Meet Isabelle](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/67ra3h/this_job_has_given_me_more_than_just_money/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Master of Masters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post is simple. It is a fork in the road, each side of which shall branch into various paths. Choose your course wisely, for if you become lost you might never return. 


Or, just click the link that applies to what you're looking for, and you'll be redirected to the corresponding Master Post directory for that topic. Never forget though, you had to experience this Master of all Master Posts to find what you sought out. 

-----

[Master Post for Discussion Threads](https://www.reddit.com/r/HylianHorror/comments/67x7ap/discussion_master_post/).




[Master Post for Stories](https://www.reddit.com/r/HylianHorror/comments/67y858/library_story_master_post/?ref=share ref_source=link).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discussion {Master Post} </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **We're sorry to inform you that there have been no discussion threads opened yet. This page is merely a placeholder for things to come. Have a creepy day.**

-----

Hello, and welcome to the Master Post for Discussion Threads. Below you'll find links to each discussion thread that has been opened on the sub. Categories include Active Discussion, Closed Discussion, and a link to Archived Discussion for a series of topics that are greater than two months old. 


Additionally, the bottom of the page contains links to the lists of specific discussion topics.


**Active Discussion:**


Links N/A


**Closed Discussion:**


Links N/A 


**[Archived Discussion.](link).** 


**[Complaints/Concerns](link).**


**[Questions](link),** *see also, [FAQ](link).*


**[Open criticism, Suggestions](link).** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Latin seems the most likely answer, but first I'll need to find out what those Latin words are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> N.F * 

I feel like that's too obvious, no? 

Looking back through the posts from others, I've started paying more attention. Tyler got a scientific name, Alphaea got a Latin nickname, so I'm figuring rather than outright name me as a creature, it's something Latin and descriptive of whatever I am.

I've never hurt anyone else before, I'm not sure what could have happened in the hotel that would cause me to not remember acting out of sorts, if that's what happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A list would be helpful, but I'm not sure how the guests would feel if a list existed merely to make them easy to indentify. Perhaps such a thing exists though, I'll have to look deeper. 

Also, as far as I learned in my final interview, no one *really* applies to work here. If you find an advertisement or message that leads you to this place, it's not by chance. 

Someone, somewhere, pointed you out to the hotel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually heard a lot about the Irish and more modern lore on Fae/Fey/Faeries and it's quite interesting, I'll see if anyone at the hotel knows anything about this.

Obviously I'm not completely clueless, I have Tyler's post to guide me, shifts to work, and a hotel full of inhuman guests... Any of which could be related to me.

I wonder if it actually was my blood that caused the awareness of me being unnatural, or something else. 

I have no idea what type of creatures Rose and Mister Smith may be, but they both seemed to know that I was different when we met

So many questions, fortunately I have at least 3 months to find answers and piece it all together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That actually makes a bit of sense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be such a great way to express things which you have trouble expressing elsewhere, it helps vacate troublesome thoughts, and can take you out of a stressful world for a moment and into a fictional one where more answers usually await.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Start here, or go no further. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello creeps and creepettes, and a good afternoon, morning, evening, or night. Whatever time of day it may be, you seem to have found your way down a dark alley and into a strange and rarely seen place. Maybe it's rarely seen because you're one of the first few souls to even bring yourself into such an obscure corner. Eventually this corner may be frequented, and this message will have aged by then, but I'd like it to retain its relevance over time. 


Welcome reader, whether you be new or old. Whether you stumbled upon this sub by chance, or you followed a pale writer through the streets and cornered her here. Whether a fan of the work, or simply a curious onlooker questioning if this place is safe to enter. No matter who you may be, this is a fond greeting to you. Unless you happen to be an asshole for no apparent reason, then you can walk away now because I will not spare you the full extent of my wrath when I am annoyed. 


There are a few basic rules here, which can be found by [following this link](https://www.reddit.com/r/HylianHorror/about/rules/) or the link in the sidebar. Don't forget to brush up on your [rediquette](https://www.reddit.com/wiki/reddiquette) before you decide to take part in the community. We're just a peaceful group of people who enjoy cannibalism, nothing wrong with that.


Now for the rules, you'll find yourself at the mercy of myself and whatever other mods may be recruited in the future if you don't follow the guidelines for being a part of this little community. 


**Be Respectful.**


*It is never acceptable to degrade, disrespect, slander, or negatively criticize any user who posts or comments here. We do not allow spamming or trolling, and those who partake in these activities will face the maximum penalty that a mod can inflict.* 


*Constructive criticism about the stories linked in posts is welcome only on posts which state it is permitted. Not every post linking to a story is meant for readers to freely air their grievances with the content, and out of place comments such as these will be removed without a reply. If you wish for a reply, please comment on the appropriate post.* 


*There are times when other authors may be mentioned in posts, it is never appropriate to negatively criticize, disrespect, or act offensively in any way towards those users or the posts mentioning them.* 


**Remember that this is a place for discussion, not merely categorization.**


*Primarily the idea for this subreddit stemmed from wanting a place where stories by subject374 were organized in such a way that stories old and new would be easily found by readers old and new.* 


*The categorization system being used organizes every story written by our topic author into comprehensive lists based on what series they belong to (whether you know it or not), what genre they were written for, or what type of subject they include.* 


*These lists are not meant to be commented on, unless you believe a story is missing from the list.*


*Discussion posts are something that we hope gets the readers involved with this community, and with the much larger r/nosleep community.* 


*The same discussion will likely be featured multiple times, to make sure that new members of the community have their opinions heard. If your opinion, concern, or comment in general was not addressed in an old discussion post, feel free to restate it in a future discussion post.* 


*Do not abuse the opportunity to restate your opinion, comments that are repeated multiple times without positively adding to the discussion will be removed. It is never necessary to spam the sub with your opinion.* 


*Discussion posts are open for any visitor to comment on, but please remember to follow the guidelines given during each post for comments. Remember to keep all comments respectful and civil. Certain discussion posts will ask for criticism, complaints, or questions about stories. Feel free to speak your mind in a civil manner on these posts.*


Those are basically the primary rules of being here, so please keep them in mind and refer to the official rules list to see each rule described. Only two are currently listed in this post, but the descriptions here covered almost all of our currents rules.

There you have it, the gist of this sub. I apologize if you're viewing this sub in its fetal state, we hope to mature fast a become exactly what we were meant to be.

For now, this is where I let you go. You have received your introduction and your briefing on the organized chaos which roams here. Dare you enter further, or will you run screaming while you can and never look back?


----- 


**Much smaller welcome, to a dark little pit we like to refer to as the update log! This area contains the date and purpose of each update to this post, so you can see how much this post-- and the sub itself-- has grown since its first feeble day of existence.** 


*Updates:*
 
**Original post,12:50am, EST. Thursday, April 27th, 2017.**

**Links to rules,1:32pm, EST. Thursday, April 27th, 2017.**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My suggestions fall perfectly in line with the other commenter. Edit out redundant bits, format a few paragraphs a little better, fix some grammatical errors, and make your narrator easier to understand and connect with. We want to *feel* what she feels. 

I really like the concept of this story, it contained enough horror elements to be left where it is, which is exactly what each part of a series should be. 

At the same time, the questions brought up and the final line leave the reader curious for more, which is a great feeling to give people when you're creating a series. 

Remember, at the very least you should outline where you want to take the story with future posts, and make sure that each part of the story has enough meaningful content and builds upon the story well enough to warrant an entire part. No one enjoys reading a series of lackluster short posts which drag a series out too long. Get your ideas and your entire plot played out in as few posts as you can. The easiest way to do so is to know exactly where your story will go before you post the first part. You don't *have* to have it all written, but you'll find that planning it out well enough to post the entire series within whatever time frame you give yourself, will take a lot of the stress that creating a series may bring.

Long posts in series that do well to build upon the story and the characters within are generally the best thing that I've noticed. We enjoy meat to our stories, we want the blood that flows through the veins of a story to spill brightly, and filler is never fun. Don't waste your writing ability on something meant to merely tide over the readers until a better post in the series comes along. 

Make every post count. Make sure you get out all the things you want to be a part of it. 

You've got a great start, keep at it. I'd love to check it out once it's posted. And good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll let you know as soon as I find out for myself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much for thinking so highly of my random stories!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the story is really well done, and you shouldn't worry about the upvotes. Don't let invisible internet points be your only motivation towards writing. 

Write what you know, write what you enjoy, and let the rest be damned. The most important part of writing in enjoying the process, regardless of the outcome.

Not every story is going to catch the attention of the masses, but not catching attention doesn't make a story a bad one. Keep working on stories, keep putting out content that *you* enjoy writing, and eventually your hard work will be noticed. 

Amazing stories that have been overlooked in the past will be read by future readers interested in seeing more of work. The votes don't account for the actual readership of your stories. 

Who knows how many people loved it but didn't vote, or don't have accounts to be able to vote? 

Keep it up, you can do this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, fellow cleaner c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, Confluence Event? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea what it could be, but hopefully someone at the hotel will have the answer I'm searching for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad I could help out, at the least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, good to know. I'm always behind on the trending memes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've honestly never heard of it, I haven't travelled very much since I've been in the states, and I don't recall learning about that in high school. Maybe it's taught to younger students and that's why the information bypassed me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I knew who or where she was, maybe then I wouldn't be receiving a long overdue revelation about myself from a nametag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, did you miss a bit? You are correct in assuming the Good Shade, but I'm not the same employee that has posted before. 

I got in contact with Tyler after my shift about the story he had posted about the Good Shade, and he gave me the log in credentials because other employees have also used this account to freely discuss the things they are supposed to be keeping secret. After the confusion of my first day, I felt the need to get it off of my chest before my next shift.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Job Has Given Me More Than Just Money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Where do you see yourself in five years?* 

Happy maybe, or dead. 


It's a question I've been asked a lot, and I have never been quite sure how to answer it. There are things I *want* to do, there is so much of life I haven't experienced. Yet I couldn't pinpoint what to do. Often enough I feel entirely at a loss for what to do with myself, I mean, what's the point?


Here I am at 19, working in perhaps the strangest and most secretive hotel ever to exist, because I really needed for there to be a point. I needed a way out of the life I'd found myself stuck in.


Four years ago was when an abusive man made me realize my only option. I had to run. I had a friend who I'd known since elementary school who was several years older than me, lived in the U.S, and was already engaged with a baby on the way. They were just scraping by themselves since they were both barely 20, but they knew the extent of what I was living with and offered me a hideaway. 


It was the end of my freshman year of highschool, and I told my father about plans to *visit* some friends over the summer. He seemed to be fine with having me gone, but the weeks leading up to my departure were some of the worst. I used all the money I had left from babysitting to buy a bus ticket-- which was a small sum, since that's what happens when your father borrows your money for beer-- and packed my bags days before I was set to leave. 


The morning of my trip my father woke me up at 6am. I had to be out of the house and in the car within five minutes if I wanted to leave, he was not in a good mood. We drove at 90(Km) on a street that I believe was 30. I think we hit 140 on the highway. By 6:30 we were at the truck stop where the bus would be picking me up. Usually a 45 minute drive at the least. When I got out of the car, he peeled out of the parking lot, causing bystanders to stare. 


It was nearly four hours til my bus would arrive, I had no spare money to buy food from the truck stop, nor any food with me, and I sat at a picnic bench outside and waited with my single suitcase for hours. Thankfully my phone was working, and I spent the time texting my friends to tell them I'd see them in a few weeks. Those texts changed into goodbyes later when I was across the border and safe. I got on the bus and travelled to the biggest city in the country, where I met with my friend, Emily. 


She was a dual citizen, and planned to drive me from this city to her house. We got in the car and drove, stopping at the border to identify ourselves. Being under 16 I didn't need a passport to cross, but a birth certificate. They also asked if I had permission from my parents, since my friend was obviously not old enough to be my guardian. I actually had managed to get my father to drunkenly sign a note I'd typed up to give myself permission to go for a few weeks; He assumed it was a school form and didn't read it. We got across and back to Emilys house in a few hours of relative peace. I was finally in a place where my father couldn't follow due to his criminal past.


Money was often tight, I couldn't work because I had no social security, and no one would pay me under the table within a reasonable distance. I had no car or license, and couldn't get one. Emily attended a local community college and her fiance worked, but it was just barely enough to cover the bills and cost of her classes. The process of becoming a citizen took awhile for her, she was lucky that she came here when she was older and had a better paying job before coming. Emily had a nice chunk in her savings by the time she crossed over, and it still took her over a year to become a citizen. 


I've been here for nearly five years now, I'll be twenty pretty soon. We've hardly got anything saved towards paying for my citizenship, and I constantly feel guilty that I can't help get things moving. Since I've been here they had their first baby, and now Emily is pregnant with their third. Since both of them are still trying to lead normal lives, I've been helping to take care of their kids and the house. 


Emily has managed to continue to go to school, though taking certain semesters off to care for her kids has definitely slowed down the already long process of nursing school. Her fiance, Jeremy, has been working a steady job all this time. It pays well, but with a growing family things can be pretty rough at times. 


I finished out high school here, because schools can't decline you based on citizenship apparently. I have a high school diploma, from an American school. That helped me not feel so useless for my first couple of years here, but since money is too tight for me to attend college as well I've been doing a lot of nothing for nearly two years. I just help around the house, spend time with Emily and Jeremy, and help with the kids. I've always wished I could do more. 


That's why yesterday when I got a text from a number in the same area code as me, that said there was a way that I could earn money without needing a social security number, I was more excited than wary. I assumed it was a friend who I had given my number to on Facebook while discussing my job search, and didn't bother asking who I was talking to. I figured I could do just about any job that would help towards becoming a citizen, finally attending college, and becoming someone real within the world. They ended up sending me an email to contact. I didn't hesitate to send in an email containing my nearly empty resume.


I received a reply within minutes, asking me to detail my current financial situation and my reasoning for wanting the job. 


I explained how I had been told that I could be hired here without a Social Security number, and how I couldn't find anywhere else that would do so. I also told him why I needed the money, and vaguely described my living situation.


He seemed very kind in his reply, letting me know that he could have someone pick me up to bring me in for a final interview, after I filled out their application form. I quickly filled out the form that was sent to me, slightly confused by some of the questions it contained. He gave another hasty reply, seeming pleased with my application he offered to have an employee come pick me up at three that afternoon to have our final interview by 5pm. 


He gave me some details of the job they wanted me for, and I was pleased that it seemed to be simple work. $40 an hour to do housekeeping for a hotel. $10 from my pay would be taken each week for the cost of having someone from the hotel driving me to and from work. All further details would be discussed during the interview.


Emily arrived home at two, and I excitedly told her about the job offering. One of the emails told me that I should not reveal the name of the hotel that was hiring me to anyone, because they didn't want it being known that they would pay under the table. I told Emily this, and she didn't pester to know the exact details of my employment. 


At 3:10pm a truck pulled up in front of the house, a good choice to fit into the middle-of-nowhere area we lived. I told Emily I'd see her later in the evening, and set outside to introduce myself to the stranger in the car. I've never been the outgoing type, but I've been told that I'm always a really friendly person. I don't have many friends, but I've met many people and all of those first impressions seem to have gone well.


The driver introduced himself as Tyler, an employee at the hotel, and he apologized for being late. He explained that he didn't drive a lot for the hotel, and he'd never picked up a passenger like me. He didn't ask me many questions, and didn't seem to be aware of the reason he was picking me up. 


Will you be driving me everyday? I asked him to break to silence of the drive.


Everyday? He questioned back. 


For work? I'm going in for an interview, I told him.


Ohhh, the word was dragged out, as though it was dispelling whatever other reason he had thought he was escorting me to the hotel, If we're on the same shift probably, your house is on the way from mine. 


I debated asking him what the he initially thought he was escorting me for, but instead I let the car fall into another moment of silence. I've never been the best at keeping a conversation going, but his voice soon filled the vehicle again.


If you get the job, I can tell you it's an experience like no other. I can't tell you much, since you're not an employee yet, but Mister Smith will go over all the details with you, I'm sure, he paused to smile at me for a moment, Any idea what position you'll be working?


Housekeeping, I replied distractedly, wondering about what sort of hotel this could be to provide experiences worth talking about, while being unable to talk about them.


Ugh, he made a face of exaggerated displeasure, Better you than me, I couldn't clean up after strangers. I'd find it tedious.


I shrugged, It's pretty much all I'm good at.


His face was in an expression of apology when he glanced at me, I didn't mean anything bad by that, it's valid work.


I smiled at him, not wanting him to worry over a comment that I honestly hadn't taken any offence with, I know, I was just saying. That's why it's a great job for me.


He seemed relieved that he hadn't come off as rude, and we spent the rest of the ride cycling in between small talk and silence. It was pleasant, I felt comfortable and relatively confident about the job. Meaning that I didn't really feel confident whatsoever, but I'd choke those feelings down and attempt not to let my nervousness shine through during the interview.


Tyler pulled up in front of the hotel, and I was astounded that such grandeur could exist in the heavily wooded area. The forest that surrounded must have been ancient, because the trees that filled it were taller than I could have ever imagined any trees to be. Somehow the hotel looked natural among the towering foliage, as though it was meant to be in this place. It was beautiful and remote, a perfect getaway. I felt at peace as I got out of the car, *almost* enough to ease my nerves over the rapidly incoming interview. 


Tyler directed me to head into the lobby and speak to someone at the front desk while he parked the truck with the other hotel vehicles. I entered the hotel to find a lobby as immaculate as the exterior, the hotel was truly extravagant, and I could almost understand why the application featured such odd personal questions. It brought the large paycheck into perspective as well, and defeated any wariness that may have been held deep within me. 


There was a girl with long, raven-colored hair, and shocking blue eyes who stood behind the front desk. 


Welcome to the Good Shade, I'm Dawn, how can I help you? She greeted cheerfully as I arrived at the desk. 


I squinted for a moment at her name tag, which quite obviously did not say Dawn. That was the only opportunity I've had so far to look at her name tag, but if I recall correctly it said *Alphaea I.C*. I'm not sure what that means, but it didn't really look like a name to me, so I dismissed it as some sort of labelling the hotel has for staff. 


I returned her smile, I'm here to see Mister Smith about a position here. 


Oh! She gasped excitedly, I knew you'd be here soon, right this way, he's waiting for you. 


With a glee filled smile she gestured to a door behind the front desk. I wasn't sure what she was so excited about, but as I walked towards the door I could swear that she *sniffed* me. I found myself slightly concerned about the mental health of the girl at the front desk, and wondered vaguely if people like her were the reason that the application contained such odd questions.


A tall man sat behind a dark wood desk, and introduced himself as Mister Smith. He was the owner and manager of the hotel. He created all the rules and guidelines for the staff and guests, and he oversaw all that went on inside the hotel. He also personally dealt with all applications for employment, which apparently didn't happen often. Before any conversation about the position took place, I had to sign an agreement to keep everything confidential. Honestly, I wouldn't even know that posting here was an option if I hadn't seen [Tyler's post](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6104g9/the_good_shade_hotel/) on here a while back. 


I've been reading the awful tales of the darkest moments in the lives of people for many years, but I never thought I'd be one of the people posting. That's besides the point though, I have to finish detailing what I experienced last night. 


After signing the form we began discussing the job. I'd be doing regular hotel housekeeping-- for the most part. My job would not always be a regular one, there was the possibility of my assistance being needed with guests, or I may end up requested by a guest for certain actions. I was fine with all of that. Some of the actions detailed deep within the contract seemed odd, but it was all well within what was worth it for the job and the money. This was the only job I could get, and it honestly didn't seem like a bad one.


We arranged to have 30% of my pay deposited directly into Jeremy's account, after a quick phone call with him to confirm this was acceptable. That portion would be what I used to pay back Emily and Jeremy for housing me for free over the years. 60% would be deposited into a savings account that the hotel had provided me with. Another contract had to be signed there, but all Mister Smith did was make a phone call in private afterwards. The final ten percent would be put into a chequing account that came with the savings. That was the money I planned to spend freely, whether I used it to buy clothes, groceries, or help out with the bills when things were tight at home. 


My savings would first be going towards citizenship, then getting a cheap place for myself. I plan to stop being a burden on my friends as soon as I can, they have a growing family and shouldn't also have to deal with a nearly 20 year old woman living off of them. Once the apartment was in place and I had enough in my savings, I'd be able to work towards college. Living on my own would have me spending a portion of my cheque on rent, but if I manage to keep this job that won't be an issue. This job paid more than well enough for me to finally get myself out into the world.


I suppose that I should have been concerned when he asked me to confirm my genetic background. When I replied that I was fairly certain that I was 100% human, he seemed skeptical. He squinted at me for a moment, and it made me nervous. *Why on Earth would you question whether I'm human or not?* Then things got really strange, he asked me if I would mind consenting to a blood test. I agreed, but it definitely freaked me out. I kept reminding myself that this was my only option. 


By the end of the meeting I had agreed to the requirements of the job, had my blood taken, and signed what may have been dozens of forms. I also found out that my first shift had already begun, and I would be spending my night at the hotel. I called Emily from the phone in the office to let her know that I wouldn't be returning until morning. I was about to leave the office when the girl from the front desk entered the room. She held out a plastic card to me, and I was shocked when I realized what it was.


A debit card from a bank local to my area, it had my name on it and looked exactly like Emily's card from the same bank. Mister Smith assured me that this was a fully functional card, and that he had pulled some strings with a friend at the bank to create an account for me. As long as I was employed with the hotel they would be sure that I would face no consequences from possessing an American account before becoming a citizen, and Mister Smith would be glad to have his friend add my social security information once I become a citizen, so creating a new account and transferring the money would not be necessary in the future.


I was beyond grateful as I left the office, for the job, the bank account, and the understanding that my boss seemed to express over my confusing situation. I was told to speak to Dawn so that she could give me the items I'd need to begin my shift. When I was once again facing the front desk, both Dawn and Tyler stood behind it smiling.


Did you get the job? Tyler asked me.


I smiled, I did actually, Mister Smith told me I needed to speak to Dawn before I get to work. 


That's great-- He stopped short to stare intently at the computer screen in front of him for a brief moment, --Sorry, I've been requested to a room. Are you coming, Dawn? 


She shook her head, I have to help our new friend meet with Rose, but-- she squinted at the screen for a moment, -- It's just my stupid brother, you'll be fine, she rolled her eyes as she stepped away from the counter.


Tyler shrugged and walked off towards several sets of elevators, and I watched as he produced a key card and swiped it through a card reader before pressing the call button. As he got into the elevator I looked back to Dawn, who was pulling a piece of paper from a filing cabinet, then she walked back towards me. 


Read this, let me know if you have any questions, she stated simply.


I took the paper and looked it over, some of it brought my concern back into full force. 


*Welcome to housekeeping at the Good Shade,* 


*Your position is a key role in our hotel, as we are well known for how immaculately kept such a large establishment remains constantly. On request you may be provided with a brief map of the property, which explains some of the regulations about guests located in different areas of the hotel.*


*Certain rooms require specific towels, sheets, blankets, soaps, etcetera. Please refer to the head of our housekeeping crew for a list of rooms and their requirements.*


*At this point, you have already signed various contracts restricting you from speaking about any aspect of your job. This was included in the documents you signed, but we must reiterate that in the case of finding items that you consider to be suspicious, dangerous, illegal, evidence in a crime, or remnants of a crime, you are not to react as you would in a normal situation.*


*Emergency services are unable to be contacted from or enter our establishment. We have medical staff who can deal with any wounded person(s) found in a room. We also have teams to deal with any person(s) found who may be deceased. Please refrain from touching any person(s), whether they be living or deceased. This also includes any other guests, and generally the other employees.* 


*If accidental contact is made at any point, please refer to the front desk for treatment of any negative side effects. Other than the items above, housekeeping here is relatively the same as everywhere else. Please remember that we take pride in immaculately clean rooms. Please refer to the head of housekeeping for concerns about anything found while working, and further details about the job.* 


*- A. Smith, Owner   Manager* 


I think it's hardly a question that anyone who read such a thing would be fairly concerned about what kind of hotel this truly was. 

I need the money though, and on the bright side, at least if I find a dead body I don't have to be the one to remove it. After reviewing that sentence, I realize that my life may have hit it's utter low. 

Once I get enough money though, I could put this all behind me. I have a chance to quit in three months according to the contract, and there were consequences that I didn't want to learn about for quitting before you had worked the allotted time. 


This place seems to be incredibly serious about the whole secrecy thing, and I think this subreddit might be part of the reason that the employees can handle holding it in around the rest of the world.


I didn't bother asking Dawn any questions at that moment, I just steeled myself for the night ahead of me. She pulled out a key card and handed it to me with a smile.


Head to floor U1, and Rose should be in the laundry room waiting for you. That's the storage floor. 


U1? The strange label of the floor gave me pause.


She smiled as though this was a charmingly innocent question that was often brought up, Mister Smith always forgets to tell the new employees, we actually have 50 underground floors. When we send you to a room with the label U in front of the number, it's underground.


I nodded, I honestly had guessed as much when I'd first heard her announce the floor I needed to go to, but it was still a little surprising to know for a fact that this hotel has underground floors. What could have possibly motivated someone to build a hotel that had its majority of rooms below the earth? 


I thanked Dawn for her assistance, and headed towards the elevators. There was a handwritten message on the back of the housekeeping paper that I hadn't noticed until then, it said *Use the second elevator * 


I glanced back towards Dawn and she gave me a small smile and wave, before turning to type something into the computer. I arrived in front of the second elevator, and I swiped the card I held through the reader as I had seen Tyler do. The call button lit up when I pressed it, and the elevator opened before me in less than a minute. I got to the correctly labelled floor and was in the laundry room too fast to calm my nerves about my first shift.


There was a woman in there, maybe in her mid twenties. She was beautiful, tall and curvy, with honey-blonde hair spilling down to her waist. She turned to me as I approached, and she gave me a smile that warmed her ice-blue eyes. She straightened as she took in my appearance, and her sudden change in expression made it seem as though she sensed something was amiss. That expression quickly changed back though, and she introduced herself as Rose, the head of housekeeping. 


For my first night all she wanted me to do was two of the underground floors. Approximately ten rooms on each of those floors had been vacated earlier in the day and needed to be arranged for new guests. Around twenty rooms in one shift didn't sound bad. She told me which rooms needed certain things, and gave me a list that carefully inventoried every item that needed to be present in each room that I cleaned. She also explained to me the hotel protocol for cleaning various things, including blood. 


After all of the preparation I was finally ready to get to work. It was more than twenty rooms, but I didn't complain. I took a cleaning cart and headed off to the floor below me to begin. That floor consisted of mostly regular housekeeping tasks. I took my time, not wanting to be left with nothing to do halfway through my shift. After nearly three hours I finished 12 rooms on that floor. They were all pretty basic, each room was the same. 


I moved on to the next floor with around six hours left in the ten hour shift. The first few rooms went simply, I made beds and restocked towels. I vacuumed, swept, mopped, and wiped things down. As I progressed down the hallway I heard strange noises coming from occupied rooms. It ranged from crying, to screaming, to what seemed like some intense sexual activity. From one room I heard what sounded like chanting in a foreign language. All the strange noises put me slightly on edge, and I tried to push through the 15 rooms on the floor that I was assigned to clean.


I got to the last room and found blood splatter in the shower, fresh enough to still be pooling in the tub. 


The sight made me dizzy, and I had to take a moment to catch my breath. It freaked me out, I wasn't sure how fast blood dried but I felt like I had narrowly missed seeing criminal activity. I cleaned out the tub using the methods Rose had described to me, and finished that room faster than any other. Or at least, I thought I did. 


I walked out into the hallway and noticed a dried smear on the wall that hadn't been there before, assuming it was blood I quickly cleaned it. I wasn't about to get in trouble because a murderous guest was running rampant through the hotel. I was afraid though, what if the person who caused this bloodshed was still nearby? 


I strode hastily towards the elevator with my cart in tow. I let out a breath that I didn't realize I was holding when I met Rose back in the laundry room.


What took you so long? She asked as I put away the cart.


I was confused by the question, I still had hours left in my shift. I looked at the clock on the wall and was surprised to see that my shift had ended thirty minutes prior. Somehow I had lost a lot of time. I explained to her what I found while cleaning, but she seemed unconcerned. She dismissed me for the day, and I went up to the lobby to find Tyler. 


He informed me that his shift didn't end for over an hour, but I could nap in the office on the couch while Mister Smith was gone. I took the offer, and awoke later to have Tyler escort me to the truck we had arrived in. As we got in the vehicle I noticed his nametag, *Tyler Stephens, H.S.* 


What does H.S mean? Is that some sort of hotel label? I pointed towards the tag. 


He glanced at it and smiled, Kind of a hotel thing, they put your species on your nametag to help the guests. 


I was surprised. H.S is quite obviously homosapien, but what did Dawn's nametag mean? Was I truly working with people who weren't human? I didn't know how to respond with anything more intelligent than, *Oh, okay.* 


Tyler had just started the engine when I saw Dawn come running from the hotel. She stopped at my window and gestured for me to open it, and once it was down she handed me a small piece of metal. 


She told me it was my nametag, and I thanked her for delivering it. We drove away, and I found myself staring at the nametag. I wondered if I would fit in as an employee at this hotel. 


Perhaps most importantly, I'm wondering if the people here can answer a question while I'm employed. A question that Tyler had no clue how to answer on the drive. A question about what their blood test revealed, because I'm not sure why my nametag reads *Isabelle Lawrence, N.F.*


The last thing Tyler said to me before he dropped me off was this, You're going to see a lot of things that you've never expected, imagined, or wanted to see. If you think you've had a weird night already, you haven't seen anything yet. 


I had trouble going to sleep as the sun rose, I took the time to think about my life. 


*Where do you see yourself in five years?*


How can I know, when I'm not even sure if I'm human anymore? 


-----


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back for a fourth time, and excited as ever. Something funny etc 

Congrats on joining the wedded world sir Gravy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww I'm completely floored by being part of this list, thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww lol, thank you for reading!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is amazing advice, I'll let Chrissi know she should look into it, because the compensation isn't going to last forever, and having a savings for the future would be wise. Thank you so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww you're so pretty and you two are adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hilarious, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Lotion](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66f7sa/dont_use_dove_lotion/)


[Walls](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66psez/our_home_inspector_overlooked_the_walls/)



[Icecream](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61oydb/i_was_almost_in_the_lucky_47_club/)


[Rivalry](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5x5cpc/not_your_average_sibling_rivalry/)


[Father](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/592px2/my_children_never_lied/)


Shameless self promotion because why not. I highly recommend the last two stories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you recommend Autopilot? That story is one of my all time favorites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS; what's an instructable
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Our Home Inspector Overlooked The Walls](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66psez/our_home_inspector_overlooked_the_walls/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one would ever want to visit if we stay lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a decent outcome, so many lives stolen under the nose of the neighborhood. A memorial would be nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other commenter was correct, he was using a Polaroid camera
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robert* I apologize, I accidently called him the name of my father in law near the end of my account </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That situation sounds almost preferable to what happened here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprisingly no, but almost anything that could have rotted was eaten. Those people were almost entirely consumed. Bone doesn't leave a smell I suppose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could save you a lot of trouble, good luck with the house! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was an inspector that we sent that died, I'm not usually the one to deal with the financial or legal decisions, but according to my parents the people who sold us the house should have done an inspection before they tried to sell it. They should have known about the man long before we bought it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least they came through for us. Great people, though they were not impressed with their findings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, kind internet stranger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Home Inspector Overlooked The Walls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not too long ago I became engaged to a wonderful girl named Ragini. She was smart, beautiful, and funny-- the perfect woman to spend my life with. We were so happy together, and not long after the engagement we began planning the date and looking for a home. The house came before the wedding date by a mere month. 


The house was a decent size for a family, three bedrooms, two bathrooms, fenced in yard. It was within our budget, but it was also a little run-down. We would be spending the first few months of our marriage repairing small issues and making the house our own. The first order of business was to call the man who inspected my parents home. 


It had been quite a while since they bought their current home, but Mike was still doing the same job. He was friendly, trusted by the family, and he was good at his job. He actually saved us some money by the time we made the deal and paid for the house, a few thousand dollars had been knocked off due to the repairs needed. Mike told is that there were no huge issues, everything could be done without outside help. I was happy to do the repairs on my own.


Buying a house was expensive, the wedding would be expensive, if doing the work myself meant saving a little money then I was more than up for it. Things went well for the first week, there was only one odd issue. Several times throughout each night it sounded like there was something scratching at the walls, clicking in the vents, or running through the house. I shrugged it off as mice, but Ragini wasn't so inclined to ignore the situation. 


She insisted we get rid of them, and was upset that Mike hadn't told us about a rodent issue. She ended up getting me to call Mike about it the next morning, and he informed me that he hadn't thought to check the walls himself. I heard him shuffling through papers over the phone.


Ah, yes, he spoke in a gruff voice, Robert was sposed to inspect the walls. You've got yourself an old house, lots of space between the walls. File says he was in, but it seems I'm missing his final report. 


What should we do? I asked, his information wasn't very helpful. 


Well this is probably just a filing error, if anything was seriously wrong he would have come to me about it. Hasnt been in for a few days, but I'll ask about it on his next shift. I'd say that you ought to get an exterminator before it gets worse. I'm sorry we didn't catch that for you. Do you need us to come back out? 


He sounded very understanding, and I ended up declining his offer to come back. It was a simple rodent issue, we could fix it on our own. The results of the call didn't please Ragini, but she was satisfied enough to let it go and call an exterminator. 


Ragini was a little too worried about whatever the exterminators were going to use to some our pest problem, so we ended up spending the rest of that day and night at my parents house. She didn't want to smell the poison, or the dead pests. We arrived home the next day to find a note taped to the front door. It was just the number for the exterminators. 


I called, and they explained that they were coming back today to remove the bodies. There had been an issue with another house, and since my home was a short notice job it wasn't their first priority. I was a little grossed out knowing that there were dead rodents in my walls, but at least they would be gone soon. 


My fiance wasn't impressed, and we ended up going out for lunch when the removal team arrived. We returned to the house a few hours later, we assumed it would be empty and rodent free. 


Arriving home did not yield the expected results. The truck which the removal team had driven was still parked in the driveway. Also parked in front of our home were two police cars and an ambulance. I had no idea what was going on, and Ragini stared at me with her own look of confusion. 


An officer came up to us, asking if we were the homeowners. I was too distracted to respond though, because at the same moment two other officers were exiting the front door of our house. They had a man in handcuffs between them. He was haggard and filthy, rust colored stains ran down the length of his clothes, and he was barefoot. He whimpered as they guided him towards their car. 


No, *no.* Please? Oh *please,* I'm sorry. I was *so hungry*. I'm *starving.* Let me eat, God *please* let me eat. 


His gaze darted across all of the people outside, and suddenly landed on Ragini and I. He lunged when he saw us, trying to remove himself from the clutch of the officers. They weren't prepared for the abrupt resistance, and he was stopped by a taser when he ran towards us at an inhuman speed. He collapsed to the ground mere feet from where we stood. 


He whimpered for another moment before he started to laugh. The officers began to lift him from the ground, and he giggled as he rose. Before they turned him away he let out a howling bout of hysterical laughter and stared directly at my fiancee and I. 


You two smell *delicious!* He spit as he fell into another round of the off-putting noise.


The officers roughly pulled him away. I stood there in shock, I had no idea who that psycho was. Ragini looked near tears as she stared up at me. 


He spit on me, she said quietly, not wanting to exaggerate the inconvenience. 


It couldn't have been exaggerated though, because her white blouse was covered in red specks. It wasn't saliva that had come spraying from his mouth as he laughed, it was blood. I planned on not telling her right away, but she lifted a finger to my face and wiped a drop off of my cheek. She stared for a moment before giving me a panicked glance, and I answered her silent question with a nod.


From that point on, the authorities gave us nothing but horrifying discoveries. The easiest way to tell you about it would be to skip ahead to where we are now. 


My family has decided to attempt to sue the real estate agency which sold us the home. They should have known what was going on. How could they not inspect their properties more thoroughly? I'm not sure how that lawsuit will go, but I don't think money is going to fix the traumatic after effects of living there. We're not sure if we want to live in the house, we've been staying with my parents until we decide. It should be safe know, but knowing the truth is off-putting. Our wedding went as planned.


After the investigation and our house being closed off as a crime scene for a while, the authorities told us the truth. The man that they arrested had been living in the crawlspace between our walls for years. He had been there since shortly before the previous homeowners left. They thought he was mentally ill, apparently he claimed was entirely cannibalistic and had not yet eaten a thing since his arrest. That was a week after he was put in.there.


The real reason that Robert never got his report to Mike was because he never left the house. Richard's remains were found in the walls, half of his body was eaten down to the bone. Richard wasn't the only body in the walls though. There were tons of bones found all over the crawlspace, it was practically a graveyard. 


That wasn't even the worst part. Apparently this man wasn't a strict cannibal, the remains of dogs and cats were found as well. They believe that they were all animals that had gone missing around the neighborhood. The last thing that they found might be the most terrifying, at least for Ragini and I. It's what keeps us from going home, it's what makes us wonder if there is anywhere truly private and safe. 


There were pictures. Hundreds, if not thousands. They were all of different people, but almost every recent one was of my wife and I. Apparently nearly every photo has been matched to a missing person, and this man is assumed to have murdered over 50 people in the last few years. The truly scary part? 


There was a week's worth of pictures for each person, a date on the back of each. The last picture in each set had two dates, the day it was taken and the day after. Beside the second date was a comment, usually something along the lines of *delicious*, *bitter*, *salty*. All descriptions of taste. 


The last picture of Ragini and I was taken the day of the extermination.



[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's rare but it's an amazing feeling when it happens c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I make stupid faces 90% of the time](http://imgur.com/Htcz6hZ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think both would be good because the readers would be able to give constructive feedback before a story is posted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't read yet but when I saw this I screamed internally.

Edit: Holy shit. Revenge is within your reach OP. Get itttt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I've seen in the contracts, it seems that was an oversight. They never specifically barred us from being able to tell people the brand of lotion, just to not name the specific product that was tested, or the company name to anyone. 

The other oversight was in the clause about not talking about the side effects, there was no restrictions about posting an anonymous account on another forum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of similar. Besides the fact that many more layers are removed at once in large disgusting chunks, leaving behind a strange clear coating and bleeding in places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the reason humans can't have nice things. Fucking backwards thinking moron.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally all you had to say that it was not intended for male use, it is a product marketed directly at females. This isn't even the lotion I was talking about anyways, so I'm unsure of why you're ranting here. 

Seriously, I'm just fucked up over you saying lotion will *turn* you transgender. How fucking ignorant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, I'd say no offense but you're either a troll or severely brain damaged. 

Merely introducing a low level of estrogen into a male body *does not* "turn" them transgender. That's ridiculous. I'm not entirely sure you're aware of what you're talking about. You sound like the classic priveledged white male, *it has estrogen so I can't touch it because my balls will die!*

Fucking ridiculous. Get a life. So what if it's makerketed directly at females, then don't use it, duh. There was literally no reason for you to claim using it would *turn you transgender*. Stupidest thing I've ever heard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense random internet stranger, but this makes about -35 sense. 

Less than no sense. 

Lotion can't "turn" you transgender... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
