<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4900</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fully expect some sort of escalation that will be an attempt to dominate the news cycle when Yates and Comey are testifying about Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump right now.......

https://imgflip.com/i/1nhhqu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy is virtually James Bond...he was also key in bringing down FIFA....

I mean that's a pretty solid resume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the constant anti-establishment narrative being anger that politicians were treating voters as being idiots....

Well Trump's shown that a large portion are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as internet twitter sources go...Mensch and JSR seem to be pretty accurate. 

I forget who but one of them also predicted the FBI raid on a shady casino that just happens to be funded by multiple Trump/GOP officials and Russians (and is speculated to be just one of the methods of laundering money between Russia and American politicians).

John Schindler seems to be more of the pure speculcation/opinion anti-trump twitter voices though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably won't get another one until it gets close to filing charges time....

Louise Mensch is getting her info directly from the intel community. 

She reported the Carter Page FISA warrant last November....you see how long that took before the major media outlets got the story, and it's unclear if they would have even gotten it/reported on it if Trump himself hadn't made it a story by talking about being his transition team being monitored.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She also very clearly states when she is purely speculating, and she does so primarily to give other information context, not just to spout some Alex Jones hur dur pizza party fake news.

When it comes to her "insider" info, it's been pretty spot on. I mean she had the Carter Page FISA info in Nov of last year.

It's pretty obvious that she is being fed information by sources very high up in the intel community, and I've yet to see anything significant she's reported to turn out false. 

She's basically providing context/detail about the Steele dossier...both are constantly being proven to be accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
