<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject792</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah nice catch. Shes gonna get hit no doubt, but whos in the body at the time is another thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well they would get plenty of screen time if thats what you mean, syd at least. They would be in a relationship.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yh i def think it will go down pretty much like this. This would also serve as  a base to explain the multiple personality/powers of David in the next season, as he literally explains things to syd. 


Would be interesting if Lenny still 'exists' in him too. Those two competing for his affection somehow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice on weed control/weedkiller </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, i have a 'berry section' of sorts, where i grow raspberries, gooseberries and blackcurrants and i'm just looking for advice/opinions on weed control in this area. 


Previously i've just let the weeds grow until you can pull them out by hand, but this isn't very effective and time consuming. Hoeing isn't an option because of the nature of the plants makes it difficult. So basically, is there a weedkiller that can control the weeds but will leave the plants untouched? 


The gardens just waking up, so i thought id nip it in the bud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really hope theyre back next season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i think he marketed it wrong at the start. He didn't just put everything on youtube, i think it was on dvd or something. Dude should no doubt be a youtube household name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm guessing they are keeping the drop rate so low to make it easier to spot the spoofers. .... maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the obvious solution is to buy some corrosive acid and pour into the sink. Wait a few hours and before you know it, you have a sludgey mess that can wash away with lots and of water. 
 
bonus tip. gently set alight the mixture to speed up the process </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truly the golden age of the internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah, if its not a 'blockbuster', hollywood only likes movies about hollywood. Any film will make money if marketed right, its about putting up the money to do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the film, over sued sentiment for sure on here, but genuinely underrated film. Hollywood don't like films like this tho.

Clive Owen played his role so well, his progession is so subtle through the film, its brilliant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a very bad zoo yes. But all zoos kill their animals when they become surplus or problematic. For example the of killing lion cubs is general practice in un-neutered lions. I personally don't think the good they do balances out all the shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he make da face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was MY shower thought when i was a teenager you mind rapist. I thought of a youtube mini series "If fish could scream" basicially featuring sceens of fish being caught, with screaming from movie excerpts.


It remained a showerthought only.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the old pokey eye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love a sequel to this. Could feature loads of modern toons, film and tv, simpsons cameos, the lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the players feel guilty af right now. They've let him down this season. 

Still, a ridiculous decision to sack him. Modern football for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats a stretch. Interesting tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, being white af i think i have a hold on world news n such and i def hadn't heard of any terror attacks last night in sweden. So, i guess he's spinning the swedish immigration 'problems'. Fair do, he may have even accidentally thrown 'last night' in there.


Interesting tho, that journalists are weighing in on that. Ignoring the problems that sweden have. He's spinning one way, the press, the other. Kinda awesome watch it all play out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so, wait. Did anything at all happen in sweden that got him confused? or he got the name wrong? Or he just intentionally made it up? Surely, not even trump is capable of that?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is cool, i spose im not that surprised they now have actors approaching them to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Hardy reads a bed time story. yep, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this seems entirely pointless, but, uh.. lets see what happens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some peeps outside the uk cant see bbc content. And so, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Hardy reads a bedtime story (for all) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, i'm not gay, but damn that man is attractive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> arent they tho? seriously, they all seem so legit. Even Simon Pegg who i thought had got a bit hollywood cuz he started dressing fancy, he still comes across as decent, normal human being in his interviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i live near (in...) the area its constantly sending up, where Wright lived. They got it so insanely spot on and still kept it hilarious. Def one of my fav all time comedies, if not films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't get away from this atm, so i'm just remembering the mastery of the original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bag Raiders - Shooting Stars [Alternative/Electro House] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> supplies muthafucka
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Running out of cement too. And tarmac. And road grit. And bananas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [yes muthafucka] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2tpHq8jMyhw)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any big public outcry always reminds me of this. Song and the video work so well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faithless - We Come 1 [Alternative/Dance] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9 years ago ffs. I'm biased, but 10 years ago was a golden age of interesting music.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloc Party - Flux [Indie/Alternative] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a  brit watching from a afar i thought this was an interesting little addition to a speech, that didn't have to be included at all. Hasn't got any media attention either. Interesting to see what it means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at least they didnt decapitate the dog with a helicopter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your life is a lie. this mistake was put there by someone trying to reach out to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Society </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 17:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> james milner could be the single most under rated english player of all time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 11:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [squiddies] (http://25.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lzixaunt1I1r9egpco1_500.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean, they make some strong points, but its worth watching this from mark kermode for a more positive take https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QCEVfNjsHW8


Its a valid point that there aren't really any original 'blockbusters' being made anymore tho. I think Dunkirk will be the biggest film of the year. This generations 'Saving private ryan' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 19:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold my coconut whilst i get drain bamage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't fuck with rolf harris </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes its transparent, they just call it a 'foil' for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my all time favs from one of my all time favs. Absolute beaches, sunsets and traveling vibes.


Hope they make a 3rd album sometime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he's only gone and done it again. jezeus, the mans a beast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a neutral, kinda, im glad preston scored first. Will be a lively game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sweet. i just hope he has a better celebration when he scores </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> captain giroud? how longs that been going (not a gooner btw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 14:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Titus Bramble] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1FYFG3FrD5I) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 14:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if he was rubbish cuz he never got enough game time, which became the joke, so i suppose he was likeable.... But anyway, Marcelino. He mustve played about 10 games in 3 years, he was always injured! I think he was out for a year with a broken finger! 



Actually, forget that. My answer is def Titus Bramble. What a legend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 14:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really want some kind of ETFE foil, large buildings and greenhouses use this, but it can be pricey for small scale. 

You may be able to mimic this with layering some rolls of clear polythene, which wouldnt be as strong or last as long but would be massively cheaper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To this day, I have no idea what that woman was singing about. Like, literally, no idea. I don't know what a "Hollaback Girl" is, but I have to imagine it's a foul, disease-ridden thing, that wears too much makeup to cover up the fact that it's a 47 year-old fish-dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm not even french and this disgusts me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't think we'll wait around to do last minute business in the transfer window. I like Mitro, but it all looks a bit suspect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as i remember it you could also easily run the whole length of the pitch, beating every player to smash it in and win each match 20 nil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a non story? when theres so much speculation about him leaving anyway? No way the board are happy paying his wages to not even get on the bench. 100% he's out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i agree, but its a bad habit this season where we dominate the game without scoring enough goals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colback reminds me of another ginger i'd rather forget, butt i won't dirty this sub by mentioning his name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our next striker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i'm guessing Mitro is on his way considering he's not injured and not on the bench. He's been linked with palace amongst others  but even after a meeting where he supposedly said he wanted to stay, he's not even on the bench? Looks like he'll be leaving then.


So who can we get in to replace him? With xmas n all i'm not up to date on the rumour mill, I've only heard of the Callum Wilson rumour, which imo would be a great signing. 


Also, i know we really could do with a steady centre mid atm, but as today shows (25 shots on goal) we desperatey need someone to take these chances. Too many games we dominate, without scoring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really awful. Blackburn are not a good team and we've had no answers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so mitro is injured?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is he injured? seems ridiculous to leave him on the bench?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2RRGeIketm4 

Early 90's, thats the earliest i've seen so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, whatever we do to combat global warming, the earth could spew out a lifetimes worth of Co2 in one hit, at any second.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he used to hit the ball so hard, the only trouble was half the time it flew 20 yards over the bar or out of play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was arrogant for sure but his ability was off the scale. Underrated imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha yeah but his wasn't a shot, so doesn't count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all this talk of scorpion kicks, lets not forget the original and best, Newcastle Utds Laurent Robert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha! sadly, i didn't choose the song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't think of anyone else who did it earlier? i'm sure someone will pipe up tho...

(also pls forgive the potato quality and the even worse soundtrack, but its the best quality i could find. I'm sure theres better out there) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all this talk of scorpion kicks, lets not forget the original and best, Newcastle Utds Laurent Robert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> almost as good as Laurent Roberts effort back in the day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah, it won't matter when they remake the originals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'crabb stepping aside' killed me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, sucking up the downvotes. Its funny that even a 'liberal' site like reddit will upvote a video of a guy bullying someone. hah, pranks yo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, i just watched short circuit 2... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emma Watson 2016 / Cynthia Gibb 1988 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uploading this in the hopes non uk peeps will watch and wonder wtf is going on. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bo Selecta - Proper Crimbo [Christmas] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this would only be a christmas tree in the world of futurama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 18:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing that could stop this is ranking things on the number of comments it generates. Which as its problems, so wouldn't happen. 


What it really comes down to is us, the users, to see through the bullshit. But thats a losing game as reddit expands further into the general populace. Without sounding like i'm inserting my member into my own ass, the standard of reddit user has gone notably downhill in recent years. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 18:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this has the same kick as Saving private ryan. That was a film that had a huge impact for generations of children, me included.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this needs answering. Also, what happens to the food they eat (these two may be the same answer) But by the end of seaon 2 could we see loads of massively bloated hosts rolling about? literally full of rotten food?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i always thought it was a clue to see whos a host or not, but turns out its just another polar bear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah thats where i recognise him from, x men! fuck...


I'm actually not looking forward to the whole, can he really love her/what is love discussions that will flood the boards.


Theyre just robots meatbags. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i likes the reboots, but this trailers has me worried. Kinda awful speech over basically running around and shooting stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 08:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree, except i'm not sure Dolores has reached it. At least i think theyve left it open. I think shes got as far as her wyatt programming and is now acting on his narrative, angry killer bot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know all that, and i will rewatch. But i know its left unclear if she got past her prgramming, which includes wyatt. Everyone on here is jumping to that conclusion. 


(also, don't downvote comments just cuz you dont like it. Its ok to discuss things. Reddit has a real problem with the duality of liking something, and criticising it at the same time) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 21:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should rewatch with that in mind, Fords whole new  narrative has led everyone to this point.


 I'm open for her choosing to be an angry killing machine, but we as the audience don't know whether shes 'awoken', or whether its her being wyatt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernard is potentially the only host that has reached 'sentience'. He's the only one whos knows what he is and what the world around him is. 

Ford changed maeves narrative, or at least, got bernard/arnold to do it.

We also don't know why maeve got off that train. Whether it was because shes reached 'a new level' and accepted that shes a host, or that she simply can't escape her cornerstone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its assumed the pic was in the park, from the old timey photo guys we see during episode 1 or 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> by his choice. Dolores is in wyatt mode. I agree tho, the scene in the basement could be her reaching a new level of consciousness. That inner monlogue, her 'self'. But it could also mean she went as far as she could towards 'sentience' before wyatt 'took over', so to speak. Just as with Maeve, we don't know yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 08:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know if dolores reached 'sentience'. And maeve cut through presumably programmed or intentionally weakened security. Ford controls the park yes, but theres no reason to suggest he controls anything in the real world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wonder if the stuff with them was cut from the show? its weird we don't see anything on them, only glimpses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you say they don't have the means to kill the hosts? Its made out to be a massive company, with other parks to boot. 


And we have yet to see if they (if that means every host, or just arnolds 'originals') is even able to go beyond programming. 


(incidentally, how are the hosts even powered?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 23:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to what ends tho? Unless theres a whole story we don't know about, as soon as delos realise whats happened, they will destroy every host.

 Unstable bernard and idiotic william are the only two things that could potentially prevent this. This is not a good plan. This is smashing his toys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so his plan to set them 'free' was?.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sadly, i think this is true. But i'd hope they gave him a decent plan, that we're yet to fully understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wondered about this. Is there any info on things they cut out? I thought the indians were gonna have a lot more of a role in things but we only see glimpses of them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you could read the whole season as Ford master plan to destroy the park, guilt free, framing maeve in the process. It *could* have been a host that got shot, it could have been him and he's a made a copy of himself. Or, its his final masterpiece of a host that we've yet to meet. He doesn't mention about wanting to live forever or anything along those lines, so it would be a bit out of the blue. 


The fact that its Hopkins playing Ford makes me think he isn't coming back, but i would love it if he did. Theres still a lot of explaining to do. Exactly what was his plan again?..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> basically, they pushed it too far. They used it as an excuse, rather than a tool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we're not sure if they all can? Either way Ford programmed that, and did so they would destroy each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the fact that its not dealt with and left to the audience to assume things. Other tv shows (Lost for example) did this, and i would hate it if westworld did more of it just to keep the audience entertained by moving the narrative along. Which is what i thinm maeves entire story was about. When you see security teams throwing themselves at bullets, host or not, its annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How has Ford 'freed' them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i agree. except fuck william. All he wants is chaos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think reddit, like everyone else, just really loves Anthony Hopkins.


But i'm not sure he turned on skynet either. Didn't he just "smash his toys and go home" ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, kinda.


Actually, no. But it ended nicely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fords story was far from concluded. If he's really dead, i'm hoping we see flashbacks with more insight into wtf he was thinking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
