<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8214</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Western Digital Is Having Growing Pains After Takeover Of SanDisk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana Stocks Go On Reversal Mode After 8 Weeks Of Gains: Cannabis Index Down From 52-Week High </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.benzinga.com/news/17/02/9061511/marijuana-stocks-go-on-reversal-mode-after-8-weeks-of-gains-cannabis-index-down-f

After posting eight consecutive weeks of gains, the Viridian Cannabis Stock Index, which groups a majority of the most relevant securities in the marijuana space, experienced a reversal last week.

For the five days comprised between February 6 and February 10, inclusive, the Cannabis Stock Index lost 1.5 percent, marking the first weekly decline since the beginning of the year. In contrast, the four major market index ETFs, the SPDR Dow Jones Industrial Average ETF 
DIA
, the PowerShares QQQ Trust, Series 1 (ETF) 
QQQ
, the SPDR S P 500 ETF Trust 
SPY
, and the iShares Russell 2000 Index (ETF) 
IWM
, all surged over the week.

In order to get a better picture of what happened, Benzinga reached out to Viridian Capital Advisors analyst Harrison Phillips, who is in charge of the Cannabis Stock Index weekly report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sirius XM Stock Is Now Accelerating Towards Higher Prices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are You Ready For A Snapchat Phone? Here's What It Could Look Like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cute Couple:Kiss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres how Googles own ads impact bids   pricing in AdWords auctions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://searchengineland.com/how-google-ads-impact-bids-pricing-adwords-auctions-269153
Google and its sibling companies at Alphabet collectively bid on thousands of keywords in AdWords. That has been going on for years. The search giant has said its ad buying does not directly inflate pricing for other advertisers because advertisers are charged as if it wasnt bidding. However, thats not quite accurate.

Participating in its own ad auctions has long raised conflict of interest objections. A report from The Wall Street Journal last month put a spotlight on the practice again with some eye-popping stats and renewed our questions about how these ads affect other advertisers.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google: No Comment On The Google Search Ranking Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nvidia shows why it is the hottest stock on Wall Street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chip maker Nvidia Corp., showed investors on Thursday why shares soared 224% last year, with stunning growth rates in every business but one and more profit in the holiday quarter than it had in all of 2015.
http://www.marketwatch.com/story/nvidia-shows-why-it-is-the-hottest-stock-on-wall-street-2017-02-09

Nvidia NVDA, +0.37%  reported fourth-quarter revenue growth of 55% to a record $2.17 billion and earnings per share of 99 cents, up 183% from last year and 19% higher than analysts estimates. Full-year profit of $1.67 billion was nearly equal to Nvidias earnings of the three previous years combined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk's Trump Alliance Indicates Great Things for Tesla Stock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Inc. Stock Keeps Rising, Putting A Chokehold On Short-Sellers (AAPL) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://investorplace.com/2017/02/apple-stock-keeps-rising-putting-a-chokehold-on-short-sellers/#.WKRau3V97J8
Apple Inc. (AAPL) stock is choking short-sellers after Goldman Sachs Group Inc (GS) boosted its price target 13%, pushing the iPhone makers shares to new highs again and again.

Apple Inc. Stock Keeps Rising, Putting A Chokehold On Short-Sellers (AAPL)Analysts and investors are practically salivating over the yet-to-be revealed iPhone 8/ iPhone X, and they lapped up Apple managements comments about services revenue doubling over the next four years.

Meanwhile, short interest in Apple stock rises along with the share price as bears bide their time and try to wait out the growing pain.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The space agency used the Polar Satellite Launch Vehicle (PSLV) for the launch. It carried a 714 kilogram main satellite for earth observation and 103 smaller "nano satellites" which weighed a combined 664 kilograms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These 8 Hilarious Valentines Day Messages by Celebrities Prove That They Are Just Like the Rest of Us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana Stocks: Aphria Stock Is on the Verge of a Breakout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Valentines day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Monday, Elon Musk launched his companys electric vehicles in the United Arab Emirates. This market expansion is good for Tesla Inc and TSLA stock as the Middle East is expected to be a big market for the companys luxury cars and sport-utility vehicles. The company will soon accept online orders for its Model S sedan and Model X SUV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Is Best Performing Dow Stock of 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://finance.yahoo.com/news/apple-best-performing-dow-stock-135402470.html

Shares of Apple Inc. (AAPL) posted a new 52-week high on Friday that is just pennies short of its all-time high posted two years ago. A strong first fiscal quarter earnings report and speculation about the next round of products are driving the stock higher.

Even CEO Tim Cook's outspoken comments on President Trump's travel ban have not been enough to chill investors' enthusiasm for the stock. Shares have added about $16 to date in 2017, an increase of 14.07%.

In Apples most recent quarter, sales of its core products did well. Cook said:

We're thrilled to report that our holiday quarter results generated Apple's highest quarterly revenue ever, and broke multiple records along the way. We sold more iPhones than ever before and set all-time revenue records for iPhone, Services, Mac and Apple Watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Augmented Reality to Shape the Future of Apple Stock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock/augmented-reality-shape-future-apple-stock/

Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) stock has made a strong comeback and there is renewed investor optimism on the record number of iPhone units shipped in the December 2016 quarter. Moreover, the continuous rumors and news surrounding the iPhone 8, to be launched this September, is keeping AAPL stock in the limelight.  
Investors are also excited by the potential of the companys Services business, which grew 18% to $7.2 billion in the quarter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicky Minaj Hot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dads Brilliant Business Plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scene: A conversation with my friends father, who knows I do Web design.

Father: I have a business idea. How hard is it to make a Facebook?

Me: Oh, very easy.

Friend: He doesnt mean to make a Facebook profile. He means to remake all of Facebook.

Me: Oh. Very hard.

Father: Oh, OK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What My Girlfriend Thought, First four Dates: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Nice shirt.

2. Wow. A second nice shirt.

3. OK, first shirt again.

4. He has two shirts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nvidia Corporation (NVDA) Should Clobber Q4 Earnings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMD Stock Chart Implies MUCH Higher Prices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lady Gaga   Other Top Female Artists Are Proving That Perfection Isn't Important Anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cute kitten </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Snapchat IPO Is Great for Alphabet Inc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spotify IPO in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as investors may want to see more huge tech IPOs hit the markets in 2017, those bullish on the Spotify IPO will more than likely have to wait until 2018, according to the most recent reports.
TechCrunch reported that multiple insider sources are saying that despite the companys initial plan to make Spotify stock available to the public in 2017, the streaming service is now looking towards 2018 to file. 
[Read More](http://www.profitconfidential.com/ipo/spotify-ipo-2017-trouble/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stocks close mixed as banks notch 3-day losing streak; oil rises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No big changes to the reflation trade	No big changes to the reflation trade  
23 Hours Ago | 03:11
U.S. equities closed mixed Wednesday as financials led decliners, while oil rebounded following the release of key supply data.

The Dow Jones industrial average fell about 35 points, with Goldman Sachs contributing the most losses. Apple, another Dow component, closed near its all-time high. The index had fallen about 75 points at session lows.

The S P 500 dropped ended just above breakeven, with real estate outperforming and financials falling 0.75 percent. The Nasdaq composite closed 0.15 percent higher at a record.
[Read More](http://www.cnbc.com/2017/02/08/us-markets.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street stocks mark time ahead of Twitter results </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U.S. stock futures pointed to a quiet open to trading Thursday, but earnings from closely-watched companies such as Twitter Inc. and Coca-Cola Co. could provide impetus for investors.

Dow Jones Industrial Average futures YMH7, +0.18%  were flat at 20,002, while S P 500 index futures ESH7, +0.20%  rose 0.3 point to 2,290.50, and Nasdaq-100 futures NQH7, +0.14%  added 1.25 points to 5,192.50.

U.S. stocks finished mixed on Wednesday, a session marked by the second-straight closing record for the Nasdaq Composite Index COMP, +0.15% , which closed up 0.2% at 5,682.45. The Dow industrials DJIA, -0.18%  closed down 0.2% to 20,054.34, while the S P 500 index SPX, +0.07%  edged up 1.59 points to 2,294.67. 
[Read More](http://www.marketwatch.com/story/wall-street-stocks-mark-time-ahead-of-twitter-results-2017-02-09) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justin Bieber and Hailey Baldwin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jennifer Lopez </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many people don't know, how much money I spend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The WEED Stock Chart Points to Higher Prices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Hatch, 'Battlestar Galactica' Star, Dies at 71 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexy dance Move </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What President-elect Trump means for the stock, bond, other markets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is the nations president-elect. Wall Street investors have let that stunning outcome of the U.S. race for the highest seat in the land wash over it for all of about two seconds before wagering broadly that there may still be money to be made. Stock markets have mostly soared, with the Dow Jones Industrial Average DJIA, -0.03%  touching record closes and the S P 500 SPX, +0.06%  and the Nasdaq Composite Index COMP, -0.11%  touching their own recently.

Warren Buffett purchased $12 billion of stock since Trump election victory

Billionaire investor Warren Buffett revealed he beefed up his stock portfolio at Berkshire Hathaway after Donald Trump's election win.
In an interview with talk show host Charlie Rose that aired Friday, Buffett said, "We've, net, bought $12 billion of common stocks since the election."

Buffett added it was "in large part" his decision.

The Omaha, Nebraska-based conglomerate owned $102.5 billion of equities as of Sept. 30, excluding its stake in Kraft Heinz, according to a regulatory filing.

Stocks and Treasury yields jumped in the wake of Trump's victory, amid the prospects for looser regulations in certain sectors, lower tax rates and fiscal stimulus. The rally has waned recently as investors evaluated the president's executive order that barred entry of certain nationals into the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stardew Valley Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the minimum amount of money to buy a stock? Where and how? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short answer: $5.

Better answer: $500, and only AFTER you have built up your emergency savings.
"We really encourage people to have six months of savings first," says Yvette Butler, president of Capital One Investing. Once you have a few thousand in savings, then you can start investing.
The goal of investing is to make your money grow faster than it would in a typical bank account (especially since savings accounts barely spit out a little more than 0% interest now). But investing is risky. You can lose money, especially in the "short run."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [meta]Everything You Need to Know About the Snapchat IPO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> kim kardashian lip lock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven threats of Email </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any IT department looking for potential vulnerabilities would do well to start with the following seven threats:

Mobile malware
Device loss or theft
Unencrypted email
Open Wi-Fi
Faulty firewalls
Broken web filters
Ignoring Macs
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Helped Beyonc Make Her Pregnancy the Best-Kept Secret of 2017? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samsung's Galaxy Tab S3 Tablet Leaks With A Curved Display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 11:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does the housing market affect the stock market? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Stock Market and Housing**
	
The housing and stock markets are interconnected in multiple ways. Major home builders shares are traded in the stock market. Home improvement companies tied to home building also trade on the stock exchange. The housing sector dips deep into the economy as furniture manufacturers, plumbers, electricians, landscapers and more are all dependent on housing. Housing starts and the stock market are both leading indicators of economic activity.

**Consider the three areas below:**

1. Credit
2. Consumer Behavior
3. Competition

**Good**
The best thing that a moderate market dive could do for real estate is keep the Federal Reserve from raising interest rates on mortgages.

**Bad**
Low inventory and a healthy amount of buyers have created a sellers market in the U.S. real estate market for the past 6 months to a year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicki Minaj </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Pics from Beyonce's Pregnancy Photoshoot! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Stocks to Watch Tuesday: Nextera Energy Partners LP (NEP), GoPro Inc. (GPRO), Fitbit Inc. (FIT) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The top stocks to watch today (Tuesday) include energy company Nextera Energy Partners LP (NYSE: NEP), wearable camera company GoPro Inc. (Nasdaq: GPRO), and fitness device maker Fitbit Inc. (NYSE: FIT).

There's a lot of U.S. economic data reports being released today, including Case-Shiller home prices, Chicago PMI, and consumer confidence.

Economic data along with earnings reports are going to be the cause of market moves today. There will be at least six reports before trading begins today, along with releases after the closing bell.
[Read More](https://moneymorning.com/2017/01/31/top-stocks-to-watch-tuesday-nextera-energy-partners-lp-nep-gopro-inc-gpro-fitbit-inc-fit/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Stock Surges After Strong Earnings Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weightlifting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dollar struggles after worst start to year in decades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dollar recovered a little ground on Wednesday after recording its worst start to the year in three decades on concerns the United States was poised to ditch its two-decade-old "strong dollar" policy.

The greenback skidded 2.6 percent against a basket of major peers .DXY in January, its worst showing since 1987. It fell first on worries over signs of protectionism from U.S. President Donald Trump and then on mounting unease that the new administration is set on talking down the currency.

A senior trade adviser to the president, Peter Navarro, said on Tuesday that the euro was "grossly undervalued", sending the single currency soaring above $1.08 for the first time since early December EUR= and knocking the dollar index down almost 1 percent to a seven-week low.
[Read More](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-global-forex-idUSKBN15G30D?il=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Resident Evil 7 UPDATE: Why chart-topping launch isn't all it's CRACKED up to be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resident Evil 7 dethrones GTA 5 from the top of the UK all-format games chart, racking up nearly three quarters of its sales on PS4.

But it might not be all it's cracked up to be, because as UKIE points out, it's only the third best opening week for the Resident Evil series, behind Resident Evil 5 in number one.

"Resident Evil 5 launched on 360/PS3 in week 11, 2009 and the highpoint was reached because this was also the first time the franchise launched on a Microsoft platform," the latest UKIE press release explains.
Original source:http://www.express.co.uk/entertainment/gaming/760697/Resident-Evil-7-UPDATE-top-chart-sales-Resident-Evil-6-sales </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May futures will surely for android  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are paying for Super Mario Run in surprising numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walmart Reduces Free 2-Day Shipping Requirements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 15:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Are the Best Ecommerce Stocks to Buy in 2017? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is made up of different sectors, some of which are more promising than others.
For instance, online retail stocks are on the verge of exploding, meaning that growth-hungry investors should keep a close eye on the best ecommerce stocksthey could provide triple-digits gains in 2017.Buffett peeks under the hood, kicks the tires, and looks at the sticker price of every company. We have followed from his example and compiled an ecommerce stocks list. Some names on our list are instantly recognizable, while others are lesser known. However, there is one thing that connects them all: massive upside potential.
[Read More](http://www.profitconfidential.com/stocks/best-ecommerce-stocks-buy-2017/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Selena Gomez Hinting Dating Status With The Weeknd On Instagram? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Is Dead, Long Live Google </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the close of trading last night, Google reported results for its quarter that ended in December came in well ahead of revenue estimates, but "missed" on the bottom-line. The company reported revenues of  $26.1 billion, up 22% year on year or 24% on a constant currency basis. Revenues of $26.04 billion beat consensus of $25.2 billion by roughly $840 million. However, Street consensus for earnings for Q4:16 was $9.67 per share and Google reported $9.36 per share.

[Read More](http://www.forbes.com/sites/jaysomaney/2017/01/27/google-is-dead-long-live-google/#7dac43074cd8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VW ex-CEO Martin Winterkorn in fraud probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana Stocks: CARA Therapeutics Stock Is Set to Soar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 15:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puppy playing a game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seagate Technology STX +14.03% reported earnings after the bell that came in ahead of Wall Street expectations and also guided well higher for the current quarter, sending its stock higher by almost 14% in post-market-trading activity.Seagate remains cheap, trading at under 10 times is fiscal year 2017 consensus analyst estimates. Thats despite impressive earnings growth at the moment: those same analysts are projecting a 32% increase in adjusted second-quarter earnings year-over-year. In the first quarter, STX almost doubled earnings, with non-GAAP EPS of 99 cents, up 83% over the prior-year 54 cents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Future: Working cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venus Williams to face sister Serena in Grand Slam final for first time since 2009 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actor Shia LaBeouf arrested at anti-Trump installation in Queens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xiaomi is skipping Mobile World Congress entirely this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here Is the Complete List of 2017 Oscar Nominations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Qualcomm Stock: The Sharks Are Circling Around QUALCOMM, Inc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oscar nominations 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stock Tracker: Looking at the Numbers for GoPro, Inc. (NASDAQ:GPRO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Investors might be looking to check on Free Cash Flow metrics for GoPro, Inc. (NASDAQ:GPRO). Free cash flow represents the amount of cash that a company has generated for shareholders after paying off expenses and investing in growth. FCF may be a very useful way to help measure the financial health of a specific company. At the time of writing, GoPro, Inc. (NASDAQ:GPRO) has an FCF quality score of 0.516821.

Original Source:http://marionbusinessdaily.com/stock-tracker-looking-at-the-numbers-for-gopro-inc-nasdaqgpro/76696/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats Wrong with Barron Trump? Donald Trumps Youngest Son Looks Sleepy   Confused </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spoilers: The secrets behind M. Night Shyamalan's surprise 'Split' ending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Stock (TSLA): Tesla Motors Inc Just Won a Big Lawsuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TSLA stock dropped below $200.00 as investors priced in effects from a horrific car accidentthey believed this accident could be the downfall of Tesla stock. Heres what happened.Tesla was completely cleared of any charges. Apparently, Elon Musk wasnt exaggerating; they really had done enough due diligence.
Full Article:http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock/tesla-stock-tsla-tesla-motors-inc-just-won-big-lawsuit/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Android Circuit: Samsung Reveals Galaxy S8, New Nokia Sells Out, Deciding On The S8 Launch Date </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix, Inc. (NASDAQ:NFLX) Quarterly EPS Set At $0.425 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zacks is famed for its evaluations that it carries out to get a price target of the establishments listed on the exchange. The firms take the financial report views and stock targets from top brokerages. The poll displayed that Netflix, Inc. (NASDAQ:NFLX) can post EPS of $0.425 in the next quarter. The numbers can be posted nearby 2017-04-17.

Full Article:http://www.thestockobserver.com/stocks/netflix-inc-nasdaqnflx-quarterly-eps-set-at-0-425/26746/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Denies Pardon Request for Former Alabama Governor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Soros Portfolio: 5 Top George Soros Stocks in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **George Soros Stocks**
George Soros is in the limelight to begin 2017 and it has little do with George Soross net worth of $24.9 billion, or his ranking on the Forbes list. The media is having a frenzy with the $1.0 billion in losses that were incurred in the Soros Fund Management LLC holdings after Donald Trump surprised the world and won the presidential election.
Original source:http://www.profitconfidential.com/stocks/george-soros-portfolio-5-top-george-soros-stocks-2017/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix, Inc.: NFLX Stock Soaring on Earnings Was No Surprise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NFL Says Lady Gaga Not Banned From Talking Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 People's Choice Awards winners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gigamon Inc: The GIMO Stock Chart Foresaw This Sell-Off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **GIMO Stock: Getting Crushed**
After the close of trading on January 17, 2017, Gigamon Inc (NYSE:GIMO) warned that its fourth-quarter results, to be released on February 2, are going to fall short of expectations. This shortfall is going to affect both the top and bottom lines, and as a result, both were guided lower. This shocking news caught investors off guard, and to show their displeasure, they sent Gigamon stock spiraling lower by 22.26% in after-hours trading.

First Publisher:http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock/gigamon-inc-gimo-stock-chart-foresaw-selloff/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gmail customers targeted in new phishing attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Trump tweet activates thousands of computer algorithms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stocks, dollar steady after Trump-led dip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stock markets steadied and the dollar recovered some ground on Wednesday after unease over how U.S. policy will develop under Donald Trump's presidency drove the currency to its weakest since early December.

Traders in Asia said shares were helped by hopes that the concern about a stronger dollar expressed by the U.S. President-elect at the weekend would benefit emerging markets where companies have borrowed heavily in dollars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely they will fix all the issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WWE Monday Night RAW Results - Brock Lesnar Returns, Six-Man Main Event, Title Match, More </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to our WrestlingINC.com Live WWE RAW Viewing Party. We will be providing live ongoing coverage of tonight's RAW, while you all can chime in with your thoughts throughout the show.Reigns talk about how he's winning the WWE Universal Title at the Royal Rumble and going on to main event WrestleMania 33 again. Reigns states that no one can beat him one-on-one right now. 
First published On http://www.wrestlinginc.com/wi/news/2017/0116/621271/wwe-monday-night-raw-live-results/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Corporation: Data Privacy Could Send MSFT Stock Soaring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Important Branding for Microsoft Stock (MSFT)**
Microsoft Corporation (NASDAQ:MSFT) is updating its Windows 10 software to put a greater focus on data privacy, something which it hopes will become the companys trademark. These changes are more than cosmeticthey could spark a bullish run on Microsoft stock (MSFT stock).

First publish On:http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock/microsoft-corporation-data-privacy-send-msft-stock-soaring/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Great Dividend Growth Stocks That Simply Print Money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aaron Rodgers' father confirms son is estranged from family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civil War set up that Black Panther was a stone-chilly rebel from the country of Wakanda. Be that as it may, what with all the superhero-on-superhero dramatization, it didn't have much time to demonstrate to us how he came to be the person he is today. That occupation will fall on the Black Panther solo film being coordinated by Ryan Coogler. What's more, one bit of that astound, clearly, lies in 1990s California. Another report shows Black Panther will streak back to T'Challa's developmental years, when he was going to class in America. Take in more about what we can expect beneath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Wiki:**
James Reiher Snuka[a] (born James Wiley Smith; May 18, 1943  January 15, 2017), better known by the ring name Jimmy "Superfly" Snuka, was a Fijian professional wrestler and actor.

Snuka wrestled for several promotions from the 1970s to 2010s. He was best known for his time in the World Wrestling Federation (WWF, now WWE) in the early to mid-1980s and was credited with introducing the high-flying style of wrestling to the WWF.He was inducted into the WWF Hall of Fame in 1996. Snuka was the first WrestleMania opponent of The Undertaker (at the seventh annual event), this being the first match in The Undertaker's undefeated WrestleMania streak. Snuka was the inaugural ECW Heavyweight Champion (a title he held twice) in Eastern Championship Wrestling (later Extreme Championship Wrestling). His children, Jimmy Reiher, Jr. and Tamina Snuka, are also wrestlers.

**Cause of death:**Stomach cancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's Xi Jinping Defends Globalization at Davos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chinese President Xi Jinping offered a full-throated defense of economic globalization at a time of global uncertainty fueled by Britains decision to leave the European Union and the U.S. election victory of Donald Trump .

Some people blame economic globalization for the chaos in our world, Mr. Xi said in a speech at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland. Mr. Xi countered the notion, saying that neither the refugee crisis nor the international financial crisis were the product of such globalization. In particular, he said, the financial crisis was the consequence of excessive profit chasing and the grave failure of financial regulation.

First Published On:http://www.wsj.com/articles/chinas-xi-jinping-defends-globalization-1484654899 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Europe Is Worried About Donald Trump's Latest Remarks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana Stocks: Second Week Of 2017 At 9.5% To 12.9% Returns From The January Effect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tweed Farms is the largest marijuana-producing greenhouse in the world, certainly legally that weve ever come across, with over 350,000 square feet of licensed cannabis production space. The scale and the passive processes allow the Farm to produce environmentally friendly cannabis at extremely competitive cost per gram. The Farm combines traditional and state-of-the art agricultural techniques, using the natural power of the sun and recycled rainwater to nurture genetically identical plants produced in the on-site tissue culture propagation lab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lindsie Chrisley Wiki: Everything You Need to Know about Todd Chrisleys Daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JPMorgan Profit Rises as Bond-Trading Revenue Beats Estimates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earnings benefited from better credit quality among U.S. consumers and corporations, allowing the bank to pull about $400 million from bad-loan reserves in the mortgage, energy and metals businesses, New York-based JPMorgan said Friday in a statement. Fixed-income trading also contributed to the gains. Chief Executive Officer Jamie Dimon, 60, said last month that bond and stock trading volume was much better after the U.S. election.
Full Article:https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2017-01-13/jpmorgan-profit-rises-as-bond-trading-revenue-beats-estimates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AAPL Stock: Peter Thiel Delivers a Blunt Reality Check to Apple Inc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **4 Top Stocks in the Growing Medical Marijuana Industry**

1. AbbVie (ABBV)
2. Cara Therapeutics (CARA)
3. GW Pharmaceuticals  (GWPH)
4. Insys Therapeutics (INSY)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canopy Growth Corp: CGC Stock Is Now Set to Surge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I continue to believe that the electricity powering this turntable is the speculation surrounding the legalization of marijuana. Last year, the government promised the legal framework behind legalized marijuana and the recreational market that will follow. 2017 is now here, and that announcement from the government is now only months away.

Original Source:http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock/canopy-growth-corp-cgc-stock-now-set-surge/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitcoin slides as China's central bank launches checks on exchanges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China's central bank launched spot checks on leading bitcoin exchanges in Beijing and Shanghai, ratcheting up pressure on potential capital outflows and knocking the price of the cryptocurrency down more than 12 percent against the dollar.

The People's Bank of China (PBOC) said its probe of bitcoin exchanges BTCC, Huobi and OKCoin was to look into a range of possible rule violations, including market manipulation, money laundering and unauthorized financing. It did not say if any violations had been found.

Chinese authorities have stepped up efforts to stem capital outflows and relieve pressure on the yuan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you have Verizon or AT T, you may soon be paying more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon VZ, +0.95%   has increased the price it charges subscribers to upgrade to a new device or add a phone to a new line. AT T T, -0.51%   is nudging up the price of its unlimited data plans, which are no longer available but are still held by certain longstanding customers.

Verizon increased its upgrade fee from $20 to $30 as of Jan. 5. This fee is paid whenever you buy a new phone from the carrier, at the full retail price or through one of Verizons device payment programs. Verizon also upped its activation fee, for adding a phone to a new line, to $30.

Original Link:http://www.marketwatch.com/story/if-you-have-verizon-or-att-you-may-soon-be-paying-more-2017-01-10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coen brothers to make first TV series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo Switch Accessories Leak Suggests Zelda Is a Launch Title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The announcement furthers Alibabas foray into physical stores and underlines a push by Alibaba Executive Chairman Jack Ma to deepen links between the retailers online operations, brick-and-mortar stores, and logistics. Alibaba, which runs popular shopping websites Taobao and Tmall, also has a stake in Suning Commerce Group Ltd. 002024, +1.73%  , a large Chinese electronics physical retail chain. Alibaba said more Chinese are choosing to shop online through their mobile phones, providing an opportunity for physical stores to reach mobile shoppers on their devices via location services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ready to invest? $NVDA is definitely worth checking out today!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Celebrate the iPhone's 10th birthday by watching the gleeful original announcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for providing the information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
