<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3700</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Centrist democrats don't learn.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carter was a center right neoliberal FFS.  What the fuck are you talking about?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Hillary win?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democratic party primaries are fucking useless at picking winners. 

Gore, Kerry, Clinton.  Lose, lose, lose.  Centrism does not win national elections anymore.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carter, Gore, Kerry, Clinton.  

Centrism is sure as fuck not the way forward.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White men vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither was Hillary.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tweet, email, and comment on the AARP site supporting Medicare for All.    

Once the pensioners got on board with NHS in the UK it was unstoppable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Single payer is over 50% support in the House for any party for the first time in US history, so we'll see if Sanders can get 50% of the Democrats in the Senate.  I agree, it is time for Sanders to put up or shut up.   

Will you still call him weak if he helps pull off Single Payer?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got more angry at every Democrat voting to exempt themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you support Gorsuch?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why?  Single payer is inevitable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, Centrist Democrats are like Blairites before the Tories swung into power, they are as unpopular or more unpopular than the conservatives, but somehow that is good.  

Sanders is popular, Pelosi and Clinton are not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The electoral college really is the foundational problem of the Republic.  Why should the Dakotas have more say than California?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What we need is a single GOP congresscritter to support single payer.  That is how it started in Canada.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem stems from the electoral college giving outsized power to rural states.  Electoral college needs to go.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K Falls has fallen on hard times since the loss of the lumber unions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will if you are male, erectile dysfunction and male pattern baldness are covered, pregnancy and heavy periods are not.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summers are hot, summers lead to riots during unpopular presidents, ask Nixon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans only count as 1/10th of a person.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry erectile dysfunction and male pattern baldness are still covered.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read a book.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it is not, it one of the most difficult citizenships to get in the world. 

Easier to go to Canada.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Northeast Cali is pretty much Idaho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2017 GOP's alignment is Ignorant Evil.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erectile dysfunction is covered though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Australia has better healthcare than U.S. (they have universal health care) Watch the reaction from @BernieSanders to @chrislhayes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 bucks it is run by 30-something libertarian manchildren.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 45k a year will die if this passes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder who has been turned?  I bet Jared and Ivanka would fold like a cheap rug on Donny Boy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 70+ convictions in Watergate, right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that America is as polarized electorally today as it was right before the Civil War.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less than 15%.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rape, domestic violence, heavy periods, and pregnancy are pre-existing conditions in this bill.  Why does the GOP hate women so much?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is probably drinking Bud Light at the White House as we speak.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 years ago I would've agreed with you. The modern GOP is not future-oriented.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, yes they can it is parliamentary rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that, but the linked comic believes that so I commented on it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taxes redistribute wealth and pay for public roads, did you read the linked comic?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of today, do you really trust the GOP to hold to that if it looks like the AHCA will fail again?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not pointless.  The GOP Senate only has a two vote majority, even so Trump might try to ram this through with 50+Pence.  

Don't underestimate the cruelness of the GOP.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you believe in public roads you are a socialist according to this comic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City, county making good progress on reducing carbon emissions, in contrast to nation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firefighters do controlled burns here in Oregon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let Trump try to come to Portland.  There will be unending riots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anarchism and Communism both reject political pluralism so those of us who believe in an open and free society should reject them.  

Same with Libertarianism, these manchild philosophies reject the concept of a mature civil society with competing worldviews.  Fuck em.  Democracy is a nice thing, we should take care of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For good fucking reason, Oregon itself is flammable.  A major forest fire started by arson could kill 100's.  That may not have happened in our lifetimes, but it sure as fuck did in the past, and if rural counties keep skimping on their firefighting duties, it will happen again.     

That is why the cigarette butt littering fines on highways are so high here as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a human wheel too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans for partisan reasons have been openly tolerating treason since Iran Contra. Treason is good if it helps their ideology or gets them elected.  Everything is fair if it benefits them.  

FFS, some of the same Republican Senators are still in the Senate that helped old Ronnie Raygun escape impeachment, and they'll do the same for Donald Trump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't have stopped at Berlin, should've kept on to Moscow.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patton was right.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No conjugal visits in federal prison.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thank you Clinton supporters for President Trump.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you are in the minority then, Sanders has 20 points of favorability on Clinton.  

How does it feel to be a minority?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has power, and Clinton is a grandma.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like a common bigot, not even worth my time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is still Senator.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanders won his election, take notes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton helped elect Trump.  It is shameful she dares to show her face in public.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton is human garbage.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton failed twice.  Do you think she is going to win in 2020?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton is garbage.  She is the result of New York and DC elites deluding themselves that they were the smartest bestest people in the country and anyone they back would win.  

Idiots.  I can't wait until the inevitable swing away from the NorthEast as a power center and towards the West Coast as demographics change.  Honest progressives  conniving corporatists.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donny has been taking a drug called Propecia for 30+ years which has side effects like mental fog, depression, suicidal ideation, anxiety, panic attacks, Peyronie's disease, penile shrinkage, gynecomastia, muscle atrophy, cognitive impairment, insomnia, severely dry skin and tinnitus.

Why?  Because it is for hair loss and Trump would rather be vain than sane.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Civil Rights bill was talked about before the Civil War, guess who was against it?  

Rural states retard progress.  There is no reason to give them more political power than populous urban states.  None.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree, 99% of the species that once existed on this planet are gone.  Clinton is a paleodemocrat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So?  I still don't give a fuck what the Dakotas think about anything.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if they remove the cloture rule.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait till the AIs drive our cars for us.  I just hope I don't live long enough to see them putting us into zoos for the universe's safety.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should strike her name from history like the Romans did when their leaders fell.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A majoritarian Senate is wholly undemocratic as there are 30 rural states that will always lean conservative.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said she nearly ran down pedestrians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a pastry chef who worked in a ski resort town working and dealt with these richie rich kids.  It wasn't abnormal for a bunch of 20-something trust funders to order $200 in just cookies for a ski weekend, and then not tip the delivery driver.  $200 was min for delivery.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drove so much better with a pure analog dashboard and a radio knob, not even a tape player.  

Us humans aren't properly made for the pace and distractions of this digital world, we need to become cyborgs or some shit.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been a Green since Bill Clinton signed DOMA and took my rights away.  I won't be in any party that allows bigots like Bill Clinton or Donald Trump.  

Don't dare call me a Democrat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Holocaust started with mentally/physically-disabled patients.  [Aktion T-4.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aktion_T4)  Why?  Because they were pretty much defenseless.  

That is what they are doing, going after the weak in society because a goodly portion of them think the disabled as less than human.  They believe that folks' disabilities reflect upon them morally, that folks' are responsible for their own predicaments.  Same sort of poor moral reasoning leads them to a Dickensian hating of the poor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pain and suffering caused was priceless to those who vote on hating *moochers*, immigrants, and other "others" instead of working seriously on the social, economic, and international issues of the day.  

Conservatism has turned from questioning the pace of social change to a merciless counter revolution against hard fought and won civil rights.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if you are a Trump voter that might explain your failing grades.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have zero tolerance for dangerous drivers after losing my best friend to a texter.  

They really need to treat distracted driving like a DUI.  Two or three and you get jail.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call the DMV on her.  I got my dad's license taken away because he wouldn't go to the doctor for his cataracts because he was afraid of losing his license.  He hit cars on his street and drove over an unoccupied Big Wheel the week I called the DMV.  

If your mom is a danger to others, you need to do the right thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop wasting my fucking time with braindead talking points.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one cares about your opinion.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is an old and stupid right wing talking point that has no basis in fucking reality. 

50% of min wage earners are over 35.  Please don't comment on things you know nothing about, you wasted my time.      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubtful, most of that sort of stuff is in-house.  Infosys is contracted to do basic Windows support for corporations like Bank of America.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't change the fact that no one can have a family on these jobs that Trump is bringing back.  

Does Trump hate children unless they are pissing in his mouth?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is doing 40 years in a fucking call center in the United States.  Median pay for phone tech support is under 15/hour in most cities.  That is poverty.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are shit jobs not careers.  Once Trump is gone they'll fire everyone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had only 4 points more favorability than Trump.  Now she has lower favorables than Trump.  You guys going to see if Hillary can lose twice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton would've made a fine president in 2008, not in 2016.  There was too much baggage, even if it wasn't legit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democrat's political power only exists so long as the demonstrations, phone calls, and bad polling for Trump and his policies continue.  

Bush was doing shitty in polls and then he shot up after 9/11 and the first few years of the Afghan/Iraq wars.  Trump really, really, really wants to go to war and most conservatives, some centrists, and the rare progressive will rally around any president during times of war.  Mindless patriotism while America engages in a prolonged conflict with North Korea, Iran, Syria, Afghanistan, etc could see Trump get 8 years, just like Bush.  That is if we aren't dealing with LARPing Fallout on the West Coast.  

     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the one who is ignorant.  Please stop wasting people's time with your comments, thanks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you got nothing, just like most centrists.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so since 1980 the festering assholes known as Democratic centrists lost more than half of the presidential contests and they still think they are the smartest person in the room?  

Pathetic.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so Gore, Kerry, and Clinton won?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superdelegates are an undemocratic abortion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roosevelt, Truman, Kennedy, and Johnson weren't even nominated by the same primary process.  What are you talking about? 

The problem started when superdelegates came about, the party ran to the center and prevented grass roots popular candidates from winning primaries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, Senate?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People can't just be expected to vote for terrible candidates because they have a D next to their name.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America is a ruralarchy where citizens in Wyoming have 60x the electoral power of citizens of California.  

If we had a national popular vote like in other countries, the GOP would stand no chance.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democratic primaries are useless, they keep picking losers.  

Gore, Kerry, Clinton.  Lose, Lose, Lose.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you just regurgitate talking points all day or do you want to make a citation champ?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a reason for that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile in reality, 1/4 teachers make under 40k a year.  

https://www.bls.gov/oes/current/oes252021.htm

You are talking about the top 5% of teachers in the country,  FFS stop being disingenuous.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red States all look in the same to me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahhaah, wut   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I value my kidneys thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as it is fresh.  Make sure to try a pint before you buy a growler.  

Old root beer will have a flat metallic taste.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> North Carolina is a pretty shitty state, I wouldn't ever go there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking nonsense.  If teaching gigs were so wonderous there would not be a nationwide shortage.  

Do you like working 12 hour days and buying your own office supplies?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck should the rest of country be governed by rural red states?  

I live in Oregon, we treat our rural folks right and they still vote Republican.  We build tuition-free community colleges for them and they whine they have to pay local taxes to maintain them.  There is no winning with these folks.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are advocating starving people, get help, you are not a normal human being.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His supporters are too subliterate to have heard of WaPo.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYT subs are going down now that they hired a climate science denier.  

Watch CNN fuck up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll hold a rally in Moscow.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
