<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9440</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freaking called it months ago.  It was almost guaranteed that Elektra and Punisher would be in this.  Now we got a Elektra confirmation.  Now all that's left is Frank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your point of trying to bait me into answering your loaded question?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its an actual laptop?  The screen doesn't detach?  No Pen?  Why is this labeled Surface when it doesn't feature any of the defining traits of the surface?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they hid the Joker.  Nobody knew going in that he was in it.  His big reveal was so damn amazing.  I remember my first playthrough I said "Oh shit!" when he showed up.  If they didn't connect the Batmobile to every aspect of the gameplay it would have been the best Batman game of all time.  As it stands I think City still is the best of the three. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going off of what the other guy said.  I didn't know they were already filmed.  I just assumed Netflix did a similar deal to what Charlie Sheen had on Anger Management.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just want to say I fully support the gay relationship on Supergirl and kinda hope they double down with Kara and Luthor.  Every time those two are together they put off a serious vibe.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie did portray the FBI allowing Bulger to do what he wanted.  It was literally what 'Black Mass' was about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about this FOX.  Make an Office style comedy about a group of attractive women working in a lingerie shop at a mall.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love this moment from Arkham Knight [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im so excited for the rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't know.  I was just going off of what that other guy said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He played Limehouse on Justified.  He was [awesome](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DsOG0ZVNftE) in that role.  He shows up the first time on the third season and fit in that world so well you barely even notice its his first episode.  Thats talent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same about Louis CK.  I loved his old specials before his TV show.  Now it kinda feels lazy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait?  Netflix made him do the work before they paid him?  I guess he'll never live down that "Running to Africa" thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trevor : Moses, I swear we past that same sand dune for the last 39 Years.  
Moses : FINE!  You lead us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got ripped for it.  The dude put in the work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have a real easy life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please be Max Payne 3 BC!  
Please be Max Payne 3 BC!  
Please be Max Payne 3 BC!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but Beyonce told me too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't look bad on TV.  Its probally the lighting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many men? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a one disc rule.  I put a disc in my console and that's the game I play.  It doesn't come out until I beat it or I give up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right?  Remember the wonderful heartwarming story of Anne Frank? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im very excited for Ghost~~bust~~e~~rs~~  d.  Big fan of Scott and Robinson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Problem.  FYI, Legion isn't for everyone.  It's like if David Lynch made an X-Men show.  
  
Edit : [Trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4SZ3rMMYBLY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legion was set in the X universe, but for some reason that link was removed before the pilot aired.  (Most likely because Stewart and McAvoy aren't contractually obligated to appear on TV.) Now FX is doing a second show that is hardcore set in the universe.  It's being ran by Matt Nix (Burn Notice / The Good Guys) and stars Stephen Moyer (True Blood) and Amy Acker (Angel, Dollhouse, PoI). The second show is titled "Gifted" its unclear if thats the production code or the title of the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a common misconception that confuses a lot of people.  FOX owns X-Men and Fantastic Four.  They use the Marvel logo because its a Marvel property but Disney has no input.  This is why Disney / Marvel started using a new logo, to make it clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X-Men is FOX.  They did make a fantastic Wolverine game years ago for Wolverine Origins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's co-worker will glow in the dark? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy a sheet of tollhouse ready to bake cookies for like $2 at the grocery store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its rumored to be Avengers, but it's not even remotely confirmed.  
  
Edit : [It is confirmed, my bad.](https://youtu.be/rq_V6WHSmQs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the reason EA forced them to release the game at least 6 months early.  This is exactly what im saying and being downvoted for.  PEOPLE LIKE YOU are the "built in fanbase" of a franchise.  You will go out and buy the X branded shit no matter what. You're the reason Apple keeps releasing the same iPhone every year.  You're the reason COD is still coming out.  You're the reason Madden isn't a subscription service. You're the reason Transformers has a fifth damn movie that isn't actually about the robots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and the elevators.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realise by starting that statement with "as a massive mass effect fan" it makes you a hypocrite, right?  Actual Mass Effect fans were disappointed with the game.  I know because I am one and there are millions of us.  You can go home and be happy that you own the new mass effect game all you want, but don't delude yourself into thinking its a good game or that it stands with the others.  It doesn't.  Anyone that played it for more than an hour knows it doesn't.  You're lying to yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're applying common sense to something that has none.  A board of executives doesn't think "we need to keep spending the same amount of money on brand X so we can keep up our sales"  they think "how much less can spend on brand X and keep our customers".  This applies to everything, and the more people that buy the product the less innovation and change there is. If you honestly don't know this, you're blind to the real world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ME1 started the franchise.  MEA killed it for most of their fans.  It's a stupid fucking opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Most people in hollywood are related to other people in Hollywood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats happening, BTW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CD has talent.  It's the same reason people freaked out over the news that they were doing a Marvel property. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part of this whole thing is that Square built a team just to make Tomb Raider games.  That never works because its already viable franchise.  They know they don't need to spend time on the game because it already has a built in fan base.  This is exactly why Mass Effect Andromeda sucked.  This is why IW hasn't made a good COD game since MW2.  Its why WB Montreal hasn't made a new Arkham game.  Its why Microsoft just came out and publicly apologised for Halo 5's story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ending was so great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Him narrating sex in that voice, I couldn't stop laughing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI : This is not being made by Crystal Dynamics.  They are working on an untitled Marvel property.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Sandman good?  I just read his American Gods because I was interested in the TV show.  I liked the book a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate playing the game because of the Warden Eternal. Everyone acted like he was normal, when hes never been mentioned in a game again.  Also they kept reusing the same cheap boss multiplied by a bigger number throughout the game.  
  
I also hated the coop team aspect of the story.  Master Chief was the most bad ass SOB in the galaxy.  The coop bs made him fall on one knee every time he "died" and scream 'I NEED HELP!  SOMEONE HELP ME!".  This wasn't in character.  [This guy](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yzXx8MiHV9g) doesn't ask for help, he is the help.  It just pissed me off everytime it happened.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw Sandcastle this weekend. Why is Henry Cavill so bad as Superman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get over it. He was excellent in Man from UNCLE. He was great in this movie as a SF dude from Texas. He was so good I didn't realise it was him until the end of the movie. Why is he so bad as Superman? None of his natural screen presence or charisma come through at all. Hes almost a chore to watch in these films.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you turn that bookshelf into a fireplace?  Are you a wizard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat did this with Frosty lids from Wendy's.  The first time she did it, I picked the lid up after she left the room.  She came back an hour later and started looking for it.  She spent 20 minutes sniffing the ground and furiously trying to dig up the carpet.  I felt so bad I opened a can of tuna for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching CSI means that outside is literally covered in semen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't impressive, clearly OP is the rock version of Magneato. He's Rockneato.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Scumbag Customer**   
  
My dog is a vegetarian you ass hole! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he pay for a dude to slap cookies out of your hand?  That's what Oprah did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ubisoft said they took the servers down because they heard your plans.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss that cue on the TV show.  Its a decent show, but the rap music just seems out of place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know that for sure.  Money comes with strings.  Its why Ryan Reyonlds turned down 200 Million budget for Deadpool 2.  He knows that if you get real money from someone, they demand things in return.  Sony bought their game.  They marketed their game.  They probally funded that lying ass CGI trailer.  They could have forced them to lie about features.  Most contracts today don't allow any party to disparage the product.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so hyped for that after Goldmember.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sequel is coming now that Will Forte has a hugely popular TV show on FOX.  He has more name recognition, which means a much better chance at box office profits.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone felt bad for Conan when he was booted off Tonight Show.  Dude made 42 Million dollars when that happened.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 27-point turn was pretty hard. I only got one or two takes on it. We were in a location that if the car hit the wall, it would be $100,000. I got told right before the take and I was like, "Oh shit."  
  
One of the most iconic scenes in the movie and he got two takes and stressed about costing the production 100k.  Damn.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The top half of Ryder's face still isn't moving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you removed the hair and painted his face green, he'd look just like Shrek.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last Saturday my nephew woke me up at 7am asking if we could play Halo 5.  So, being a good uncle, I got up and we started a game of Warzone.  10 seconds into the game he starts giving me shit because he was winning.  By round two I was two spots ahead of him.  By the end of the game I was #2 and he was dead last. I taunted him the entire game.  He claimed I was #2 because I got a wraith.  So the next game I didn't use a vehicle and hit #3 and he was still dead last. He didn't talk to me the rest of the weekend.  Played Halo by himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have to put a target on the picture?  Are kids so fucking stupid today that they don't know a tail goes on the butt?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat would physically fight me when I would put her over linoleum during a hairball. One time she jerked her head and launched the hairball over her shoulder and onto the carpet.  Then she gave me this fuck you look.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll get that next year.  Laurel will be on her own side like Catwoman.  Sometimes working with the heroes, sometimes against, sometimes she'll double cross them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially now that Forbes won't let you view their bullshit with adblock on.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just another useful tip.   
  
Call your cable company and ask for the new services sales rep, then ask that person for current deals.  You physically have to ask for the deals, they will not tell you on their own.  Nine times out of ten the show you want to watch has a current deal.  I never pay full price for cable channels.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're essentially this universe's Ewoks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did the same thing with firefly.  I bought the DVD and didn't watch the three unaired episodes.  It took me about three years before I've seen them all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You used oil for Drowners?  Were you super bad at fighting?  All you had to do was set them on fire and dodge a few times.  Not hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took 2 years to get in her pants?  Damn, son.  I would have gave up after the second week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have motion sickness and that issue made the game unplayable for me.  It triggered my motion sickness, after 5min I threw up.  Now that its fixed, I have almost beat GTA IV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still believe No Man's Sky was Sony's fault.  They took an indy game and literally opened their E3 conference with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The line about the nielsen ratings system is true, BTW.  At the wrap party for the season some of the yahoo execs told him how many people watched the premiere.  Community was watched on NBC by way more people than their .9 represented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate his magic balls.  I don't care if they are canon, so stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delusion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!  That will learn them.  Now start making good movies you fucking dumb pricks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Distant Past?  Bro.  Hes Barry's Time Remnant from Season 2.  Trapped in the Speed Force at the end of the season.  He saw all of time simultaneously. Past / Future / Present.  Hes mad at Barry because he willingly sacrificed himself to save the world, and then Barry went and made his sacrifice meaningless with Flashpoint.  
  
I even have proof.  [Clip 1](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mIKziwwlfow) [Clip 2](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0JQb_rBJbxo)  See?  They both "died" the same way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the trailer for Episode 8.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He didn't die.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VZSKN312BXw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [No](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VZSKN312BXw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When a bunch of out of touch asshats are in charge of making those decisions, it won't happen.  Sony looks at the money it costs before they do anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sucks so bad, but at least this means I get to watch Conan sans writers again.  That month or so was the best hes ever been.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its ok.  Its got some hot girls and the death scenes aren't bad.  I actually liked how that one dude died at the end of Season 1.  It was very damn clever.  The story is a little goofy and filled with plot armor, but its really great watching the main chick run away.  Shes got a fantastic booty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait so the chick with the ass and the chick with the tits won't be in it?  They are the only reason I watch this show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game was before the internet.  This doesn't make sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not far fetched at all.  All the links to that result accidently fell on some bullets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvel brought him on board as an executive producer specifically because of his involvement on Guardians.  They needed to make sure they were still portrayed correctly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #"Wild Baby Rocket"  
  
What the hell is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This exchange happened at my father's house this weekend.  
  
Me : I bet half of those cars in the background aren't there.  
Dad : Why would you say that?  
Me : These ads are fake and a CGI car would look more pristine than a real one.  
Dad : These ads aren't fake, it says "real people" when it starts.  
Me : Seriously?  Do you also think Fargo is a true story?  
Dad : FARGO ISN'T REAL?  
Me : Seriously?   
Dad : It says "based on a real story" when it starts.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fact That Will Date Me : I saw Masters of the Universe in theatres as a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was she on Friends, Seinfeld, Breaking Bad, Game of Thrones, Westworld, Always Sunny or Fargo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot secret nazi.  
  
Edit : uh?  [Whats with the downvotes?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4elj5tIfizY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can track your child all across the globe and there's nothing you can do to stop me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Prometheus hit them with a bomb last night, so clearly they are playing Battleship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stephen Amell said he had a meeting and put his foot down regarding the content and direction of the show.  I think hes the one who righted the ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its rumored that neither Emily or Stephen wanted to do that during Season 4.  I'm pretty sure its true considering Stephen put his foot down and stopped it this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starting to wonder why the BC games are coming so quickly now.  Did they finally get their software so good they don't need to tinker with it anymore?  Or is Microsoft devoting more resources to pad their numbers before E3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His Cameo on Big Bang Theory was so great.  Sheldon got a mint Wesley signed by the actor and Spiner comes from behind him, rips the package open and says "Hey remember when we used to make these things bang?" 
  
Edit : [Found the clip](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5XD9P8bhYSA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the first version of that song when he kept saying that he was dead.  The music in this show was great because they never had the good song first.  It always evolved and sold it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practically everything that has come out this year is 40 to 60% off in a matter of months.  It makes no financial sense to pre-order or pay full price for a game anymore.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he walks around his house with the hat and glasses and rings on?  Thats his normal?  I just thought he did that shit when he went outside.  That can't be comfortable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to give Sledgehammer the benefit of doubt.  They are talented and actually improved the engine when they made AW.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't be long if the rumors are true.  Apparently, Leto has been breaching his contract.  Doing and saying things that are in direct violation.  Hes trying to get out of it, become such a risk that the insurance can't pay for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLAY SUPERHOT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its called "Click Bait" and it should be banned from Reddit.  Every single day there's multiple articles with attention grabbing headlines that don't say anything.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wichita, KS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've done same day?  Is it expensive?  How long does it take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been asking for 40 Million a film.  Kinda makes me wonder what he got to do this.  I bet it was high.   
  
Also, he's so damn anal now about his shots now.   How is that going to gel with Blockbuster spectacle?  This is just weird and has me excited to see what it looks like.  This could be something special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kinda funny because Chris Rock is known for repeating himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awwwww....   I was hoping for Max Payne 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His Netflix movies aren't terrible. They are actually pretty entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who was the guy that hoped an emp took out Felicity's legs?  Because its fucking happening next week! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 2 Oliver wouldn't have stood there.  He'd put a fucking arrow in her leg.  I miss Season 2 Oliver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lyla : Hey guys I need help protecting a dude.  
Team Arrow : We'll Help!  
Lyla : Sorry he's in another castle completely unprotected and twelve miles away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll have to stop me?   
YOU'LL HAVE TO STOP ME?!?  
  
WHO THE FUCK DOES SHE THINKS SHES TALKING TOO?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's *currently* alive.  
  
Fixed that for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quentin just said Daughter.  So...  Sara doesn't exist anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9Gs in an elevator?  Excuse me?  
  
Edit : Most rollercoasters hit 4 to 6 Gs.  Rocket takeoff is under 3 Gs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people have same day delivery now.  Thats just bonkers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you were referring to image.  That story happened a few years ago before I was on reddit.  Wichita is filled with assholes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never asked him to move.  If you read the meme, he asked me and then moved on his own.  He was a good guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The* Psych?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some actresses don't do nudity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *cough* The Munsters *cough* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is the problem with Craps.  The table and the lingo is so confusing to people that they avoid the table.  It's actually a fun game with generally decent odds.  Much better than slots or blackjack.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it does, Sledgehammer Games actually has talent.  Which is something the COD franchise has been missing since MW2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are forcing her to do things without actual information on what she's really doing for them.  Thats shady as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its like Justin Beiber.  We hate that he exists.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You *loved* it?  Really?  Is your bar really low or did I miss something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was my birthday and my mom wanted to meet at the casino because I had a day off.  I'm not bitching about smoking at a casino.  I'm just saying the dude was considerate which is never the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're fired or they will be stabbed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite part was when he was heading to the new rocket.  NASA saw a storm coming and knew it would cripple his solar charging times and were powerless to do anything about it.  I was so tense reading it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Flash being disappointing as shit again, bring it on.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It requires a little leg work and effort](https://youtu.be/cjuT_63Ioig) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **I WILL NEVER PUT ON PANTS!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have stunt tracks and tiny cars now.  It's exactly the same.  The only difference is this is Branded and costs money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously?  Amazon Prime isn't available in Canada? Why the fuck not?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always watch that scene first then the entire movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen anyone act so considerate at a casino before.  NEVER.  Most people walk up smoking and sit down like "fuck you".  I had a guy walk up to the craps table once smoking a cigar.  Stood right next to me and told me to fuck off when I asked him to move.  Then the moron threw money down in the middle of a game.  Anyone that knows craps knows that its very rude to start playing in the middle of a game.  You wait until the table is off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI : You can do this for free in GTA V : Online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL on August 25th im buying Amazon Prime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at this casino.  It's all smoking all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesse and Hank were both slated to die at the end of Season 1.  Writers strike killed those plans.  For Season 2, Walt was supposed to give Jane an OD but AMC decided that it was too early for Walt to go full evil and they changed it to an accidental death.  Also every season after 2, the writers got together to try to make Walt unlikable and every year they failed.  They couldn't believe after Brock that people were still rooting for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun Fact : Mike Ehrmantraut was added in the show because they couldn't get Bob Odenkirk for the day.  He came back as an employee of Gus for the third season due to fan response over the character.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> meat?  Dude its 'SPOON!' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Met the Most Considerate Person at a Casino Yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still hate that they took out my favorite part of the book and ruined the ending.  The first 90 minutes of that thing are damn near a perfect adaption then it just goes Hollywood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] What was the deal with the writing last night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So....  Barry gives up on Team Flash a few months after Iris dies but he has a fancy new suit?  A suit that the villains know well enough to point out?  
  
Barry traveled to another universe, the past and future BY HIMSELF but needed Wally to help him get to the future?  
  
Why couldn't Cisco still vibe out of his feet?  
  
Why is Barry still keeping damn secrets?  Didn't tell Wally or Cisco what happened to them.  If anything Cisco needed to know immediately to make heated vibe gloves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still can't believe the logic with the intro of that game.  A fucking undead super soldier that saved the fucking galaxy *TWICE* is standing in front you saying the mother fucking reapers are coming and they are all like "Bro, you trippin'" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, based on that first poster, that his eyeglasses saved him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else notice he looks younger this year?  Not sure if it's makeup or what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  Now lets up jail karma catches up with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not familiar with dark souls so it looks like someone put a drink on your arm without a coaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The vet took my cats temperature once.  The thermometer went up her butt and she started slowly walking forward with her tongue sticking out of her mouth.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I so called it.  It's 'Avengers : Thanos Removed Ice Cream from Existance' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one on the left please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Knight Rises in IMAX.  About thirty minutes in the
film the projector shuts off.  It got so dark in that room.  Then the cellphones and yelling started.  Ten minutes later someone came in with a flashlight and said they would get the movie back on in a minute.  Almost twenty minutes later the movie starts up and it's an hour further into the movie.  Then more screaming.  The movie stops the flashlight lady comes back and says they're working on it.  About five minutes into the new wait this old man gets up and loudly excliams "Fuck this horse shit!".  This fat woman turns around and gets mad because he cursed in front of her child.  The old man screams "I DIDNT KILL FUCKING JAP PRICKS SO I COULD WATCH MY LANGUAGE!" and walks out the of the theatre.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't want to see it again?  Shit.  I saw GotG like 4 times in IMAX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the depiction of Spidey Sense in Civil War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew a guy named Nick in elementary school.  He stole my Excitebike cart on NES.  I'm still a little mad about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an entire sub Reddit about how much he sucks.  r/fuckchuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it tomorrow yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #"New" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found an interesting glitch in Far Cry 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 13:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just meant because of the ice cream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished the book, it was great. Kinda wondering how far from the novel it's going to stray.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S3 will be up 8 days after it's over.  You got a month and a half tops.  Also, lower your expectations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe Slade does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chase is dead.  You don't recruit your greatest enemy when you're still wearing your kid gloves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
