<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4054</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the original Viseart palettes.  Bye paycheck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be there in 2 weeks, thanks for this!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Northern Liberties, home of brunch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A surprise, to be sure, but a welcome one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there.  As someone who just received a dual diagnosis   has put her marriage in jeopardy many times because of drug abuse while manic, I'm going to go out on a limb   say tell your GF the whole story, once you figure out if you have an STD.

You say she suffers from depression; you may be surprised by her reaction, maybe she can identify with what you're both going through.

Just try to hold on until you have all the facts, ok?  I know waiting is the worst part.  Believe me.  Almost all my ideation happens when I am waiting for the consequence of something I did or thought I did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bang it!  Looks cute   easy enough to grow out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is a great conversation.  I'm prob about 20 years older than most of users on the makeup subs in general.  I grew up in the grunge/punk scene (nary a festival in sight thank god) and cultural appropriation just wasn't a thing.  We were all sort of androgynous as far as fashion   makeup went.  So I have seen so many trends come and go.  And I've worked in the fashion industry for a long time (Urban's Kent State sweatshirt debacle anyone?  I had to gather a bunch of mid 20 somethings around to tell them WHY is was offensive.  Fun convo!)

My point is, I do understand cultural appropriation but my friend group (Gen X, the forgotten ones) could give a shit about girls wearing bindis to Coachella.  And yes they are practicing Hindus.

TLDR

My youngin's just keep reading and be open.  Educate yourselves.  The boomers   the millennials are so entrenched in their viewpoints.  Common sense goes a long way.

Signed,

Makeup Crone

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serving Juggalo realness here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So weird.  I'm prescribed xanax   I don't turn into a zombie.  If I take it on an empty stomach, I might end up wishing I could take a nap, but I always remember what I did.  And it definitely works for acute panic attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Srs KVD Light 41 would look like kabuki makeup on her.  These girls all have average fair complexions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treebeard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #FatStacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do these girls already have gunts?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do all these girls wear falsies when they know they'll be crying about something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's got kind of a Forrest Gump vibe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no it's Matt in a wig time!!!!  Get your counseling on Ty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cold shoulders are OVER Deb!  God! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is nice seeing Jerry so involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what the heck are they sitting in?  Looks good for nappin'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok if my mother ever said we need to touch base I would scream and run away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, let's blame Tyler's tiredness on Cait's mental illness issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
