<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2372</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there was actually an interesting exchange a couple weeks back where James was talking about that misreported story that there would be no dual citizenship in France for Jews if le Pen wins. Someone called up to correct loads of misconceptions James had about the timeline relating to Arab countries banning Jews from visiting. The thing I like about him is as soon as the facts were pointed out he put his hands up and admitted he was wrong then praised the caller for the quality of his contribution. Not many media figures would do that nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Furious Trump Fan Flounders When Asked To Name Just One Media "Lie" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China awards Donald Trump valuable trademark days after he agrees to honour 'One China' policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 09:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even when they're dragging him to the gallows he's still going to be screaming about his imaginary landslide. I feel sorry for American journalists right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We may be sleepwalking towards world war, says respected Princeton historian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's policies risk sending US economy back to the 1970s, warns former boss of Federal Reserve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian government dismisses claims intelligence officials in contact with Donald Trump election campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 10:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
