<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3157</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved them ! Check out the Video of Marco Pierre white on youtube for the pork belly (to have the exact recipe). It's amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I added a vinaigrette to the Crushed potato and also on the salmon once placed on the potato. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got The idea mainly from Gordon Ramsay's Crispy Salmon video but tweaked it to my liking. Added Dill to the Salmon before cooking. Added Mint to the potatoes and I also made my own vinaigrette to complement the changes I made in the dish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 18:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Hadn't either, but it pairs really well ! will definitely do again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crispy Skin Salmon with Spring Onion and Mint Crushed Potato [Homemade] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 15:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy a good piece of pork belly, Score the skin, season the skin.

Pre heat oven at 160 celsius, put in room temperature pork and cook for 2.5-3 hours (If skin is not crispy put heat up to 200 with fan for the last 30 mins).

For this particular recipe I followed Marco Pierre White's video on youtube. You could find it easily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow Cooked Pork Belly with Honey Glaze [Homemade] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 10:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow cooked Pork belly with Honey Glaze. Tender and Crunchy, Amazing.. [Homemade] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 09:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grazie :) Pero Io non e italiano </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freshly prepared Tagliatelle with Butternut Squash, Guanciale, Pine nuts and Ricotta Salata. [Homemade] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly as Zoelc explained, you could find some guides on the net on how to do it right  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just melted some butter in the same pan were the steak was cooking threw in some sprigs of Thyme and a Crushed clove of garlic and placed it in the butter for a while then started basting the steak with the liquid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got it from the Grocery shop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 08:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't like Gravy with my steak ! Just love that great Beefy taste on its own :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian Rib-eye seared and basted with Garlic and Thyme with a side of tripple cooked fries that were prepared in Duck Fat. [Homemade] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Crispy Pork Belly With Infused Honey Glaze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 10:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
