<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5136</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not able to overcome significant warming in the later forecasts, crashed shortly after the rally and closed at 3.470, down almost 15 cents from the high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actual -147

Immediately jumped 7 cents.  Waiting on the GFS and Euro to see if the bullish s/d balance can overcome the look of a warm-up in the 11-15, and closer to norm medium term forecasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NG Storage Report 12/15/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estimates:

SMC Report -144

Schneider Electric -144

ION Energy -139

Thomson Reuters Supply Chain   -136

Commodities Research (SC CR)

GMP FirstEnergy -134

Stephen Smith Energy -134

Energy Ventures Analysis -132

UBS -130

PIRA Energy -129

INTL FCStone -128

Ritterbusch Associates -128

C H Guernsey -127

PointLogic -126

Energy Management Institute -125

Tradition Energy -125

Citi Futures -124

ARM Energy -123

Price Futures Group -122

Raymond James -117

Ecova -114

Gelber   Associate -114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So one of the the "skeptic" arguments is that "Anthropogenic climate change poses a serious threat to biodiversity," as cited in one of  the papers listed on your site?

[This XKCD explains why "0.85 C" matters](https://xkcd.com/1379/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 04:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am by no means confused about the misleading list used by climate *deniers* to say that global warming is not happening, is not caused by human CO2 and other greenhouse gas emissions, and/or will not have net negative social and economic effects.

The overwhelming majority the scientists writing the papers in your misleading list acknowledge that global warming is happening, is caused by human released CO2 and other greenhouse gas emissions, and will have net negative effect.

as they all accept that there has been a global temperature increase of **a fraction of a degree** since the end of the little ice age.

More misleading statements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 13:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's some interesting ones from the misleading "1300 peer reviewed papers."  One of the scientific papers directly refute your Telegraph article.

 [**Anthropogenic climate change poses a serious threat to biodiversity.** In marine environments, multiple climate variables, including temperature and CO2 concentration ([CO2]), are changing simultaneously.](http://www.pnas.org/content/106/23/9316.abstract)

[**Now that it is widely accepted that global warming ishappening**, there is a growing demand for accurate forecasts of its effects, and much concern about its effects on biological diversity.](http://www.bioone.org/doi/full/10.1641/B570306)

[The mean sea level has been projected to rise in the 21st century as a result of global warming1. Such projections of sea level change depend on estimated future greenhouse emissions and on differing models, but model-average results from a mid-range scenario (A1B) suggests a 0.387-m rise by 2100 (refs 1, 2). The largest contributions to sea level rise are estimated to come from thermal expansion (0.288 m) and the melting of mountain glaciers and icecaps (0.106 m), with smaller inputs from Greenland (0.024 m) and Antarctica (- 0.074 m)1. ](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v439/n7074/abs/nature04448.html)

[Rapidly rising levels of atmospheric CO2 are not only causing ocean warming, but also lowering seawater pH hence the carbonate saturation state of the oceans, on which many marine organisms depend to calcify their skeletons](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/v2/n8/full/nclimate1473.html)

[Recent global warming has demonstrated that organisms respond to climate and climatic change in a variety of ways, depending on the nature, rate and duration of the change, and the range of available biological responses ](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0960982209011828) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 13:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a a good one or your list: [**Anthropogenic climate change poses a serious threat to biodiversity.** In marine environments, multiple climate variables, including temperature and CO2 concentration ([CO2]), are changing simultaneously.](http://www.pnas.org/content/106/23/9316.abstract)

[**Now that it is widely accepted that global warming ishappening**, there is a growing demand for accurate forecasts of its effects, and much concern about its effects on biological diversity.](http://www.bioone.org/doi/full/10.1641/B570306)

[Climate change is expected to cause extensive vegetation changes in the Arctic: deciduous shrubs are already expanding, in response to climate warming.](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/j.1365-2486.2009.02110.x/abstract)

[Recent studies have shown that the polar bear matriline (mitochondrial DNA) evolved from a brown bear lineage since the late Pleistocene](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/336/6079/344) - ?

[The mean sea level has been projected to rise in the 21st century as a result of global warming1. Such projections of sea level change depend on estimated future greenhouse emissions and on differing models, but model-average results from a mid-range scenario (A1B) suggests a 0.387-m rise by 2100 (refs 1, 2). The largest contributions to sea level rise are estimated to come from thermal expansion (0.288 m) and the melting of mountain glaciers and icecaps (0.106 m), with smaller inputs from Greenland (0.024 m) and Antarctica (- 0.074 m)1. ](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v439/n7074/abs/nature04448.html)

This list is beyond misleading.  Please stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has Monckton himself joined the debate?

Your proposed strawman (strawman used incorrectly) is not at all what I am saying.  There is connotation in the language used in the title that these papers were written to support deniers' arguments, which *they were not.* Deniers cherry picked the data out of them, amalgamated them together, then tried to use that as an argument against alarmism, which is not how it works.

And again, I scrolled through a lot of the papers, particularly about heating in the oceans, and many were along the lines of -this specific type of coral in the GBR outperformed others as the oceans heated and acidified, while admitting that there was a huge amount of bleaching and dying. That combines with another paper about a species of crab that didn't die off as expected, to argue that the ocean is fine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1350+ Peer-Reviewed Papers Supporting Skeptic Arguments Against ACC/AGW Alarmism.

Neither the papers nor the scientists cited are supporting deniers' arguments, which is directly stated in this title.  Deniers are cherry picking the data and pulling studies out of context to fit their narrative, then claiming the papers support them.  *Huge* difference between the two.   This title is bullshit and misleading, and on purpose.  What are you missing here?

You think that if any of these scientists were asked if they themselves or their papers were meant to disprove AGW, they would say yes?

  I was trying to give you some of those arguements

You gave me arguments unsupported by scientific evidence, and barely qualify as arguments.  What scientific papers quoted here which do purport to disprove some claims have been challenged, such as the Maldives studies on sea level rise.

Finally, Monckton flat out denies AGW, and is not a scientist.  His lectures show he doesn't understand any of the science.  He's a political hack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 20:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not seeing many of the 1,350 articles listed describing "alarmism," let alone any denying (which is flat out what Monckton, with not scientific background, is claiming).  The *overwhelming majority* of people on that list are not skeptics and understand and support AGW, and what he's claiming that these papers reveal is not true.  Every one I've sampled is explaining regional effects, or some species will handle the human caused warming and ocean acidification better (which all climate scientists agree with).

Its there so that when you look at all of these skeptical arguments from Monckton and others and you ask 'where are they getting these numbers?' you can check the database.

"1350+ Peer-Reviewed Papers Supporting Skeptic Arguments Against ACC/AGW Alarmism."  He wrote it like this on purpose to trick people into thinking there are 1,350 papers refuting AGW.  *They don't support his bullshit arguments.* He pulls the data out of context and claim they do, but he doesn't understand the data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... Did you get tickets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 15:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The IPCC took a vote and decided that the sun has nothing to do with warming.

The **abnormal** warming.  Do you really not understand this?  That's just ridiculous.

Can you please link one of the 1,350+ studies that says AGW isn't happening?  The ones I'm looking at all show climate change is happening.  Cannot find a single one refuting it.

[Rapidly rising levels of atmospheric CO2 are not only causing ocean warming, but also lowering seawater pH hence the carbonate saturation state of the oceans, on which many marine organisms depend to calcify their skeletons](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/v2/n8/full/nclimate1473.html) - Different organisms will be affected differently.  Who's saying  different?

[Recent global warming has demonstrated that organisms respond to climate and climatic change in a variety of ways, depending on the nature, rate and duration of the change, and the range of available biological responses ](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0960982209011828) - Same thing.

[An analysis of data pertaining to the period 18611986 reveals that (1) a 1 C rise in the mean annual air temperature of the British Isles has historically been associated with a 35% drop in the percentage of days that the United Kingdom has experienced cyclonic flow](http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2FBF01027343)  - Climate scientists are the first to tell you that AGW will affect different regional climates in different ways.

Every single one acknowledges AGW is real.  Monckton full on denies it is happening.

You are a member of a religion trying to persecute skeptics as heretics.

Religion is blind following with no evidence.  There is so much evidence; it's hilarious when people call it religion.  Those 1,350 papers are evidence of AGW.  The funniest part of this is that many politicians (Inhofe for example) say that humans cannot effect the climate *because the bible refutes it.*  Projection much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is really funny, considering the NIPCC is funded by the Heartland institute, who stopped releasing their contributions after their fiasco where all external funding was cut and they essentially became the coal lobby.  Which side are you talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is just ridiculous.  You think climate scientists just forgot about the sun.  "Fuck, why didn't we look at that! Man, silly us." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [In my link, Monckton vs. the scientists he lies about quoting PDF](http://www.skepticalscience.com/docs/Monckton_vs_Scientists.pdf)

Again, he lies about the people he quotes then refusing to change it in his political presentations, why would anyone believe his "peer reviewed studies." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You are right, it's higher than 97%](http://www.jamespowell.org/index.html)

Edit:  It's funny, you list to a blogspot, he links directly to peer reviewed literature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 13:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope you are kidding... This guy has been called out for using incorrect stats over and over and over again, and refuses to change his bullshit. This guy is a political hack pretending to be a scientist.

[Here's a list of his incorrect claims and the science as to why they are wrong.](https://www.skepticalscience.com/Monckton_Myths_arg.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an idiot with an MBA doing everything in my power to have an exit from my startup and get into VC, I genuinely laughed at your comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 15:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone fill me or correct me in how MW and MWh work here?  I know it gets confused and explained here often, but I'm still a little confused.

AES to install two energy storage projects totaling 37.5 MW, 150 MWh.

___

Once in operation, the two AES systems will combine to provide 37.5 MW of power for four hours on a nearly daily basis.

____

So, the 37.5 MW would be the power output per hour, and the MWh would be the total produced/released? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CL/RB/HO storage report 12/07/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NG Storage Report 12/08/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 13:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EIA Natural Gas report for week end 11/25/2016

Week  |   Nov  (2016)   |  Nov  (2015)
:-:|:-:|:-:
CDD    |            |       
HDD    |          |     

ICE Swaps:

Storage Date | As of 12/5 | Change | As of 12/07 | change
:-:|:-:|:-:|:-:|:-:
12/8 | -36 | 0 |  | 
12/15 | -120 | -5 |  | 
12/22 | -170 | -10 |  | 
12/29 | -150 | 0 |  | 
12/1 | -150 | 0 |  | 

End of Draw down to 1710 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Celsius Energy Dec 2, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 14:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11-15 day mean looking pretty cold per the

[ECMWF](http://i.imgur.com/hZSi14l.png)

[GFS](http://i.imgur.com/nvlxnkB.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wind generation output tops 15,000 MW in ERCOT region </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wind generation output tops 15,000 MW in ERCOT region </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CL/RB/HO storage report 11/30/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 14:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NG Storage Report 12/01/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 14:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EIA Natural Gas report for week end 11/25/2016

Week  |   Nov  (2016)   |  Nov  (2015)
:-:|:-:|:-:
CDD    |            |       
HDD    |          |     

ICE Swaps:

Storage Date | As of 11/25 | Change | As of 11/28 | change
:-:|:-:|:-:|:-:|:-:
12/1 | -50 | 0 | -52 | -2
12/8 | -70 | 0 | -32 | 38
12/15 | -85 | 0 | -110 | -25
12/22 | -80 | 0 | -130 | -50
12/29 | -107 | 0 | -140 | -33

End of Draw down to 1810

End of Draw down to 1765 -45

__________________________________________
Bentek: Flows @-49, S/D @-54

Andy Weissman, EBW: -59 Bcf

Reza Haidari, TR Analytics: -56 Bcf

EMD Editor -55 Bcf

UBS: -55 Bcf

GWDD Model: -48 Bcf

PointLogic Energy: -46 Bcf

Tony Yuen, CITI: -45 Bcf

Kilduff Report: -33 Bcf

Price Futures Group -65
First Enercast -62

 
GMP FirstEnergy -62

Energy Management Institute -60

Energy Aspects -58

SMC Report -56

Thomson Reuters Supply Chain   -56

Commodities Research (SC CR)

UBS -55

Stephen Smith Energy -55

C H Guernsey -54

Raymond James -54

ARM Energy -53

INTL FCStone -53

Citi Futures -52

Gelber   Associates -52

PIRA Energy -50

Tradition Energy -50

Energy Ventures Analysis -49

ION Energy -49

Macquarie Group -49

Schneider Electric -49

Wells Fargo -49

PointLogic -46

Ritterbusch Associates -41

Ecova -26 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 00:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Conservatives push their Creationism but I doubt anyone would argue that they managed to stifle the study of evolution.

Are you being serious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even funnier, he has history of bitching about CTR on T_D.  His projection is almost as strong as his ignorance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CL/RB/HO storage report 10/13/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estimates from @EnergyBasis

[Crude Oil Estimates](http://i.imgur.com/TcSiFei.jpg)

[Gasoline Estimates](http://i.imgur.com/xBKFgj4.jpg)

[Distillate Estimates](http://i.imgur.com/Gcnpb1y.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CL/RB/HO storage report 11/23/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Renaissance's Medallion Fund Became Finance's Blackest Box </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NG Storage Report 11/23/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EIA releasing Petroleum Status and Natural Gas reports on Wednesday, 11/23 this week due to Thanksgiving holiday.

Week  |   Nov 4-10 (2016)   |  Nov 6-12 (2015)
:-:|:-:|:-:
CDD    |            |       
HDD    |          |     

ICE Swaps:

11/23: 2

12/1: -50

12/8: -70

End of Draw up to 1830

__________________________________________

Analysts estimates:

Price Futures Group -1

Tradition Energy -1

GMP FirstEnergy 1

ARM Energy 2

Thomson Reuters Supply Chain   2

Commodities Research (SC CR)

INTL FCStone 3

PointLogic 4

Stephen Smith Energy 5

Ecova 6

Gelber   Associates 6

ION Energy 6

Macquarie Group 6

Ritterbusch Associates 7

Energy Management Institute 8

Wells Fargo 8

SMC Report 9

Schneider Electric 10

Citi Futures 11

C H Guernsey 15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 14:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wouldn't you post the UPI article to begin with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actual at 30.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NG Storage Report 10/13/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 13:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EIA set to announce a new record high storage at 10:30am ET today, with projections ranging between 20-40 bcf, average putting total stocks at 4.027 tcf.

Week  |   Nov 4-10 (2016)   |  Nov 6-12 (2015)
:-:|:-:|:-:
CDD    |     6.87       |        7.88
HDD    |     69.38     |     83.41

Platts survey at 30bcf, range 25-35


ICE Swaps:

11/17: 24

11/24: 1

12/1: -55

End of Draw up to 1800 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama's oil and gas regulations face fire from Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 13:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 13:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An unarmed revolution brings support. An armed revolution will be crushed and instills and empowers a full on authoritarian military state, purging all opposition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 14:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This trick works for me for now](http://www.ghacks.net/2016/02/26/read-articles-behind-paywalls-by-masquerading-as-googlebot/).  FT is pretty good about patching these loopholes though, so gotta change it up now and then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet with all the influx of these left leaning individuals, the economy is booming and population continues to grow, fueling engineering unemployment below 2% with a 100k median salary.  

[Meanwhile, the Kansas experiment...](https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2016-10-24/kansas-ends-bad-economic-news-by-not-reporting-it)  I really wish there were some place in this sub that Brownback's policies and effects could legitimately be discussed.  I know if i posted this article it would get downvoted to oblivion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand where you're coming from, I'm certainly not defending the US government.  I'm just saying that I think Russia *is* the devil the media portray them to be (and they should portray the US government in a similar, yet less bad, light).  Right now, a strong portion of the media in the US are clamoring that the election is rigged. I'd love to know what happens to media outlets within Russia who claim the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just making sure we're not, out of one side of the mouth saying that pay to play is a huge problem, while out of the other side saying pay to exist is not that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are in a libertarian sub, saying that a country dictatorially run by a man who has never held a position outside of the government, and is by some accounts the richest man in the world, is not the demon we make them out to be?  I thought corruption was bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [SNL had a breakdown of the costs including SO and NO, and $/MMbtu NG equivalent.](http://i.imgur.com/9bA16qw.gif)  

I haven't looked too much into the costs for MATS, but it's crazy to think that we are just now setting these limits for mercury, arsenic and other heavy metals...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CL/RB/HO storage report 10/13/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Report on Thursday this week due to Columbus Day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NG Storage Report 10/13/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/9:
ICE @ 88  +6
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 03:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My city has a vote for municipal broadband.  I got the email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 03:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately [I wouldn't count on it](http://www.recode.net/2016/8/25/12644888/google-fiber-broadband-cost-cuts)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 17:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kudos on the call! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank Estimates for Medium Term Price </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 19:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Caelus discovers about 6 billion barrels at Smith Bay

* Field could one day produce as much as 200,000 barrels a day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alaska Oil Known Reserves May Have Just Grown 80% on Discovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 14:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 23:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's bringing you up vs. other vendors?  I'm still working on updating my model, probably won't have estimates for next few numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CL/RB/HO storage report 10/5/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> API:
Crude: -7.6
Gas: +2.9
Disty: -1.3
Cushing: +0.435

EIA courtesy of @energybasis

https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CuAs516UMAAJVUG.jpg:large </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NG Storage Report 10/6/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be updating this freely without denoting edits.

ICE Settled 73, currently 74@76

PL @ 73

Thomson Reuters @ 76

Demand Days:
http://i.imgur.com/ADBZ3go.png

Winter Probability Scenarios:
http://i.imgur.com/ARnl9vG.png

PJM Load Futures.  Peak outage 10/17
https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CuAGXp4VUAAXCHK.jpg:large

Late to the show...

Organization Forecast (in bcf)
Citi Futures 62
Price Futures Group 63
Energy Aspects 64
C H Guernsey 65
Raymond James 67
Gelber   Associates 68
Stephen Smith Energy 68
Ritterbusch Associates 69
ARM Energy 71
SMC Report 71
Wells Fargo 72
Energy Management Institute 73
Energy Ventures Analysis 73
FirstEnergy Capital 73
PointLogic 73
IAF Advisors/ION Energy 74
Macquarie Group 75
Thomson Reuters Supply Chain   76
Commodities Research (SC CR)
Schneider Electric 77

Actual: 80 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FDA and Crony Capitalism: Is there a government conspiracy against Hampton Creek? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 21:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's plenty of evidence.   Lead in gasoline, mercury regulations, CFCs, rivers lighting on fire in the Northeast, banning plastic bags.  And then there's stuff like mining regulations and best practices that the hypothetical free market would never even see.  In most of these cases, the market participants actively worked against regulations which reduced or prevented pollution.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think that putting massively crippling sanctions on Saudi Arabia's major geopolitical rival doesn't prop them up?  SA has so much more regional power because of the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanctions on Iran certainly prop up Saudi Arabia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily disagreeing with the too complicated *to start*.  
*Once you learn the system, it's super easy.  
*You can be anonymous, but not sure if that's the best option.  I go to FEF specifically to see some users' posts.  I never skip pjm's posts.

*You can check the security here, no dev you hire can beat the security.  
*You can upload and/or link everything to imgur or reddit uploads.

I just think the overwhelming majority of the forums out there have terrible, horribly outdated functionality.  Hiring a dev to implement a forum system will get that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple people can comment on one specific comment below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Others can easily add comments with pictures, charts, or anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  @timeontarget
 This next week wasn't quite as bullish as my original take, but I thought still looking pretty bullish.

There is a huge dichotomy between the legacy CDDs and what I recorded for the GWDDs. I was actually not very good about writing down the GWDDs for several days, so my numbers may be off. But, the change week to week in GWDDs and Legacy CDDs is fascinating.

So far this summer I have found the GWDDs to be a far more reliable indicator of power </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting to see ICE EOS swaps still at high 3.9s.  

I've been watching U/V and V/X the past few weeks.  I think V/X could come in a lot if there's any storage left getting near end of injection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Storage Report 8/19/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romed - Stole your two pics to show how this could work.

[PL](http://i.imgur.com/vWeJZcF.jpg)

[ICE](http://i.imgur.com/I8zX12f.jpg)

Edit:  Whoever creates and stickies the report can edit and add as much info at the top as possible.

Edit 2:  Once the report is over, admins can un-sticky and the thread will naturally flow off the main page.

Edit 3: **Point Logic final 15bcf** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool pic.  We used to have an office @ 1610 Wynkoop and there was a cool setup on the roof.  Right as Union Station finished they jacked the rent up 50%.  I miss being right in the middle of the action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 16:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got the beetus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 21:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like rektbot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 18:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halliburton advertising on the radio in CO for drilling gigs.  

What's the rationale for watching someone previously in offshore?  He probably has skills for shale, but there are plenty of onshore shale experts that will be hired before him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  1-2% for 40 years because that's how many people actually agree with us.

Those 1-2% don't agree with each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you listened to [the Planet Money on Six Policies Economists Love (And Politicians Hate)?](http://www.npr.org/sections/money/2012/07/19/157047211/six-policies-economists-love-and-politicians-hate) An interesting podcast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 19:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully that will help.  What year are they?  Unless you have really poor quality soil in your area, nutrient deficiency won't hit for at least a few years in hops directly in the ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 17:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the hops are in the ground or in pots?  How's the drainage?

I would say disease and/or over watering rather than deficiency.  Going from looking fine to unhealthy, and from the pic leaves directly next to the unhealthy one look fine as well, it's less likely nutrient deficiency.  

Definitely cut off all the bad looking leaves and remove from the area to start, just to be safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweden's deal leaves door to nuclear power open, but only just </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 19:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 18:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There weren't any shows in my state.  Not that it mattered, I tried to buy tickets to a few around the country and they all had errors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 23:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got my codes, "We're sorry, we're unable to process your request. Please try again." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 19:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, bots constantly pinging the site going to get the 2% of the tickets sent out that they are accepting...  People are going to love TM after this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is saying:

Below are voucher codes for your account. Please remember to copy and enter them when you are purchasing in order to redeem their value.

There are no voucher codes...

I guess the scalpers already got all the tickets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 21:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha.  Do you do macro pricing?  You don't have an S/D model?  Even traders using weather regression models typically integrate some of sort of S/D balance in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know if Celcius is your writing, but really nice info, and (if it's you) you nailed it today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pricing info, no one follows EIA pricing.

The inventory data is from a sampling of compulsory reporting.  Every gas trader in the world watches the Thursday number.   ICE has weekly and EOS storage contracts which are traded regularly, although liquidity has fallen.  Calling this data "abhorrent" is amusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get paywalled:

**Environmental Groups Change Tune on Nuclear Power**

Focus on climate change has raised profile of reactors, now viewed as reliable, carbon-free source of energy

By AMY HARDER
June 16, 2016 2:10 p.m. ET

Some of the nations most influential environmental groups are softening their longstanding opposition to nuclear power, marking a significant shift in the antinuclear movement as environmentalists priority shifts to climate change.

The change is lowering one of the biggest political hurdles facing the nuclear power industry in the U.S. and comes at a critical time, as several financially struggling reactors are set to shut down.

Because the historical context is that these groups were opposed to nuclear, their absence on the opposition front is noticed, said Joe Dominguez, executive vice president for governmental and regulatory affairs for Exelon Corp., the biggest owner of nuclear plants in the U.S. I think its pretty significant.

Nuclear power, which emits no greenhouse gases, provides roughly 20% of U.S. electricity and 60% of carbon-free electricity, according to federal data. Pressed by cheap natural gas and state policies that favor renewables over nuclear power, roughly a dozen reactors are either poised to shut down in the coming years or have already.

The Sierra Club, the countrys oldest and largest environmental group, is debating whether to halt its longtime position in support of shuttering all existing nuclear-power plants earlier than required by their federal operating licenses. The environmental groups leaders see existing reactors as a bridge to renewable electricity and an alternative source of energy as the group campaigns to shut down coal and natural gas plants.

The Environmental Defense Fund is similarly deciding to what extent it should adjust its policy, potentially lending its support to keeping open financially struggling reactors.

In Illinois, the Natural Resources Defense Council, along with the Sierra Club and EDF, are among the advocacy groups working with Exelon and state lawmakers on a legislative deal that would reverse a decision the company made in early June to close two nuclear reactors in the next two years. The agreement would promote more energy efficiency and renewable energy while ensuring the reactors remain in operation by providing financial recognition for the zero-carbon electricity they produce.

The shift in attitude, Mr. Dominguez said, has a clear impact on energy companies bottom line because it allows for agreements on statewide policies, whereas before I didnt think we could get there.

Michael Brune, executive director of the Sierra Club, says his group is focusing most of its resources on closing coal plants and preventing the construction of new natural gas plants.

Were actively debating the timeline in which nuclear plants should be decommissioned as we reduce our reliance on coal and gas in the electric sector, Mr. Brune said.

The shift is twofold. Some environmental groups that have in the past protested existing reactors are now at times staying on the sidelines. In other cases, such as the one in Illinois, environmentalists are actively working toward keeping reactors open.

Very few new nuclear plants, meanwhile, are set to come online soon because of market conditions, so the debate has focused largely on the fate of existing reactors. Most major environmental groups remain opposed to creating new nuclear plants, instead preferring renewable electricity.

Most environmentalists have long opposed nuclear power due to a host of concerns, including the risk of a catastrophic accident (a worry heightened by Japans Fukushima disaster in 2011), unresolved questions on radioactive waste storage, the potential for weapons proliferation from the fuel and a preference for renewable energy such as solar and wind.

Over the last couple of years, as climate change has climbed to the top of the agenda of nearly all major environmental groups, influential leaders in both the climate science and policy arenas have shifted positions. Many now back this carbon-free source of energy, especially the existing fleet of approximately 100 reactors at about 60 power plants, which provide a steady source of electricity compared with the intermittence of wind and solar.

Michael Shellenberger, co-founder of the Breakthrough Institute, a progressive think tank, founded an organization in January called Environmental Progress whose initial mission is focused on backing nuclear power to address climate change.

If anything gives me hope in these dark times, its that so many environmentalists are changing their minds about nuclear, said Mr. Shellenberger, who says he switched his position and began supporting nuclear power in 2011. What was just a trickle of converters a few years ago has become a positive stampede.

Some environmental groups, including Greenpeace, continue to actively fight to shut down existing nuclear plants, saying the environmental risks, from radiation emissions to waste disposal, far outweigh any climate benefit.

That is prompting these groups to oppose deals like the one in Illinois. Illinois should not be bailing out old and dangerous nuclear reactors just because they cant compete, said Jim Riccio, nuclear policy analyst for Greenpeace.

After reactors closed in Southern California and New England in 2013 and 2014, respectively, emissions in those regions rose after having declined for some time, according to data from nonprofit electricity transmission organizations. Regulators replaced those reactors with natural gas, which is often the cheapest option but emits carbon dioxide.

Mr. Dominguez of Exelon cited a December announcement by New York Democratic Gov. Andrew Cuomo in favor of the continued operation of upstate nuclear plants as symbolizing the new mood.

When Gov. Cuomo put a stake in the ground saying were going to save the upstate nuclear plants, I think that was a really significant turning point, Mr. Dominguez said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmental Groups Change Tune on Nuclear Power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would by no means consider myself a Bernie supporter, but environmentalism isn't addressed by libertarianism and is a big issue to me, so I looked at the Green Party platform.  Jill Stein's AMA was such a massive turnoff, she is probably the last person I would support in this race.

She is an "environmentalist" who is avidly anti-nuclear.  A physician who is a proponent of homeopathic medicine, and doesn't wholeheartedly support vaccines - forget compulsory, she doesn't support them at all.  A quasi-scientist who is against GMOs for bullshit anti-science reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will encourage growth elsewhere, and that growth can also get unruly. Side shoots will come out and it should get bushy. Depending on how much you clip the top, it might keep trying to go up.

But, the goal of first year rhizomes is to develop good root structure. You might get a few flowers, but they won't have acids to brew. Moderate pruning won't hinder root structure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 18:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What year are those?  Location?  Did you trim the bottom leaves?

Possibly nutrient deficiency? Unless you have significantly trimmed the bottom they should be much more filled out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not even going to throw in a *now kith* meme? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your longs from 45.50 must be crushing it.  Here comes 55! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 17:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/2F4G6x8.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I'm saying is got about 75% of this move up when everyone else was bearish.  Good luck picking up pennies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 13:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that I was saying a weak dollar increases the price of oil, you just had the wrong reason.

[You can also take a look at this.](https://www.reddit.com/r/energy_trading/comments/4cvclg/0401clk6/d1ls1w3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 13:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you?  If you are in CO, I took a large amount of clones from 2nd year Cascade and Chinook, and would be happy to share.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck.

[Using recent advances in panel data estimation techniques, we find that an appreciation of the US dollar exchange rate leads to a significant decline in oil demand for a sample of 65 oil-importing countries](https://www.ecb.europa.eu/events/pdf/conferences/mopo_commodity/peersman.pdf?4f6b917a3a688b180d589de9ac1f6170)

[The Wall Street Journal Dollar Index, which tracks the dollar against a basket of other major currencies, recently traded up 1%. Oil is priced in dollars and becomes more expensive for holders of other currencies as the greenback appreciates.](http://www.wsj.com/articles/oil-price-hurt-by-dollar-strength-1432631484)

[Oil is priced in dollars on the world market. When the dollar is weaker, foreign currencies are stronger, by definition. That means people in other countries can buy more oil for the same amount of money. So let's assume oil is $100 per barrel, and $100 is equal to 70 euros. If the euro appreciates against the dollar by 10 percent, then instead of 70 euros it will take only 63 euros to buy one barrel of oil. So that oil becomes cheaper to foreigners, and they can buy more. And do they buy more? Usually, yes. There are other factors obviously, like in many countries taxes are such a big portion of the cost of oil that the savings aren't that dramatic. But it would still make sense to buy more if the price in your own currency goes down. So for those of us stuck with the dollar, why does that make the price of oil or gasoline go up?](http://money.usnews.com/money/blogs/flowchart/2008/03/10/why-gas-prices-rise-as-the-dollar-falls) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know reading and changing your mind can be tough, but 3 links is all I need. Check fucking mate. I've yet to see anything countering these, and silly that you still stick by your wildly incorrect rationale.

[Using recent advances in panel data estimation techniques, we find that an appreciation of the US dollar exchange rate leads to a significant decline in oil demand for a sample of 65 oil-importing countries](https://www.ecb.europa.eu/events/pdf/conferences/mopo_commodity/peersman.pdf?4f6b917a3a688b180d589de9ac1f6170)

[The Wall Street Journal Dollar Index, which tracks the dollar against a basket of other major currencies, recently traded up 1%. Oil is priced in dollars and becomes more expensive for holders of other currencies as the greenback appreciates.](http://www.wsj.com/articles/oil-price-hurt-by-dollar-strength-1432631484)

[Oil is priced in dollars on the world market. When the dollar is weaker, foreign currencies are stronger, by definition. That means people in other countries can buy more oil for the same amount of money. So let's assume oil is $100 per barrel, and $100 is equal to 70 euros. If the euro appreciates against the dollar by 10 percent, then instead of 70 euros it will take only 63 euros to buy one barrel of oil. So that oil becomes cheaper to foreigners, and they can buy more. And do they buy more? Usually, yes. There are other factors obviously, like in many countries taxes are such a big portion of the cost of oil that the savings aren't that dramatic. But it would still make sense to buy more if the price in your own currency goes down. So for those of us stuck with the dollar, why does that make the price of oil or gasoline go up?](http://money.usnews.com/money/blogs/flowchart/2008/03/10/why-gas-prices-rise-as-the-dollar-falls) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious that instead of actually reading the correct answer and admitting you are wrong, you follow me around trolling.  Good luck in your paper money account in mommy's basement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Using recent advances in panel data estimation techniques, we find that an appreciation of the US dollar exchange rate leads to a significant decline in oil demand for a sample of 65 oil-importing countries](https://www.ecb.europa.eu/events/pdf/conferences/mopo_commodity/peersman.pdf?4f6b917a3a688b180d589de9ac1f6170)

[The Wall Street Journal Dollar Index, which tracks the dollar against a basket of other major currencies, recently traded up 1%. Oil is priced in dollars and becomes more expensive for holders of other currencies as the greenback appreciates.](http://www.wsj.com/articles/oil-price-hurt-by-dollar-strength-1432631484)

[Oil is priced in dollars on the world market. When the dollar is weaker, foreign currencies are stronger, by definition. That means people in other countries can buy more oil for the same amount of money. So let's assume oil is $100 per barrel, and $100 is equal to 70 euros. If the euro appreciates against the dollar by 10 percent, then instead of 70 euros it will take only 63 euros to buy one barrel of oil. So that oil becomes cheaper to foreigners, and they can buy more. And do they buy more? Usually, yes. There are other factors obviously, like in many countries taxes are such a big portion of the cost of oil that the savings aren't that dramatic. But it would still make sense to buy more if the price in your own currency goes down. So for those of us stuck with the dollar, why does that make the price of oil or gasoline go up?](http://money.usnews.com/money/blogs/flowchart/2008/03/10/why-gas-prices-rise-as-the-dollar-falls) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are WTI and USD strongly negatively correlated?  The root cause on S/D is all I'm trying to get at.


[Using recent advances in panel data estimation techniques, we find that an appreciation of the US dollar exchange rate leads to a significant decline in oil demand for a sample of 65 oil-importing countries](https://www.ecb.europa.eu/events/pdf/conferences/mopo_commodity/peersman.pdf?4f6b917a3a688b180d589de9ac1f6170)

[The Wall Street Journal Dollar Index, which tracks the dollar against a basket of other major currencies, recently traded up 1%. Oil is priced in dollars and becomes more expensive for holders of other currencies as the greenback appreciates.](http://www.wsj.com/articles/oil-price-hurt-by-dollar-strength-1432631484)

[Oil is priced in dollars on the world market. When the dollar is weaker, foreign currencies are stronger, by definition. That means people in other countries can buy more oil for the same amount of money. So let's assume oil is $100 per barrel, and $100 is equal to 70 euros. If the euro appreciates against the dollar by 10 percent, then instead of 70 euros it will take only 63 euros to buy one barrel of oil. So that oil becomes cheaper to foreigners, and they can buy more. And do they buy more? Usually, yes. There are other factors obviously, like in many countries taxes are such a big portion of the cost of oil that the savings aren't that dramatic. But it would still make sense to buy more if the price in your own currency goes down. So for those of us stuck with the dollar, why does that make the price of oil or gasoline go up?](http://money.usnews.com/money/blogs/flowchart/2008/03/10/why-gas-prices-rise-as-the-dollar-falls) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying it's the other way.  Dollar strength from yields effects physical oil demand, driving speculation on futures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
