<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7806</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such negging, much effective

Mah hamster is full of tingles

...

...

...

Bepis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upd8: he finally talked to me today.

Asked, as I "am a woman", why wymeen blabber so much simple things that could be said in a single phrase.

"I don't think I have this problem at all"

My boss was on the backroom and just "Oi, can confirm", lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I have enough air in my lungs to say this entire phrase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm intimidated by women

Honestly, this always cracks me up because of the kind of people I deal with. There's an older man who often goes to where I work at, and he's always all about "how young women are asking for it".

That is, until he sees me. He literally shuts up when I'm present and is *scared* of me. According to my boss, every other woman who worked here had to deal with some sort of verbal harassment from him (and my boss indeed did try to call his attention to something else to avoid situations like these back then, even apologising to these women later on), but me? He's scared shitless of me. He tries to go away as fast as possible from me because I'm taller than him and *somehow* have the "eyes of an angry commie ready to stalk and kill".

I'm not even a commie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You find that "defensive"?

LOL

Really dude? I wrote this on the most chill tone possible, thanks a lot for misinterpreting. But whatever.

Edit: also, you can come to this country. I don't give a fuck, you know? The more people working, the better, innit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want me to start asking women around until I reach around 1500 people asked and do a graphic to be put on r/dataisbeautiful or something, mate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada's Disney prince

God save the Trudeau. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> need to stay out

Good thing I never liked the US, but eh, you think your nation is every latino's dream or summat, don't ya? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think he was probably laughing his ass off when he hid a fetish on me that I just discovered I had recently.

And that'd be men in high heels. I mean, it's just *fabulous*, Jesus on a bycicle Christ, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thinks I am a mysoginist

I don't at all

His dread game is so good he dreads himself and doesn't even notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oi, thank you c: I had some spare time of 20 minutes at work and decided to write this yesterday, lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Cue Psycho Killer playing on the background* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just call him asshole. Double meaning :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, the manliest man of my family (on the physical sense) is the one who "teached" me the first steps of the BP path when I was a kid.

He's my brother. If he was RP, he'd probably be TRPers propaganda guy lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen more of the types who say that if they were the prince charming, they'd get all da boosy.

Thing is, they thought they got good a bit too early :v but yeah, I am aware of the bunch you mentioned here. Still, it's a fantasy based world but these bits have pinches of reality (and that is also something kids notice; I personally did because I dealt with neighbours who fit into a lot of these things back then). As lots of people said here already, those who tend to fall for it have a bad background (coupled with low self esteem) that can fuck things up.

Aaaaanyway, thanks for the compliment; me is not native speaker :P

Edit: as for the "prince charming" there, I can make a correlation with the Shrek's prince charming to get the point better. Seems like he'll be that, but in reality, he's fucked up and goes back to the same trope of Disney villains. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people say that whenever we are close to a war of sorts, extremist ideologies start to pop up.

I say *the internet is full of crap*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: probably just a bug.

And uh, these guys do realize people who do that are on every demographic, right...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "A Fantastic World" - or why Disney's got nothing to do with your delusional mysoginy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stupid Disney movies lied to me!"

Disney did not lie to you, and the proof is within the reach of its villains. Why? Because most of your male childhood villains are exactly what the manosphere advocates for with a pinch of "magic" as to not turn them into characters too somber to be put in a kids' animation.

We're all aware of how unsufferably cringeworthy Gaston was (or is, if you watched the 2017 remake), and how he is proud of his manliness on some uneven ways. In fact, the remake shows that with even more precision: his enraged expression hid behind what probably would be perceived as "amused mastery", how he describes his dream marriage with Belle exactly like manospherians also dream of... and the fact that he describes her as "prey", and whose nature is to be prey, "waiting to be hunted" by a man. And I didn't even begin to describe the fact that he depends on his hunting companion to feel "validated" - not even noticing that the compliments are mostly originated by an one-sided attraction of the poor man, but you know, *nobody is as oblivious as Gaston~* -, nor how he feels intimidated by Belle's relative independence and right to reject him.

Outside the princesses universe, there is also a perfect example inside The Lion King. The acceptance of Mufasa did not come from his "alpha"ness - one can even argue he was "beta", considering that his proximity with his son did not come from attempts to dread Simba's mother, but purely based on his *feelings* for his own child, as well as on teaching his son what one could also argue were "beta values" or morality -, but from his care and dedication. That can be proved by his (tragic) death, in which he took his own life to save Simba. Also on the same animation, we have Scar as the perfect example of "alpha captain": his will is the only one that matters, and he ought to use Machiavellian tactics to remain in control by having hyenas as allies. And as we can notice by the ending, there were not as many lions on his side: as soon as Simba was found to be alive and seen as a possible saviour out of the current situation, the "revolution" began. And without a CCCP National Anthem playing on the background. In short: Scar was also an example, on his personality, of what the manosphere can advocate for, and the conclusion is that 1. he was downright wrong and a cartoon example of "dark triad" based character and 2. his lack of care, coupled with the arrogance to think himself as hard (or even impossible) to outsmart, brought his ruin.

Aladdin also has his share of "manospherian villain". Jafar is unescrupulous and, along with the already mentioned Gaston, feels intimidated and uneasy about Jasmine's personality and rejection. Hell, even Aladdin himself had his share of manosphere moment on a belief he later found to be wrong: his first wish was an attempt to impress Jasmine, as he thought being powerful and wealthy would get him her love. In reality - and also proved by the beginning of the animation -, she didn't care enough for that. Either way, back to Jafar: he thought himself smart and superior to everyone else, including feeling above everyone else, in your typical r/iamverysmart way.

And let's not start on the lovability of the *blue* Genie. He'd be the "funny beta" to redpillers if he was real, much probably, and well, most non-redpilled people who watched the animation did like him as a character.

We also have The Hunchback of Notredame to add on this list: both the original and Disney's version show Frollo as what one could even consider a show of MRA line of thinking: he mistreats Esmeralda hoping that she somehow ends up falling in love for him, tries to dread her by the typical "do what I want *or else...*" and, in a MGTOW fashion, blames her for his own problems. Focusing solely on the Disney version here: both the Hunchback and Phoebus loved her, too, and none had the urges and apparent lack of self control like Frollo did. Her beauty and carefreeness does not justify his actions like he tries to convince himself that do.

On a more recent note, we also have Maui from the Moana (or Vaiana) movie. He starts off with the exact feeling manospherians often have of entitlement and "I did this, you should thank me!" when, in fact, there are things of which he wasn't responsible at all but takes the credit. And do I need to mention his disbelief around the fact that the Ocean chose a girl at first, and how he blatantly stated that she probably should be on her village "taking care of the babies or something"? Fortunately, he does change and is not the villain (probably the reason why he changed, though), seeing he was wrong - also about stealing Te Fiti's heart. On a personal level, I wouldn't put him on this list considering the possibility that he'd act on such way with any human being in general, but you get the point here.

Lastly, we have Atlantis. The main character, Milo - fortunately for us, not Yannopoulos -, is a complete beta according to redpill definition. And adorkable, according to TvTropes. Yet, he's seen as a lovable and well built character in general, including by me, who's writing this wall of text for some reason. Oh, and do I have to talk about that Mole faced guy? It's a pretty general consensus that his flirt attempts were funny, but realistically they'd probably be creepy, too. Still, he's a good step above the typical manospherian as he still holds some respect for women and sees them as humans.

As the final point of this text, I can actually contest the concept of "Disney lying to men". Especially if, considering how most of the fantasy based, romanticized animations are focused mostly on the feminine public - and yet, the women who do complain of men are aware of how unrealistic Disney princes were and do not accuse it of lying to them about reality. They knew right from the beginning it was just fantasy and fictional. Accusing things made for *children* to be delusional when it leaves obvious remarks about how it's all fantasy *is*, on itself, delusional; something must be really out of place to think it's realistic after growing up.

Note: posted this before but it didn't show up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take u/CrazyTom54 turn this time:


Bepis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL TRPers are a bunch of incubi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, Leviticus.

I hate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.

I mean, wouldn't it be more logical to be the same amount of time to both? :I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get #12. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dolphins

LMAO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehhhhh alright, 'll just make my "nevermind" leave and delete my comments, excuse me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *IS THAT A MOTHERFUCKIN' MOTHER  REFERENCE?!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she thought like that to herself only, then yeah, I would have nothing to do with it.

But "Red pill" thrown in the middle...? Go fuck yourself, dude, you *know* what you're doing instead of a personal preference here. Thinking a sex should be placed higher than the other is surely the easiest route to break the world and your oh so valued society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just look at u/saturnapartments comment again and you can get it.

I see MGTOWs and Incels often complaining of having a low self esteem because of how people perceive each other and such aesthetically; it's the same thing. Men probably would do the same wasn't for the "makeup is girly".

I personally don't use any, but that doesn't mean I don't have self esteem problems. I don't use because I dislike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
