<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1410</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lot of friends who are vegan, and I myself enjoy eating meat free as well. I like the fact that there's a lot more vegan recipes here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can almost hear the "Uh, sorry mate, I have to deal with something here. I'll call you back in a minute." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how many clips they used to put it together. Minus the last one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if she actually knows that she's anglo-saxon, or if she just think it's cool.

Since the anglo-saxons goes back to the fucking 5th century. That's 1600 years of family research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never going to punish her for what my last girlfriend did to me. That would be outrages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, random internet person! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a rather morbid name for a dish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the person I went on a date with? We matched on tinder, haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 12:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, that was intentional, since I didn't want to cludder the picture with 175 characters. And since everybody knows that sucess kid means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 11:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made this wrong?

Yeah. We're taking it slow and steady. I have large trust issues, so I try to keep it pretty low and mellow in the beginning. I know far too well how things end up if you're going to fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 11:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear that you're in a loving relationship! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 11:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to take it slow, at least for now. Because of my prior problems with trust issues, that has gotten worse during my last relationship, it's not been "easy" for me to get into something new.

But me and her are just taking it slow and steady right now. I know far too well how stuff ends up when going too fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 01:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to add that. My bad.

I don't mind noise. I actually prefer a keyboard that makes some sound. It's kinda soothing imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a complete noob when it comes to mechanical keyboards and I'm looking for something to use both for gaming and for typing. I would say the most important part is the typing.

I have no clue about anything when it comes to different switches. The only experience I have is with Cherry MX Black and I feel that they are bit too "soggy" (if you catch my drift) to type longer text posts with.

I found the ANNE PRO, but I want something with the numpad as well, since I use it a lot when I work. I liked the ANNE PRO a lot because of the price, so I'd be glad to have something in the cheaper range. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got out of an abusive relationship, broke down and didn't know when or how I was going to recover. Recently went on a date and we're really hitting it off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 00:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daeshfest Open Air Festival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 22:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how, but I've always had a knack for giving oral sex to a female. I think it might be because I never really associated with pornos. I've never seen it as something that you had to be forced to do, but instead something I enjoyed to do. In comparison to a lot of guys who brag about how much they love eating pussy and then backs off as soon as they are asked to do it.

My best recommendation would probably be something in the line of what /u/zyzzyva82 mentions. There is some really good literature out there.

Have you tried talking to your S/O outside of the bed about it? It might feel awkward, but I think it's something you both could benefit from. Him talking about "his idea" of giving, and you telling him what he should/could do better etc.

I hope it turns out good for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 22:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I just found one of my new favorite frogs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an accident waiting to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best guess is that they are ornamental. I recognize the cap of the middle bottle and I'm pretty sure it's just molded plastic.

Probably not anything fancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get's blown off.

"You're just mad I blew you off."

Eh... ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of my favorite gifs, ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the ending scenes of Requiem for a Dream.

That's a movie you only watch once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eeeeeeey! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use the term "tryhard" as well when it's a person not knowing what they hell they are doing, but still keeps on trying to be over the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 22:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will read that! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is "tryharding" used as something negative? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a person who plays a lot of online games in competitive modes, from time to time I stumble upon salty people using "tryhard" as some kind of slur for people who try to do their best tow in. I feel that it's mostly used by a member of the losing team as an "excuse" for losing the game.

Why do you think it's used as something negative when it's basically what the competitive mode is based around? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first things that pops to my mind is either some kind of tag, or it might also be a hobo sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I immediately thought about this sub when this picture showed up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definetely recommend it! I started playing it a while back, stopped and played something else, but got in to it a few weeks back and I am so hooked! It is so relaxing and comfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "LET ME DOWN. I AM THE KING OF THE OCEAN." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still an accident you don't see coming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Lawyers made me remove a reference to a certain movie scene in which a man says 'ass to ass'." I lol'ed pretty hard there.

Overall the music video idea is really funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's something special about bodies that bounce when they hit the ground. It hurts watching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously. But since he didn't expect to fuck up, he didn't think of that either.

That's like saying that money spent on repairing a car that crashed because of ice patches could be spent on something better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sandwich looks fucking delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it as "1991 yearbook photo. Yugoslavian family [....]" and thought for a second that I was at /r/blunderyears </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a whisky decanter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother worked as a photographer before. I sent her the album link and asked her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably love coriander more than the next guy, but isn't that a bit too much with the powder as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to original post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't it yellow like at the cinema? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 23:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 22:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, co-presents then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 20:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! My bad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those not knowing - Rachel Riley is the co-host of the ~~BBC~~ Channel 4 show Countdown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Mathematician] Rachel Riley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Countdown] Mathematician Rachel Riley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 17:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, bit it's not a live show, a runway or an actual strip show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, your cheekbones are to die for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this OnStageGW? It's from a film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 16:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bobcat needs tp for its bunghole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 15:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the best projects I've seen here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My condolences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 04:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have thought about too, as well. And it might be that. It might me the fact that I am around people that knows people that knows people, that I know. So everyone knows everyone.

So no offence taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second from right - that's a low hanging ball.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I'd match with you, haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are super gorgeous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this. It kinda freaked me out that you sound almost exactly the same 20 years later in your newer vids, but I got used to it!

Also, what is up with the wet spot on the backside of the arm on your t-shirt? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My deepest condolences.

In 2014, my 15 year old sister killed herself. I still haven't accepted it. I don't think I ever will do it, deep down inside. For me, she's just studying abroad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in '92, so I am kinda in the middle of what people call the millennial generation. The way I see it is that people my age and younger are both extremely self centered and egoistic. Of course not everyone, but a large chunk that I see on a daily basis act both like they are the center of the universe and like other people don't matter.

One thing I've noticed about people around my age (+-2/3 years) is that they define themselves not on who or what they are, but what a doctor tells them. People my age demand that other people change according to them instead of trying to cooperate with the world in a way where both work together.

I don't know how many times I've got the argument "I have *insert mental illness here*, so I am allowed to act like this.". It's not "Just so you know, I have this mental illness in where I can go into fits of rage, or fits of sadness, and I can't really control it, but I want you to know.". I have had friends telling me that I am a bad person because I can't cope with them being complete assholes. "You know that this is how I act, I can't control it."

I am myself diagnosed with both severe depression, anxiety and panic attacks. I get panic attacks almost on a daily basis. I don't blame my actions on them. I don't tell people that things I've done during those moments were correct and brush it off with "I'm sick." The world doesn't work that way, no matter how much you want it to.

A second thing that really grinds my gears is that some kind of "post ironic" movement has sprouted. I call it "post ironic" because the people in that category act in a way that I would do when I was maybe 13 or 14 on the internet. When being edgy and "ironic/sarcastic". It's the "I don't care what people think about it, it's just the internet. I don't care if I hurt someone.". The difference is that these people aren't 13. They are 20+ and have started acting like this. "What do you mean people take death threats seriously? It's just the internet." I've found two things that these people often have in common:

* Intentionally spelling like half of their keys on the keyboard are missing

* Listening to Yung Lean and similar artists.

I'm not bashing YL, for the bashing of it (which I easily could do otherwise, because I despise that kid), but it's just a thing I've found them to have in common. If you look at some interviews with YL, he really comes out as an asshole. I remember one interview where the journalist said "I heard some stuff that you could be kinda rowdy and annoying before shows."

His reply was "Haha, yeah. One time when we were gigging in Berlin, we annoyed the sound tech so much that he threw an ash tray after us. That was hilarious."

The third, and maybe the most controversial, thing is - they are lazy. And as with my first point, it's not everyone. But I've never seen so many people from a single generation that demands so much without wanting to give or do something back. 

I was recently unemployed and the "activity" (as they call it) was filled to the brim with people my age who didn't want to start at the bottom or work with something that wasn't top. Many of they, when asked "What do you want to work with?" often said "I don't know." and when asked "Well, would you consider working with this?" the reply was, in nine out of ten cases, "No, it's boring.". A lot of them wanted jobs, but they didn't want an education or start from the bottom. It's never their own fault when things go wrong. It's always someone elses. You're not supposed to work for your earning, you're supposed to be served it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Who doesn't fart in public?

2. What the fuck is up with his arm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yayaya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In comparison to me, haha. I was 5'4" when I was twelve. Then during three years, I grew to 6'4". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 21:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12?! I would say like 15-16. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come you can't do lines with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does that work out? I remember having a laser mouse a few years back that would freak the fuck out when used on a mousepad with a lot of colors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are very welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really, really want to hear this story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so number three is a lie. I love coffee. It's one of my passions.

Explanations:

1. I studied music in high school and during first and second year, choir was mandatory. I had a habit of not eating breakfast, but instead go through the days with coffee and sodas. Just before our first year ended, we had a school concert where the choir performed. I, being a second bass (the lowest range), was placed standing on a chair in the back row. Before the concert, I was feeling a bit queasy, but I shrugged it off since I always feel that way before a concert. During the concert, I kept getting more and more queasy and started cold sweats. At that point I thought "Fuck if, our dirigent can get pissed, I just have to explain to him afterwards. I have to sit down." The second I think that, I black out. I woke up with the two guys next to me holding me in one arm each. At least I wasn't the only one who passed out that day!

2. During the first semester of my last year in elementary school, the national television broadcasting company had the idea of switching out all of regular teachers for "super teachers" and film that for half a year.

 The backstory is that my school was one of the worst schools in the country when it comes to students grades. I think about 43% of the students from the classes two years prior to us got into high school. So they came up with this pitch. They probably thought that since the two other classes were that bad, the next is probably the same. And they weren't completely wrong. So they switched out all the teachers and put in "super teachers".

 They recorded practially every single day of school, all classes, for six months before airing it on national TV. In the end, the show was awarded with a trophy for best documentary series.

/u/Jirajirajira  /u/mr_malhotra /u/btwIAMAzoophile /u/MBncsa /u/agirlhasnoname99 /u/Joi_Boi /u/Disembob /u/IaniteThePirate /u/Coolfoolsalot /u/literallymagic /u/PatrioticGreek /u/Bacon_Hero /u/sooperlooper1 /u/Cesare_MA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are absolutely beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 01:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to bed now, will reply to the posts arriving during the night and then tell what my lie was! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want the first thing to be true.

I think number two is a lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, the situation isn't that fun, though! Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope number two is a lie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna go with three. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're supposed to guess which is a lie ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your friend did not get arrested in Abu Dhabi! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to hope that number three is a lie, since I know very well how it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna go with number two as the lie, and hope for number one being true, because I agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Writer and editor at Online Marketing", "Social Media Account Manager at Online Marketing" and "Accountant at Small Business".

That's the kind of jobs people who don't have any jobs put in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reference](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=476e_ck5H-M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to let some people reply before I tell which one is the lie. (And also I can't seem to get the spoiler tag to work here)

I hope number three is correct, so I am going to say that number two is a lie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, only when they're dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to let some people reply before I tell which one is the lie. (And also I can't seem to get the spoiler tag to work here) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to let some people reply before I tell which one is the lie. (And also I can't seem to get the spoiler tag to work here)

I would say number one is a lie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to let some people reply before I tell which one is the lie. (And also I can't seem to get the spoiler tag to work here)

I am going to say that number three is a lie, because I'm hoping that number one is true. I just got the idea of maybe starting skating again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who here would like to play a game of two truths and a lie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this over at /r/AskWomen and the mods at /r/askmen didn't like it at all, so I am trying it over here!

List three things about yourself. Two things that are true and one that is a lie. It is then our job to guess which one is false.

And I guess that I, as OP, should start.

* In high school, I passed out during a show with our school choir and knocked over two people standing in front of me.

* I frequently starred in an award winning TV show.

* I can't stand the taste of coffee. It makes me want to vomit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of my friends who are involved in BDSM are poly, but I have realized that I could never be it. I have too much trust issues and not enough self confidence to be able to have a poly relationship.

Even though I would like to be able to have multiple partners, I know that it isn't fair for my S/O (if I would have one) if I am allowed and she isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the average delivery of Postnord here in Sweden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, alright! Thank you! I forgot that I had remove and reinstall a bunch of addons, so I don't have BTTV at the moment!

Solved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are people spamming "haHAA" in the AGDQ chat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AGDQ is running live right now and one of the chat memes is people typing "haHAA" multiple times. Anyone know why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who here would like to play a game of two truths and a lie? (Shamelessly stolen from our sister sub) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she believed she could break her face, then it's a success? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also /r/trashyboners  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-shirts for my height and things to go with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 19:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 6'4"/193cm and I love t-shirts. My biggest problem when buying t-shirts is that they're either fitted perfectly around my body, but too short, or they are long enough, but then baggy.

I feel comfortable with more slim t-shirts but I only have two or three that actually fit both around the body and with my height.

Are there any specific where one can order shirts that fit with my body type?

Also, what goes good with t-shirts? Especially the slim fitted. I usually wear jeans and a belt together with a hoodie and a flat cap.

Pictures can be provided if needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 14:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's kind of the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks nordic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It puts the lotion in the basket, or else it gets the hose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfotunately I have not fixed the problem.

I talked to the PS support and they couldn't do anything. I just have to wait until sunday when our properly working PS4 is back inhouse to see if I can fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have not yet, but I'm heading down there later to see if I can fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried with four different controllers on two different consoles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't do that. As soon as I start the PS4, I get the "Welcome to your PlayStation. Press the PS button to connect your controller" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Tried different cords as well. Made sure that it worked since the controller pulsated in yellow as well.

I asked another friend of mine and shall try her ideas tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried that as well. The controller just flashes white for a while and then goes back to sleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a mayhem shirt I'm seeing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazilian pianist realizes that the piano isn't working properly. Handles it perfectly! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually a griffin and it's the crest, not the flag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since /u/kezar23 posted [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/vexillology/comments/5m5xdx/flag_of_swedish_finns/) thread about the flag of the Swedish Finns, I got the idea to post the flag (though unofficial) of the finnish swedes, which is a minority group in Finland.

Internet points for anyone who can say where this design of flag is, officially, used! No googling! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unofficial flag of the Finnish Swedes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, alright. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not put some kind of liquid in it for the actor to drink? It's not like an ounce of water for a five minute scene will make them piss themself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Postal 2 was the game where I realized I was into bsdm... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racist snowflake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm feeling really stupid now, but I can't for my life figure out what "C/S" stands for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 15:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting for it to pulse yellow and then press the ps button. Nothing happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Oooooh](http://vignette4.wikia.nocookie.net/powerlisting/images/a/a9/I-see-what-you-did-there.jpg/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/480?cb=20130925101955) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taken from your own sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that they exchange swedish crowns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's trashy af, but that tattoo is hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried with having them turned off, having the controller connected and pressing the ps button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 00:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest pet peeve there is in series and movies. When they audibly have to show that there's something in the cup, so they make it sound like there's barely any liquid left. No matter how much or how little they've drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tinder in a nutshell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Soft brexit, hard brexit, white brexit, grey brexit, I want a red, white and blue brexit!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me, or does it look like the cups they are tipping over aren't actually containing anything?

"It's perfect for bedtime!"

Or for when you're shitfaced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS4 controllers refusing to link with anything other than the first console? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work as an administrator at our local video game club and today it was my duty to see if our consoles's were working properly. Because of a few reasons, we do not have the consoles rigged up permanently atm, so I had to check so everything was alright before sending them of to a convention for the week.

When testing the first console, everything went great. But when trying to test the second and third console, the controllers refused to connect with the consoles. 

No matter what I did, they wouldn't connect to it. Plugging them in and pressing the PS button didn't work, resetting them with the button on the bottom did nothing, and when trying pressing down Share and PS button it did nothing except making it flash rapidly. I tried with different cables in case there was something wonky with the cable I used, but it worked fine. 

When reconnecting the first PS4 to the HDMI and power (I only had one console plugged in at the same time, trying to make it easier to connect one controller to all of them one at a time), the controllers connected to the console without a problem.

What have I done wrong and what should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, he looks like the sweetest person.

This brought a tear to my eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first thing was that I enjoyed scratching, but I tried biting pretty early as well. Mostly because one of my ticks is to bite on things. Basically anything I could get my hands on, I would put it in my mouth.

Got too much to carry and still have something small, for example keys? Put it between your teeth!

After that biting has become one of my main things.

I was curious to strangulation as well and I realized that it was the thing that I really loved.

One thing that I found out by random was with my ex. She was having a lot of anxiety over school and when we went to sleep she started bawling her eyes out. That gave me a massive erection, which really wasn't the reaction I had expected from myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never, ever, ever, ever, ever, ever press down on the windpipe. 

When you do that, you cut off the oxygen to the lungs, which not only hurts like a bitch (try pressing your finger against your own throat) and can actually hurt the person permanently, but it puts the body in a kind of panic mode as well. When the lungs aren't fed oxygen they will do everything they can to get more. That is why you can't hold your breath until you're blue, because the body forces you to breathe in. That is also why it hurts like a bitch when inhaling water. The body forces you to inhale and the water goes into your lungs.

What you want to do is cut off the blood that goes to the brain by putting pressure on the external carotid arteries which are the main arteries that delivers blood to the brain. That way you're cutting of the oxygen filled blood going to the brain, without putting the body into panic mode. You're more putting it in... sleep mode. If one would like to put it that way. Because as soon as you let go and the brain gets blood again, it starts up again and the person wakes up.

But you also have to remember to be very careful when doing this, as lack of oxygen to the brain can also damage the brain when exposed to it for too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...that looks like lemon juice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks rather yellow and lumpy, so I can agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The boss of a friend of mine accidentally forgot to remove the PornHub tab on his work iPad. He was out of office when two customers arrive to discuss a horse they're thinking about buying.

The only one who knew the passcode for the iPad, apart from the boss himself, was the boss' 9 year old son. They call him in to open the iPad for them. So yeah, you can see where this is going.

My friend and her coworker did the only thing they could think of afterwards. Ordered PornHub t-shirts for the boss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being in the beginning of my teens when 4chan blew up, if my (or my friends) parents would see our browser history, they would probably ask what the fuck we were doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's mostly the race thing that you're bringing up that I don't understand. But we might just be misunderstanding eachother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 14:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a scene that I've never understood, haha. His "super" could mean "Ok, there's penises" or "Ok, there's vaginas". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I don't agree with your opinion, I understand what you mean. I also read your previous reply about living in South Africa, so I can understand why you see it that way as well.

The one thing I'd like to take away from that list of things is "age". Since there's always a lower border that I'm not willing to cross. But maybe you're talking about people being older than oneself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember watching QI and learning that wifes and family of captured troops (I think) where not allowed to send playing cards or knitted things to the troops since they could contain secret information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like such an idiot for going "Why is Greenland pictured in the pie chart?" for a solid minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, bi isn't to do with my skin colour. Bi is someone who's attracted to both male and female. But I go under pan since I don't care what gender the person has or not. Especially since I have a lot of friends who are non binary as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pan. Always known that I wasn't straight, but learnt like two or three years ago that bisexual didn't fit.

And yeah, I just want to be thinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god.

I didn't notice the underline... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 29 just looks durpy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two occasions.

Being 14/15 and having my first girlfriend. At this time, I was also starting to experiencing my first real panic attacks. At one time, during an attack, I picked up my phone and dumped her. That's dick move number one. 

 She first said that she didn't want to have contact with me, but after a while she unblocked me on msn (good old times) and we started chatting again. After a week or so, she blocked me again, telling me that she didn't want to have any contact with me.

Me, being 15 years old and an idiot thinks "Oh, she just can't let it go. Why can't we just be friends?" so from time to time, I try shooting her a text. If I've passed her on the street or something. I kept doing this for quite a while, with the same mantra in my head. "She can't let it go. She can't let it go. She can't let it go."

It wasn't until the day I added her on facebook and she sent me a message saying "*You're really not giving up?*" that I realized. I started with replying "*Haha, you're the one who can't let it all go and become friends.*" and got a reply saying that she doesn't want to be my friend ever again and that I was a complete dick. She couldn't understand how thick my head was ([Mandatory](http://i.imgur.com/2H9nylb.png) meme) or how I couldn't see it all. It was at that moment I realized "Holy shit. She's not the one with problems letting go. I am."

 I ended the conversation with telling her all of this. That I never realized what a jackass I am and how I never understood that I was the one who couldn't let go. The last thing I wrote was that I was sorry and that I will never try and contact her again.

Second occassion!

A few years back, me and a few friends were visiting a music festival, and as everyone who's ever been to a larger music festival knows - losing each other is a bit too easy. Especially when the festival's major crowd is described as 6'+, blond hair and beard.

Either way! We bumped in to some acquaintances who in the end wouldn't leave us alone. Especially one girl who was super annoying. She was also having a massive turn on for one of my friends. And he did not have the same... feelings for her. After a while, we did our best to try and lose her in the crowd. Like deliberately walking in different directions away from each other and then meeting up at a predetermined spot. The problem was - no matter what we did, she would always find one of us.

Eventually we got rid of her. We got the brilliant idea of meeting up at the camping spot. The place where her ticket didn't let her enter.

Fast forward a few years and me and a few friends were sitting at  a bar. We were six or seven people and we were talking about two acquaintances we had bumped into during the evening (one of them being this chick) and I start telling this story about how annoying and bothering she was. I go on for a good five minutes on how I really didn't like her until one of the guys says "*Uhm... you know that's his girlfriend, right?*" and points to the guy sitting almost next to me.

The hole I wanted to drop down into could not be big enough.

The weird part is that he took it extremely well. He just said "*Well, you can't like everyone*" and didn't hold any grudges against me when I met him a few months later.

Talking to him about it a few years later, he said that he wasn't mad at me and that he also realized what a twat she was just some months after that.

One thing is for certain. SHE was told what I had said, because she would never try to say hi to me again, ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am interested in why it says "Yes" and "On". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the Prestige

I just read through the plot of that movie three times, and I don't understand anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks delicious af, but what is up with all these "chicken lasagna" recipies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
