<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8940</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked in a bookstore for a long time and wish there were more customer that had done this.  I spent time on those reviews darn it!

There were so many fiction books that came through that I heard all these great things about, read a 100 pages and just had to stop because I was so annoyed with the accolades heaped on it or just could not for the life of me get into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do lies create best-sellers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen several articles lately on how a huge portion of people lie about having read a book they really didn't.  They've even created lists of the mostly commonly lied about books - http://www.nydailynews.com/entertainment/books-lied-reading-article-1.3108606

After having read a few books that made the best-sellers lists, were featured in magazines and raved about on social media that I didn't think lived up to the hype, I'm now wondering if some best-sellers are simply created because people want to appear better read than they are.  If the right person recommends it will people buy it, never read it, and rave about it anyway?  I know that we all bring our own perspectives to books and there will be a vast assortment of those loving and hating the same book, so have I simply missed the point of some these hits or has social media and celebrity made certain books over rated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping this is along the lines of what you're looking for...

S. (Ship of Theseus)  by J.J. Abrams and Doug Dorst is...  a book within a book with clues and a mystery on top of a mystery.  It's truly amazing.

It's classified as YA and the story itself is definitely more for teenagers, but there is "Cathy's Book" by Sean Stewart.  There's a "evidence pack" (in the paperback it's all printed in the back as opposed to being separate physical pieces in the original publishing) that has phone numbers, websites, etc that you can call or look at to help fill in more of the story.  There are 2 sequels to this.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone said - used bookstores.  Then thrift shops (Goodwill, Salvation Army, independent charity shops).  Many libraries have used book stores attached to them.  If you're in the US or Canada there's booksalefinder.com that can give you a better idea of when the big area/library/charity book sales are.

Coupons, bargain books, clearance at big box stores.  Checking used listings on Amazon, checking ebay.

If you have an e-reader, check out bookbub.com - they'll at least give you notification of e-books that are on sale or free.  If you aren't branded with an e-reader but have a tablet, download the various apps (nook, kindle, etc).  Many library systems also have the ability to borrow ebooks.

Sign up at sites that do giveaways or ARCs in exchange for reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what counts as a less well known winner but I recommend Number the Stars, Jacob have I loved, The Westing Game, Island of the Blue Dolphins, The witch of blackbird pond, Cassie Woodlawn, and I absolutely loved this year's winner - The Girl who drank the moon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
