<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5492</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the opposite, I did PHUL and then switched over to ICF.

I really enjoyed PHUL though. I had fun going to the gym and the split and exercises incorporated were really fun. I usually spent an hour to an hour and a half in the gym so it wasn't that time-consuming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 18:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love them. I'll eat them as a snack in between meals or before the gym. Cookies and Cream is best imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 18:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My groin kills during squats. Is there anything I can do about this? I do limber 11 for warm-up and other stretches but no matter what once I go down on squat my groin feels like its tearing. But it isn't a lasting feeling though. It only feels that way when squatting. Anyone know what could be causing this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two-day rest is for more structure since then it will be a consistent 7-day cycle. Over the summer when I had more time I only did a 6-day cycle with one rest day in between each workout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus there is Close-Grip Bench on "B" days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 00:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to do ladder drills for lacrosse. One rep would be down and back, and we would do it for 10 reps. Usually 3 or 4 sets.

The best time is after the workout. Yes, you'll be tired from already lifting but it will be more beneficial. Ladder drills take a lot out of you and it would affect your lifts negatively if you did it before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 21:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 21:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a few samples of MuscleTech Platinum Casein (Gourmet Mik Choc) over the summer and it tasted pretty good. Mixed great with milk. Water was pretty good as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 21:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two questions:

1) What exactly do aminos do for your workout? I'm currently taking 2 scoops of PWO but would it be worth it to switch to one scoop of PWO and one scoop of aminos during my workout?

2) How do you count breaded chicken cutlets? MFP lists all these different options with all different macros. I like to get a buffalo chicken cutlet from my local deli about once a week but never know how to track it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 20:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVEN THE MINOR LEAGUE STOVE IS HOT  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 00:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AT COOPERSTOWN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 17:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had someone to workout with from time to time. I love being at the gym alone don't get me wrong, it's basically my "me" time. Sometimes though it would be nice to have someone there to chat with and motivate each other. It's tough sometimes to mentally hype yourself up without help.

The gym I go to at home is basically full of people 30+ and I'm only 20. Also at school most of my friends play on sport teams so they already go to the gym at different times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 17:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: Don't judge a book by it's cover because the book might deadlift more than you.

This isn't my victory but hopefully it counts. Yesterday I was doing deadlifts and my gym doesn't have chalk and mine hasn't come in yet from M S. So I ended up doing 3x5 of 255lbs because that's all my grip could take.

I'm on my 2nd warmup and this kid comes up to me and asks if I'm using the bar that was in front of my in the squat rack. I say no so he takes it and low and behold he sets up for deadlifts. I'm not a judgemental person but wveryone has those moments in the gym. This kid didn't strike me as a big lifter or someone who is pulling weight so I was curious to see how much he does. 135(check), 165(check), 185(check). Pretty impressed at this point and now I'm working on my first working set. He moves up to 225 and gets 5 reps. Then 245lbs. Now I'm looking like a fool cause I doubted this kid and he is lifting almost as much. I finish up my last set and am unloading when he pulls 265 for 5 and finishes up.

He walked past and I told him nice job. He wasn't big or anything and was not expecting what happened. So good on him for making me feel stupid and pulling 265lbs no chalk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 22:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry Bill. I thought it was a good idea as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 22:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SLATER'S MISCALL IS THE  TO SUCCESS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 17:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suffer from substance-induced mood disorder so I know I had too much to drink when I end up trying to fight everyone and everything I see, including that chair I just tripped over. And then I become very depressed and have to be consoled and put to bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 17:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't finish with a condom on so if I need endurance I throw on the trusty weenie hat.

In all other instances I think recite the alphabet backwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 17:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to class. Seriously just fucking go. I had a professor this semester give me a B+ because I went to every class, even though I failed two of his tests. Some professors just want people to show up and it can tremendously help your grade. Even if you never pay attention it just helps that you are there.

Ratemyprofessor.com also is a great tool to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 07:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got dumped, found out I don't meet the minimum requirements for grad school and just finished 6 hours with of homework.

But I hit a new deadlift PR, so I've got that going for me, which is nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 07:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same man. I feel you. We can get through this together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 05:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TAKIN' CARE OF BUSINESS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 05:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IS OVER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 05:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE BALLGAME IS OVER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 05:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AND THE BALLGAME IS FUCKING OVER. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 06:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE BALL GAME IS OVER </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 16:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started middle school.

I'm a junior in college now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 15:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone going to the game today? First time at Citi and I'm so excited!

What's the best place to eat? Also best shop?

I hope to see some flamingos today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 17:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bench is stalling very badly on 135-140. The mental aspect is just killing me. My chest is always just pretty weak in general. I have two options that I'm considering.

I'm running ICF and know you arent supposed to change anything. I feel as though chest isnt emphasized enough. Could I do one of two things?

1) change bench to a 5x3 format instead of 3x5. Same amount of reps, but easier in the mental aspect.

Or

2) add in DB bench(3x6/moderate weight) for my volume.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 04:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I WANT WHATEVER WAS IN THOSE COOKIES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 04:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITS OKAY. THEY DONT KNOW WHAT KIND OF COOKIES.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 04:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step 1: Bring back the Captain

Step 2: Have him bring cookies

Step 3: ????

Step 4: Hit massive bombs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixed. Mah bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Results) Who is the most underrated NHL player in each position? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 18:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello again!

So after of week of leaving the poll open and gathering around 350 (serious) responses I have put together the top 5 list of underrated players in each position. There a ton of landslides for the top ranking and even a few surprises who didn't make it.

**Centers**

1. Nicklas Backstrom *NHL Stats: GP:577 G:145 A:427 P:572*
2. Bryan Little *NHL Stats GP:556 G:146 A:197 P:343*
1. Anze Kopitar *NHL Stats GP:683 G:218 A:392 P:610*
1. Kyle Turris *NHL Stats GP:398 G:93 A:133 P:226*
* Ryan Nugent-Hopkins *GP:258 G:65 A:123 P:188*

**Left Wing**

1. Max Pacioretty *NHL Stats GP:399 G:144 A:136 P:280*
1. Andrew Ladd *NHL Stats GP:691 G:185 A:235 P:420*
1. Nick Foligno *NHL Stats GP: 545 G:116 A:163 P:279*
* Taylor Hall: *NHL Stats GP: 299 G:106 A:157 P:263*
1.  Jaden Schwartz *NHL Stats GP:207 G:62 P:73 P:135*

**Right Wing**

1. Blake Wheeler *NHL Stats GP:533 G:147 A:215 P:362*
1. Kyle Okposo *NHL Stats GP:450 G:117 A:188 P:305*
1. Jiri Hudler *NHL Stats GP: 604 G:145 A:226 P:371*
1. Wayne Simmonds *NHL Stats GP: 524 G:139 A:145 P:284*
1. Phil Kessel *NHL Stats GP:668 G:247 A:273 P:520*

**Defense**

1. Chris Tanev *NHL Stats GP:226 G:10 A:37 P:47*
1. Roman Josi *NHL Stats GP:253 G:38 A:91 P:129*
* Marc-Edouard Vlasic *NHL Stats GP:670 G:39 A:148 P:187*
1. Tyson Barrie *NHL Stats GP:186: G:27 A:77 P:104*
1. Victor Hedman *NHL Stats GP:392 G:39 A:143 P:182*

**Goalies**

1. Cory Schneider *NHL Stats GP:212 GAA: 2.17 SV%:.925*
1. Steve Mason *NHL Stats GP:351 GAA:2.71 SV%:.910*
1. Braden Holtby *NHL Stats GP:178 GAA:2.44 SV%:.921*
1. Craig Anderson *NHL Stats GP:406 GAA:2.72 SV%:.915*
1. Corey Crawford *NHL Stats GP:268 GAA:2.34 SV%:.917*

And now...

**Top 5 overall underrated players**

1. Cory Schneider
1. Max Pacioretty
1. Blake Wheeler
1. Nicklas Backstrom
1. Steve Mason

Thank you to all who participated in the survey! It was fun reading all of the different players people thought were underrated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 21:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking great my man!

I know the feeling of eating a shit ton of food. I would eat two servings of every meal and then snack all day. My family is very unhealthy. At 17 I weighed my heaviest of 215lbs all from eating the food my family bought and cooked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 19:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cutting version is the same as the regular. Only difference is that the main lifts is 3x5 and accessories are 2x8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 18:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I would visit it would be for 2-3 days. Usually 3-4 weeks in between visits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 18:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah once you get a little familiar with your cafe you'll get the ins and outs of it. Be nice to the workers and they'll give you whatever you need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 18:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is what I am doing now on ICF. I think I just needed to deload, work on form and get confidence.

Bench has always been mentally tough for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 17:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly if you are a beginner I say Ice Cream Fitness 5x5. More volume that SL and I love the accessory work.

If you have pretty good lift numbers i'd go with PHUL. PHUL got me pretty toned on the 6-weeks I did it and it was always fun. I also enjoyed having 4 days in the gym.

For HIIT look up the bodybuilding.com 8-week program. It is basically just running, so nothing too complicated. I always work up a sweat and feel great after </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 17:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get all my big meals from my school cafeteria.

They are pretty good at meeting what I want. I can get egg whites, whole wheat bread/pasta, salads. Stuff like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 16:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat on campus and have a meal plan. If you track calories it should be easy to find your school's food supplier on MFP and use that to help you. I do buy snacks and things as well though (such as peanut butter, bread, protein bars and tuna) to snack on in my dorm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 15:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With ICF I do it 4 times a week with 3 rest days, so I'm on a weird 6-day schedule with it.

HIIT is about 15-20 mins. I do 15 second sprints with 60 sec jog for 10 sets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 15:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this wasn't me, but my friend who texted me this yesterday while on vacation.

He was working out in the hotel gym which only has one bench. The only people there were him and some other kid. He was doing sets of dumbell bench and going good. Then the kid comes over and doesn't ask to work in or ask how many sets he has left, he just says "hey I'm using this now and proceeds to bench as well." My friend is a pretty nice dude and was kind of shocked so he just agreed and didn't cause anything. Although he got really angry when the kid wouldn't gwt off the bench after his sets and he would have to continously ask him to move.

When I saw that I actually got pretty angry as well, goddamn entitled brats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 15:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would bake the chicken breast and then weigh it out on a scale.

For pasta I used mfp to see what a serving size of dry past was (i.e. 2 oz dry=1 cup cooked) so I would weigh a bowl, then put the pasta in the bowl and just subtract the bowl from the total weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 07:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are 2x8. Except cable crunches are still 3x10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 06:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Home from the summer. I get my eggs from the supermarket and the chicken breast from a local butcher shop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 06:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is 17-18% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 03:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just personal preference  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 02:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though people say my bench is high compared to my other numbers bench is my hardest lift. I have plateaued at 145 for about 5 months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 02:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ICF all the way. Towards week 9 I began to become skinny fat. ICF helped me avoid that plus I love the program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 02:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 1.5-2 pounds a week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 01:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I started at a 1000cal deficit and have stayed there.

And yes I do cardio about 2-3 times a week. I tun a HIIT program </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 01:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome man!

Where you playing if you don't mind my asking?

As for advice, school comes first. The season will be rough. you'll have a lot of classwork as well as practices that will take up about 3 hours of your day. If you are struggling, talk to your coach, a captain, anyone. Don't hide it like I did. The best thing is to face a problem.

It'll be a great time though. I am still good friends with the entire team and some of them are brothers to me. You'll develop connections and relationships that will last forever. Have fun, play hard, party hard and work hard. Good luck to you man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 01:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying I don't go parallel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 01:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around 1600-1700.

I've added a little more fat to my diet to keep my hormones in check </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 01:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 01:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never took a cheat day if I could help it. The only time I went over calories is if I went to visit friends or my girlfriend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 01:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha hoping no one would notice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just use the stopwatch app on my iPhone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.

150g of protein, 173g of carbs and 40g of fat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope just natural gut ahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No still on a cut till I hit 145lbs. And i actually workout 4 times a week because I only take 3 rest days instead of 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My new TDEE is around 2200-2300 as well.

When I first started out 2400 was the low side. The highest I got was 2600. Chose 2400 because I felt 2600 was too high </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For now I have 3 rest days. Two of those rest days I do HIIT.

I have a track near my house so I use that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well like I said in another comment I had horrible deadlift form so I have deloaded a couple times throughout the 12 weeks to fix it. I now add 10lbs to my deadlift every time I do them. Currently at 175lbs. Really easy. I'm sure the more I progress the more my lifts even out.

Also when I lifted for lacrosse we always did bent-over rows but never deadlifts. So i do have more experience with them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 22:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I follow the 8-week HIIT program in the wiki. Right now I do a 15 sec sprint and then 60 sec jog. Repeat 10 times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 21:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I know. I think I was around 25-26%.

Now I'm guessing 17-18% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
