<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1334</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 22:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgetfulness is defintely a part of ADHD. I believe it is connected to the inattention and lack of focus component. You don't pay attention to what day it is or what you're doing so you do things like get ready for school on a Saturday. Or you don't pay attention to what month it is so you look for homework in July. Or you don't focus and pay attention to when you put your keys down somewhere so you can't remember where you put them. Everybody forgets things, but it's a lot worse with ADHD. When you don't pay attention or focus when you're doing something, it makes it a lot easier for your brain to forget whatever it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackberries are technically a whole different thing. Sometimes the blue raspberry fruit is referred to as black raspberry though since like I said they are more a blue-black. But yeah, so that's where blue raspberry comes from. FUN FACT: They started using blue raspberry as a flavor instead of a raspberry flavor because, back in the day, there was cherry, watermelon, and strawberry and they didn't want to have yet another red flavoring because it'd be too confusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is. It comes from the Rubus Leucodermis plant which produces a different type of raspberry that is blue. You are right, they do put bright blue food coloring in blue raspberry flavored things because the fruit is more of a blue-black than a straight blue. But a blue raspberry is a real thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you don't. Blue raspberry is not a mix of blueberry and raspberry. It is a specific, different type of raspberry that is actually blue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 19:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think so. That's not the publicity they want. People don't want to buy faulty products, so they don't want people showing everybody else that their products are faulty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 18:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also make envelopes where you just peel off a tab and the sticky part is underneath, no licking necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 18:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It never ceases to completely blow my mind that people believe things like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skibs- Notes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 15:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://m.soundcloud.com/skibsinternational/skibs-notes

In my opinion, this guy is absolutely amazing and deserves to be known. I'll make him famous if it kills me. Also check out his East Meets West mixtape. 

What are your honest opinions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 15:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting thought. The only thing is that a criminal working directly with people, especially in the scenarios you're talking about with related crimes, whether right or wrong, even with sufficient supervision, is going to make people very, very uncomfortable and uneasy (for lack of a better word) and consequently probably wouldn't work out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the medicine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is, I don't think it's necessarily wrong. I used to message with a German girl I knew, English was her second language, and she would do things like this all the time. She would turn everything into a contraction. Literally every opportunity. It sounds wrong to native English speakers because that's just not how we say it, but to someone that doesn't live in an English speaking country that learned English as a second language, it probably doesn't sound wrong. The only way to know that that's just not how we talk would be to live in an English speaking country. So I don't think it's necessarily wrong, I just think it's a cultural thing of, for whatever reason, that's just not how we talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true of all drugs. (Which is one reason I believe all drugs should be legal, but that's another discussion for another time.) There's this stigma that drugs ruin your life, harm you, and make you stupid and unsuccessful. But the scientific data doesn't back that up. There are plenty of successful, smart people doing all sorts of drugs, not just marijuana, but people have this stigma about drugs because the stupid, trashy people are the ones that get caught and that we only hear about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 22:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fine to take it as in nothing bad is going to happen to you. Stimulant medications just don't work quite as well if you're sleep deprived and tired. You don't seem like you'd be THAT sleep deprived so it should still work relatively well. So you should be just fine. As long as, depending on how long it lasts you, you can still go to bed tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 01:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an extremely hard pitch to throw and throw well. Most pitchers either don't have the ability to throw and control it well enough to be be an effective pitch. Or they don't want to put in the immense amount of time and work that it would take to make it an effective pitch. It's a really good pitch, just extremely difficult to throw. So most pitchers just don't find it worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PINEAPPLES DON'T HAVE SLEEVES. I had that exact same story on one of my state required tests. It was the weirdest thing. To this day, 6 or 7 years later, my friends, who also took the same test, and me still make jokes about "Pineapples don't have sleeves." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 22:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a dumb picture to represent the word, but I believe the word is supposed to be 'pure'. Unless the 3 pictures combine to make like a sentence or something else like that. In which case I have no idea. But if not, I think it's 'pure' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 19:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even when I was at my worst, if you would've asked me if I was depressed I would have said no. I didn't think I was. It was only until I started my antidepressant that I realized just how bad I was. Now I'm not saying you do have depression. Maybe you don't. And I'm no doctor so take my comments with a grain of salt. All I'm saying is this. Firstly, go to the psychiatrist. You shouldn't be having any doctor other than the psychiatrist dealing with your situation. Secondly, I would recommend trying to get in to see a Psychologist and get a definitive diagnosis of what's going on, if you haven't already, because it sounds like you could possibly either not have ADHD and it's something else entirely, or more likely, there's something else going on with your ADHD that's still causing the problems. And lastly, start seeing a therapist so you can learn things to help you deal with all of this and you can get help with your struggles along with medication. Just my two cents. Best of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 00:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me add, that you are not even close to the only person struggling like this. I struggled the same way. ADHD was also destroying my life. My life was a complete disaster and mess and everything around me was falling apart. And I couldn't do anything about it but stand there and watch as my life just continued to fall apart and turn more and more into shit. It fucking sucks. And I'm sure there are plenty more people on here that can attest to the same thing. Untreated ADHD is one of the hardest and most debilitating disorders to live with. Again, it just fucking sucks. But it can be managed. Which is why it is imperative that you find some way to get to the doctor and get professional help. If you are still taking your medicine, it sounds like your dose probably isn't high enough or you need to be switched to a different medicine. It's obviously not working for you. But getting in to see the doctor, and explaining all this to them is the only way to get that fixed. Hope you can get figured out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 00:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed with Depression along with my ADHD, and I believe my depression was caused in large part because of my ADHD. You sound like you very well could be in the same situation. You absolutely need to go to the doctor and get medication. Nothing worked for me either. Once I got my ADHD medicine and my antidepressant, my life completely changed. It was incredible. It was a life saver. I know you said you haven't gone to the doctor because of money issues, but you need to find a way. Hopefully someone else can offer specific things you can do to still be able to get to the doctor. Do you have insurance? Is there any way you could possibly get insurance? Like I said, you absolutely need to find a way to get to the doctor for help. Best of luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 00:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To specifically answer your question, you WERE just being non-attentive, but I think it's safe to say that that's because of your ADHD. Most people wouldn't start fidling with the seat, while paying no attention to the road whatsoever, as they cruised down the street. And it is not safe for you to drive without medicine, but there are strategies you can implement to keep yourself focused while driving without medicine when you absolutely need to, like in this situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 23:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Driving without your medicine is significantly more dangerous than driving with it. ADHD, because of the issues with focus and attention, understandably so, severely affect your ability to drive a car safely. Most doctors will recommend you take your medicine daily, even when there's nothing specific you absolutely have to get done, because of things like the danger of driving without it. The first day I tried not taking my medicine, I also blew right through a red light. Almost, thankfully I didn't, caused a wreck because there were cars going the other way. I've taken my medicine every day since. I've also been in 4 wrecks, totaling 3 cars before I had my medicine. So yes, it is significantly more dangerous to drive without your medicine, however, in your case, I don't think you really had a choice. You didn't have your medicine and you were on your way to get it. You just need to figure out strategies you can implement in situations like that to keep yourself focused and attentive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 18:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back then, security was not anywhere close to how it is now. Hence how JFK was able to be murdered in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 21:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true. And a very good point. He defintely does need to learn to manage it on his own. And the best thing to do is to help him in managing it on his own. I'm glad it was said that it's not an excuse. I was going to say something about it, but my comment was already long. There's a fine line. People seem to automatically associate having ADHD to being lazy, not caring, and not trying. And that's not always the case. Often times, that's not the case at all. However, it is in no way an excuse to act lazy, or to not care, or to not try. There just have to be ways to manage it.  Like I said, it's important that you be there for him. Support is huge. And goes a long, long way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/-b22rjX2RGc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I replaced the o-rings and that completely fixed the problem. Thanks a ton!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely can't read with music on without my medicine and I haven't really tried with it. Without medicine if there is any sort of noise I often find myself distracted and having to go back and reread things. Even in silence my mind wanders and I always have to go back and reread. It happens so often for me without medicine that reading is almost pointless. With medicine, when I can actually focus, I just focus on what I'm reading and everything else just gets tuned out and almost seems to disappear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will also add that it's probably, often times, just like with everything else he does, not that he doesn't care. That is absolutely not the case. He just doesn't know what to do. Help him through that. You will probably have to take the initiative in fixing things most of the time. My girlfriend hates to do that, but she does because she understands that I don't know how or what I'm supposed to do. I imagine he's the same. Just be there for him, it'll go a long way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Untreated ADHD is a serious struggle for the person themselves as well as someone that is dating them. It can be a struggle for my girlfriend too even, when my medicine wears off. The things you described, as I'm sure you've found, are typical of people with ADHD, which is why dating them can be such a struggle. The fact that you researched it in hopes to understand and want to give it another try shows that you really care about this guy, and is a HUGE step towards making it work. I would just go to him, explain what happened to him, just like you just did to us, tell him that you understand things now, apologize, and say you want to try things again. Hopefully he'll understand and want to try again too now that you have more knowledge about what's going on. As far as what to do while dating him, each person with ADHD is different, but the two biggest things, in my opinion generally apply to everybody. If he's like me, he hates his ADHD and these things you described about him just as much as you do, so you absolutely HAVE to be understanding. Which you're already far down the right path on that one. You have to understand that he's not doing any of these things on purpose. He wishes he could do better, but no matter how hard he tries, he just can't. You need to still love and care for him despite that. Understand that this is how he is and it can't just change on its own. Encourage him. Encourage him a lot in the things he struggles with. And encourage him to go to the doctor, if he hasn't already, and get professional help. The other thing, which might be the most important, is patience. Dating someone with ADHD will not work if you aren't patient. Period. He's going to forget to do things. It might seem like he's not pulling his weight or accomplishing much of anything. You can't get mad or frustrated when this happens. Be patient. Like I said before, encourage him. Help him find coping strategies. Remind him to do certain things. A lot. Constantly. And, if he's like me, I had a really bad habit of getting frustrated when my girlfriend would remind me constantly to do things. If he does that, diffuse the situation and explain that you know this is how he is and you're just trying to help. Give him a to-do list. Give him specifics tasks you want or need him to do and a time at which you want or need them done by. Remind him periodically until the time comes. Or help him set up periodic reminders himself on his phone or something. All of that will help. The problem comes in when people don't understand and aren't patient and get mad when typical symptoms of ADHD show themselves. If you really love and care about the guy, which willingness to do the above shows that you do, it will all be fine. And while it can be a struggle, if done right, people with ADHD can be some of the funnest people to be around and date. Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 15:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just ahead of the curve for when we populate the moon and/or Mars and they start making shit. Or that company has a strong belief in Aliens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 22:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because your brain and your body want and need to go to sleep. So they're trying to go to sleep regardless of whether or not you're in a situation where you should be sleeping or not. You need sleep to survive and your body is more concerned about survival.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 22:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like u/zeldamakessandwhiches was saying, there shouldn't be a problem with your doctor giving you 3 paper prescriptions (or 90 days worth) to be filled when you run out each time. Especially if you explain to him/her your situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 22:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the exact same way. Except my dry mouth is mild and defintely bearable. My mood is so much better on adderall, plus I don't frustrate the people I'm around nearly as often because I can actually focus and do things. I'm 20 years old and most people feel like they're babysitting me when I'm not on my adderall. And I also, which some people don't understand, feel so much more like myself. My ex-girlfriend and her family seemed to think I was taking it to change who I was, and that's not at all the case. I feel more like myself and a much better version of myself on it. I was also diagnosed with depression, which I believe was mostly caused by my ADHD, and I seriously, absolutely hated myself without my medicine. To the point that, when I didn't have it, I constantly felt like I had to alter myself, and self medicated with anything and everything I could get my hands on. Sorry for rambling, but yes, I agree. Adderall makes me more me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 21:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work at Target and there would, all the time, be "sale" signs placed over price tags and they would still be the same price. Being the person that would have to go around taking off the infinity expired sale signs, this royally pissed me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 21:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work at Target and they sold these at the store I worked at. Every time I saw them I thought they were strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 21:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did sound like that the way it was worded. I think another would be cool. But yeah, that's my bad. I agree Ghost and Steel would be really cool as well. Especially steel. I'd take fairy, dark, ghost, and steel gyms for sure. I don't know how likely it is that all 4 would be in Sun and Moon though. I'd actually probably rather have another Ghost or Steel than another Fairy now that you mention it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 21:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Defintely my favorite scene. Can't stop watching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 23:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the tank may be leaking too now that you mention it. How do I fix the o-ring? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 21:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't contain lactose so someone who is lactose intolerant, who normally can't consume dairy, can drink it. However it still has milk, so that have to put that on there so people with milk allergy, who aren't affected by whether it has lactose or not, know not to drink it. Still seems a bit misleading though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 21:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's defintely just Pierce being Pierce. I don't think the intention was to have them make babies with his sperm. I mean he gave it to all the guys as well. He just wanted to give them his sperm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 21:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fairy type gym and a dark type gym would be cool. Also dual type gyms if that's even allowed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 21:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a really good idea. And even urinals can be placed in stalls like toilets. I saw a restaurant that had stalls that extended ceiling to floor. It was like the toilets were in a seperate room. It was pretty cool. I think it'd work out really well honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 00:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/us0UdqW

Here's a picture of the ad if anyone wants to see it. I must agree that it's quite a powerful ad and hit very, very close to home. I feel for all those who are still struggling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 00:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guys at the vape shop have just automatically been making it 70/30 because that's what they said to use. I'll try 50/50, maybe that's it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
