<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 08:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think so? I thought it was a cool idea in thought but in practice it ruined some otherwise good charts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 08:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. By RB3 I was happy with the approach there was. No need to go all Guitar Hero and try to mix it up. If I wanted mixture I'd play another rhythm game, I appreciated RB staying true to form </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These are my daily thoughts. What're yours? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 07:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In no order

"I'm surrounded by people, but if my heart finally gives out, what can they really do? They'd be just as confused as I would be if it happened to someone else. It would probably take me a long time to communicate how seriously I needed help. If I had a heart attack or a stroke, I'd be gone by the time help arrived. At best I could look forward to a life of being disabled. And holy shit how embarrassing would it be to have a heart attack here? If it's gonna happen I hope I can make it to the bathroom before anyone notices. But being found on the bathroom floor seems embarrassing too. How will my family react to that?"

"But maybe I'm not having a real problem, and it is in my head. Or maybe this is actually it, and I'm just telling myself to relax and I'm fucking myself over in the process."

"This person is taking it easy on me. They're being too nice. Do they think I'm retarded? Do they feel like they have to take it easy on me?"

"Maybe I am significantly mentally disabled?"

"I'm probably not going to live to see age 30"

"It's probably mental, if I could snap out of my own head I'd be straight. I just need a few more hobbies or a few more friends"

"I can't handle the friends I have. I can't keep track of the hobbies I pursue."

"This isn't my fault, it isn't just in my head. I likely have a neurological disorder that forces me to be like this. Maybe it's cancer or a tumor. That would explain the headache from earlier and my stammering and when I twitch" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes I think I subconsciously like the anxiety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 15:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else ever feel like that? It's hard to explain it, but I'll try.

I fucking hate anxiety, at least I feel like I do. If there was some quick trick to making it go away, I would be all over it. "If I could make it stop, I'd make it stop". I'd gladly take the "normal" life. I mean, I wouldn't have to be relaxed all of the time. Just normal. Relaxed sometimes and super stressed other times. That sounds awesome compared to NEVER relaxing (which is my state). At least, that's how I think I feel.

But then there's all these methods on fighting your anxiety and bettering yourself. I try them, but they take a lot of time. I do them for an hour, a day or two, whatever, but eventually it's a sort of "this fucking sucks", and I stop. And then it's back to where I was.

As motivated as I feel to address my anxiety, I never actually follow through on it. I realized this and thought it must just be depression. But depression doesn't stop me from doing anything else. If I want something tangible, I still work and save up to buy it. When I want to make a piece of art, I still invest the time into working on it and not letting fucking up make me stop. Getting over anxiety seems like the only thing motivation isn't enough for.

I guess being anxious is just easier than not being anxious. And I'm more comfortable being uncomfortable than I would be if I were relaxing. And I feel sometimes that I subconsciously like the dwelling and the panic, even though consciously I hate it every step of the way. Deep down I prefer this over being better.

And that's what gets me and makes me think I'll never not have anxiety problems. 

Does anybody else ever feel that way about themselves? Am I just over analyzing? How would I approach this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
