<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7881</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Costa Coffee owner welcomes plan for 'barista visas' after Brexit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact-checking President Trumps Pinocchio-laden Associated Press interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it can't benefit its financiers any more so what's the point of FFP?

I'll be curious to see how long it takes Gichuhi to see Bernardi's contempt.  Edit:  Looks like she might have worked it out already.  Gichuhi by all reports will sit as an independent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how Nate from Virginia is feeling tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 days of Trump Resistance: the wins so far and battles to come </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eventually, but at a later date so we can get started early, a meme will arise, in some form, of this inanely worded tweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biggest downsides are probably the difficulty in getting short term sub 2 year rentals (and a huge AirBnB effect in some cities/sectors because of it), some fiddly contracts for the early years of a tenancy and some strict and sometimes fairly expensive requirements when handing a property back to a clean and neutral state which can involve extensive painting/carpeting etc. 

When it comes to actually living though, you've got security and strong legal backing as a tenant and it's a model from which we'd do well to adopt large portions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 12:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1414 onshored per senate questions on notice and the Cocos Islands incident.

Even a cursory inspection doesn't hold water but that's never stopped this government, or much of their support base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the budget falls on its face again and Morrison's destruction is complete.  Then all he has to worry about is Bishop and, well...she's a woman.

Put me down for September. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant piece and it's great to see such an underread subject published in longform.  One of the advantages of digital distribution I guess.

On the premise of the lede I agree entirely but, in an Australia struggling to reconcile personal politics and prejudice with the structural realities of an Australian identity, I hold little hope of an open reassessment of the racial aspects of founding myth.

Edit:  This post's rather predictable position near the top of today's controversial listings on "lefty" /r/australia exemplifies the reason for that cynicism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To an extent, though that irony can be instructive for the inquisitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes it no less disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly not sure.

My two theories are that outright reneging on this would paint our government into such a spectacularly awkward corner with their own pet xenophobes that Trump might actually lose a potentially supportive voice because of it.  On top of that, Trump's new "extreme vetting" policy and its requirement for country of origin involvement is quite literally impossible to ethically or legally comply with for agencies managing refugees and practically impossible for the refugees themselves.  It offers a very, very easy out and one that I doubt Bannon or Sessions have missed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This riot police officer told me he was filming all people on Science March Sydney "for their records". - Marcus Strom, SMH Science Editor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US can "honour" this deal by taking no one and between Trump, his xenophobic base and aides and Pence's line today...

Pence told a joint news conference with Australian Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull in Sydney that the deal would be subject to vetting, and that honoring it "doesn't mean that we admire the agreement".

I wouldn't count any chickens.

And none of this, no matter the outcome, diminishes the disgrace of our inability to act in accordance with our responsibilities and undertakings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The QandA jacket.

http://i.imgur.com/2HiCSj4.jpg

You'd be forgiven for forgetting it, that Malcolm died a long time ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder whether the odd romanisation points to anything notable about the way it was produced.  There's a dozen different romanisation systems for Russian but this almost looks like it's gone through another language's phonetics first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The calculus behind Jason Chaffetz's sudden decision to walk away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagon experiences communications breakdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imprisoned Russian pedophile appears to be linked to hack of DNC computers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Stone Convinced Trump to Hire Paul Manafort, Former Officials Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sweating on every word  how ASIC massaged the banking message </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Higgins?  With the local Liberal complaints on tone, Credlin's  role in creating many of them and Turnbull's current appeal to them that could be a tone deaf, and hilarious, misstep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legal and Constitutional Affairs References Committee Report  Serious allegations of abuse, self-harm and neglect of asylum seekers in relation to the Nauru Regional Processing Centre, and any like allegations in relation to the Manus Regional Processing Centre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manus Island refugee who died in Brisbane waited 12 hours for medical evacuation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arkansas carries out first murder since 2005 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Push to impose GST on all imported online goods breaches best-practice rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PNG police flatly reject Peter Dutton's account of Manus shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/costareports/status/855096408898240512

Here's something to pay attn to: many Hill Rs skittish about key WH players making a deal w/ F. Caucus, revving up expectations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treat Louise Mensch as The Lone Gunmen of this saga.  A lot of kooky conspiracy with an increasingly worrying habit of accurately predicting future plot progression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I see your point. I think it's you that's missing mine.  We've been a multilingual society since the death of the white Australia policy in 66, including official support in the provision of government services.

If you want to apply an English test to skilled working visas and the like, that's fine.  But it seems extremely hard to support a requirement for citizenship that is neither required nor expected of other citizens.

And on indigenous languages in schools, we do teach them.  There's been programs operating for over 20 years teaching 1000s.  Not just second language and revival programs either, first language programs as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia has no official language and, if anything, the only languages likely to be granted formal recognition any time soon would appear to be indigenous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The arse falling out of housing prices overnight benefits no one.

Affordability needs to be addressed but a rapid correction with current lending could quickly become disastrous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super funds targeted in Shorten's housing affordability package </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unnamed source in a single in article in The Oz by the looks of it.

https://twitter.com/susanamet/status/855046351930785792 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> English is only the language of the country you are trying to be a citizen of.

You know it isn't right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Plot to Paper College Campuses with Racist Posters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Pence positioning himself for a Trump impeachment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, turning them back.  In fact, we handed people directly to regimes from which they were seeking asylum with results ranging from at *least* imprisonment to torture.  I'm pretty confident I've got the loose ends of worse than that on my desk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, on boats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gillard's responsible for the "enhanced screening" processes we've been refoulering people under ever since.  *Personally* responsible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The full 7.30 piece to air is here: http://www.abc.net.au/7.30/content/2017/s4656410.htm

The interview here:  http://www.abc.net.au/7.30/content/2017/s4656418.htm

Turnbull did not fair well.  I'd argue unsurprisingly so given how increasingly desperate and incoherent this push is looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malcolm Turnbull grilled by Leigh Sales over 'Australian values', citizenship test overhaul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you arrest Dutton, are you going to arrest Rudd, Gillard, Shorten aswell?

Please.  I for one would gladly see every single immigration minister, department head and Prime Minister who has overseen mandatory detention, onshore or off, hauled before court and commission for acts and failures to act under their respective tenures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghosts of the Civil Dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's that projection again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't give a flying fuck what she portrays herself as.  When you choose to finance and promote your project via white supremacists I kind of lose interest in anything you have to say on most any subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful news.  Your hatred isn't owed a platform nor a revenue stream.  This isn't a violation of your freedom of speech no matter how much you may care to bleat about it.

Feel free to finance your own showing in your own establishment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far removed from any and all reporting on the matter thus far that this looks to be a complete fabrication.

A statement from the PNG Defence Force alleged that an officer was assaulted by an asylum seeker, "which led to an escalation of the confrontation".

"Rocks were allegedly thrown by the asylum seekers and shots fired by the members of the Naval base," it read.

"Few people [were] treated for minor injuries."

A statement from PNG Police alleged that the soldiers involved were drunk.

**Neither statement referenced a child.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an ineffectual threat tied to an actively detrimental consequence for all parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually it's rehabilitation and parsimony requirements though things like mental impairment etc. can also factor in.

As an example, an offender with a serious medical condition that could not be managed appropriately in a prison may preclude a custodial sentence despite circumstances where that would be expected.  A judge has the right to deprive someone of their liberty in the course of serving justice, but not to deprive someone of their health.

This can get particularly involved with youth sentencing where expectations of undisturbed education, training, parental access, the family relationship and other formal and informal rights of the child all factor into the decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has "law and order" politicking in Australia ever had anything more than a cursory connection to our justice or corrections system though?

The intent here is to garner a polling boost on the back of public perception and an easily demonised "other".  Nothing more.  On that metric, the Australian public has unfortunately shown to their disgrace that it does work, repeatedly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Curiel, Once Criticized by Trump, Gets Deported Dreamer Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, this current round of race baiting from Turnbull would fit pretty tidily into the idea of a Great White Hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Ludlam: 'Malcolms Handcuffed To Some Delusional Right-Wingers' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Press Freedom Tracker will keep tabs on the safety of journalists in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dissembling on North Korea, Trump creates a crisis of credibility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he didn't know Bannon prior the campaign, right guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He says he's going back to the private sector.

https://twitter.com/frankthorp/status/854707612373438464 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derp, yes.  Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easter recess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were it played as a tactic it would have been merely hamfisted*.  The miscommunication however is completely, terrifyingly, incompetent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pence: Misstatements about U.S. aircraft carrier location not intentional </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITV are hosting one apparently.

https://www.theguardian.com/politics/live/2017/apr/19/election-2017-theresa-may-mps-early-vote-politics-live?page=with:block-58f75518e4b05776df18f171#block-58f75518e4b05776df18f171 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Dirty Dossier' helped the FBI obtain a surveillance warrant for former Trump adviser Carter Page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Shorten claims 77pc of 457 visa workers excluded from checks thanks to FTAs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Tony Abbott problem just multiplied </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animal Liberation spokeswoman Kristy Alger said the group opposed the performance because it "trivialised the nature of slaughter".

The irony in that statement is positively painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Website of Liberal MP Stuart Robert appears to contradict his fundraising claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't rule it out with how effectively his poisoned working relationships with state police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you've got nothing left as a Liberal PM it must be nice to know that you've always got blatant and gratuitous race baiting to fall back on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your definition of Australian is a stagnant, inflexible society that remains unaltered by those brought into it then I'll gladly wear the un-Australian label in its face.

The country you seem to describe died in 1966 and I will not mourn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.

How Australian is Australian enough to be critical of Australian society?  How do you determine that?  Who determines that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you enforce a vendor based collection model if the vendor is outside of your jurisdiction? 

Strictly?  You don't.

Where is AusPost getting the $900m figure from?

Probably from the bare minimum number of employees it would take to inspect and loosely value every inbound parcel from offshore passing through Australia Post's hands.

That this idea makes no financial sense shouldn't really surprise.  We've been told that several times in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apart from the arrogance and utter navety that any society is best served by stagnation do you mean?

We are far, very far, from a flawless society.  Build the post-scarcity, egalitarian utopia first and maybe we can revisit the sentiment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rumour is Pezzullo is set to get it, which would be an appropriately fucking awful decision from this government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't love it, leave?

I was born here and I'd like to change Australian culture quite a bit.  In fact, the spectacularly lazy approach to Australian society encapsulated in the phrase above would be a case in point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to pay closer attention to whats at play in this particular race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Ossoff can bait Trump into sticking his nose into this race over the next few months he might do this yet.

Handel is no Trump fan either but Trump's sportsball approach to politics could have that R sitting around their neck like an albatross. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DIBP itself fails points 1 and 3.

Edit:  And 6 and 7 for that matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Call to classify shark culling and drum lines as threats to endangered species </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we've already undermined legal rights for about 2/3rds of the country, why not undermine the rights and value of Australian citizenship entirely at this point?

It's both disgraceful and *completely* unsurprising how much has been eroded without a peep from the electorate.  "Fuck you, got mine" is pretty easy to exploit when no one really regularly tests whether they've actually got anything anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia's multicultural society values and is built upon integration, not assimilation.

So I guess that's you gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got two pairs of R.M. Williams boots that between them are my daily wear shoes.  One would be close to 15 years old, the other over 10.  The 15 year old pair are just starting to crack in a few places and that's mostly because I traipsed around a beach in them one time too many.

If you'll actually look after them and don't mind resoling/reheeling them now and again they're money well spent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, this is done and dusted unless I'm misreading it or The Guardian are misreporting it.

The high court rejected Labors challenge on Wednesday on the basis that there was insufficient evidence Gichuhi was ineligible and Labor had had three months to put a case together.

From that, it was thrown out in part because Labor had ample time to put together a coherent case and failed to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, if this challenge gets up then the whole eligibility criteria need a full legal review.

The law at the time was extremely clear, Gichuhi lost her Kenyan citizenship by voluntarily acquiring another one.  This is the agreed position of the Kenyan representatives of state.

If changes in legal apparatus in foreign countries can disqualify an Australian citizen from office after the fact that's simply unacceptable in a nation of immigrants.

*If* this gets up, and I remain skeptical of that, then Frydenberg, Danby and Dreyfus need to have their eligibility challenged just to establish the scope of the legal problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Supreme Court denies Arkansas request to begin executions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd laugh my arse off if he joined Cory's Tories and then started white anting for the leadership.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point, this is the best approximation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if Joh had made it to Canberra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could arguably argue for Deakin but its hardly comparable.  Abbott defecting would be unprecedented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low-income earners turn to negative gearing, report says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren Entsch pleads with Tony Abbott to shut up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melania Trump hosted a private Easter Egg Roll exclusively for the rich and powerful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Atlanta's conservative suburbs became a frontier of liberal resistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polls like this http://media.wix.com/ugd/3bebb2_48c528e288844bb1b7e525cfb5af450a.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> El Paso: the border city grappling with the ramifications of Trump's proposals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you look at where this thread and specific comments in it are linked the reason become pretty obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks that way, and a little more polished than the usual examples.

Gotta do something with those Cayman Is accounts I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's An Army Of Twitter Accounts Pushing Identical Pro-Adani Messages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guardian Australia understands that Abbott defended the program in a party room meeting in 2014 and several attempts to have its funding axed by then parliamentary secretary for education, Scott Ryan, were rebuffed.

Ryan now being Turnbull's Cabinet Minister Assisting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 06:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence "may" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 06:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reviews are good for what data a VPN service may collect or leak.  Realistically, they approximate the job of white papers and independent audits that are frighteningly absent from most of the sector.

I'd add that you need to consider the location and structure of the company(s) operating the VPN and its respective connection points, their payment processing structure and location and the legal frameworks and requirements for capture and disclosure in each of those jurisdictions.

But that depends how paranoid you care to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made all the worse because many of those reactionaries are raising the kids this program is aimed at.

With parental engagement levels in any program, let alone Safe Schools, broadly falling and doing so with some pretty nasty correlations it feels like these programs increasingly need broad public awareness and education components.  Government leading from the front and educating and informing the electorate though?  That seems a long forgotten skill in Australia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in any amount since the Tooheys/Swan/Castlemaine merger.  CUB put it on tap, people realised it was shit next to the older draughts and that killed its pseudo-premium brand image.

So yeah, not since the early 80s and it would have been on the slide since the early 70s I'd guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too late, he's already turned into a pumpkin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a traditional coach made from historically sourced antique timber, so it's got the armour of an old garden shed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly not as a first preference.

There's a duty of care owed to those we detain however.  If it's deemed necessary for an evacuation option to exist for Australian staff, why is there no equivalent for the detainees?  What's been done to secure it?  And, when push came to shove, why staff placed their own safety over the hundreds in their care is a question that needs to be asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Danger not passed on Manus Island after detention centre shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought better of you /r/Australia.

I'm *well* past thinking better of this place unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than regional UN budgets just to run concentration camps to appease the bigoted, the ignorant and the carefully manufactured frightened.

http://www.abc.net.au/news/2015-07-14/cost-of-offshore-processing-united-nations-fact-check/6609764

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 12:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/BehrouzBoochani

Navy have shot more than 100 times, some of them have broken into rooms. The situation on #Manus is critical

Everything we're hearing appears to be coming out of the Mike and Foxtrot compounds at the far side of the camp from the Navy Compound.  No news yet out of Delta, Oscar the (now former) IHMS or ops offices, all of which are closer.

Edit:  This sounds encouraging

https://twitter.com/BehrouzBoochani/status/852867516984508416

Police in control now, driving around the centre to protect refugees. Navy has left. Australian officers will return soon. Sounds positive

Looks like those whose duty it is to protect these asylum seekers and refugees will be returning from their hiding spot shortly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 12:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fairfax covering some aspects of that here: http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/sustained-gunfight-breaks-out-at-manus-island-detention-centre-20170414-gvlcnh

Several detainees reported sustained gunfire from outside the centre after violence erupted when a local tried to shut down a soccer game involving detainees in the Navy base that surrounds the compound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His attorney is probably the attorney-general.  It'd certainly fit Sessions' level of complete and utter incompetence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of me wonders whether he's just making sure he's in front of cameras so that we'd notice were he suddenly not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've a player that supports youtube-dl or similar, you can just open the URL for the episode you want.

On macOS I use IINA as it works out of the box but I'd assume you could get it going with VLC as well.

Edit:  Best way of navigating because of the Flash pop-ups and redirects is to browse from http://iview.abc.net.au/programs/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The federal government is expected to kill off a proposal to allow first home buyers to use their superannuation to buy a house, with cabinet ministers lining up behind Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull to pan the idea.

Oh.  The other interpretation of the headline wouldn't surprise me either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tasmania Has Apologised To People Convicted Of Historical Gay Sex Offences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tailspin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was sitting at the table.  We had finished dinner.  We're now having dessert.  And we had the most beautiful piece of chocolate cake that you've ever seen and President Xi was enjoying it.

And I was given the message from the generals that the ships are locked and loaded, what do you do?

And we made a determination to do it, so the missiles were on the way.  And I said, Mr. President, let me explain something to you.  This was during dessert.

We've just fired 59 missiles, all of which hit, by the way, unbelievable, from, you know, hundreds of miles away, all of which hit, amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trumps throughly confusing Fox Business interview, annotated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump sounds sick of Steve Bannon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Choice of Pro-Immigration Economic Adviser Riles Trump's Base </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but that would require thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly Leadback, those kids can be not really people if you just hate them enough inside.

- /r/Australia, probably

It's a fucking depressing attitude on civil rights and state responsibility but I guess it's only emblematic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 09:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's going to be a big problem for picture books like the Hun and Terrorgraph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gelatin can be an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Trumps Syria Strategy, One Voice Is Missing: Trumps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if any of the corporations also own Pauline's plane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assad's a war criminal.  Being one war criminal in a war between war criminals doesn't lessen that any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately there's no good public access to the press release wires in Australia.

You see this a *lot* here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4Corners struck a nerve, asked to comment or something fresh in the pipe or the human soul known by Malcolm: Ieuen-Roberts off his meds again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May budget: Axe hovers over government's $648.5 million work-for-the-dole program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People Just Flat-Out Lie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overhaul shakes up Trump's National Security Council </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mainstream and conservative media are living in different worlds. So are those who read them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change notification sounds on ALL apps please!

I've a number of notifications muted solely because the sound is obnoxious and doesn't fit with my system sounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 10:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless there is far more to it, I'd argue it's likely actionable.  A studio has crew for a reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal defenders of free speech curiously silent over banning of Bassem Tamimi  Jeff Sparrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Westpac are by far the worst of the big four when it comes to climate issues.  On the Adani front in particular it's the only one not currently in the process of a review.

https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2017/apr/07/climate-change-three-of-australias-big-four-banks-reviewing-exposure-to-fossil-fuels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd make a G.I. Joe of him, only they're *action* figures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain says administration "partially to blame" for chemical attack in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah there's a *huge* gulf between what's coming out of State and UN staff.  I suspect there's a major, major story just in explaining that gap as it's extremely unusual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria missile strike: Assad regime change Trump administration priority, Nikki Haley says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In theory.  The practice of it may fail to meet either standard if restrictions on movement and documentation being threatened materialise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people are lying.

Think Inc reported 2000 tickets sold for the tour in total prior to the cancellation and that wouldn't fill the smallest venue, let alone all 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devin Nunes' role turns from controversial to untenable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Kayfabe](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kayfabe) might be more appropriate for Trump.

In professional wrestling, kayfabe /kefeb/ is the portrayal of staged events within the industry as "real" or "true," specifically the portrayal of competition, rivalries, and relationships between participants as being genuine and not of a staged or pre-determined nature of any kind. Kayfabe has also evolved to become a code word of sorts for maintaining this "reality" within the direct or indirect presence of the general public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: U.S. told Syria of airstrikes before launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kushner's meetings with Russian officials draw closer scrutiny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ethics panel steps into spotlight with Nunes inquiry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd give Flynn immunity if he could serve up the president on a platter.  They'd do the same for Bannon.

And don't forget from the Nixon affair, that doesn't mean they don't go to gaol as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now this is actually news.  If no one's prepared to challenge it, and I'd be surprised if they were, this hands Russia air superiority.

And we've all seen what they'll do with that in recent years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Australian Journalist Has Been Arrested On Manus Island </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 07:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 07:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can get along to it, this should be a good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question Time - Sydney Writer's Festival panel /w Bridie Jabour, Chris Uhlmann, Steve Lewis, Jeff Sparrow and Mark Di Stefano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 07:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  I'm just not confident enough to say precisely where in the sentence that likelihood collapses on my current level of knowledge and information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PHON?  When he's this blatant he should give Saleam a call, run for Australia First. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treat my statement as a whole for the time being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On whether they will I pretty much agree.

On whether they *should* I'd ask just how large of a genocide we're prepared to turn a blind eye, and whether the ensuing escalation of the refugee crisis would even allow us to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 59 Tomahawks at a single target with the advisors informed ahead of time?  The only way that's *not* a dog and pony show is if Assad's use of these weapons fucked up an agreement with Putin and I rather doubt that.

Even if the Russian's didn't explicitly let the Syrian forces know, it'd still be pretty obvious why every Russian suddenly had to be somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sad reality of the world is that it often needs something so horrible you can't look away rubbed in its collective faces to spur action.

It's far too easy for far too many to push the acts and peoples from just over the horizon to some far removed place in their mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  Doesn't mean we shouldn't give a damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crimes against humanity are all of humanity's business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be stunned if they weren't, on several fronts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considers just turned into act for the US.  Strikes on military aviation infrastructure at Ash Sha'irat as of a few minutes ago.

I suspect, and hope, that's as far as it will go for the time being.  The current US administration hasn't got the capabilities for a war with much anyone presently, let alone one with a Russian backed opposing force.

That said, a NATO intervention along the lines of Bosnia is over due, and something I'd welcome were it clearly operated out of Brussels and not DC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A US war in Syria would be a disaster, in part because you're currently led by an overly sensitive man-child heading an administration hopelessly compromised by, if not beholden to, the government behind an opposing force.

NATO intervention ala the Bosnian War however, that is long overdue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pro-Trump media and pro-Russian media, but I repeat myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Labor queries Coalition MP's eligibility after Bob Day high court ruling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Kushner better keep it quiet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stepping aside over an ethics investigation per his statement.

https://twitter.com/MichaelRWarren/status/849980186107969537

The Daily Beast carrying that angle already 

http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/04/06/house-ethics-committee-launches-investigation-of-devin-nunes-for-spilling-secrets.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US Strategic Command tweeting Breitbart stories.  What the actual fuck America? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter users jab Stratcom on Breitbart link </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure Reagan's executive would qualify in the eyes of these goons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stepping aside over an ethics investigation per his statement.

https://twitter.com/MichaelRWarren/status/849980186107969537

Edit: Daily Beast carrying that angle already 

http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2017/04/06/house-ethics-committee-launches-investigation-of-devin-nunes-for-spilling-secrets.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jewish Leaders Cheer Ouster Of Steve Bannon From Security Post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump might not want to bring up golf with Chinas leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she became an Australian citizen in 2001 I believe this should be a non-issue for her.

http://kenya.asn.au/?page_id=13515

Any person who voluntarily applied for the citizenship of another country lost his Kenyan citizenship as a matter of law.

Under the new laws she'd be entitled to regain it but I'm fairly sure it was automatically lost back in 2001 when she acquired her new citizenship.

One thing I am curious of now, I've seen several people suggest that even if there was an outstanding issue she would have the opportunity to correct it prior to being sworn in.  If anyone's got the basis for that claim I'd love to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as a single component.  They can replace the set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mediscare campaign that precipitated a policy backflip and predicted what fortunately ended as a senate defeat or Brexit's project fear predicting just about every significant piece of Brexit news from the past 4 weeks (reversibility, trade deal timetables, position of Scotland, freedom of movement, banking, EU reimbursements, NI border concerns etc. etc. etc.)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think that an apple authorised repairer would be any different?

Apple authorised repairers have to replace the pairings as a set.  The pairings are done at the factory at time of manufacture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been a rough week has it, Mal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it's a matter of security?  Yes.

Phones carry and access sensitive private and commercial information and it's frankly kind of depressing how quickly people will trade privacy for a few dollars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a job for [Media Watch](http://www.abc.net.au/news/image/6525636-16x9-700x394.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A "scare" campaign according to conservatives that proved to be entirely well founded?

Don't know...Brexit maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The decline of Americas moral authority </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you knife someone in the back with a potato peeler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just in case you happened to catch this bullshit earlier.

https://np.reddit.com/r/australia/comments/63oxvn/happily_never_after_gender_bias_fairytales_facing/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Premier Andrews says the gov is not banning fairy tales and if they did, some media would be out of business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 06:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, draw attention to the woman with another shell in the chamber.  What could possibly go wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh some do.  For a circulation its size it remains frighteningly influential thanks to the amplification effect that remaining readership can offer in other publications and platforms.

Now, is there anybody left reading it who stands to benefit from a deconstruction?  *That* is another question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ASP is a corporate lobby pretending to be a political party.  No it does not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can stomach it, a perusal of Quadrant's output over the past 25 years or so is a pretty fascinating snapshot of the standard of conservative discourse in Australia.  Notably its decline.

There's a good opportunity for a book in it, similar to the few histories of The Bulletin, but I'm not aware of anyone having written it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a statement, Mr Porter's office said he received "direct verbal briefings" about the program.

Likely consisting mostly of "Don't you fucking dare put anything on paper that might tie me to this in case it all goes tits up" I would assume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would potentially make sense with the other big news today.

My other guess would be Cohen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be my guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't get what Carter Page's angle actually is but he's definitely got one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Trump adviser admits to 2015 communication with Russian spy: You can draw your own conclusions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
