<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3967</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of a computer as an employee (person). In order to tell this person what to do, you need to be able to speak in his/her language. Python is a way for you to tell this person to do things.

Now, the computer has a brain that does some stuff to "interpret" what you're saying. Python isn't his/her first language, so he/she has to take into account your words and transform it into something that computers understand.

Hope that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are looking to buy a house in Columbia City. A couple of years ago, we wouldn't even consider it due to the commute downtown. Now, it's a prime spot for us!

The Light Rail is amazing. It "shrinks" our city in terms of choosing where to live and work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really easy to write and run. Just fire up an interpreter and go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great news about the XPS line, but I still think it's a valid reason to pick a Thinkpad in 2017, IMHO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  300~500 miles one way

Just make sure to check everything before going on those long hauls. Carry spare parts/fluids with you just to be safe.

 Once or twice, it happens. But if it becomes a frequent issue - and XJs are quite old - perhaps it's not the best vehicle for me.

I'd be lying to you if I told you my XJ hasn't broken down on me more than twice while on the road. Your experience may vary, but I've had my fair share of AAA calls...

That said, more often than not, the fixes were cheap and doable myself. Which leads to my last point...

 I really don't know much about cars but I'm willing to learn and repair myself.

I'm not proud to say, but I didn't know jack about cars until my 30s. I learned everything I know about car maintenance and repair from working on my XJ these past 2 or so years. Because of how old XJs are, things are fairly straightforward to pull apart and piece back together. It's an excellent learning vehicle, IMO.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trackpoint and decent Linux compatibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird. There was a similar article written about ET3's eating habits: https://munchies.vice.com/en/articles/how-5-time-nfl-pro-bowler-earl-thomas-eats

Both are interesting reads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. When I was in Rome last April, this was undergoing maintenance and we didn't get to hang out on the steps. It was blocked off... the view of the sunset at the top of the steps was gorgeous though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, where do you host the websites? AWS? Heroku? A homelab? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always hear about how Austin has been undergoing a "tech revolution" of sorts. Has that changed the city in a way that made you want to leave? Do you see similarities to what Seattle is going through right now?

I had considered moving to Austin once upon a time, just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the quality of the screen is the only concern you have, look elsewhere. I have the FHD IPS screen on my TP13 and it's such a step down from my 15" Retina MBP.

Quite literally everything else about the TP13 is decent, but the screen is one of the worst parts of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a Cali-native, but anytime I'm in San Diego, I'll eat Lolita's at least 5 times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, because I am not a rabbit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck? The Crocodile does pizza? I'm noob... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy writing scripts in it (as opposed to Bash, for example) and if I need to scrape some data off a website or interact with a public API, I almost always prefer to do it in Ruby. Obviously, it's because I'm familiar with the language. It's a really nice syntax to work in.

I'm sure there's more sophisticated ways to use Ruby, but I think it's popularity will always be with web folks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your favorite burrito in California? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's surprisingly hard to find friends who are genuinely happy for you when things are going well. I fight the hardest to keep those people around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which pizza? It's odd, but I'm convinced that my favorite pizza in Seattle is from Bill's Off Broadway... delicious, buttery crust with a pint of Manny's Pale Ale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go to the Rancho Bravo on Capitol Hill (I think it's the same?). It's cheap and filling, especially after a night of drinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah man.. I've never been to Bimbo's Cantina for food, only drinks. I'll have to check that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Taqueria la Pasadita

Is this the truck near the McDonalds drive through? I always pass by this when I get McDonalds or Starbucks there. I'm gonna have to check it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god. I love Tacos Chukis... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried the large burrito from there. It's definitely filling, but I wasn't blown away by how it tasted. If I'm super hungry, that's the place to go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love burritos, what's your favorite burrito in Seattle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a burrito connoisseur, but my favorite burrito in Seattle has to be a huge, grilled chicken burrito from El Camion, with a hold bunch of the verde sauce.

I've had my fair share of Chipotles, Taco del Mars, and Qdobas as well... and I love them all.

Where do you like to get your burrito fix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who's been disconnected from Python for a couple of years now, why is it so popular for data science applications (ex. fintech)? I've noticed that many prefer to use Python to mine and analyze large datasets. Is it the eco-system? The speed? It's simplicity as a language? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm creating a Pingdom-like clone in Flask+Celery. I'm a Ruby on Rails developer, but my first love was Python (in college). It's been painful, but it's good to work with Python again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt very content. I am just so mentally exhausted hating (but respecting) TB12, BB, and the Pats as a whole. It reminds me a little bit of my bitter, irrational hate of the Bulls in the 90s.

This last SB solidified, in my mind, there is no question that we are witnessing a GOAT-level franchise with a GOAT-level QB and HC. These guys know how to win the big games.

That said, I think the Seahawks will experience similar longevity and dominance over the next couple of years. There's something special about this time right now. Ugh... is it football season yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 05:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone else just plain exhausted from cheering against this franchise? Like, I'm tired. They're just so... fucking... dominant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm sure the lid is putting the laptop to sleep. I'm still having the same issue. I'm starting to think I have a faulty battery. I suppose I can load up Windows and see if I have the same issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Revenue: $43.7 billion vs. $44.68 billion average analyst estimate (up 22% year-over-year)

I'm no financial stock analyst, but damn, 22% increase in revenue YOY seems like a good sign of continued growth. I guess I'd like to compare the same growth from the year before to see if there's a significant slowdown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had this issue. If you're sure it's not just the cap, I'd go about replacing the keyboard entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took me 2 years of CL hunting before I found my 98 Sport. 4 doors and 5-speed, completely stock, and rust-free.

Don't give up, yours is out there. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, why Twisted? I'm curious, I'm using it at work for developing SSH server/client applications and... it's the last thing I'd use to serve a REST API. Then again, I'm still learning it. So, there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no sushi connoisseur, but I'm a fan of [Nijo](http://nijosushi.com/) in Pioneer Square, [Momiji](http://www.momijiseattle.com/) on Capitol Hill, and [Kudasai](http://www.sushikudasaiseattle.com/) downtown (for a quick bite).

I do enjoy conveyor belt sushi as well, though! There's [Sushi Land](http://www.sushilandusa.com/LocationsSeattle.php)(cheaper) and [Ten Sushi](http://www.tensushiseattle.com/)(pricier) in Queen Anne.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sushi Maru...? That's honestly my favorite conveyor belt sushi place... I always go nuts with their salmon nigiri there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 09:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The X1 Carbon seems like it'd be of higher quality in terms of build quality. I've had the Thinkpad 13 for a couple of months now and it's noticeably less sturdy than my X220. It's nice and light, but something about it feels cheaper than the Thinkpads of old.

I did a quick little review [here](http://era86.github.io/2016/11/26/a-quick-review-of-the-lenovo-thinkpad-13.html). Note: I have the last generation Thinkpad 13, things could be different in the upcoming model.

Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 22:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We got outbid at 2 different townhomes on California Ave (just south of the Junction). One went $20k above list, the other went just under $10k above list. You are right, it's brutal...

 How many attempts did you have to make? How many weeks/months did it take you to finally secure a house?

We finally got an offer accepted for a townhome down in Columbia City. While it isn't West Seattle, the commute into downtown is far better (we're walking distance from the light rail!) and the home is a brand new construction. It took 1 month of negotiating and 3 counter-offers to finally agree on a price.

 Did you do pre-inspections at each house you bid on?

On the first townhome, we didn't do a pre-inspection. However, the seller provided one for the second townhome.

 How much did you typically over-bid over the asking price?

For the ones in West Seattle, all we did was ask for closing costs. We offered to pay listing price, which was still really high IMHO.

 How did you keep your chin up while fighting in this bloodbath?

Frankly, by being flexible and exploring other areas. 4-5 years ago, I was SURE I was going to own a house on Beacon Hill. There was no "if" "ands" or "buts" about it.

However, it just wasn't working out (price wise). So, we started walking around West Seattle and Columbia City... turns out, we love these neighborhoods! And even better, we found a home within our price range!

 Any advice other than "don't even try?"

Be open and flexible on what or where you buy, but don't settle. If you really MUST be in West Seattle, be prepared to either save up more money or wait longer.

Good luck! Try to remember that buying a house is quite a privilege here in Seattle. You're in a really awesome spot! Stay positive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, "boilerplate" was bad word-choice. I guess in terms of getting a web application up and going, Rails does a lot of "handholding" for you. Flask requires more explicit code to render stuff that Rails would render "auto-magically", assuming you follow its conventions... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could follow the directions in the [HMM](https://download.lenovo.com/pccbbs/mobiles_pdf/tp13_hmm_en_sp40k22761.pdf). It looks fairly straightforward to take out the keyboard, clean it, then put it back in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on a small web application serving up JSON using Flask. There's so much Rails gives you right off the bat, you really don't appreciate it until you don't have it. I love Flask, but Rails has far less boilerplate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the classic jerseys myself! However, I'll take mine over yours any day... http://i.imgur.com/vQwdyJl.jpg

Good pickup though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a potential new home-owner, can I ask why you should never go to Home Depot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... the Vivace espresso stand is right across the street. I don't think Let It Bean will be missed that much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What OS are you running? I have the same annoying popping noise on my Thinkpad 13 in Ubuntu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Middle Click and Scroll on Windows 10 (Thinkpad 13) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 01:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm trying to get my Windows 10 install on my Thinkpad 13 to play nicely with me. I don't really understand why this isn't default behavior, but I'd like my middle button on the Trackpoint to both middle-click and scroll.

I can't seem to get [TPMiddle](http://users.v-lo.krakow.pl/~mwrobel/programs/tpmiddle.html) to work because "SynCom.DLL is missing from my computer".

Is there a different (proper) way to get this behavior in Windows 10? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 01:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can somewhat understand the defense looking ugly against the best offense in the NFL. I cannot understand the offense unable to keep up with THE WORST defense in the NFL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, this is somewhat sad news. The only menu items I really like from them was their Fried Mac and Cheese and Tater Tots.

Aside: Isn't this the place where the sign fell down and killed someone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really cool, didn't know about the Requests library. Thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late reply, but I'll give this a shot. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 01:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Learning the proper form of some of the big compound movements (squat, bench, OHP, deadlift, BB row).

2. Sticking to a simple program like SL5x5.

3. Eating as much as humanly possible in my adolescence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to hit the heavy bag frequently at my gym. 100lbs is the perfect weight for someone just looking to do some basic bag work.

One thing that lots of beginners do on the bag is plant their feet and wail on the bag until they're tired. That's great and all, but you can get an even better workout by doing some basic boxing footwork.

* Step around the bag, dance with it (this will depend on your stance: orthodox or southpaw).
* Step in, throw your combo, then step out.

Naturally, the bag will sway back and forth. Once you get in a rhythm, one way to practice stepping in, out, and side-to-side is to follow the sway of the bag. If it sways away from you, step in and hit. As it sways towards you, step out and move to the side.

Good luck!

edit: Here's a good [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FZkEgqzn2os) of what I was trying to explain. Watch as he steps forward to throw his combo as the bag moves away, then steps back out as it moves towards him. Add this basic movement into your bag routine and it'll be way more difficult than planting and throwing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 02:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you need alcohol to motivate yourself to workout, you need to seriously sit down and do some introspection. There are other ways to find motivation, alcohol should be lower (or non-existent) on that list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 23:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just increase what you're already eating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like /u/montas advice. I generally let my ActiveRecords concern themselves with "active record" type things like data validation, updates, etc.

Any "business" logic goes in domain-specific objects. Here's a great article describing the gist of what I'm getting at: http://blog.codeclimate.com/blog/2012/10/17/7-ways-to-decompose-fat-activerecord-models/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pretty standard layout. Most CSS frameworks will have a demo that looks just like this. Just a quick search led me to [Skeleton's Example](http://getskeleton.com/#examples). It isn't exactly what you want, but you could easily figure it out by reading the code. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, like /u/jerrysdad69 said, that shit changed my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 07:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I watched a game at Fado on 1st. It was surprisingly fun atmosphere, nothing too crazy, but groups of people cheering. TVs everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 07:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought some last minute tickets and took my wife to her first (and only) NFL game on at Qwest Field on January 8, 2011. It was a lot of fun, and really loud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could look at Belltown, Lower Queen Anne, and South Lake Union (Dexter Ave). Plenty of apartments in those areas and very close to the Amazon HQ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What have you tried?

http://seattle.craigslist.org/search/apa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, the "not gentrified" in your title pretty much eliminates any neighborhood that would match anything else you described. You could check out Central District, Columbia City, Georgetown, or White Center.

They're not exactly "close to downtown" (that's relative anyway), but they have public transit options to get there. In terms of walkability for things like grocery shopping, laundromats, etc., each have varying degrees, but you could certainly get it all done.

These neighborhoods have a good mix of luxury/older apartment buildings.

If you happen to find this wonderful, imaginary neighborhood, please be sure to report back so we can "gentrify" it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to see JJ Watt and Clowney come to town... shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I should clarify, it runs down while sleeping almost as fast as it does when I'm using it. Though, I think this is a Linux-specific issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same issues, very similar model.

I also notice that when I close the lid, to sleep the laptop, the battery still seems to drain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, there's a lot of street art in the neighborhood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never played MW3, but I could totally see this being a map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting lost in Montmartre, Paris [OC][4032x3024] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 06:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Jekyll for my blog and it's really easy to maintain. You get full control over the design of your site and you can create posts (reviews in OP's case) in various formats: HTML, Markdown, Textile, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of me hopes Terrell, by getting more field time, can at least gain some of the instincts the ET3 has. He'll never hit the same or cover as much ground as our starter, but faster play recognition and pursuit angles would make keep him serviceable for the playoffs.

I mean, easier said than done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 11:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Unbelievable" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [WTA Trip Reports](http://www.wta.org/go-hiking/trip-reports) are helpful. They'll have trail conditions on most of the popular trails being hiked right now.

I hear Franklin Falls is really nice in winter. If I remember correctly, it isn't extremely steep. A little bit of snow/ice shouldn't turn you around.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend going for 31s. Though the 30s look fine (I love the way they look on my little rig!), I still think 31s are the perfect size for a 3.5" lift.

The only reason I went with 30s was because I started out with a 2" budget boost and the 31s would have rubbed. When I moved up to 3.5", I just kept the 30s.

If I fall into money, I'll probably go up to 31s myself.

Good luck and enjoy the pains of installing the lift! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, boss. I have a similar setup on my 98 XJ. RE 3.5" AAL sitting on 30s. Personally, I think the 30s look kind of small, but I don't think it's worth the money to move up to 31s. I don't do anything crazy in my Jeep, just USFS roads around the PNW.

http://i.imgur.com/bgIXpol.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/Mcn7CNI.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/fO0prQU.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/rqJRk2k.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5-speed 3.5" lift on 30s. Mostly city driving. ~12mpg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coincidentally, I'm in NYC right now. Just stopped by their brick   mortar location on 14th in the East Village.

[That white sauce though...](http://i.imgur.com/elVH0Kz.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Halal Guys Are Coming to Seattle - Where do you think it'll be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where in Seattle is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching Earl carted off was one of my saddest moments as a fan... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chipotle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  for coding (compilation and some vms)

You might as well get the quad-core. Code compilation, especially, will be faster and well worth the $100. Paired with increased memory you should be able to host multiple VMs comfortably (and browse Reddit at the same time). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 01:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Theo Chocolates](https://www.theochocolate.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a fellow Jeeper (98 XJ 4.0), I feel for you. I'll definitely keep an eye out around Capitol Hill and Pioneer Square. However, I know the last Jeep that was stolen and reported on the old Seattle sub ended up in Marysville.

Everyone out in the 'burbs, keep a close eye out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'm going based on my own personal experience. I see a couple of devs out here using the Dell XPS 15 w/ Ubuntu vs the latest MBP. Also, I was considering an XPS 13 myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, I also notice that my battery indicator fluctuates with its accuracy. Is there some kind of tweak or update I should make? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't plan on selling it, but you can find them for decent price online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea... the keyboard is a step down, but it just takes some getting used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did... haha I totally forgot that I did that. I hope I haven't offended anyone too bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about the build quality of the T460, but the build quality of the Thinkpad 13 isn't nearly as good as my X220. It's made of what feels like cheaper plastic than the X220, but that makes it much lighter as well.

For the price, I still think it's pretty good bang for buck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a shame. I haven't had mine long enough to notice the hinges coming lose, but I do notice that it doesn't close as smoothly as my X220. Thanks for the warning, nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the summary! It definitely doesn't have the same build quality as anything in the X or T series. Based on your info, it makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. There's nothing quite like the classic keyboard. However, it's not too bad after some getting used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've written down more of my initial thoughts [here](http://era86.github.io/2016/11/26/a-quick-review-of-the-lenovo-thinkpad-13.html) if anyone is interested. I'm open to answering any questions as well.

I love this thing so far! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out with the old, in with the new... Replacing my X220 with the Thinkpad 13 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 05:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a classic EBT Thomas jersey. It took about 3 years of scouring Ebay and Craigslist, but he's my favorite player so I kept at it. I wear it more than my Elite ET3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 10:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spend lots of time on the trackpoint, but I haven't noticed any jumpiness in the trackpad either. I know that on my X220, if the charger was plugged in, it would become jumpy as hell in Ubuntu. Do you see a difference when your 13 is plugged in or not? Are you running Ubuntu?

I'm running 16.04 on my 13 and notice no jumpiness at all.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 02:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll raise you one more bold prediction: Terrell gets a pick-six on Sunday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 08:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks really clean! Care to share any more details? How's the rust on the underbelly?

Be sure to do a full tune-up. And I believe the 2001 has a habit of cracking the header if it runs too hot or overheats too often. Be wary of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 07:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do have some lightbleed on the lower part of the screen, but not nearly as much as you do on the upper part.

Also, I don't get anywhere near that amount of flex on that part of the keyboard (or any part of it for that matter). I have the fingerprint reader, though... I wonder if the lack of the reader leaves some hollow space underneath that area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 07:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got mine last week. My last Thinkpad was an X220. I'm really liking the 13 so far. I didn't get anywhere near 40% off, but I highly recommend it... I'd pull the trigger in a heartbeat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've learned so much about my team and the game of football from this sub, just thought i'd express how i feel on this holiday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 07:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 00:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this play! I thought one of the three defenders in the area got a hand on it... I guess not. Laser. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't we have nice things?

On a serious note, I'd be curious to see how Kam and Sherm do without ET3 and Shead. I'm sure the defense will be counting on those two more than ever for the next two weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you say light gaming, I'm assuming you'll be playing low settings at minimal FPS. I'd go with an T460 or Thinkpad 13. Literally any laptop will be fine for schoolwork nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 11:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's goooooo! I'm drinking more crown yorla and chaisng with coca cala </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I don't know, but I bought mine two weeks ago despite all these potential "holiday" sales. You could probably wait until then to get the best deal. I just got impatient.

2. I think the clockspeed of the i3 would be fine, but I think you'd want higher cache of the i5 to take advantage of memory-intensive programs. On that note, I'd consider maxing out the memory, as I imagine he'll want to do Excel, Word, and web browsing all at the same time.

3. Display is meh and I do have some light leakage at the bottom of the screen. I have the 1080 version. Screen space is most important for me, but it may not be for your dad.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 32 GB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first Thinkpad I ever owned was a T61, but my favorite was probably the old T40p. It was so solidly built compared to all the stuff that came after it, peice for peice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which distro is this showing up in? Mine works just fine in Ubuntu 16.04. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one](https://www.amazon.com/Lenovo-ThinkPad-13-Chromebook-Celeron/dp/B01HBJ60ME/ref=sr_1_1?s=pc ie=UTF8 qid=1479403109 sr=1-1 keywords=thinkpad+chrome)? 

And to clarify, it's the Thinkpad 13. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 8 screws on the bottom panel. The three nubs you see on the left are the rubber covers on the three screws near the front of the laptop.

The bottom panel exposes everything inside, which is kind of nice compared to my X220! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about your particular model, but on my X220 I had mixed and matched memory. I was more concerned with capacity than I was latency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The clips did give me some trouble, but no visible gaps in the chassis. One thing I'd recommend is using something wider than a flathead screwdriver to pry it open. I've got some scratches because of a little too much brute force... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting intimate with my new brand new Thinkpad 13 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 09:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
