<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7831</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Met Someone *Wrong* on OkCupid [Part 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 05:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5hug40/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid/)]

Today I took action. I decided that most of the people who were generous enough to comment were probably right and I needed to protect myself.  I drove to a couple of stores and bought myself a new door, a 9mm hand gun, and a security camera system.  I ended up skipping work to to install the door and one of the cameras at the entrance to my house.  Replacing the door was a terrible pain, but once that was done, the camera / DVR install went pretty smoothly.  I even managed to get to the shooting range before it closed so that I could  get used to the new firearm.  I'm not a huge gun fanatic, but I have shot a handful of times so I became pretty comfortable with the weapon quickly.

By the time I got home I was really exhausted.  Frankly I was happy for that, knowing that I was nervous enough to suffer some serious insomnia.  I hoped that wearing myself down with all this activity would help me to sleep. The new camera / DVR system had a phone and tablet interface and I was able to lie in bed and set it to record on movement only, as well as send a notification to my ipad.  I made sure the volume was up and left the tablet at my bedside table.  I put the gun in the drawer of my side table next to the bed, sipped a glass of whiskey and turned in.  I was right, I fell dead asleep almost immediately.

But not for long.

I awoke to a noise I had never heard before.  It was similar to those 1950's bomb raid cycles you hear in old war movies.  My eyes focused on the near full moon hanging outside my window as I rustled around for the source of the sound.  It wasn't until my hand touched the ipad that I realized what was going on.

"Movement Detected, Camera #1, 2:46am Dec 11, 2016" I read on the notification bar.

I switched apps to the live camera stream to see that my two "friends" were back. This time they were right against my front door, one of them clearly pushing in the vicinity of the knob.  After some consecutive movements, I could see that he had a pry bar in the door frame and was trying to pop it.

"Shit". I jumped out of bed, and in retrospect made an idiotic move.  I put my pants on. Had I been thinking I would have headed for the phone first, but in this moment I was so overtaken by instinct and emotion that my first choice was to be clothed.  Instinct can be a serious detriment in these situations.

After I hefted my jeans on and grabbed the gun from my side table, I ran downstairs to get the cordless phone.  This was another absurd mistake.  I have no idea why the hell I decided to head all the way to my kitchen to get a cordless phone to dial 911, rather than just using the mobile in my bedroom.

I made it only two steps down before I heard the door snap, and the sound of fast heavy boots in my front hallway.  There was no way I would make it to the kitchen for the phone. I knew it immediately and turned quickly heading back upstairs.  I was running for my bedroom to grab my cell phone when I heard the boots tromping up the steps behind me.  They were so close.  I did the only thing I could think of and darted into the bathroom, locking the door.

The door was solid, I told myself.  It was thick wood, and the ancient designer barn bolt was extremely heavy duty.  I would be safe here, and even if they somehow got through the door, I did have my gun.   I moved the wood cabinet that held my towels and toiletries in front of the door, got in the bath tub and prepared my weapon. I had considered blocking the door with my body but decided that if they could get through that door, they could certainly get through me at the same time.

I braced myself and focused on calming my breath as I heard them approach kicking open doors as they came.

"Hurgh hurgh hurgh"  I head the low panting breathing outside of the bathroom.  

"Shit." I thought. "They brought dogs this time. They will definitely know where i am."

The guttural panting got louder and louder. I imagined that this animal must have been huge and exceptionally nasty.  I had always had a fear of being attacked by dogs and I had never in my life heard a sound quite so threatening.  The pounding, pushing and grunting started immediately.  The men were clearly trying to force their way in.  I trained my gun on the door, ready to fire if they managed to burst through.  

I heard a horribly intense creak as I imagined them pushing the pry bar into the crack of the door, and resumed slamming against it as hard as they could.  The door bent and shot cracking noises into the air, hit after hit.  This went on for some time but the door never split and eventually it all stopped.

I let out a sigh as I heard them trade some muffled words and heard their footsteps going down the stair case.  Even so, I was going nowhere.  I was committed to sitting in that cold hard tub all night until I knew for certain they were long gone. So I sat and waited.

I heard rusting downstairs and my mind raced as to how they could possibly get to me,  and what they might be doing.  It was only minutes before I smelled it. Gasoline.

The moment my mind recognized the scent I heard the telltale "whoosh" sound of the flammable liquid igniting.  Judging by the sounds of movement, they had lit the first floor and bolted out of the front door.

I sprang into action, tossing the cabinet aside and unlocking the bathroom door.  My knuckles were white and red around the gun grip. I swung the door open and headed to the staircase only to find that the floor at the bottom of the steps were burning intensely.  I didn't think that there was any way I could get through that inferno undamaged no matter how quickly I moved.

I turned back up the stairs and into my bedroom, swiftly opening the window.  I thought to grab the ipad with the intruder footage as well as my cell phone and crawled out of the window onto the roof of my garage.  The cold night air took the breath from me, being shirtless and accustomed to the high temperature in my house.  This was made worse by pressing myself against the cold iron pipe running down the corner as I lowered myself near to the ground and jumped.

I stayed low for a minute scanning the street, looking for the pickup truck.  It was nowhere to be seen. I listened intently for any sounds of movement before deciding that the perpetrators were certainly gone at which point I ran to my neighbor's house and began pounding on the door.

"David, what...." Louis was in his robe and had clearly been sleeping soundly.

"My house is on fire, I need help" I pushed my way into his hall and picked up his phone to dial it in. Again writing this now, I'm realizing that this was unnecessary since I did have my cell phone on me.  It's interesting how the mind fails in these intense situations.

The police and fire crew arrived relatively quickly but far too late to save even a portion of my home.  I was questioned on site, and then agreed to go directly to the police station to file a report while I still remembered all of the details.

I told them everything.  I told them about Erica, her muddled talk about some secretive club.  I told them about the vandalism to my door, the men in my yard and showed them the security footage to back my claims. Unfortunately the footage was extremely blurred. At no point could we find a single frame that clearly showed their faces.  They were always motion blurred, or distorted by flashes of light coming from the road.  One frame where one of the two men had faced the camera directly, showed a solid black face with two bright white lights for eyes.  No detail, no clear lines outside of the silhouette.

In the end, there was little to go on.  The truck was not on the footage, so there was no chance to get a license plate number.  No clear faces or identifying marks were recorded. I had never seen the intruders myself.  It became clear that while they were looking into it, there was nothing solid at this point, except for tracking down and speaking with Erica.

There was only one thing that bothered me about all of this.  While the camera footage was blurry, the camera was pointed low enough to see the walkway and front porch.  At no time during the entire recording did I see the dog that had frightened me so badly in the bathroom. I watched it several times looking for that beast, to no avail.

I'll keep everyone updated as soon as I find somewhere to stay and deal with the insurance company, etc.  Obviously, I'd still appreciate any advice you can give me.  The comments yesterday were extremely helpful.  Had I not had the gun and the security cameras I would certainly be dead.  The people posting who lead me to that decision may have very well saved my life.  Thank you all.

[[Part 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i8ujt/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_3/)] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really conflicted on this.  I would feel horrible to get her into trouble with the police, when clearly this is a medical issue.  As much as I am afraid, I don't want for her to end up being arrested instead of getting the help she desperately needs.  I'm still trying to sort this out, and will update soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually quite similar.  I do not enjoy or partake in casual sex.  I am looking for deep, long term, meaningful relationships.

That said, I have been in the position of truly loving more than one person at a time (I mostly kept these to friendships in the past) and I believe that if you feel this way, if you truly have love for more than one person, that it would be a terrible thing to waste or throw away.

There is so much hate and discord between people in this world, I feel like we need to use every single opportunity for connection, regardless of social norms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ayup. We've been exploring polyamory for the past year and a half or so.  It's been very exciting and interesting (and at times extremely challenging.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the compliment. I would like to agree with you but these two incidents just seem too coincidental for my tastes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I agree.  I think I will at least be getting some motion detection camera's asap.  Though I'm worried that i might need to decide between this and a gun, financially.  Thank you for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had been thinking about this for some time actually.  This might be the right time to do so. Thanks for the advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked this up, it appears that you are absolutely correct.  I'm doing some more research on this.  Thank you!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Met Someone *Wrong* on OkCupid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 04:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met Erica on OkCupid. 

After sending hundreds of messages on that site, trading occasional likes, and following down several winding paths that led nowhere, I found her.  She was quite a bit younger than me, attractive beyond all reasoning, intelligent, experienced and overall seemed like a very caring person.  We shared some phone calls after graduating from chat, and finally, the other night we managed to arrange a first date.  Being somewhat rusty in the dating scene, and being someone who always aims to please the people around me I asked her to decide what she would like to do.  We agreed to go bowling.  It was whimsical, sort of ironic in a "Lebowski" kind of way, and seemed to be a mutually safe place.

Erica did not have a car, so I drove down the winding gravel paths into a surprisingly rural area about a half an hour from my home in Bucks County.  I had lived here for decades, but had never seen the amount of deer that seemed to make her home theirs.  It took several wrong turns, google navigation, and a bit of instinct to find her house but I managed to do so right on time.  

She came running out of the dilapidated stone farmhouse immediately. I got out of the car and we immediately shared a warm hug.  As she leaned in towards me I noticed her eyes.  They were brown and seemingly normal, but when we got closer I noticed the intricate black wheel spokes leading to her pupils.  At that moment I did recall her mentioning her penchant for decorative contacts during one of our conversations.

The contacts were pretty edgy and cool, and Erica was an exact replica of everything I find attractive in a woman.  She was skinny, about 5'6", had several tattoos and wore leggings that would drive any sane person mad.  Hugging her in the driveway seemed like the start of something wonderful.  She was so warm and immediately disarming.

Bowling was a blast.  She immediately suggested that we share a pitcher of beer, and over the following hours of bowling, drinking, talking, and innocently holding each other I was feeling extremely positive.  We left the alley somewhat tipsy, and through the course of dinner I started to notice that the alcohol was beginning to affect her.  This got much worse over time.

Erica began asking me the same questions over and over again.  It got to the point where I had felt that I told her how old I was almost thirty times.  I realized that she had also been frequently asking me how I got up in the morning.  It started becoming clear that she struggled with depression quite severely and I did my best to listen and comfort her when I could.  She told me about being institutionalized for a few years, the cutting that she had done on her arms, and her tattoo.  Erica boasted an S.S. Iron Eagle Tattoo on her lower back. When she told me that I recalled that she had previously asked me if I was Jewish and I began to wonder if I was on a date with a skinhead.  I eventually brought the conversation around to her tattoo and question and was relieved to find out that she was not racist, but Jewish herself.  She had in fact,  gone out as a teenager and decided to locate and get the most offensive tattoo possible in an act of rebellion when she was younger.

This was this kind of extreme uniqueness that made me like being with her.  She was off-the-wall, and up until the point where we spoke about the cutting and the hospital, it seemed fun-crazy.  It soon surpassed that and just became clinically crazy. When she asked me how old I was again I pointed out the fact that she had asked this many times and did not seem to absorb my answer.  She stared at me dead in the eyes pausing first and then speaking up.

"No.... **They** are telling me to ask you that." She looked at me knowingly, as if I would understand.

This was the point where I decided that Erica was clearly mildly schizophrenic.  It was also the point where I decided that I would take her out for one last drink, since we had discussed a specialty bar near my home, and then immediately bring her home.

At the bar Erica became extremely erratic.  She would hug me, then push me away, hard.  She would shout at me asking why I was looking at her "like that?" and then  storm off.  She would return and sit in my lap, wrapping her legs around me.  This was when she told me that "they" don't want her seeing me.   She said that "they" were never fond of outsiders, and that she was only allowed to be with people inside "The Order."  I inquired about who she was speaking about, but only got several non-sequiturs mixed in with random information, such as the fact that Sir Elton John was part of "The Order". 

I became quite overwhelmed with her behaviour and breaks with reality as you can imagine, and drove her home quickly.  I was quite relieved when she fell asleep during the car ride.  

Upon arriving at her house and waking her, I helped her to carry some of her items in where she did everything in her power to get me to stay.  I stood firm as she tried to pull me into her bed with her.  The idea of it was beyond exciting, but Erica was sick. Anyone could see it and I could not bear to entertain even the thought of taking advantage.  I tucked her in, and kissed her on the forehead.  

"Kill me.  Please.... Kill me" she whispered softly and lovingly into my ear.

I told her that I had had a lovely time and left.  Quickly.

I drove home with very mixed feelings.  One one hand I was quite fearful that she could be dangerous in the right situation. I recall being relieved that she had not been to my home and seen where I lived.  On the other had, I felt quite deeply for her.  The pain that she was in.  The mental state which she had little control over.  I pondered whether or not it would be possible to maintain a positive friendship with her, without risk or harm to either of us.

Yesterday, the day after our date, I came home from work to find that the front door of my house had been vandalized.  I was shocked because I live in an upper-scale area and had never experienced this before.  As I walked up my porch steps I realized that what I had first thought was spray-paint was actually quite worse.  A shape had been literally carved deeply into my door, and was stuffed with some plant stalks with small purple flowers.  The symbol looked like a crude letter "P", if the curve in the "P" was a triangle, and placed lower down the vertical line it's the left.  Like so: |

I immediately felt a sinking feeling in my stomach.  Clearly Erica had found out where I lived.  I scanned my memory to see if I had left my wallet out, or told her my last name.  I could not recall but it was clear that she had found out somehow. 

"Fuck." I whispered heading into the house to get a trash bag.  I spent twenty minutes pulling the plant matter out of the door and examining my options. I was going to have the replace the door completely, no doubt.  I thought about calling Erica's parents or family but decided against that because she had spoken about them as if they were horribly abusive people.  The last thing I wanted was for her to suffer further at my hands. For the moment I decided to leave things as they were I would be cautious and vigilant, but I would attempt to simply let this pass.

I had a terrible nightmare last night.  Erica was sitting in my lap facing me, as she had done in the bar.  Her eyes started to change, slightly moving and morphing in a swimming kind of pattern as she opened her mouth wide and moved her face toward mine.  Her teeth began to replicate and shift, row after row like a time lapse of a shark's mouth over a lifetime. She unnaturally stretched forward and enveloped my face.  I shot upright in the pitch dark sweating and breathing heavy. I clutched my chest feeling my heart pounding hard, like a torturous drumbeat.

The beating stopped and silence took hold of the room.  It was dead quiet, but tense.  There was something here, something in the air.  I couldn't explain it but I felt it quite intensely, and began slowly stepping toe to heal towards my window.  I pulled a single shade and peered towards the street and my yard below.  And there they were.

Two men, dressed in dirty hunting clothes were moving back and forth over my front lawn.  They seemed to swap sides, moving fast but keeping low as if trying to make sure that no one could see them over my hedges.  I watched in awe as they darted around the perimeter of the house and one of them slowly tried approaching my front porch.  He got one step up and then turned and ran back to his companion, taking his shoulder with his hand and hastily saying something indistinguishable to him.  The two of them then hopped over the hedges and ran down the street to a blue pickup truck parked on the corner.

This was last night at about 3am.  I've not slept since.  The only story I can come up with is that maybe Erica told her family or friends that I had done something to her. Threatened her maybe.  And that they came to keep an eye on me or seek out revenge. 

I don't know if I should call her, her parents, or the police.  I'd like to leave her be if possible and not increase my involvement in her life, but I truly feel like I am not safe at home.  For now I think I'm going to go to the store and get a security camera today.  

If anyone here has any advice it would be highly appreciated.  I've never been in a situation like this and I have no idea what the right course of action is at this point.  I'm not sure I can let another night go by without doing something.

[[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i1n3o/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_2/)] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you can go out on a date, and come home and talk and joke about it with your wife in bed, then have sex afterwards.  True story. This week.  I love my wife more than I can express. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never should have been </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 06:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight, I'm going to off myself.

So I guess this is my suicide note.  Although, it is more of a story and probably belongs here, if nowhere else.

Before you all get your liberal sensitivities in an uproar, and start begging me not to, I want say a few things.  Don't bother posting that life is worth it, and I'm a good person, and start asking why I'm doing this.  Fuck that. I could tell you that I am a piece of shit.  That I've always been a piece of shit.  I could back it up too.  I live in a shitty room in a boarding house in Philly for recovering addicts.  My roommates keep me up, ass-fucking each other every time the mood strikes them. I've been through three goddamned divorces and have two kids I've not been allowed to see for a decade now.  I work on and off in a warehouse packing and shipping crappy kink magazines like "Lactating Babes" or "Men in Diapers".  I haven't gotten off with a girl for years without paying for it. And yeah, the rest of my life follows suit.

But the fact is that none of this is the reason I've decided to end it.  I like fucking street whores.  I like low shelf whisky in my Schlitz.  I like the filthy fucking life I've created.  It doesn't bother me in the least.  I live for me.  I'm not proud. I enjoy myself when I decide to. It ain't all bad really.

So yeah. Why?  Why did I buy the 9mm off the street today from Black Frank?  I'll tell you.

My life started falling apart after my mother died.  I was fourteen years old and I had gotten really sick.  I never had been vaccinated, and I got the measles which almost killed me.  The worst part about it though was that when I broke the fever, I found out that my mother had died from an aneurysm. So at fourteen I woke up and my mother was dead. Gone. boom.  And she was the only one that really raised me.  My father was a mechanic and spent most nights working late and then at the bar afterwards.  He was just never around.

When she died, my father made a 180 degree turn.  He got all religious and preachy. He started riding me hard. Cracking down on me, keeping me from seeing my friends.  He generally went all Nazi out of nowhere, and it really rubbed me the wrong way.  At this point I had written him off completely. Now my mom was dead and here he was trying to take charge when I was becoming independent.  Let's just say that it didn't work out. I went twenty years without seeing my father.  I moved out, got a trailer, and lived it up since shortly after my mothers death.  In and out of rehab, a short stint in prison, years working and years not.

Yesterday I got the call.  Actually the boarding house got the call and it took a day for them to find me, but that's neither here nor there.  My father had been diagnosed with late stage lung cancer and likely only had a few weeks. It took me a while to decide whether to see him or not, but I decided to man up.  This was my last chance and time had worn away the anger I had been holding all these years.  I was left with only apathy for the man, but this was a last chance opportunity.

He looked like I remembered him, if some child had assembled his body from tree branches.  He was so skinny. Twisted.  The nurses told me that they were putting a tube down his throat tomorrow so I'd better talk to him today, while he was still on nasal oxygen tubes.

Right off the fucking bat, there it was.  That instant disappointment in his eyes, seeing me. I almost turned and walked out immediately.  I decided to sit.

After a few minutes of him slowly, wheezing, asking me about my life, and then dropping into silence, he told me he had something important he needed to share.  He actually apologized for riding me after my mom died, but honestly it didn't seem very sincere.  I pressed him.  I was pissed and I unloaded.  I told him he was a shitty absent father who never knew me.  I told him that riding me like that was the only way he could feel like a good parent, that he was selfish and that he should have known better.

"I needed you to succeed." I could see his eyes water up. "For your mother."

Needless to say, I knew this and it didn't excuse him from being horrible to me as a teen.  I unleashed on him even harder. Yeah, I was a dick, really harsh.

That's when he told me the story.

He told me that the night Mom died he had been out drinking, as usual.  It was getting late, and he had medicine from the pharmacy for me in the glove box of his Oldsmobile, so he cut it short, downing his last beer, and speeding home.

He knew something was off the moment he walked in the door.  He said there was this horrible rotting smell all through the house.  I had been ill for days, and certainly had been putting off some bad breath and body odor, but he said this was like a punch to the stomach.

All the lights were off, except my bedroom, so he dropped his keys and headed over to crack the door of my room where he saw my mother kneeling at the foot of my bed looking straight up and pleading.  

"You can't take him, he's just a boy" she was saying, staring three feet above my bed.

"Why? Why do you want him?...  but what will happen to him?"

He said that she would ask questions then stop for several seconds listening intently. He was paralyzed watching this surreal show play out.

"No!" she screamed. "I'll do anything. You can't have him!"

Then she dropped her head onto the foot of my bed sobbing.  My father said he almost walked in the room at that point, but stopped himself when she began again.

"Yes" she said. "Yes I will.  And you'll leave?  .... Just me? .... and that will be enough?" She looked up again, tears streaming from her eyes.

"I do... Yes.... I declare myself yours.... Yes... I declare myself the property of... Ibn Iblis.... and will accompany you.... to Jahannam." She struggled with the words, starting and stopping.

At the very moment that sentence ended she dropped to the floor. She was stone dead.  And my father said that at that same moment, I had gasped an enormous breath and sat up.  My fever broke within the hour, after my shocked father had removed my mother's body and called the coroner.

Today I found out that my shitty fucking life was given to me in trade for that of my own mother.  I learned that all that good she had, all that love had been given up for me.  For me to get drunk. For me to fuck disease ridden whores.  For me to shoot up and nod off in my chair.  That's what I've created with the price she paid.  That's what her sacrifice was for.

I'm sorry Mom. Goodbye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 93 Crowley! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful, Thanks so much for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's Something Going On at The Julliard School </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 07:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone.  My name is James and I saw something tonight.  I reached out to my friend Frank in Seattle and he suggested that I write a post here.  He told me, and I confirmed after reading several entries, that you all have a solid grasp of unusual situations.  I have no knowledge of the supernatural, conspiracy theories or anything of that ilk, but I do need  help.  I don't know what to do tomorrow and I'm hoping that you can help me decide.

I suppose that some background is in order first.  I have the best possible job, and I absolutely love my work.  This is not something that people are used to hearing from a groundskeeper so I'll help you to understand.  I always had a strong work ethic.  Growing up in the rural Midwest, this always equated to working with my hands.  My father had instilled these values in me before he passed, and my whole life has been filled with satisfaction around this kind of work.  There is nothing like seeing the immediate, direct impact that my manual labor produces before my eyes.

I spent twenty years developing these skills, running small teams, and working on bigger and bigger jobs.  When I turned thirty five and Susan and I had our son Michael I decided that I needed a change.  This was also attractive to me after cancer had taken my wonderful wife Leena. The change I was looking for was not in career, but to find a position that did not require quite so much of my time and attention.  I was a single father and needed to be present to guide my boy to manhood.

With my long and exceptional portfolio of work, along with recommendations from several very influential people I had worked for, I landed my position.  I am now, and have for ten years been head groundskeeper at the Julliard School for Exceptional Children in upstate New York.  Don't bother looking it up, you won't find any sort of public presence.  This school is exclusive beyond the normal definition of the word.  At most there are only ever twenty children here, mostly in their early teens.  There is no application process.  There is no waiting list.  The students that come here, simply come here. New students are always expected and we are forbidden from inquiring about their families or background.  My assumption has always been that these are the children of those holding very high level positions in the government, or the ultra rich.

The grounds of this boarding school are beyond reproach.  There are only five buildings on the grounds proper, but each are incredibly beautiful converted 1800's farm houses and barns.  The campus is surrounded by thirty acres of fields and forest, several streams, and a separate cluster of homes for the staff a mile or so from the educational buildings.  This is where Michael and I had made our home for the past decade, and we loved everything about it.  Beyond all of this I must also say that the salary is enough for me to consider full retirement in the next five to ten years which is rare in my industry.

I have a good thing here and I am serious about keeping it.  Being such an exclusive and, I imagine, expensive school there is quite a large list of regulations that are required of the staff.  It never really bothered me before.  I had a job to do. I was paid well.  All I needed to do was keep my head down, follow the rules and things would be fine.  I was sometimes annoyed by the curfew, but I had my son at home anyway and should be there for him even if he's already asleep.  I stayed clear of the classrooms when school was in session, and in the few times that I almost accidentally intruded, I found that the classroom doors were kept locked.  Most of my interactions with the students were kept superficial though occasionally one of them would communicate something very personal to me or strangely deep and confusing.  I was careful not to press too hard but it would be a lie to say that I was not intrigued by the minds of these very special children.  You could see the wisdom in their eyes.  It was apparent, and it was somewhat unnerving at times.

Tonight I broke a rule.  I had read online that there was to be a super moon, the likes of which had not been seen for fifty years.  The sky was clear, full of stars, and I had had a couple glasses of scotch.  Michael was asleep and I could feel the night breeze calling me.  I grabbed my corn cob pipe, put on my jacket and decided to take a midnight stroll through the hills to see the moon up close and personal.  

I have to admit to you all at this point, that the pipe did not contain tobacco.  I know it's more accepted these days, but for me smoking marijuana is not something I'm very proud of.  I don't do it very often, but now and again I do enjoy a puff or two.  I hope that this doesn't cause you to question what I'm about to tell you but I wanted to be up front about it.

I was about halfway between my home and the campus, just cresting over the top of a small hill when I saw them.  The moment I did, I dropped my pipe and knelt down.  I did not want to be found breaking curfew, never-mind with contraband in my possession. I peered over the side of the hill to get a better look at what was going on.

In the valley below were all of the students and one teacher, Mr Krone.  The student body was in a circle sitting Indian style and facing the center while Mr Krone slowly circled them with his hands held behind his back.  He was wearing what appeared to be an old British schoolmaster jacket, long black and flowing.  In the center of the circle was a wide flat stone.  Upon that stone was one student sitting bound and blindfolded.  I tried to determine which student this was but I was simply too far away and a light mist was present in the valley.

I started hearing this low droning sound coming from below.  It seemed to have several levels of turning melodies melding into this multi-tone tapestry of constant sound.  The low register of the overall affect was surprising as it was clearly coming from the children.  I started to swoon a bit at this point, getting that over-tired feeling that you sometimes do after smoking.  I felt heavy and began to break out in a light cold sweat, though it could have been the moisture in the air.

I watched as Mr. Krone pulled two long black poles from his jacket.  As he walked around the children he would occasionally strike them hard against each other making a loud cracking noise that echoed through the hills. Each time I would flinch, hearing the echo of the sound behind me and wrenching my neck to check behind me.  Upon the fifth such crack he spun and pointed the sticks at the child in the center of the circle in one lightening fast motion.

What I witnessed then was beyond horrible.  That boy. That poor boy.  His body lurched upward, his back twisted and bent backward.  I swear his body left the ground for a moment as his head bent almost fully behind his spine.  His limbs broke their bonds as they twisted in wrong and alternating directions. I could hear his elbows and knees snap as each twisted left, right and back upon themselves. God.  His eyes.  His eyes looked directly at me even though I was behind him.  His head now hung behind his neck covering his back and I swear he was looking at me, hair falling down over his tailbone. He let out one long, horrible, piercing shriek that seemed to stop time dead in it's tracks while those eyes were trained upon mine, until he simply stopped and slumped to the ground lifeless.

I am not ashamed to say it.  I ran.  I ran faster then I think I ever have and didn't stop until I slumped with my back against the locked front door in my kitchen.  After a minute of getting my head straight I checked on Michael to make sure he was safe and in bed which he was.  I haven't slept since.  It's 6 am here now and I need to start work again soon, but I have no idea how I'm going to do that.  I can admit it.  I'm more scared than I've ever been in my life.  More scared that I was losing my wife to illness and taking responsibility for my child.

If you have any ideas about any of this, please tell me immediately.  At this point I feel like I have a few options.  I could confront Mr. Krone or the children and try to figure out what's going on, but this seems dangerous.  At least too dangerous to attempt unless I sent Michael to stay with friends.  I could pretend everything is normal and try to figure out what's happening, perhaps gaining access to Mr. Krone's office.  I could call the authorities and see what they can do and if they can keep my name private.  I just don't know what the correct course of action is here.

Something is going on.  It is dark and it is scary.  Perhaps I should just pack up and leave as soon as possible, though it would be a shame to have to go back to working long hours and settle in a new town. I would appreciate any feedback or advice you can give me.  If you have any idea what I witnessed that information would be very helpful as well.  

Your's truly,

Fearful and out of my depth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Don't Take My Heart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will be the first time I share this story in it's entirety.  It will also almost certainly be the last story I ever share.  I have a very short time and limited resources, so please do forgive me if I make this somewhat brief.

My name is Daryl Jacobs.  If you've not heard of me, I ask that you please read my account here before you search for my name online.  I will share the details that made me infamous, but I would prefer that you hear them from me first.  Public opinion can be  detailed, but it rarely has an empathetic or complete picture of those who suffer it's judgement.  My situation certainly exemplifies this.

I suppose that I should start with my condition.  When I was twenty-four I discovered that I had a severe congenital heart condition.  I was diagnosed with a large atrial septal defect that was growing and tearing over time.  At the time it was discovered it was so severe that a transplant was chosen as the first possible course of action.  For those that are in the know about these things, this is quite unusual.  It speaks to the severity of my condition at this point, and I was informed by many doctors during the time that I was lucky to be alive.

This situation was incredibly scary and painful as it was.  It was made worse by the fact that, at this point in my life, I had been enjoying my new family.  My wife Samantha and I had given birth to our daughter Selena just three year before this discovery.  We had bought a new home, and had been living in the honeymoon period after our recent marriage.  We had just had our first Christmas at home all together a short time before the incident that landed me in the hospital.  The thought of losing all of this so quickly, so near the beginning of this new adventure was unbearable.

Samantha had some very difficult emotional times over the following months.  Our lives were full of worry, tears, and anxiety.  We learned a lot trying to communicate about how we could structure things so that if I did pass, that she and Selena could support themselves.  These were very difficult conversations for us both but I felt entirely responsible for ensuring the continuation of my family if I did not survive. As often happens the particular difficulty of my situation became my saving grace.

A combination of my young age, decent health and new family moved me to the top of the transplant recipient list.  Only four months after my diagnosis I was being scheduled for a heart transplant from a donor who was very similar in age, size and health. We were overjoyed, but not without worry.  The success rate for heart transplants are not overly comforting.  The expected life span, post surgery, were also a grim reminder of the intensity of what I was about to go through.

As you most likely inferred, the surgery was a success.  I left the operating room at Cedars-Sinai approximately six months after my initial diagnosis, and twelve days after that I was allowed to return home with a clean, though frequently monitored, bill of health. I was also able to return to work that year having been given an open-ended leave of absence, and within one years time my life went from death sentence to a reasonable expectation of another twenty to forty years.

As dark as some of that time was, I came out of the experience with new values, and a lust for life and love for my family that I had never had before.  I was in an exceptional place mentally and spiritually at the conclusion of this little saga.  It was this, the incredible mental positivity I had, that made the upcoming ordeals feel so strange and alien to me.

The first incident that I can recall happened after Samantha and I had had an argument in the kitchen while making breakfast together on a Sunday morning.  I had this friend Kimmie at work.  She was a very attractive and incredibly intelligent thirty-something Asian woman and we had hit it off as soon as we were put into the same department a few years earlier.  We got pretty close at work and frequently shared lunches together.  There were the usual comments from our co-workers who would call her my "work wife", but it was truly just a platonic friendship, though intimate.  I guess that I had been talking about Kimmie for some time that morning and my wife Samantha just had too much of it.

"Can we please just stop talking about Kimmie!" She threw the spatula into the pan and turned glaring at me.

I felt really hurt.  I had been trying to tell her something important and I felt like she was really out-of-sorts with her own jealousy.  

"Fine." I shot back. "I'm going to go check on Selena."  This was a common relationship dysfunction that we had.  Any time we would fight one of us would step up as some kind of parenting super-hero.  

I headed down the hall to our daughter's room with the intention of spending some time playing with her while Samantha cooked and cooled down a bit.  When I pushed the door open I found Selena standing and staring directly at me, as if she was waiting for me.  I saw that she had been playing with her letter blocks on the carpet and I saw that her little left hand was pointing down at them.  For a moment, when my mind first recognized a readable word I was brimming with pride in her development.  When I read the word, and saw the smile on her face I swooned and grabbed the door frame to stop from falling.

"Betrayer" was spelled out in wooden blocks on the floor and Selena's smile turned into a giggle as she pointed at me.

I was overcome with shame and this feeling of suffocation.  I found it nearly impossible to breath and lowered myself to a squatting position, putting my face in my hands to overcome the incredibly overwhelming feeling.  Sweat beaded on my forehead as I struggled to regain my composure.

"Daddy Ok?" Selena's little voice broke the spell.  She put her little cool hand on my head and I righted myself.  When I did regain my composure I saw that the blocks were simply a random pile with no discernible pattern.  I went so far as to turn the pile of them over until I proved to myself that they could not have possibly spelled that word, even if Selena could have done so.  There were only half the letters present to spell "Betrayer". 

When I returned to the kitchen with Selena, and apologized to Samantha about going on about my friend, she immediately made me lay down in bed.  Apparently I was sheet white and sweating to a point that was immediately noticeable. I never told Sam what I had seen, just figuring that I must harbor some serious guilt about being so close to Kimmie, and it had come to a head after that argument.

In retrospect I see this as the first time it happened. I had many other similar, but different, instances of this type of thing over the coming months.  I recall walking past Selena's room one day weeks later, while Samantha was talking to her.  In just the split second of passing the door I saw my daughter look up at my wife holding her hand and asking "Why won't daddy just die?" 

I stopped dead and returned to the room. "What did you say?"

The both looked at my questioningly and asked why I was asking. 

"I thought I heard my name." I lied.

"We were just talking about her homework."

"Selena, you weren't asking about Daddy?" I was starting to feel like I was being patronized.  I had pretty clearly heard what was said.

"No Daddy. want me to?" She said it playfully, but she had this curl in her smile that felt goading.  Like it was a threat.

"No, I don't want to hear it." I was getting red in the face, I could feel it. I stormed off to the garage to work on a table I had been refinishing.

Moments later Samantha came in hot, and we fought for an hour about the way I had spoken to Selena.  I never told her what happened, just trying to blame it on a bad day.  She was not happy or particularly interested in my attempts to excuse myself.  It took a few days for us to completely recover, in which I paid particular attention to being extremely kind to my daughter and wife. This did seem to pass.

A few weeks later I got into a hot bath after dinner.  It had been a very stressful day. I found out that I was on a list at work, being considered for layoff.  Only half of my department was considered and I was included in the selection.  We were worried about income and Sam was putting a lot of stress on me to start searching for alternative employment immediately.  Selena was in a poor mood after being up late the night before and I just needed some escape.  As a father, the bathtub has become a sacred space for me to get the personal time and space that I need.  This day that peace was shattered.

I soaked and relaxed for the first couple of minutes.  I then started to notice that the heat of the bath was becoming too much and I was overheating.  I started feeling really thirsty and my heart began to beat louder and louder.  It got to a point where it felt like my heartbeat was shaking the tub, and pounding incessantly into my already aching head.  Then it just stopped.  I don't mean that my heart stopped, I mean that the intensity of the heat and noise stopped stealing my attention, and I began to hear the muffled sounds from the bedroom across the hall.

".... loves her... no ... not anymore.  I know....  we can't let him...." Sam was clearly talking to someone other than Selena. "No... done... He thinks... Kimmie and then Selena.  I know.... touched her.... middle of the night.... fuck, he's dead.... this time next week.  yes.  yes.  poison.  I need your help.... yes. hospital at 9pm.... yes. yes.  .... already dead."

I sat bewildered, intensely focused on hearing each word as this got more intense.  Her voice was cold and harsh. She sounded angry but resolved.  I had never heard Samantha talk like that before and it was frightening.  I jumped out of the bath, grabbed a towel and popped out into the hallway, trying to catch her on the phone before the conversation was over.  I found her in the kitchen doing dishes.

"Hey, who was that?" I asked.

"Who was who." without turning from the sink.

"On the phone."

"I wasn't on the phone."

I looked at her closely.  She had stopped doing dishes and seemed frozen, but still not turning towards me.  I could see tension in her shoulders.  I could feel the stillness in the room, and it set me off immediately.  I grabbed her shoulder and spun her to face me. She shouted, grabbing her left hand as I looked down and saw that she was bleeding.

"What the fuck!" She bent over gripping her hand, examining the cut and grabbing some paper towels to wrap it. "What the fuck is wrong with you?" She looked me dead in the eyes this time.

I stared.  I was caught between anger at her lies and the guild of having hurt her.  I couldn't seem to choose either direction.

"Mommy, Daddy hurt you!" Selena was now behind me.

I turned to comfort her and she flinched and backed up.  That's when the anger overtook me. My vision became like static, and started going red.  I spun and shouted "I want to know what the fuck is going on!"

Selena ran to Sam who held her close.  Sam's anger at being hurt seemed to be pushed aside instantly.  

"Daryl.  Why don't you go dry off and get dressed.  We can talk when you're ready."

It took me a moment, but the empathy in her eyes did calm me down.  I did just that, dried off and got dressed in the bedroom.  I came out to an empty kitchen. I searched the house to find them both gone and then the phone rang. Samantha explained to me that she was worried about me. That her and Selena were going to stay with Sam's parents until the weekend and that she wanted me to see my doctor.  At this point I had calmed, and Sam was very calm and reasonable, expressing a lot of concern about what was going on for me.  I was tempted to open up and tell her what I had heard from the bathroom but something stopped me. I knew what I heard, and if it was true I needed to be careful.  I was honesty afraid that Sam thought I was hurting Selena and was planning to do something about it.  The idea drove me mad, and  I didn't have any idea what to do about it.

I saw my doctor the next day, after Sam setup the appointment for me.  I assumed that she had been quite adamant and detailed about what she thought the problem was in order to get me a slot so quickly.  When I saw the doctor he said that he understood that I was experiencing some emotional swings.  After a checkup, his solution was to refer me to a psychiatrist.  On the way out of his office, headed to the front desk he inquired about any heart issues, and I described the strong heart beat in the bath tub.  I was informed that this was natural but that I should be mindful in the future with very hot baths.

He headed off to see another patient leaving me in the now empty lobby to provide my copay.  The woman at the desk was a wide eyed twenty something who looked like she was halfway between a goth club, and a Wall Street office.

"Oh, you're the guy that got his heart, right?" She said with wonder on her face.

"I had a transplant.  Do you know the donor?"

"Uh, of course, everyone was talking about it.  Wait... " she suddenly stopped and looked down.

"Who was he?"

"I'm sorry.... I." She started pushing papers to sign over the desk to me. "It'll be fifty dollars."

I could feel my temperature rising.  I bent down and slowly pushed the paper back toward her meeting her eye line.

"Everyone is talking about it.  You were about to tell me who my donor was." I recall seeing fear in her eyes. I recall that it aroused me slightly, in a way I had not felt before.

She looked to her left and right quickly, seeing no one around.  "JJ Harrow."

"Who is he?" I had no recollection of the name, though it seemed clear that she expected me to know him.

"The Philly Cutter?" concern in her eyes.

I stopped for a moment, thinking.  Then I remembered the newspaper stories from the previous year or two.  This guy, JJ, had been found guilty of several murders in the Philadelphia area and some surrounding states. I remember that he had begun randomly slashing women with a razor blade on busy center city streets.  Suddenly a victim would find themselves bleeding profusely to find later that they had been cut quite deeply near a major artery in their leg.  After a few weeks of that scare, it had stopped, and women had started to go missing at an alarming rate.  Over two months he had abducted and tortured twelve women in Pennsylvania and Tennessee.  He had strung them up and cut them slowly until they bled out.  Eventually they had decided to try him in Tennessee because that state had the option of the death penalty, which was the verdict in this case.

It all came together.  I had been giving the Cutter's heart.  I felt ill, and I could see the contention on the secretary's face.  I paid and left quickly, saying nothing further, and then returning to my empty house.  I made an appointment with a psychiatrist and had many talks over the phone with Sam and Selena over the next few days.  I didn't tell her about the heart, it was just too much and I knew it would just scare her.

That Sunday was the day.  It was the day they returned.  It was the day everything ended.  The last thing I remember was finishing a nice meal for them, and sitting on the couch waiting.  They were supposed to be home around one o'clock.  I remember it turning two. I remember sitting on the couch looking at the food getting cold on the table.  I remember hearing them come to the front door several times only to find that they weren't back yet. Then I remember nothing.

When the police cuffed and lifted my body from the pool of blood in my living room I could see the bodies of Sam and Selena.  Their eyes were wide, their mouths open.  I can still see them. I see them every day and all night.  I do my best to not think about them at all if I can help it.  They plague me and I ignore them.  There's nothing I can do for them.  I could punish myself but there is only a short time to do so, and I don't see the point.   I don't know exactly what happened but it was not me.  I. I am not me.

This brings me to the real reason I am bothering to write and smuggle this out this at all.  I am to be executed in five days.  Before I was locked up I had chosen to be an organ donor.  The prison is not allowing me to change this being so close to me execution (and I think just to deny me something, more than just my life, as further punishment.)

So I ask you.  No matter how ill you are.  No matter what you are going through even if it is assured death.

Please.

For your own good.

Please don't take my heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hellen Keller
It's all she can really do for entertainment, must be pretty pretty pretty into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 00:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderfully written! Really excellent work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hold Tight to your Children in the Dark Woods. [Part 3] FINAL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/59069x/hold_tight_to_your_children_in_the_dark_woods/)]

[[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/59b8ck/hold_tight_to_your_children_in_the_dark_woods/)]

It took our group three full days to get to New Orleans.  It was Tony and I, our two children, all of our gear and Tony's cousin Theresa.  We had offered to pay Theresa to travel with us and watch the children, as she was the only semi-responsible, unemployed person we knew.  I didn't know her exceptionally well, but we were positive that there was no way that Tony and I could deal with whatever might come, having the children at our side every minute.  

During this trip we shared quite a lot of what had happened with Theresa, and had filled the children in on some key points.  I could not bear for Hunter to know that he had this impending sickness to look forward to, so our story was simply that this man had made Samantha sick, and that we were going to find him, and force him to make her better.  Samantha was very quiet throughout the journey, clearly suffering.  This was heartbreaking for both Tony and I to watch this sweet little girl slowly wasting away mentally and physically.  It was a lot for Theresa as well, though she did an excellent job of engaging her.

We arrived in New Orleans on a Tuesday night and checked into a moderately priced hotel.   Tony and I decided that it being nighttime, it was in our best interest to immediately scope out the house under the cover of dark.  Theresa was given some spending money and asked to take the children out for dinner, and generally entertain them for the evening.  

We dressed in black, grabbed a couple of handguns and a small assortment of gear and headed out. We parked five blocks from the location of the house, and slowly made our way to the home.  When we reached the block on which the house stood we squatted in the back yard of the home across the street.  Both houses were dark, and we were able to secure a position where we could not be seen from the street.

We used our binoculars and night vision googles to visually explore the house before us.  It was a gorgeous historic two-story with wrapped balconies and columns.  There appeared to be no one home at this moment.  We began preparing to get closer and see if we could find any possible easy entrance.  Before we could cross the street however, we started hearing  footsteps tapping down the sidewalk.  We ducked deeply back into the shadows.

Click. Click. Click. The hard shoes tapped away at the sidewalk getting louder and louder as we saw the figure enter the lit area beneath the street light.  Perfectly erect but walking languidly, Jack was approaching his front door.  He was casually dressed in brown slacks and a sweater.  He appeared to be just as he had been before, unharmed, unruffled and perfectly at ease.  He turned from the sidewalk away from us toward his front door and stopped.  The small gas lamp above his head lit, and he turned facing toward us.  We watched, my breath held, as opened a small pouch, extracted his pipe, and began to smoke.  He appeared to be looking directly at us, but we knew that we could not be seen.  For five full minutes he stood there, perfectly still outside of the movement it took to smoke.  He then tapped his pipe upon a stone near his walkway, turned and entered his home.

Tony and I had a short whispered debate about whether or not we should try to enter the house tonight.  It seemed like Jack was home alone now, and we felt that we did have surprise on our side, being so soon after our last encounter.  We decided against this plan since we did not have Theresa on the ready to bring the children if we managed to discover how to reverse what had been done to them.

In the end, we setup a small video camera to the side of the house we hid against, aimed at the front door of Jack's home.  We were able to connect the device to a nearby wifi hot-spot that was not password protected, so that we could view the live stream from our room. Being a hunter, Tony was very much interesting in gathering information by tracking Jack's comings and goings.  His position was that it would be best for us to enter the house when empty, and surprise him when he next came home.

That night we went back to the room and spent a few hours with the kids before turning in.  We explained our plan to Theresa and made sure that she would be prepared to bring the children to that location once we signaled her via text.  

We spent the entire next day watching movies, ordering pizza, and keeping a solid eye on Jack's house.  There was no activity whatsoever until about 8pm.  At that time, we were alerted on my laptop that movement had been picked up on the camera.  We watched as a black sedan pulled up to the house, Jack stepped into the vehicle which then promptly headed towards the city.

We acted fast.  We were standing in the private back yard within thirty minutes, and quickly found a viable entrance.  There was high window slightly ajar and by our estimation it likely lead to the kitchen.  I was able to boost Tony first, and then Tony assisted in helping to pull me up.  As we expected, we entered over the kitchen sink, and lowered ourselves into the dark room.  There was just enough light coming from the windows to allow us to navigate the room.  We quietly searched but we knew that we would be more likely to find information in other areas of the home.

We pushed through one of the two doors in the kitchen into a pitch dark room.  We did not want to risk turning on any lights so we decided to attempt to use the night vision goggles we had brought.  The moment I strapped them to my face, there was a searing pain in my eyes and head.  I was confused and I tore them from my face thinking that I must have stabbed my eyes when putting them on.  

After a moment my eyes adjusted to find myself standing in the center of a well lit ballroom, surrounded by about thirty men and women dressed as if they were attending a party.

"Surprise!" someone said mockingly from the back of the circled crowd.  He stepped forward slowly clapping his hands.  Jack stepped through the last line of participants smiling at the two of us.

"Truly a surprise to us all." he seemed to be giving us credit as the crowd tittered and whispered amongst themselves.  "We have not had your kind of distinguished company at my home in many many years.  I dare not tell you just how long."

Tony muttered an insult and made a move to charge Jack immediately.  He was stopped by two thick and heavy men dressed in black suits who held under the arms.

"I like that energy, Tony!  That may come in handy for you.  Why don't you save it for a moment though, we have much to discuss."

"I'll kill you." Tony growled, struggling against the men restraining him.

"Ah yes, but that't the rub, Mr. Freid." he paused smiling, "You've already done that.  I do so hope that both of you are adaptable.  It will be a necessary quality shortly."

Jack turned toward his surrounding circle of guests and politely requested that they move to the sides of the room.  I had become fearful that their intention was to crowd in on us, and do god-knows-what, but this was not the case.  Once the party guests had cleared the back of the room, we could see what had been behind them.

The back of the room housed an altar and a balcony.  It was much like an altar at a catholic church, but rather then being decorated in pure white, the cloth covering the altar was red and trimmed with gold.  Above the altar was an elevated platform on which stood what looked like two ornate, standing coffins.  They were almost Egyptian looking, but there were some consistently different design elements that were clearly not of that origin.

Worst of all though, standing in front of these containers were Samantha and Hunter.  They were bound, blindfolded and sitting Indian style before the containers, with a guard on either side of them.  

Tony and I both struggled, and were now both restrained.

"Yes! You see now.  This is why you are here." he raised both arms above his shoulders indicated our children behind him.  "This is always how things should be.  Your love and loyalty to your offspring have brought you here.  Here and now.  With me, and with us.  It is beyond Poetic."

While most of the guests looked interested, chatted and sipped upon their drinks, I saw one woman push her way to the front.  She must have been six foot three, tall, dark and Romanian looking. Her face was cruel, the light only increasing the shadow in her thin, shallow features.

"Let's begin!" She croaked with a heavy accent.

Jack's eyes rolled to the ceiling as he turned toward her.  "Oh Lizette, Would you please give me a moment.  Tonight's festivities will be enjoyable for us all, but more so if we can invite our guests to understand the impact of the game.  May I?"  He questioned her in a mocking tone, and proceeded after several moments of her frowning silence.

"Gentlemen.  You are here to save your children. I wonder however, if you understand the meaning behind what you have witnessed?"

Before I knew it I was shouting. "You take them. You steal away their lives, so that you can live.  You're vampires."

"Very good.  Much what I expected, though your mythological interpretation is a tad droll.  In essence though, you are correct.  They die so that we may live.  I will not try to convince you that what we give back to the world is worth this sacrifice.  I cannot expect you to even consider that, your position being what it is.  What I can do." he paused for several seconds "is return to you what has been taken."

Tony and I looked at each other questioningly. Was Jack offering to reverse the damage done to our children?  Would we return home with our children healthy and happy?

Jack watched us closely, smiling.  He was clearly enjoying the tension in this moment and reveling in it.  It was sick.  His eyes, his smirk.  This was his design and he took an unholy pleasure in it.

"For one of you, of course." He let that statement settle. "In a few moments you will both be given knives.  The man who kills the other will have his child restored, fully.  If you refuse we will take you after we have taken your children as you watch.  You see, eternity does become very tiresome. We have other needs, beyond your years.  Now, you may be struck with the urge to attack me or my brethren here." He indicated the people around the room.  "I can assure you that it is simply moot.  I think you now understand that there is no chance of winning in this situation, unless of course you follow the path that has been laid for you, generously by yours truly.  If you choose to take a guest or two with you, so be it.  I will not protest.  But understand that it would simply accomplish nothing."

Jack signaled the men at our sides.  Tony was dragged to the opposite end of the room.  The visitors backed against the walls, as we were made to kneel and each given long, thin stiletto blades.

My mind had been scrambling to find a way out of this, but at the point at which the knife was in my hand, the thinking had stopped.  The reality of the situation took hold, and I was just a man with a knife facing an opponent.

"One more time before we begin.  When one of you is killed, the other will have his child restored.  At your convenience, please begin."  Jack and his guests became still, staring and examining the scene intensely.

Tony and I began to circle each other, slowly at first, then speeding up.We were just from arms reach when I whispered to him. "I have an idea."

He looked to his left and right, as if to see if anyone had heard the communication, and clearly excited that I thought there may be a way out of this.  He nodded his head to me.  He was ready for me to make a move and put my plan into action. I leaned in, close to his ear getting ready to whisper my command.  Then my knife was in his neck.

There was nothing for it.  I was again given a choice to save Hunter, or let him die.  Nothing could change this.  And nothing would change my choice.  Ever.

I forced myself to look Tony in the eyes as he bled out on the floor before me.  I saw his pain, his anger, his submission.  I think that I saw the understanding behind all of it as well though this may have been a hopeful interpretation.

The crowd moved forward, bending and examining Tony's body excitedly.  Three of them eventually carried the body out as there were raucous cheers and congratulatory looks from the party-goers.  I remained kneeling, staring at my bloody hands after dropping the knife to the marble floor.

"I am so very happy that it is you.  And Hunter will be as well." Jack smiled at like a loving father would, betrayed only by his dark eyes.

The two men upon the raised platform escorted our children into the two standing coffins, and shut the covers.  Shortly thereafter one of the men opened the tomb on the left and extracted the now still body of Samantha, carrying her out the same door through which they had removed Tony. 

"Now, we have another winner, aside from my friend here, namely me! More importantly, we have a loser." Jack smirked coldly.  "Lizette, if you would my dear?"

Jack took Lizette's hand in his, and lead her up the platform and guided her into the now empty casket which Samantha had occupied a moment ago.  The lid was shut and I watched as everyone in the room bowed their heads in silence.

I immediately began to weep when after a minute, Jack opened the cover of the tomb on the right and Hunter stepped out.  I saw the guard near him remove his blindfold, and point to me and whispering something. Hunter quickly ran down the steps to embrace me.

This was it.  It was done. I had my boy, he was healthy and I could put all this behind me to move on with my son.  I swept him up in my arms and stood.

"May we leave?" I asked Jack politely but forcefully. 

"You may." he stated from the platform, looking down at me. "But there is one final piece of information you may want to hear."

The bastard actually waited until I asked him what it was before speaking again.  I was once again becoming furious at these turns.  I wanted out of this place, immediately.

"Your son, Hunter.  He is special now.  He is part of our Society.  You see, due to the wager that was made, Lizette has provided your lovely son with not one lifetime, but several.  Hunter will remain as he is today, strong, healthy, and energetic for just under five hundred years, thanks to his benefactor.  You must also know that Hunter will remain exactly as he is today.  He will not grow, age or develop any further.  And, I would think, that he will continue to need his loving father in his life."

I stood in shock.  This only got worse.  Each time I thought that I had made the ultimate sacrifice for my child, the reward was tainted.   Each outcome worse than the last.

"You fucking bastard." I could only whisper it as I fell to my knees.

"Yes well.  I have been a bastard of this world in which you live for some time now.  But I am not heartless.  I have done nothing but give you choices, and now I will offer the final one.  You may leave with your son and care for him until your years expire, at which point he will likely return to our society for guidance and care taking.  Or you may collect on the remainder of Lizette's wager, and live with him until you have both expired together."

I silently took in the entire history of what lead me to this moment.  I had lost my son, recovered him, gained knowledge that I would lose him again, and was now standing here after killing my friend, being offered extended life.  It was too much for my mind to handle.  I focused upon only one thing.  My son. My Heart.  My love and greatest achievement.

I took the deal, and before morning we were both headed back home.  We had lost Tony. We had lost Samantha.  We were informed that Theresa was no more as well. I had only one thing left, and I love him so much.  I will love him for centuries to come.  I will share my entire self, my entire life with Hunter, always.  Until the long awaited end of our days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No winning :) but I appreciate that.  I became self conscious of my estimation abilities when I saw your post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None did really, I did explore that.  I had always been into camping and frequently did so.  This had been my choice fully, without any outside influence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 04:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Text was about a hundred feet, but that was just my estimation in the moment.  I could have been off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hold Tight to your Children in the Dark Woods. [Part 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/59069x/hold_tight_to_your_children_in_the_dark_woods/)]

I never expected to be writing here again.  Frankly I am devastated that this is the case.  I wrote my first post as a means of confession, to display my sin to the world and ask for understanding.  Thank you to everyone who commented and suggested alternative courses of action, as well as those who simply expressed sympathy for my decision.  I am now in the very unfortunate position to admit that my choice had been the wrong one after all.  I thought I was saving my son.  I now know that I was sorely mistaken.

I will pick up where I left off in my last post.  I had submitted completely to the man who seemed to have the power to appear and take my child at will, by promising to deliver to him the daughter of my sister.  That very day I reserved a small vacation cabin in the same forest in which I had lost my son.  I called my sister to explain that I had reserved that cabin each year and had forgotten to discontinue the repeating reservation.  I told her that I could not bear to be there, but I would feel honored for their family to use the cabin as a tribute to the wonderful times that Hunter and I had spent there throughout his life.  The ploy worked perfectly and my sister, her husband and their daughter Jessie made arrangements to take a vacation.  

I was crushed after I hung up the phone, but reminded myself over and over that this was the only option.  This was the only way that my beautiful boy could remain in this world and lead a full life.  Besides which, she would be returned, good as new sometime in the future. It was selfish, but only as much as it was protective.  I could not convince myself that I was doing the right thing.  I could only manage to steel myself against changing my decision.  I literally felt as if I was turning to stone, bound to accepting and participating in this madness out of unquestionable necessity.

Two days previous to the reservation I received a visitor.  I was surprised to hear a knock at my door, as I had made almost no social connections in our new home.  I immediately feared that it was my sister who I dreaded facing in person.

I opened the door to find Tony. I had not seen him in almost seven years but recognized him immediately.  He had changed and not for the better.  He looked like he had aged twenty years.  His hair was grey, his shoulders slumped, and his face seemed to droop from his skull as if it had given up holding on to his skull quite some time ago.

"Thomas." it stuck in his throat, and took him a second to recover. "I think you know why I am here."  His eyes looked up from his lowered head like a dog who knows he is about to be punished.

"Yes. I do."

"We need to talk." clearly relieved at my measured response. "Samantha is in the car, I didn't want to bring her to the door right away. I didn't know...." his head dropped again.  "May I bring her in?"

"Sure.  Hunter is playing in his room.  She can join him."

Tony went to the rusty station wagon parked on the curb and helped his daughter from the car. I could immediately sense that she was not well. She seemed to lean to one side, favoring her left foot and Tony held the palm of his hand to her back all the way up to my door.

I looked down to greet her as best as I could, but stopped dead.  Samantha was about twelve years old.  She clearly had a cataract in one eye, was shuffling with her bad leg, was missing at least one tooth in the front and seemed to be developing grey in her hair.

"Hi Sam" I managed to expel in a shuddering whisper.  

I looked up to see Tony's eyes welling with tears, locked onto mine intensely.  He needed to say nothing.  What he had come to discuss was already quite clear.  My heart sank as the full scope of the situation became apparent to me.  

No. It could not happen again.  I had lost my boy for years, I could not fucking do it again. A rage burned in me as I thought about this happening to Hunter.  I raged at my choices, at my lack of fight, at my deception and assistance in spreading this cancer.  I held it deep inside to smolder and burn as I introduced Sam and Hunter until they were comfortable playing together alone with Hunter's door shut.

The moment it closed I pulled Tony into the den.  I opened my mouth to begin questioning him, but he beat me to it.

"She was fine for about nine months.  Everything was perfect." He began to weep again.  "Then she got sick.  They thought it was just a bad flu and treated her with antibiotics. Then her leg. They couldn't figure it out, but they tested her for bone cancer which came up negative.  Then her teeth began falling out, then her eye, and just...." He fell to the ground, squatting awkwardly.  "It's just getting worse, faster and faster."

My mind raced.  Nine months.  I could only assume that this would also happen to Hunter in in a similar time frame.  I dropped to the floor and sat, putting my hand on Tony's back as he struggled to regain his composure.  I could not hate this man.  I understood his actions all too well.  

After a time, we both made our way to the couch and talked for several hours.  We compared stories and started a mental examination of the details of our interactions with this man, Jack. One of the first differences that stood out was that Jack's demand of Tony was simply to choose a child that he knew.  Someone that he had ties to.  As you may remember Jack had demanded that I actually arrange the trip that would lead to the abduction of my sister's daughter, Jessie.  Tony indicated that myself and my son had immediately popped into his head the moment he was questioned even though he had not seen us for years. Furthermore Tony said that Jack seemed to smile knowingly after hearing our names, as if he had expected them.

Aside from that, almost everything else seemed to be basically inline with my experience.  Samantha had disappeared when Tony brought her along for one of his hunting trips, the first time he had ever chosen to do so.  He came upon the man on another such trip years later.  His description of the contents of the "room" matched mine exactly, though Jack was dressed differently during his interaction.

At the end of several hours of conversation, emotional instability and heated debate we quickly came to a conclusion.  In two days we knew where Jack would be.  It would be our only chance to locate this man, capture and question him.  It would be our only chance to find some way to determine if we could repair the damage done to our children, and to then ensure that it never happens again.  We decided that our primary goal was to find a way to save our children, but regardless we would stop this forever.

It seemed that Tony had come prepared for this conclusion.  His station wagon was loaded and ready with an array hunting and camping gear, as well as a wide collection of army surplus items.  We informed the children that we would be taking them on a camping trip for which Hunter became very excited.  Samantha however, took some convincing.  Tony and I spent the rest of the night planning and sharing food and a couple of beers.  I liked the man.  He was entirely different from the boy that I had known in school, but he had a very quiet, thoughtful deepness to him while he retained a simplistic life.

We packed up and left my home early the next morning for the long drive to Allegheny.  Upon arrival we located the cabin that I had reserved and spent the next few hours finding the perfect place to setup camp.  We wanted to be somewhere where we could easily observe the activity of my sister's family without making our presence known.  If my sister spotted us, there would be some serious explaining to do.  In the end we picked a site on the side of a hill overlooking the cabin approximately three hundred yards away.  We setup our tents, got the children situated and began our preparations.

There were two trees very close to each other in front of our camp where Tony and I setup two tree-stand seats. From this height we were unlikely to be seen, and using his high powered binocular's we had the ability to observe almost every angle of the cabin.  We also prepared go-bags, knowing that at any moment we may have to move out and track the activities of my sister's family.  Since we had a night left before their arrival we also had the opportunity to examine the cabin's surroundings a bit.  We were lucky in that there was a motion detection light post near the entrance way to the cabin.  Having had some experience with electrical work, I was able to rewire the light to remain on permanently.  This would illuminate the grounds at night and ensure that we could clearly see any activity after sundown.

After hours of preparation we spent the evening involved with the children by the camp fire.  I remember Hunter starting to become very protective of Samantha, holding her  around the waist by the fire.  Tony and I met eyes and became silent at the sight of this, trying to hold back the despair, and hold onto our anger.  We would catch this fucker.  Jack would pay, and we would do everything possible to reverse this damage.  Focusing on this was all I could do to hold onto my self. 

After a moist and uneasy sleep we began our watch.  We sat in the trees and each watched our children playing below, and my sister's family arriving and beginning to move luggage into the cabin.  It was very odd to silently and remotely watch every move they made, trying to fill the silence of their distant conversations in my mind as I tracked their movements.  Throughout the day Tony and I took turns watching, and spending time with our kids.  When they made trips to the park offices Tony tracked them, taking his walkie with him to alert me of any unusual activity.   Most of the day passed without incident, and they  did not leave the cabin often, likely just settling in and relaxing.

That night was when it happened.  Tony and I both were in the trees and completely alert, each watching the cabin with our binoculars when we saw the front door swing open.  Little Jessie stepped out in her white nightgown, and closed the door very cautiously.  We watched as she stepped off of the front porch onto the lawn and pointed her finger straight in front of her, eyes wide. She then slowly spun as if drawing a circle in the air around her with her finger-tip, then stopped facing directly to the west. Jessie then lowered her arm and began walking in that direction into the woods. The way she was headed was perhaps only thirty degrees from our campsite, so she would pass us by two hundred feet or so.  This gave us time to do a bit of extra preparation.

 We grabbed our bags, and told the children that we were going to take a nighttime hike.  We told them that we had seen Hunter's cousin Jessie and were going to make a game of following and protecting her.  I cannot say that either child bought our story completely but they complied.  Tony had brought a hiking backpack that had a child's seat built into it.  Samantha was much too old for this, but he managed using it to carry her as we followed Jesse.  The moon as nearly full and the night was clear so we did have enough illumination to be able to navigate safely without using our flashlights and risking discovery.

In approximately thirty minutes we started to see this warm light in the woods directly ahead of Jessie.  We again stressed that we needed to be exceptionally quiet to Samantha and Hunter, and cautiously continued until we had a full view of the scene from a hundred feet away.

There he was.  Jack was sitting in his leather chair dressed to the hilt in a full tuxedo, and surrounded by his complete collection of living room furniture.  This time the lamp was off, and instead his little "room" was decorated by tens of candles.  

"Take Sam." Tony whispered urgently.

Withing a minute I had her off of his back and situated.  Jessie was quickly approaching the "room" and Tony was fitting an arrow to his hunting bow.

I lowered down to a squat and told Hunter and Sam that Jessie was in serious trouble, and that the man in the distance was evil.  I asked them to sit quietly and close their eyes while Tony and I made sure that Jessie was safe.  They accepted this and did what I asked of them, though clearly they were beginning to become very anxious.  Again Hunter reached out and comforted Sam as they sat facing the other direction.

"Five... Four... " Tony began, setting the pace and then becoming silent.

I heard him inhale, and exhale as the arrow flew through the air.  The moment I saw it strike Jack, I yelled Jessie's name and ran toward her as we had planned. I was there in seconds scooping her up in my arms protectively.   She seemed to come to as she said my name in surprise. I ran with her back to Hunter and Samantha and commanded the three of them to stay exactly where they were, as Tony and I headed toward Jack.

We could see that Jack had by now pulled the arrow from his right shoulder where it had been lodged.  He held it in his hand as he peered at us walking slowly toward him.  His recognition took a moment, but it came.

"Well, look who it is! Winner Winner, Chicken Dinner!" he boomed.

Tony and I picked up our pace, seeing that he was mobile.  The last thing we wanted was for him to escape, leaving us without answers. 

Jack reached quickly into the pocket of his jacket and extracted something, heading for the door.  It appeared that he was attempting an escape so Tony yelled for me to tackle him as he stood firm and fired another arrow.  The arrow struck his right leg, as he inserted the key into the door and turned it.

The moment the key was turned, the contents of the room seemed to fall and spread in a million loose, smoky particles around him.  As I entered the area I could see the dark wood colored cloud that had been his coffee table swirling around my legs. In the split second it took me to reach the man himself, Jack had taken the arrow that he had freed from his shoulder, and plunged it into his own neck as he stared at me dead in the eye.  He fell.

I dropped and turned his body over, blood gurgling from his mouth and throat.  I demanded he tell me how to help our children, demanded that he fix what he had broken.  He only looked me in the eyes calmly as he shivered and then fell silent and still.  His body was now the only thing in the darkening clearing. All seemed lost.  Jack was dead, but our children had no remaining hope.  I sat upon the cold ground and mourned.  I mourned what I would soon have to face, watching Hunter die a slow death.  This failure far outweighed the success we had in ending the man before me.

Tony headed back to collect and protect the children.  After a time I began to examine Jack's body, all while wondering what exactly to do with it.  Upon his person, in the interior of his jacket pocket, was one single item.  A letter.  It was elegantly penned, stamped and sealed with a small wax circle, crest and all.  

Over the next ten or so hours, Tony and I completed our immediate work.  We returned all three children to the cabin, giving hurried and worrisome information to my sister.  We told her enough to allow us to leave, return to the scene and bury Jack deeply.  We came back afterwards, tired and dirty and explained everything from start to finish to my sister and husband.  I don't know what I expected from that conversion, but at this point I am positive that it is the last one I will ever speak with them. We packed up and returned to my home, the four of us together.

We repeatedly studied, examined and discussed he contents of the handwritten letter we had found on Jack's person, which were as follows:

+++

*Jack D.*

*1XXX Third Street*

*New Orleans, Louisiana 70130*

*My Dearest, and most wonderfully despised Lizette,*

*I have heard, via my usual sources that your collection has grown by great bounds this decade.  I find it disheartening that you continue to focus so mindlessly on quantity over quality.*

*The way you destroy this art of ours is abhorrent. The way you just end things, and leave those souls to be found in such a mundane and obvious manner. Why do you insist on this stark outcome for those we collect, my dear?  There is no artistry, no beauty, no flow in what you do.*

*I take pride in my work.  Every single one I collect is a symphony of anguish.  Everyone affected by my reaping takes a journey. They follow a wondrous arc of emotion. The loss, the recovery, a miracle and then the despair of a destiny they could never have escaped.  Beauty my dear.  This should be about beauty!*

*But you have no eye for aesthetics.  You base, shallow beast.  This was so obvious to me the last time you murdered me.  Such a poorly constructed and thoughtless action, so beneath our kind.  How dare you treat me in such a gauche manner.  A shotgun to the stomach.  Frankly it was just like you, base and trite.*

*I assure you Lizette, that you will learn my artistry whether you will to or not.  I will show you what can be accomplished when one is passionate about their work, rather than a mindless hoarder such as yourself.  I shall do so posthaste!*

*All of my Love,*

*All of my Hate,*

*Jack*
 

+++

You can interpret this for yourself.  I cannot take the time to explain what we gleaned from this letter. The most important thing however was the simplest.  We had an address.  We had a location.  I am packing up my laptop now that I am finished writing and we are beginning our road trip to New Orleans. This is not fucking over.

[[Part 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5a2io9/hold_tight_to_your_children_in_the_dark_woods/)] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay strong!  Kids can be a wonderful turning point in your life if you can stand up to the pressure ans responsibility.

My life took a complete 180 after having a child, and I know that you're strong enough to do the same for your child.  It will get difficult but all meaningful things are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
