<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justin Trudeau: father's influence made my brother's marijuana charge 'go away': Canada prime ministers brother Michel charged with possession in 1998. The government facing calls for blanket pardon for past pot convictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is a theory offered by the Irish Times](http://www.irishtimes.com/news/world/europe/merkel-experiments-on-ivanka-to-get-to-donald-1.3059534)

 On Tuesday, German chancellor Angela Merkel goes back to her roots as a scientist with a very public experiment.

 Her subject: Ivanka Trump. Her thesis: the way to the most powerful man in the worlds heart is not via his stomach, but through his daughter. Donald Trump may love chocolate cake, but he loves his elder daughter more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High schoolers deliver science textbooks to their climate change-denying congressman, are sent away via intercom: The students say they'll use their first ever vote against Dana Rohrabacher if he doesn't acknowledge the threat from climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High schoolers deliver science textbooks to their climate change-denying congressman, are sent away via intercom: The students say they'll use their first ever vote against Dana Rohrabacher if he doesn't acknowledge the threat from climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada rushes to defend net neutrality as the U.S. moves to dismantle it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a significant public health victory, Mexico has succeeded in eliminating a disease which is the leading cause of blindness worldwide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a significant public health victory, Mexico has succeeded in eliminating a disease which is the leading cause of blindness worldwide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plan to legalise and tax cannabis launched in Switzerland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dennis Kucinich Is Back, With His Sights Set on For-Profit Education </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ontario plans to launch universal basic income trial run this summer: About 4,000 low-income participants will receive monthly payments to assess whether program can provide stability and positive changes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC chairman expected to unveil strategy to reverse net neutrality: sources </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haley warns N. Korea: Dont give us a reason to fight' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's AP Interview: Unhinged, Bombastic, and "[Unintelligible]" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil deGrasse Tyson: Science deniers in power are a profound threat to democracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil deGrasse Tyson: Science deniers in power are a profound threat to democracy | You dont have the option to say you dont believe E=mc2. Its true whether or not you believe it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil deGrasse Tyson: Science deniers in power are a profound threat to democracy | You dont have the option to say you dont believe E=mc2. Its true whether or not you believe it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil deGrasse Tyson: Science deniers in power are a profound threat to democracy | You dont have the option to say you dont believe E=mc2. Its true whether or not you believe it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists poring over military and satellite imagery have mapped the unimaginable: a network of rivers, streams, ponds, lakes and even a waterfall, flowing over the ice shelf of a continent with an annual mean temperature of more than -50C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan: Russia probe will help US allies | "One thing we know for certain is that Russia meddled in our election," Ryan said. "This is a foreign country trying to meddle within the internal activities of a sovereign country or a democracy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 30 people were killed over the weekend in Mexico, according to local officials, amid a widespread surge in drug gang violence that has driven murders to a level not seen since 2011 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps Earth Day Statement Is Shameful: The president has moved swiftly to dismantle a wide range of protections for the environment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Nye: Pruitt, DeVos 'the least qualified people on the planet' for their agencies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Witch Hunt Against Trump Twitter Critic Sparks Investigation: Homeland Securitys inspector general is looking into a possible abuse of authority. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps Earth Day Statement Is Shameful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China plans worlds biggest national park on Tibetan plateau: Survey to help draw boundary of 2.5 million sq km park scheduled for this summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Witch Hunt Against Trump Twitter Critic Sparks Investigation: Homeland Securitys inspector general is looking into a possible abuse of authority. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps Earth Day Statement Is Shameful: Trump released an Earth Day statement touting his commitment to protecting the environment, despite doing the exact opposite in the first few months of his administration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks releases more top-secret CIA docs as U.S. considers charges: WikiLeaks claims the 31-page user guide for a CIA device code-named Weeping Angel can turn some Samsung TVs into surveillance tools with an implant for recording audio from a TVs built-in microphone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Close to 9,000 people have died since Duterte took office and promised an unrelenting campaign to rid the Philippines of illegal narcotics. About a third were killed in anti-drug operations in which officers said the victims had violently resisted arrest.

 Many other deaths were blamed on mysterious vigilantes who killed dealers and users, or homicides that could be unrelated to drugs. Police deny any involvement in those killings, most of which they say remain under investigation.

Smart move by jailed critic Senator Leila de Lim. Bring public attention to herself just in case Duterte and his henchmen decide to make her one of the statistics of mysterious vigilantes death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Bill Gates backs open access, Steve Ballmer discovers the joys of open data: Ballmer launched his new project USAFacts -- 'a new data-driven portrait of the American population, our government's finances, and government's impact on society.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A jailed critic of Philippine Duterte praised police who alleged in a Reuters report that officers received cash for executing drug suspects, and said an international criminal case should be filed against the president for crimes against humanity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia's role in Trumpland, not just the election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As US prioritises Julian Assange arrest, UK hints Sweden comes first: Swedens existing warrant to extradite Assange over a sexual assault allegation would be the first consideration for the British gov't if he were to leave the Ecuadorean embassy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI gathered intelligence in the summer of 2016 confirming Russian operatives tried to influence Trump's team  not just the election itself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon's Opposition to Climate Fraud Probes Gets Less Sympathy From NY Judge: After case is transferred from Texas, judge skeptical of Exxon's appeal to stop NY and Mass. investigations, as company gets support of 11 GOP attorneys general. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vomitoxin makes nasty appearance for U.S. farm sector: A fungus that causes vomitoxin has been found in some U.S. corn harvested last year, forcing poultry and pork farmers to test their grain, and giving headaches to grain growers already wrestling with massive supplies and low prices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'This Is the Fight for Our Future': March for Science Rallies Planned Worldwide: Marches will protest President Donald Trump's "war on science," waged through information crackdowns and proposed funding cuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top U.S. officials to testify in Trump-Russia probe reboot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientist: Its pretty depressing that its only a couple of years since the 400 ppm milestone was toppled  Global CO2 emissions just breached 410ppm, level unseen in millions of years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientist: Its pretty depressing that its only a couple of years since the 400 ppm milestone was toppled  Global CO2 emissions just breached 410ppm, level unseen in millions of years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's FCC Gives Big Telecom "Free Reign" With Vote for Major Handouts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 162 tech companies tell appeals court that Trump's 2nd travel ban is illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran election: Ahmadinejad barred from running </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. said it was troubled by the growing number of extrajudicial killings in Philippine President Duterte's war on drugs and called on Manila to stick to its commitment to investigate them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump praises Chinese efforts on North Korea 'menace,' Pyongyang warns of strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK provides billions in credit to fossil fuel industry despite clean energy pledge: 'The vast majority of this support  4.8bn  has been pledged since 2010, despite a government commitment to back clean technologies instead of supporting investment in dirty fossil-fuel energy production. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK provides billions in credit to fossil fuel industry despite clean energy pledge: 'The vast majority of this support  4.8bn  has been pledged since 2010, despite a government commitment to back clean technologies instead of supporting investment in dirty fossil-fuel energy production. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defenders of Wildlife stashes 14,000 endangered species documents before Trump can delete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emissions Credits Likely Worthless in Reducing Emissions, Study Says: Schemes allowed by the Paris climate agreement won't help countries reach their reduction targets and should be phased out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American, Russian cheered as they reach Intl Space Station: A Soyuz space capsule on Thursday safely delivered an American astronaut making his first space flight and a veteran Russian cosmonaut to the International Space Station. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Inauguration Bankrolled by Firms Seeking Government Favor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Governing body declares: No IP addresses for governments that shut down internet access - to deny their citizens access to tools like Google, Twitter, and Facebook, which can be used to document whats happening and reach out to coordinate resistance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Governing body declares: No IP addresses for governments that shut down internet access </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Governing body declares: No IP addresses for governments that shut down internet access </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exodus From Canada's Oil Sands Continues as Energy Giants Shed Assets: Over the past year, five multinational energy companies have sold off nearly $25 billion worth of their Canadian assets to domestic companies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossil Fuel Industries Pumped Millions Into Trump's Inauguration, Filing Shows: Among the big donors were Chevron, Exxon, BP and Citgo Petroleum, which each gave a half million dollars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trillions of Plastic Bits, Swept Up by Current, Are Littering Arctic Waters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Payout Time': Exxon Seeks Waiver From U.S. Sanctions to Drill in Russia | "Exxon applied for waiver from sanctions on Russia. Among departments who must approve is the State Department, run by company's ex-CEO" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: CIA, FBI hunting for insider who gave docs to WikiLeaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast belatedly 'introduces' faster broadband to the city of Chattanooga which it sued to keep from doing the same thing in 2008. It didn't go well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Koreas simple but deadly artillery holds Seoul and U.S. hostage: These perfectly positioned offensive artillery firing positions are virtually impenetrable, extremely difficult to take out by counterfire. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Groups decry Trump plan to demand social media passwords at US border: DHS Secretary John Kelly has defended the idea, saying that if travelers "don't cooperate...they can go back" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Groups decry Trump plan to demand social media passwords at US border: DHS Secretary John Kelly has defended the idea, saying that if travelers "don't cooperate...they can go back" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI used dossier allegations to bolster Trump-Russia investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA images show Antarctic ice shelf is about to birth an iceberg: The latest images from NASA's Terra Satellite shows the crack in the Larsen C ice shelf is spreading rapidly, raising the possibility that an iceberg may soon be calved. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
 Subway claims in the filing that the CBCs tests lacked scientific rigor and were conducted by people who lacked training... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subway sues TV network over soy chicken story: The worlds largest restaurant chain is suing the CBC over a broadcast that claimed the chains sandwiches were almost half soy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science strikes back: anti-Trump march set to draw thousands to Washington | On Saturday, thousands of scientists are set to abandon their laboratories to plunge into the the political fray against Trump in what will likely be the largest-ever protest by science advocates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redrawing the Battle Lines in the ISP Privacy Debate: We cant give up just because Congress voted to overturn rules to protect consumers data. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysia Air Is First Airline to Track Fleet With Satellites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysia Air Is First Airline to Track Fleet With Satellites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook gives staff green light to join May 1 political protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alaska Senators introduce bill to expand offshore oil drilling in Arctic Ocean and Cook Inlet: Obama protected large areas of US waters in the Arctic from oil and gas drilling. Senate Bill 883 would effectively cancel these protections and force the DOI to quickly approve new oil and gas leasing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Paul Manafort Now Advising Chinese Billionaire On Trump Infrastructure Contracts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents in Germany face $26,500 fine if they dont destroy controversial My Friend Cayla dolls: '...researchers found that the dolls were recording users and sending this information out to a third party specializing in voice-recognition for police and military forces' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Manafort Now Advising Chinese Billionaire On Trump Infrastructure Contracts: Pacific Construction Group wants in on the presidents $1 trillion plan, the Financial Times reports. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% efficiency or efficacy - what's the difference? 

And how long before it's set for human trials?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cotton booed for defending Trump on tax returns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 Former EPA Chiefs Speak Out Against Trump Administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foreign criminals and failed asylum-seekers could be removed from Britain within 25 days under a new fast-track appeal system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you probably won't be allowed to video the scene or they will  confiscate your device I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Businesses pressure Trump to stay in Paris climate deal: Coal companies, oil giants Exxon and ConocoPhillips, renewable energy groups, and major American manufacturers such as GE are among those arguing that the US should stay in the deal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One broadband choice counts as competition in new FCC proposal: 'Even if a business that needs broadband has only one choice today, the FCC would consider the local market competitive if there's a second broadband provider within a half mile.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington state House committee approves internet privacy protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington state House committee approves internet privacy protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington state House committee approves internet privacy protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey's referendum campaign was "unequal", with critics suffering restrictions and state resources being misused, international monitors say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March Was Second Hottest on Record Globally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US officials warn tensions with North Korea are 'coming to a head': US national security adviser pushes for peaceful resolution after countrys failed missile test, as Donald Trump hopes for Chinese intervention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 06:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The referundum was one of his usual crooked ways of telling the world he was legitimately given the power by the people. 

 The Republican People's Party (CHP) demanded a recount of 60% of votes. They criticised a decision to accept unstamped ballot papers as valid unless proven otherwise.

Of course he had to cheat because left to choose on their own he would have lost. 

What a load of bo**ocks this guy is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Human Cost Of Trumps Rollback On Regulations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duterte is desperately looking for friends. When the US refused to sell him some M16 rifles, he turned to China.

Unfortunately for him China warned him yesterday about visiting the disputed South China Sea island and he backed down immediately giving some flimsy excuse about friendship:

[Duterte cancels visit to disputed South China Sea island after warning from Beijing
Philippines president backs down on vow to plant flag on Thitu island, citing our friendship with China](https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/apr/13/duterte-cancels-visit-to-disputed-south-china-sea-island-after-warning-from-beijing)

And now he flip-flops back to the US. Who can believe what Duterte says?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientist Say Only 10 Years Left to Save the Planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Restoring sight to over 4M people: Eye surgeons Sanduk Ruit and Geoff Tabin, along with the doctors they've trained, have helped restore sight to over 4 million people and aren't finished yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Pick For Army Secretary Has A Troubling History Of Anti-Muslim Remarks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whistleblower uncovers London police hacking of journalists and protestors: ...secretive unit within Londons Metropolitan Police uses hacking to illegally access the emails of hundreds of political campaigners and journalists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Etihad Airways has been praised for their "above and beyond" customer service when a plane was turned around at Manchester Airport to allow an elderly couple to visit their dying grandson. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erdogan trying hard to attract some attention...again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea threatens pre-emptive nuclear attack: '...one of the nations senior officials has accused the Trump administration of wanting to annihilate his country and blamed the escalating tension on the Korean Peninsula squarely on the U.S. and South Korea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VPN Traffic, use spikes in wake of death of user privacy rules: Several VPN providers have seen a more than 50% spike in downloads since the repeal of the Broadband Consumer Privacy Rules. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rain in Pyongyang as North Koreans prepare for 'Day of the Sun' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Third-party browser extension aims to boycott United: The Drop United tool blocks United flights from showing up in results for several major travel search engines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems Challenge Jared Kushners Security Clearance Over Hidden Russian Meetings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Must Reach Net Zero Emissions Sooner, Study Finds, to Reach Paris Climate Goal: Greenhouse gas emissions must peak quickly and carbon capture technology must improve if there is hope of limiting warming to safe levels, researchers find. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft says U.S. foreign intelligence surveillance requests more than doubled: The amount was more than double what the company said it received under the FISA during the preceding six-month interval, and was the highest the company has listed since 2011 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon Tells Judge It Will Continue to Fight Climate Fraud Investigations: The company wants a federal judge in New York to reinstate a discovery order allowing it to depose the two AGs investigating the company over climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla to unveil electric tractor-trailer this fall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.N. experts condemn killing and torture of gay men in Chechnya: "These are acts of persecution and violence on an unprecedented scale in the region, and constitute serious violations of the obligations of the Russian Federation under international human rights law" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft says U.S. foreign intelligence surveillance requests more than doubled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Even for Pruitt, it's outrageous": EPA chief says US should exit Paris deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA chief Pruitt explicitly called for the U.S. to remove itself from the Paris climate agreement, one of his strongest remarks yet expressing his opposition to the landmark deal to keep global warming below 2C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA chief Pruitt explicitly called for the U.S. to remove itself from the Paris climate agreement, one of his strongest remarks yet expressing his opposition to the landmark deal to keep global warming below 2C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FTC Commissioner: If the FCC kills net neutrality, don't expect our help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia blocks app used to organize protests: The app, called Zello, reportedly has been popular among long-distance truckers in Russia who are conducting strikes to protest a road tariff system. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=taeiss1zGAw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video: 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=taeiss1zGAw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of people descended on the Russian Embassy in London to protest against the reported torture and murder of gay men in Chechnya. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington state debates new privacy bills after Trump clears way for ISPs to sell personal data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington state debates new privacy bills after Trump clears way for ISPs to sell personal data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington state debates new privacy bills after Trump clears way for ISPs to sell personal data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whale rescued from fishing nets puts on beautiful show for tourists off the coast of Cornwall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S., China ramp up warnings against North Korea ahead of celebration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'F-ing horrifying': Sessions outlines immigration crackdown in 'Trump era' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceland-U.K. geothermal energy power cable link: Scientists are studying the feasibility of using geothermal energy from magma for the first time in a $100 million project in Iceland. If it is successful, we could see 10 times more energy produced from a single well than from conventional wells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceland-U.K. geothermal energy power cable link: Scientists are studying the feasibility of using geothermal energy from magma for the first time in a $100 million project in Iceland. If it is successful, we could see 10 times more energy produced from a single well than from conventional wells. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secret footage obtained of the wild elephants sold into captivity in Chinese zoos: Animal welfare advocates have filmed some of the wild elephants captured in Zimbabwe last year and shipped to China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US President Donald Trump has said Nato is "no longer obsolete", reversing a stance that had alarmed allies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unenforceable: How voluntary net neutrality lets ISPs call the shots: Pai's plan would "tilt everything in favor of the incumbents," regulator says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shell, Dow hid cancer-causing chemical in pesticides, contaminating drinking water for millions in California and beyond </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI obtained court order to monitor ex-Trump adviser in Russia probe: The FBI and DOJ obtained the warrant targeting adviser Carter Page's communications after convincing a FISA judge that there was probable cause to believe Page was acting as an agent of a foreign power, in this case Russia, </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Educators Decry Conservative Group's Climate 'Propaganda' Sent to Schoolteachers: Teaching material sent by Heartland Institute to thousands of teachers denies climate science, aims to teach a 'debate.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration considering 'back-door way' to cut social security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egyptian Christians wept with rage as they recovered the bodies of loved ones killed in twin church bombings, furious at a state they believe will no longer protect them from neighbors bent on their murder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coke Hopes No One Notices All The Plastic Bottles Floating In The Ocean: The company says its committed to recycling, but a new Greenpeace report says thats not enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moderate French presidential candidate suggests he may pressure US tech companies into creating encryption backdoors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bureau of Land Management temporarily changes website banner from green mountains to big hunk of coal - staking an obvious claim in the Trump administration's campaign to bring coal and other industry jobs back to the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada's National Police force officially confirms ownership, use of Stingray devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two Russian cosmonauts and a US astronaut touched down safely in central Kazakhstan Monday following a 173-day mission aboard the International Space Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pen isn't the only gift Trump gave Dow Chemical - the main manufacturer and defender of chlorpyrifos which is one of the most frequently cited causes of farm-worker pesticide poisoning -but is particularly toxic to young children and the fetus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Chairman wants voluntary net neutrality and critics are ready to fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The story soon caught the attention of Cui Zijian, a boyish-looking propaganda official in Xinjiang who writes about the threat of religious extremism on his Weibo account with nearly 30,000 followers. 

 On December 16, Cui suggested homeowners lobby local officials to block the construction, adding: If that doesn't work, then how about pig head, pig blood. 

A "propaganda official" - it's unfortunate that the story caught the attention of this official who is trained and experienced in spinning a storyline and incite the public against what he viewed as extremism. 

 [Cui]... arguing that his professional and patriotic duty was to resist extremism. His online speech about Muslims was part of the job, he said. 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamophobia in China on the rise fuelled by online hate speech: Imam of Nangang mosque subjected to death threats and pig's head buried in grounds as trolling on Weibo disturbs centuries of harmony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah..I must be slowly getting desensitized and that's worrying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Editorial: Trump says, I have won awards on environmental protection  EnviroNews says, Bullshit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers post code in Trump protest: 'Don't forget about your base' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG - this depression is worst than I thought - its making me forgetful 

Edited to include that incident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a summary by the Telegraph but days after the event.

https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/64acag/stockholm_attack_driver_deliberately_targeted/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A rare one-horned rhinoceros has been killed by poachers at a national park in Nepal: The male rhino was shot in the head and left in a pool of blood at the Chitwan National Park; its horn had also been gouged out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
