<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1493</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet Obama wouldn't have played the "find the electrical socket that doesn't work using a fork" game. Only the bravest of presidents have tried that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I hope Colbert is the only one willing and they have to go with him. I think I'd be able to feel the heat off Trumps face all the way up in Canada  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> COME MISTER TALLY MAN, TALLY ME BANANA   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soft shell tacos

Hard shell tacos

Pick one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That aid either directly or indirectly lead to the formation of al-Qaeda as well. The whole soviet-afghan war was sort of a clusterfuck.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See your mistake is bribing the teacher. You need to bribe an administrator, a vice principal perhaps. The bureaucrats give you more bang for your buck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the "go to college!" push really should have had a caveat explaining that not every college degree makes you hire-able to everyone. And that some degrees really are more desirable than others. 


The go to college message I got in school made it seem like any degree is better than no degree but frankly you'd make far more money in a trade than with an art history degree or a gender studies degree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Uncle ExtenZe   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ass is clenched and my heart is pounding, this is a new level of cringe video  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great movie. Jake Gyllenhaal really hits it out of the park with his character  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then secretary of defense Mattis  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for cheating on me, Susie. Best thing that ever happened to me.

The very last sentence. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Byron_Looper

Holy shit he almost won the senate seat too. After the incumbent senators murder Byron was the only one on the ballot since dead people must be removed. But the parties also couldn't change their candidates that close to the election. The murdered senators widow actually won the seat on a write-in thanks to a coordinated effort from the community. What a crazy situation though, a murderer almost becoming a de facto senator.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Trump really needs a good reason for his base to be OK with it tbh. He just needs to say something like "Bannon let the pressure of being on the NSC get to him. It's a lot of tremendous pressure. And it turns out hes weaker than he makes himself out to be. But you know not everybody can handle pressure like I can. I'm the best at it and when people in my administration can't handle the pressure. (Points thumb over his shoulder) They're fired. That's how I'm keeping the swamp drained" 

And then anything Bannon says is ignored after that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they'll block people and inconvenience them in the name of their cause but they won't stand up for it as soon as it looks like they'll need to stand up and be inconvenienced/incarcerated? Way to show people you're really behind this shit and weren't just doing it to virtue signal. 

I get protests are supposed to inconvenience people and I'm probably more sympathetic than I should be sometimes (vehemently disagree with blocking a highway/ambulance though). But how the hell is anyone who gets stopped by this or sees it in the news going to be sympathetic when the leader doesn't even think it's worth really fighting for. Like everyone else needs to get stopped and bothered by this but the actual people leading it? Nope not worth getting arrested or standing up for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like how Qatar has one of the highest GDPs per capita despite having a large slave population literally making nothing or next to nothing. There's enough wealth concentrated at the top to pull the average up that much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like people can't reconcile their idea of what Rays relationship with everybody was and what the reality of it is. There can be a real difference between work friends and regular friends. Doesn't mean you don't like your work friends but outside of work you might really not be that compatible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 07:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not your decision to make for anyone but yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching something like The First 48 really made me realize how much old school detective work goes into solving murders. If there aren't great witnesses and no motive within the people that know the victim, it can be almost impossible to get a lead. Cicumstantial evidence only goes so far in some cases. 

From what I remember though, truly random murders are relatively rare. Not every case that goes unsolved means it was committed by an unmotivated stranger, lack of evidence can play a big part as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 31 unanswered points, how do you manage that after dominating the first 3 quarters?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alex Jones had some theories about weird stuff happening at a place called Bohemian Grove. A lot of powerful people are known to meet here, including a lot presidents and bussinessmen. So he infiltrated the gathering and found them doing some odd rituals. Not sure what the wider implications were but he was right that odd stuff goes on there. https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bohemian_Grove#Infiltrations   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the same guy but the argument I've heard is that it constitutes a religious test under the first ammendment. The SC will likely hear this case and they take intent into account. So even though it doesnt say muslims in the ban, they may see it as effectively a work around to the constitution No idea how valid that is but that's an argument I've heard floated around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want water? Like from the toilet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he had one for dropping bombs too? Or is that more of a button of some sort?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was accidently shot in the woods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 05:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Science has gone too far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coyote Peterson is a total badass. Dude doesn't swear once through all those bites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they were making fun of the guy getting punched and his girthy body just above you. Is that hating on men? Or is it only hating on a gender if women are involved in some way?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve was a man but only in name 

For his wife had his balls affixed to a chain 

And cry as he might, at any perceived slight 

She would never release his manhood 



Now Growing blue from the build up of splooge

It drew Steve of shives into madness anew 

Throwing his world into a feminist stew 

Where his only release is banning all but a few 



This is where Steve is resigned to stay 

Living out the remaining dregs of his days 

And what more else is there to possibly say? 

His wife gets fucked while he watches in vain   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got some really sexy hips  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Broken condom finger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apl iz craple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bcuuz thae dnt mak PC nd r lik consuls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the wording is important too. Kraut said to "back it up with facts or hang yourself with it". Basically the equivalent to saying put up or shut up. So it wasn't even him telling the other guy to literally hang himself. He used a turn of phrase that the other guy took a snippet of to get Kraut banned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wanted to say I loved your conversation. The way you both approached it was very refreshing in the current climate. Nice level headed discourse is something we could all use more of I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 11:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont watch football but i hope your preferred team beats the other team by scoring more points in the agreed upon manner in which a team may score points. And that they t-bag the quarterback or something (8)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 11:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Potheads can't do anything right lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 11:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like saying "Guns and rifles" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 10:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They inject rats with increasing amounts of thc which is either extracted from marijuana or synthesized by other means. They also give oral doses and inject it into the abdomen of different tests groups to test lethality that way. This continues until they find the dose that kills 50% of the rats they inject. 

There is no known human ld50 as far as I am aware.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .9x19mm parabellum to make it ironic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My prediction is that they are waiting for at least the SC nomination before they'll do any serious opposition to him   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's the difference between pure populism and fascist populism. Neither is great but the pure one will at least respond to the masses. The fascist one only seeks to use public opinions to further power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe its a subtle jab at how presidents play themselves up as larger than life people who will get things done. Only to turn into talking heads when they're in office. That or they didn't have the budget to animate his body every time he appeared. Either one could be valid for Futurama honestly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was 1-900-PEE-ONME taken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many a great atrocities have been committed by well intentioned men   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's he doing fantastically? Genuinely curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he was supposed to be a leader? What leader goes around whining this much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The courts are starting to strike down gerrymandered district maps. Hopefully enough get corrected by 2018  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The staff put on Fox News and he forgot what he was doing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 05:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are true patriots. They wanted nothing more than to thrive in the freedom that the west can offer. Risking the life and limb of them and their families on the promise of safety and the chance at living outside of fear and tyranny. 

And they've been utterly betrayed.

Disgraceful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Cameron doesn't do what James Cameron does for James Cameron. James Cameron does what James Cameron does because he is James Cameron! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sic semper evello mortem tyrannis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experience (which is just as valid as pauls) is that it's largely personality driven. In my elementary school the kid who got picked on the most was a scrawny weird kind of kid. He wasn't a pussy but he was kind of small and had a lot of anti-social behaviour which means he was easy picking for bullies.The biggest bully in the school? Some fat kid a year above me with a gaggle of smaller friends. They would pick on anyone they could get away with. He was just a mean guy and the mean guys gravitated together to pick on people.


So in my experience bullies just bully anyone for anything they can. You aren't special because you got bullied over being fat, no more than I'm special for being bullied about my parents divorce. You also can't say that any fat person was bullied. It's just as likely that they could be the bully (if we're going by anecdotes).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 20:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not only the politically savy thing to do, he's almost certainly contractually obligated to not say negative things about the movie. Breaking that agreement can result in lawsuits but it usually comes with a serious blackballing by the industry. They'll simply refuse to work with you. He definitely did what he should have done if he ever wants to work with them again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look they used a computer to *download files* from a *public server*! If that isn't hacking I don't know what is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E Pluribus Unum

Good luck out there guys  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fiscal Conservative" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The German war machine took many forms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Average age for the onset of dementia is 80. Early onset is somewhat arbitrary but is usually considered to occur before 60-65. So he would definitely be on the younger side for dementia, only slightly outside the general early onset range.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to lean towards this theory. Trump came out and said everything the fox news crowd believes. They really didn't need convincing, they just wanted validation, and he gave it to them. The rest kind of got swept up in the momentum that the base created.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 05:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So its not benevolent to stop a child rapist/murderer because it strips away the offenders free will to commit horrible acts? 

It just seems odd that a benevolent god would prioritize the right to choose to murder over the right to not be murdered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The U.S. constitution provides pardoning power to the President for all federal crimes"

The only restrictions as far as I know are judgements from impeachment proceedings, and civil responsibilities (ie. Civil court rulings for civil liabilities). 


https://pardonandparole.uslegal.com/scope-of-pardoning-power/pardonable/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: This practice is what intially got the ATF involved with investigating the Branch Davidians in Waco. They had been purchasing large amounts of AR15s along with M16 receivers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't use it, you lose it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seriously think that speech at the CIA will come back to haunt him. Of all the agencies, the spooks really don't seem like the type to insult like that....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 05:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 hours seems lofty at this point. Guys complaining about snl at 3 am.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally, a politician that speaks to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the lady in Ireland who was left to die because they refused to abort. The baby was going to miscarry and they couldn't save it. They refused to remove it though, because it had a heartbeat and Irish law prevents abortion based on that. The baby went septic and it killed her. Now there's a widower husband with no one left when they could have saved at least one of them.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Death_of_Savita_Halappanavar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep and Zac Efron is the main kid who has a crush on her. Efrons voice is like 2 octaves deeper than it should be for that character too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two rules when dealing with people:
 
1) Never let them know all the info you have  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probe you on your thoughts about the socioeconomic implications of Britain leaving the European Union  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insurance contracts generally have a common clause called a force majeure clause. This removes liability from both parties in the event of an extraordinary event or circumstance outside of either parties control. Things like riots, war, strikes, or "acts of god" like hurricanes, earthquakes, and volcanic eruptions. Generally these clauses don't entirely remove the obligation of either party to fulfill the agreement. Only suspend it until the event is over.

Your specific contract will likely have one of these clauses but the level to which liability is diminished can vary. Read your contract if you're curious, it probably has some force majeure provisions.  

IANAL btw.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As if Trump will even read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Florida and Ohio   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, this is the system they designed. If they didn't want this happening they shouldn't deregulate the market to allow companies to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Halloween theme is definitely up there with "Tubular Bells" (the exorcist theme) as the scariest horror songs of all time. It's just fits so perfectly with the theme of Halloween and the movie itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries man, I just wanted to include the full translation of the quote  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, was only commenting on the compensation for doing prison time part of your comment. Reputation is hard as hell to recover.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can sue for compensation. Lost wages, emotional and physical trauma, damage to reputation. All these can earn you a big settlement. It is kind of fucked up that you have to sue to be compensated at all though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Beware that, when fighting monsters, you yourself do not become a monster... for when you gaze long into the abyss. The abyss gazes also into you." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like it's trying to escape  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would probably take President Comacho over President Trump at this point. At least Comacho sought out the smartest guy he could find to solve his nations problems.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 21:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That movie gets scarier every time I watch it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that what a timeout is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up and coming YouTuber saved by eccentric fashion choices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's an Asian immigrant though. It's a coin toss as to whether they're oppressed or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd make a fuckload more money than he's ever made on YouTube. Assuming he'd actually put some effort into it... unlike his YouTube channel... nevermind...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it depends on how much this person means to you. 

If its a close friend then i would suggest starting a dialogue. Maybe try to figure out what they like about the comic. It could be that this is the only one they've seen and they just liked it. Or they could be a big fan but perhaps an outside perspective may make them question the comics messages. You know the person better than me so you'll have to figure out the best way to approach this, and determine whether or not they'll be receptive to your opinion. If that's what you decide to do. 


If it's just an aquaintance then the hassle probably isn't worth getting into. Let them share their shit and move on. Or troll them. Your choice honestly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at that smug little bastard oppressing everyone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I made sure to use "stabilize" instead of "treat". Unfortunately, they only have to make sure you won't die then and there for the most part. Which is certainly better than being turned down outright for having no insurance but it definitely isn't the best solution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 11:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hospitals are obligated to save your life if you are going to die regardless of your ability to pay. At least in emergency situations. Even in the US. If someone shows up at the ER with life threatening injuries or some life threatening medical condition (heart attack, pneumonia, etc) the hospital has to get you into a stable condition. Insurance is only brought up after the fact.

I guess things get squirelly with long term treatments for chronic issues  la Breaking Bad. From my understanding though, you can't be turned away for emergency treatment.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to look at it like this. I'm much happier having known the little guys than to not have. They would have lived and died regardless of if I had done anything. Its just how nature works. But I was able to be part of that cycle, and I got too make it the best life possible for them. They still die but i got to make sure they died loved and comforted, having lived a life of the very same things. And that's the greatest gift I could possibly give them.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
