<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6914</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a pop-up magazine experiment is turning journalism into performance art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In 1785, the Marquis de Sade wrote The 120 Days of Sodom in his cell in the Bastille in 37 days. At this point in his life, he had spent eight years in prison. He had also been burned in effigy, survived attempted murder and lived for months on the run as an outlaw after a series of scandals with prostitutes. The 120 Days was his first  albeit incomplete  attempt at a novel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the Marquis de Sade wrote his first novel, about debauched aristocrats in an isolated castle with prostitutes, after being held in Paris's Bastille prison for 8 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In bid to eliminate state income tax, fears of another Kansas-style disaster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Across 13 studies, we found that the simple act of scheduling makes otherwise fun tasks feel more like work. It also decreases how much we enjoy them.

For example, in one, we asked participants to imagine grabbing a coffee with a friend. Half of the participants imagined that they planned this gathering a few days in advance and put it on their calendar, while the other half were told that they decided to grab a coffee on the fly. We found that this simple, relaxing activity was associated more with work-like qualities (obligation, effortful, work) when it was scheduled, compared with when it was impromptu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL behavioral scientists have proved that scheduling a fun activity reduces enjoyment of the activity over just doing it spontaneously </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they recently had an episode on police technology (and how nightsticks led to the Taser): http://99percentinvisible.org/episode/tom-swift-electric-rifle/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
