<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8653</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 03:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the photos on my website www.fraternalties.com are original high resolution photos. I also release design "blue prints" during pre-order phase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid advice! Many thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! Thanks for sharing that bit of info! Do you by any chance know where and how to approach angel investors? I googled "Angel Investors Toronto" and I found a few. Should I get a lawyer first to protect my interest before approaching angels? Once more thank you for your time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, you're not alone... There's a lot of misconceptions that surrounds Freemasonry so I don't blame you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 3 or so years ago, I was diagnosed with anxiety, depression, and PTSD. I couldn't function well as an office worker so I lost my job and primary source of income. Because I couldn't afford to pay some of my bills, I went on "consumer proposal" which is almost like bankruptcy. I don't think anyone will give me a loan because of that record.

On the positive side, I am capable of pulling in big sales in a matter of hours. We made about USD $10K on our latest collection. $8K of that amount was made on the first few hours when I offered the necktie collection for pre-order. Shopify can corroborate this. By the way, the website of the company who stole my designs also run on Shopify. 

I really appreciate your time sharing your thoughts. Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for commenting! We're working on having a distributorship program but it looks like it will take me a while to implement it. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I produce a very limited quantities (like about 100 units per style only). These ties get sold-out within hours of offering them (pre-order). The most amount people would buy are about 7 but most just buy anywhere between 1-3. Also, some of the ties that they have copied are commissioned works that was not supposed to be for sale to the general public.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually in Canada but the vast majority of our customers are in the US. Last year I sent out a newsletter asking if anyone would like to be an official distributor of our products. The response was overwhelming. The thing that prevents me from implementing the distributorship program is the lack of business know-how and the lack of financial means to afford a CPA-lawyer. I know nothing about royalties and such. I am seriously disabled when it comes to business administration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I checked copyright is automatically granted to the creator at the moment of creation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protected in the sense that some of the designs they took are commissioned work- exclusively made for certain groups within Freemasonry. Those neckties are meant to be awarded and not supposed to be bought or sold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a conversation going on on fb and ig already so I can't delete those anymore. Thanks for the tip though! I'll draw upon this experience in case I encounter something similar in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly me. Your comment make sense now after I saw the parent comment. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't afford a lawyer but I tagged them on facebook and about to do the same on [instagram](https://www.instagram.com/fraternalties/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if serious... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the tip and vote of confidence! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip bro! I called them out on social media.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh dang... that's such a great idea... but I think a bit too late because I just finished calling them out on social media. Note to self: don't let emotions blurry your vision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Masonic Regalia company in UK stole 8 of my necktie designs. xpost from entrepreneur. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the short version of my original post. Basically I was informed by a customer about this regalia company in the UK who possibly took 2 of my designs. I investigated and found out that they not only took 2 but [8 of them](http://imgur.com/gallery/Ly125). 

One of the styles is a necktie that I made exclusively for the [College of Freemasonry](http://imgur.com/kZ3gzGH) here in Ontario, Canada. Those ties are meant to be awarded and was never supposed to be for sale. 

I think they might have taken designs from Masonic Revival and The Craftsman's Apron as well. 

Here are the 8 designs that they have taken from me http://imgur.com/gallery/Ly125 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a necktie designer from Toronto, a regalia company in the UK stole 8 of my designs. What do I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **TL;DR** I found out last night from a customer that an established store in the UK serving the same demographic I'm serving have stolen two of my designs. When I looked, I found out they have taken not just 2 but 8 of my creations. http://imgur.com/gallery/Ly125

**UPDATE** They commented on my [Instagram post](https://www.instagram.com/p/BQbXh0iAHRJ/?taken-by=fraternalties) with this: *"We are just retailer in the UK NOT a manufacturer! As you can see on our website we have more than 70 Masonic Tie Designs We have been supplied all of these designs including the 8 designs which you believe belongs to you. If you have any copyright issues then please contact the manufacturer of these ties directly [email address here]"*

----------------------------------------------------------------------

Hi there! It's my first time posting here!

I suppose I'm supposed to fill out the survey first. 

**1) What is your product or service?**
I design awesome neckties for the members of the oldest fraternity in the world- Freemasonry. My elevator pitch is *"Family, Freemasonry, Muaythai: Fighting anxiety, depression,   PTSD the natural way- with love, philosophy, and sports."*. And then at that point I bring out my phone and show them [my life story and my cute kids](https://www.instagram.com/fraternalties/). 

**2. What motivated you to start a business?**
I have 3 things: 

**a)** As a means to adapt. I have social anxiety due to traumatic childhood experiences- working with other people have always been a challenge. Art is my therapy- a trait I got from my dad. Entrepreneurship is a natural progression for me. But business savvy I am not- me and my wife fight about this A LOT!

**b)** Growing family and membership requirement. We are a family of 6 now but I was working as a tech support callcenter agent at the time with baby no. 2 on the way when [FraternalTies, the tie that binds](http://www.fraternalties.com) was conceived. I wasn't particularly fond of neckties until I joined the Freemasons- a group of men who love to wear formal attire and speak flowery words when they meet. I thought it would be cool to come to meeting wearing a nice Masonic tie. I looked online and found nothing but tacky ones. I chanced upon an article by My Wife Quit Her Job and an idea came to just design my own necktie and see if anyone would want one as well. We have grown from that 1 necktie that I auctioned on eBay back in 2009.

**c)** My wife constantly challenging me. 

**3. How long have you been working on your startup?**

Since 2009.

**4. What is your 6mo  / 1yr / 5yr plan?**

Honestly, I have nothing penned down. I just go with the flow.

**5. What have been your most memorable positive and negative experiences.**

*Positive:* People telling me how they relate to my artwork and brand on a personal level. It's humbling to know that people are willing to pre-order something and be willing to wait over a year  for a necktie. It feels encouraging that people are willing to give their hard earned money for one of my creations- I have a necktie from our 2010-2011 collection that was originally sold for about 30 something dollars that was sold on eBay for over $200 last year.

*Negative:* My work getting stolen all the time. This is the reason why I'm posting this here. I have pretty much given up chasing after people selling my designs on zazzle, teespring, etc... Last night, a customer informed me about a UK based Masonic regalia company who have taken 2 of my necktie designs. Upon checking their website, I have learned that they have stolen [not just 2 of my creations but 8 of them](http://imgur.com/gallery/Ly125). One of the styles that they have appropriated is the one I made exclusively for the [Fellow of the College of Freemasonry](http://imgur.com/kZ3gzGH)- an education program for Freemasons in Ontario, Canada. Those neckties are not meant to be for sale. They are supposed to be awarded only to those who complete the program. Can I get ideas on what to do? One of my followers already told them that he knows where the original design was from- but my designs still remain up for sale on their website. Can I get compensation from this?

**6. If you could travel back in time, what advice would you give yourself. **

Don't be afraid of emails and phone calls (I currently have 21,700 unread emails). 99% of the time they're actually good stuff- like people asking what's coming up next, or them giving you a good testimonial. 

**7. Not soliciting or selling anything. Actually, everything in [my website](http://www.fraternalties.com) is sold out right now. **

**8. Karma, I hope I have enough. :-)**

----------------------------------------------------------------------

**Edit:** grammar, grammar.

**Edit:** An update. They commented on my [Instagram post](https://www.instagram.com/p/BQbXh0iAHRJ/?taken-by=fraternalties) with this: *"We are just retailer in the UK NOT a manufacturer! As you can see on our website we have more than 70 Masonic Tie Designs We have been supplied all of these designs including the 8 designs which you believe belongs to you. If you have any copyright issues then please contact the manufacturer of these ties directly info@nanbagroup.com"*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you find it motivating. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [For the lazy](http://www.ifmamuaythai.org/2013/02/the-world-celebrates-muaythai-day/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Muaythai Day! Today is also my birthday! Would anyone buy this shirt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, I know this may seem spammie but this is actually near and dear to me. I'm a graphics artist and dad of four- Muaythai and marijuana literally saved my life. [Story 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/comments/4bau2q/is_it_too_late_to_get_in_shape_i_thought_so_but/), [story 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/MuayThai/comments/5c9alm/for_those_wondering_if_its_too_late_to_begin_muay/) 

**As a Muaythai addict**, I am delighted to find out that today is also *The Day* of the great sport that saved my life! 

**As a stoner and lover of philosophy**, it's pleasant to share birthdays with the legend Bob Marley. 

**As a Freemason**, it's interesting to note that the founder of the Illuminati, Adam Weishaupt, was also born on this day. I must add though that Illuminati is not Freemasonry. Some people just like to think that somehow they're one and the same. 

What does the Illuminati have to do  with Muaythai? Nothing, unless you believe they control everything. Anway, if you have a thing for nice and unassuming t-shirt, then please consider my work http://bit.ly/2lggfIj *Do it. I command you.* 

Edit: I document my daily progress on [Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/fraternalties/) (in case anyone want to see if the story checks out).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some students are new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One with everything! LOL https://youtu.be/xlIrI80og8c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kick from Kru sent my 7 y/o son's tooth flying! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Year, New You! 10 Quotes by Freemasons that Will Make You a Better Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 01:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18 Popular Brands You Didn't Know Were Founded By Freemasons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm... you sure that's mj that you smoked and not Salvia divinorum?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 07:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate! I get sentimental too with the items that I wear. Case in point [then](https://www.instagram.com/p/BM-j_FUh751) and [now](https://www.instagram.com/p/BM-ldO-BV-k).

This [longsleeves shirt](https://www.instagram.com/p/BLXBM7uhZAg) is more than 20 years old.

This [Adidas tanktop](https://www.instagram.com/p/BLXhigkhp74) is also more than 20 years old. 

And this is how I make sure that my [Muay Thai shorts will age well](https://www.instagram.com/p/BHv6SiAjMuW).

Edit: link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 21:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thanks for your kind comment! I appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the support and the feedback. Do you prefer pre-tied or self-tie bowtie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I know Eldritch but it turned out that the knot I like to use a lot is something new way of making an Eldritch variant that I stumbled upon. Pardon the mess but here's a quick "tutorial" that I made some time ago. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EGPhWuBLyqI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An old African proverb goes "If there's no enemy within, no enemy outside can hurt us." Thank you for your kind thoughts. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for taking the time to share your thoughts. I appreciate it the kind words and the well wishes! Sawadee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'll keep at it! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get it!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kids deserve a better version of myself everyday. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that! Once you hit rock bottom, there's no other way but up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the kind words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the kind comments and well wishes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for commenting. Speaking as someone who have lived the life of a bullied child (an only child from a broken family in a society where divorce is outlawed), I used to be wary of people. But the awareness that I am now physically stronger to defend my self and my loved ones from those outside who could potentially us, that awareness gives me a strong sense of confidence and calm that I have never felt before. Same with your experience, my anxiety is at bay as long as I maintain a calm heart and mind and I get that from martial arts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect then. The average length of a tie you can get on the market is 57". But you Brothers can't deny when I say [I like big knots](http://i.imgur.com/hRfhkF8.jpg)  so our ties are 60" in average, and the extra tall version is at 64".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks for the kind comment. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. Looks like have to close the pre-order earlier than expected. We ship and pack everything from home. From past experiences, I don't really want to deal with too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I design them myself and I have a partner in China who translates my design into a format that the Jacquard loom would understand. We've been partners since 2009. I hope to visit my country the Philippines next year (I haven't been since arriving here in Canada back in 2004) and when I do I'm gonna go on an Asian trip. I hope to visit Thailand for Muay Thai and China to meet the people who make magic for us. I hope this helps :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Xpost r/muaythai) Am I too old, or too sick, or too busy for Martial Arts? I'm a 35yr old father-of-four diagnosed with anxiety, depression, and PTSD. Martial Arts saved my sanity and my life. See my journey with before and after videos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 00:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR If you're just curious to see the before/after videos, see links below. 

I was a physically and mentally abused child. I have a certain naive demeanor that made me a constant target of bullies at home and at school. I didn't know how to label it back then but I've been afraid of gatherings of people for as long as I can remember. This condition gave me a natural aversion to team sports. Though I prefer reading and drawing as my main activities, I also did enjoy certain physical activities that DO NOT involve being with a lot of people such as long walks alone and mountain climbing in my teens. Walking and climbing trees and mountains aside, I have never played any sports in my life before except for Taekwondo back in gradeschool (I never went pass white belt). 

Fast forward to college. I was 16yrs old and on my own for the very first time away from family. I lived in a small apartment cramped with college kids right next to the University. When I say small apartment, I mean 3rd world small (this happened in the Philippines). 

We have a big drug problem in the Philippines and that led to the rise of the current president whose name became entwined with extra judicial killings of users and pushers back home. With that said, more than half of the students in my apartment were meth users. I tried it one time and I was instantly hooked. It made me feel less anxious and depressed. I felt happier when I was on it. I didn't know it then but I was practically self medicating. I kept the habit for 3 years until I began using my college funds for it and I got kicked out of school. I felt extreme shame for my family because I was an honor student before college, and being the last male in the clan to hold the family name, I felt that they have high aspirations for me. 

Fast forward to 2013. My kids number 3 and 4 (twins) were born a day after my mother-in-law lost her battle to breast cancer. 3rd major death in the family within 4 years- first my father-in-law due to sepsis, and then my dad also due to sepsis which led to multiple organ failure. The following year my grandma who I'm really close with passed away too. My marriage was deteriorating at a very rapid rate at this point in time.

One day my left eye began producing tears as if I was crying on just one side of my face. It went on for 7 days until I made a decision to speak to my doctor about it. I was referred to an eye specialist who found my condition peculiar but otherwise nothing was wrong with me physically. After some interviews and test that followed, my doctor concluded that I was having physical manifestations of a mental ailment. I think this was the point where I opened up and spoke about the things that happened in my life. I was referred to a psychiatrist and I was diagnosed with anxiety, depression, and PTSD. I was prescribed medication which made me feel suicidal so I ditched that and now my therapy and medication is Martial Arts- Muay Thai in particular. 

It's interesting to note that I was over 200lbs (I stand at 5"7 in height) before martial arts. By the time my twins were born, I was totally depressed, couldn't sleep, smoked a lot, ate a lot. My health got so bad that I had to sleep with a CPAP machine just to help me breathe at night. My joints would crack when I walk. My doctor thought that my cartilage and tendons are getting weak so she advised me to avoid all sports and most exercises with the exception of yoga and swimming (no thanks to both). I'm not saying that you disregard your doctor but looking back, if I actually followed her advice and I did not sign up for Muay Thai with my family, I would have never known that all I needed to cure my "weak tendon and cartilage" was Martial Arts. Because of Martial Arts, I became a better version of myself and it placed me in a much happier place.   

I have more videos below but first let me show you my [BEFORE](https://www.instagram.com/p/BI03VgwDXj0/) and [AFTER](https://www.instagram.com/p/BMdQETthg_5/). The 'before' was from November 2015, the after was from November 2016. I don't normally shave my beard except on Movember because I'm a MoBro! I lost about 30 lbs in between Movembers.

[My painful attempt at combining kicks and punches on the heavy bag with my wife on the background also hitting the bag but better than me](https://www.instagram.com/p/BJF28N_jIGC/). I see mustache so I know this video was towards the end of November 2015. For comparison, [here's me from November 2016 video from just a few days ago](https://www.instagram.com/p/BMdCHonh1cv).

[Me throwing roundhouses on the bag on August 2016 eleven months into Muay Thai](https://www.instagram.com/p/BJFp47ajNgw/) I trained consistently with the Kru as our personal trainer for at least 6 months. I stopped formal MT training around summer but I try to run everyday if I can. Thankful that our Kru was kind enough to let me hit the bag when I take my kids there to train. [Here's another video of me throwing consecutive roundhouses back in August](https://www.instagram.com/p/BIySe9MjIlq/).

[Me shadowboxing- day 2 of my coming back to the gym after a long break](https://www.instagram.com/p/BMk9xQzh9fp) After several months of hiatus from formal MT training, I decided to join Krudar Muay Thai once more last week. 

I started this post thinking of just posting my progress videos but I ended up having a joyful trip back to memory lane. Thank you for reading and watching. 

Edit: In case you're interested in reading more about my personal journey - depression, drug addiction, salvation via Muay Thai- check out my post on /r/fitness from March- https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/comments/4bau2q/is_it_too_late_to_get_in_shape_i_thought_so_but/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! Cool! Let me know if I can help clarify anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not printed. Prints don't get a nice ombre effect. Our ties are Jacquard loom woven silk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm posting this here for the benefit of those few members of this sub who requested that I post an update during rare occasions where I actually have something to offer. For the most part, my website is actually empty of merchandise. With that said, I hope the vigilant ones won't think that I'm just here to linkbait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "From Darkness to Light". My latest Masonic Paisley collection. Inspired by duality of life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and eldest kid (16yo daughter) used to wonder why I even bother taking videos when I was just beginning because obviously my moves at the time were far from okay. I told them that I capture moments so that one day I can look back and see my old self and smile and contemplate how far I have gone. :-)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Sylvie! You're an inspiration to us and I am one of your proud Patreon supporters. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Thanks for commenting. Thank you for the kind thoughts. We love your technique breakdown videos! Benson is truly a great guy (and a new dad!). I'm wondering though how you knew his name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh cool! Please extend my regards to Kru Darwin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank for commenting! All the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome! And thanks for the comment! I appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Perhaps I will :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for sharing your story and for the kind words! Flying the dork flag high and proud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh way!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for sharing a piece of your story as well! Completely agree with the tremendous boost in confidence and self-worth!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really know. It's like a pat. Like "treat me well bag". I do weird stuff when I get nervous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you like! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tag Brother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for commenting! Glad to hear that you and your family will be training soon! Get photos that you can use for before-after's in the future. I track my family's progress on my [Instagram page](https://www.instagram.com/fraternalties/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 22:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost. Had to delete the other one. Wrong account used. Sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From 1949 to 1954, eighty-nine percent of the U.S. Supreme Court Justices were Freemasons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 22:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was organizing tons of my scattered files and also looking for stuff I can post on [Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/fraternalties/) when I stumbled upon one of my old [Did-Jah-Kno posters from June 15, 2014](http://imgur.com/YHcbQnP).

It made me wonder how we went from being trusted figures to becoming objects of conspiracy theories? There's no hidden hand here. The primary objective of Freemasonry is simple- and that is to "make GOOD men better." Notice the capitalized word. Our Gentle Craft don't simply admit ALL men. There is no place for men of questionable character in our Brotherhood.

Much like the USA Presidential election, we follow a voting process which involves a background check. A few bad apples slip through the filter every once in a while, but I suspect that a cowan's true color will soon be seen by the Brothers with pure hearts.

Edit: Reference [http://bessel.org/sctfmy.htm](http://bessel.org/sctfmy.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP here. I posted using the wrong account. Messaging the admins to see if author can be changed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 02:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and daughter extend to you their appreciation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I see your perfect egg and I raise you this one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 21:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 15:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been to the US but I was made an honorary member of this lodge. My 2nd home. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 02:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're very proud of Janice! Her home gym is also my gym- Krudar Muay Thai here in Toronto. We have an event this April 9 and she will be there with us. So proud!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 17:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for bringing up the topic of postage (and you forgot to mention custom fee on top of that too). Those things are one of the several reason why we're not increasing production quantities. Good news is that we are working on implementing a [distributorship program](https://form.jotform.com/53524050168248). We have more than a dozen applicants in the US already and a few more International applicants. The future is bright for FraternalTies. If only I have a day job to inject funds it would have been a lot easier to implement things like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 14:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for commenting Brother. Yes I remember that. If this Patreon thing flops, I'll definitely look into kickstarter once more. We do have some old ties in my personal collection that I may or may not release- depending on how well we do with our finances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 14:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro, you're awesome! I don't know what to say... My first patron. Thank you soooo much! Thanks for the kind words too! Such a gentleman! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 14:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you happen to know why I don't want any of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 06:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sorry. [I made about a hundred of those](http://i.imgur.com/L0VCtJ6.jpg) but not too happy with the outcome so the project is on hold and it's been on hold for quite a while now. I need funds for these things and more that's why I'm on [Patreon](http://patreon.com/fraternalties) now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 05:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. It's not always easy to explain myself. I'll do everything in my power to make this patreon thing workout for me. It's my only way out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 05:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your thoughts. I have approached banks and other institutions before and they cannot help me mainly because I'm on Consumer Proposal. For those who may not know, that is somewhat the same as being bankrupt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 05:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the candidness. There's a rationale behind the madness is all I can say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 05:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your kind suggestion brother! We have considered Kickstarter before but I feel that Patreon will best suit our needs. Once more, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am the brother behind FraternalTies. I'm hoping to get some help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 02:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone! I am John Paul Gomez, a member of Doric Lodge No. 316 in Toronto and an honorary member of Harmonie Lodge No. 699 in Buffalo, NY. In case you're not familiar with FraternalTies, it is a Masonic lifestyle brand that I founded on 2009. Basically, I design stuff using Freemasonry and Philosophy as my inspiration and I monetize some of my designs by turning them into merchandise. I distribute the vast majority of my artworks online for free. I'm a constant target of plagiarist. 

FraternalTies became somewhat of a popular brand among the Freemasonry crowd. The demand for our products far exceeds what we can comfortably handle. Because we are a two person operation only with myself doing the creative and marketing stuff, and my wife on the financial side, we are finding it hard to cope with a huge demand. Being located in Canada with more than 90% of our client base located in the USA presents unique challenges as well specially for a small business like ours. Imagine shipping and customs fees.

Since I lost my job about two years ago due to illness, I found it harder and harder to provide funding for my business endeavors. Like any other business, we need money to pay for hosting, software (Adobe cloud subscription), storage, equipment, manpower, and materials. Though our neckties are bestsellers, the fact that we produce a limited amount only twice in a year means that I have to find other means to support the business that I love and my family at the same time. 

An opportunity came 5 days ago on Holy week Monday when my [personal story of struggle and triumph](https://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/comments/4bau2q/is_it_too_late_to_get_in_shape_i_thought_so_but/) hit the front page of the /r/Fitness sub. Someone introduced to Patreon and I thought it was good. If you're not familiar with Patreon, I invite you to [visit my page](https://www.patreon.com/fraternalties) where I will explain what you can do to help.

That's all for now. I'm here to answer your questions. 

Once more, here's [the link](https://www.patreon.com/fraternalties) to my Patreon page.  

TL;DR: I manage a popular Masonic brand but because I no longer have a dayjob that can inject much needed funding, the business cannot sustain itself anymore. I'm looking for sponsors. There will be rewards. [Here's the link to my Patreon page](https://www.patreon.com/fraternalties).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 19:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 19:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 19:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I remember this. This is actually what my Kru taught me to do. I was doing it this way because I read somewhere that it might be beneficial to do a full spin (for beginners) because (1) you get to feel the shifting of the weight (2) develop balance. But thanks for reminding me to listen to my Kru more! LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 19:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but... but... I thought we're supposed to do it like a ballerina? :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 18:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Chris! I hope all is well! Sounds like you're on to something good. Have you heard of [Patreon](https://www.patreon.com)? Wishing you all the best in your future endeavors! 

Sawadee krup

-JPG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 18:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't read it yet but thanks in advance for posting this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 18:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the candidness of your thoughts but please don't get me wrong. Discarding actual criticisms is not what I meant. What kind of student am I to throw away good stuff like that? I am on a journey of bettering myself and I am at a time of my life where I no longer hold any interest in pat-on the-back pleasantries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your comment. It must be the age factor then. The main concern here is that since they were born with the condition, the brain may not learn to see clearly- even if the other eye is okay. Patching can help prevent this but it's so hard to keep a patch on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
