<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4083</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you're putting out quality content at a fast pace, so obviously you made a good decision!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A business has to make money. Otherwise it's a hobby.

Understand 100%!  Wasn't disparaging, just curious, figured that might be why.  Thanks for the reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/TheSmokingTire

Did you cut back on more produced episodes like this since One Takes are a bit easier/quicker?

Also, did you ever buy a 1M?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The BMW 1M: The Last Drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The BMW 1M: The Last Drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The old Car and Driver review and MotorTrend reviews seem pretty good overall.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did not know that!

It's definitely a distinct vehicle.  Tubby is an understatement.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a fan of the Challenger, and had a Hemi Magnum for about 10 years.  250k miles and it kept blowing out the tie rods some how, some way, every 5k miles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I feel if anything Pony car is just a subset of sports car

Pony Car just means American Sports car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  hear why you disagree with the definition I've used.

Pony Car is an American thing.  If the Mustang was put out by Alfa or Porsche or whoever back in the 60s it would be called a sports car then and still today.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Town and Country

According to this subreddit, this is faster than the BRZ/86, so I dunno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need some of what R T is smoking.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A coupe is a 2/4 seat 2 door car which may also be a sedan, but is generally smaller than a sedan.

Coupe is defined only by it's roof line.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A GT car is a sofa on wheels, it prioritizes comfort, and the Mustang is definitely no 'couch slouch'

Yeah Porsche fans will tell you the 991 is no longer a sports car even though it still performs amazingly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   it looks cool in a very juvenile macho way 

So you're saying it looks like a muscle car?  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're not buying a second vehicle to strictly be one for fun/slopes/hill country, there's no need.  

"This is my car with blue tooth, and this is my car with storage space" makes 0 sense.  Just buy the Prius you're talking about and pocket the cash.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently people agree with you.  The 1M's I've seen for sale on the 'net that are low mileage are still north of 50k!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Literary the only model I can think of is 135i which is an overrater understeering teletubby.


That so?  It looked like a good deal.  The 1M is holding it's price as a ridiculous level.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A year ago we didn't see broken and ignored A pillars, buggy software, etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bold?

The Q60 looks great, but that's the only bold thing about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but I cannot stand grey or silver colors.

It's just an old man's color for me.  Where I'm from, every dude in his 50's owned a silver or grey Mercury or Lincoln or Caddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Thanks Peter.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z3MhS_TzPbA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything that doesn't match the specs of a 356 exactly is not a sports car /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF is The Verge even about anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porsche fans and their grey/silver I'll never understand.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  that every UBI game is a failure

Depends on how you define it.

Sales only?  Complete success.  But sales isn't the barometer anymore, but instead, a long and healthy community buying post release content.

In that regard, Ubi ain't doing so hot.  Division sold a ton and then the community died.  Same for Wildlands.  For Honor has less active players than both.  

They probably are NOT hurting financially.  But given that they're about to be taken over by a corporate overlord their track record of being unable to build games that foster lasting communities is going to be a mark against them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Can we expect a similar value drop like the 996

Probably not.  997 has the better reputation than the 996, but it depends on the model.  997.1S manuals and 997.2 manuals and PDK will probably hold pretty well.  Especially the Turbos.

The NA engines will probably see a big benefit in value due to the swap over to an all turbo/small engine platform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking forward to it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my ultimate takeaway from it.  We had just natto and bonito flakes.  I bet if it was served with a starch and something else to even it out it would be a nice Earthy undertone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Folks who agree to change are generally reluctant to make their views public for fear of downvotes.

A better way of going about it would have been to solicit feedback and prompt people to voice it via an off site anonymous poll.  

Instead you took the advice of a very small minority and framed the issue as one of appeasing them first and not the actual community.

Also, who cares if they get downvoted?  It's part of Reddit and it is of absolutely no consequence.  Mods aren't here to shield people from feeling hurt due to a down vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Murray reviews the Macan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 Mazda MX-5 Miata RF Design REview with Mazda Design Manager Ken Saward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep videos.  No reason to dump them and the community has the tools available to sort out quality ones from bad ones with the down vote button.  If you need to help people ignore a video them give them the option to filter them via CSS.  

A vocal minority who don't like YT videos shouldn't be able to take YT videos away from the rest of the community.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just something stuck in the back of my head when I went cross shopping a year or so ago.  Some folks in this sub were talking about problems that pre updated (the gen with the new headlights you see now) 335s were troublesome.

Thanks!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Uniqlo Airism

Googlin now!  TY!  

ed

Seamless is sold out. :(   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aka "drama free" and "more guy friends than girlfriends".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vineyard Vines has a terrible reputation but a local place has them on sale for 50% off.  Is the quality decent or should I just avoid?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone recommend me a flesh colored undershirt that doesn't have very large seams and, hopefully, a wide U or V neck?

The "Invisible Undershirt" that always pops up when looking for these is the right color and neck size, but the seams on the neck are obvious and visible when I wear the undershirt under thinner fabrics.

Also it's almost 40 bucks and lol at spending 40 bucks for a cotton undershirt.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not an expert, but when I last played PC it was similar to GT.  Very sim focused and had a good choice of cars to choose from.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seeing 7 for under 70k on Porsche's own CPO locator.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GT Sport comes out this year and has the GT3.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2nd Street, east side.  If you want to show tribute, then you can hit them up there or hit up one of their Ramen places in North Austin or Houston.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been a few times and had a good portion of the menu.

Dipping ramen, beef tongue, natto, eel, the sashimi and strawberry red fish which is fucking AWESOME, chicken hearts, the hot pocket, the corn which is also super good..... lots of stuff.  I'm not a tequila drinker at all but that cocktail on the menu is really good.

https://www.reddit.com/r/austinfood/comments/64b5pj/second_trip_to_kemuri_heres_a_few_pics_natto_beef/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not regularly, but I imagine on more than one occasion I have specifically looked for exhaust videos, so I would eventually catch your channel.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MotorTrend did a shoot out between the M6 and an Alpina.


https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TKqHQ_PvlXM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Austin, TX.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moment Porsche, Audi, MB, and Volvo drastically modernized their design language and BMW didn't.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2012/2013.  I should have said end of generation.  And I should have also specified the M3.  Sorry.  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankfully their stinky tofu is stinky due to the cheese and not because it's actually stinky tofu.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like ya'll are getting a ton of good press.  And I'm glad you started taking reservations.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno if they're "half finished".  Alpina works inside the BMW plants with them, and I know that the cars are shipped back and forth to specific Alpina/BMW locations before they're ready. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMG is owned by Mercedes and does sport tuning on Mercedes cars.  

Alpina is not owned by BMW but they work closely together and cars are worked on both Alpina and BMW while on the production line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did.  It's pretty legit.  We usually get a round of the chicken hearts as well.  They had beef tongue pastrami one trip and it was amazing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on.  I'll meet ya for a drink.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Central TX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a couple floating around here.  I saw a B7 at the local dealership about a year ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's with the microphone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the Californians aren't.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you work now?  I dig Ramen Tatsu-ya and what these guys are doing down town.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it's still a BMW.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But the grits and fire roasted veg all take some time to prep during the day

What do you do to keep the roasted veggies from not getting mealy as they sit?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this ride is more in S class territory though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Austin, TX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Left to Right:

Kenny G - Skinny white dude who wrote elevator music

Bootsy Collins - [Bass player for James Brown and Parlianment/Funkadelic](https://youtu.be/3byI94zEjc4?t=15m14s)

Leslie - Cross dressing hippie from Austin, TX who basically OG kept Austin Weird.

James Brown - Godfather of Funk

So you take something like Monk Fish liver.  It's kinda fishy but it's pretty good but otherwise inoffensive. 

Or Crispy Ray Fin which is basically just fried manta ray.  Good, flaky, not funky at all, totally Kenny G.

Then you take something like the Salted Cod Row which is both strange and funky cause it's fishy and salty.  Way up there.  Weird and different like Leslie.

And then you have Natto, which looks like thick slime colored edamame that is covered in bonito (dried fish) flakes and tastes like the scum you could scrape off the bottom of a dumpster.  AKA you nasty for eating this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard about him years ago before moving out here, how he was almost the personification of Austin's weird culture.

Then when I moved here and the next thing I saw was that the same city he personified basically murdered him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Walter White

Who puts pictures of Walter White on their car as a positive representation of their political ideology?  

Also, Walter White applies to the same Humbert Humbert/Cartman situation I posted else where.  Obviously and intentionally disgusting people and only the absolute most stupid people in the world identify with them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  she's definitely intended to be a sympathetic character.

Just a quick Google...

Her name is literally Tanya the Evil and regularly employs torture and murder to enforce her will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The funky menu at my favorite izakaya restaurant [misc] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DO YOU EVEN ANIMU BRO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like this restaurant very much, partially due to their menu. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has lots of exposure to the Mazda folks.  Maybe if we can get him on this sub we can get some word out to them as to why their sales keep falling.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this one of those situations, like South Park, where the creators specifically introduce a character that is supposed to be disgusting and unlikable, but so many people see themselves in the character that they genuinely like it?


Or like how you can out real pedophiles because they unironically like Humbert Humbert and don't realize he's a villain?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motoman doesn't get enough love on this sub!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 BMW Alpina B7 FIRST DRIVE REVIEW  A less perfect   brilliantly bonkers tuner car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 BMW Alpina B7 FIRST DRIVE REVIEW  A less perfect   brilliantly bonkers tuner car? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> G37 fans pissed at the changes they made.

First real Q50/Q60 gen forced some really bad electronic steering with the performance trim.

Doesn't sound good.

Garbage interior.

The price of the Red Sport version puts you firmly in BMW 440 or really close to CPO M3 $$$. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How reliable would an end of life E93 be?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sir, I don't like it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk around, brief talk about the car, and the first minute or two of his feelings.  I'm usually done by the 4 minute mark.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't sat in the new Jag, but I have seen the new Giulia.  "Design" wise, it's fantastic and looks amazing.  But they skimp on materials in places they obviously shouldn't.  But that's FCA for ya.

BMW uses Grade A materials, but the design is very conservative and iterative and dated.  

Maybe this will make sense:  BMW's Interior is to Audi's Exterior.  

Or something like that.  I tried to remember that "antonym game" I played in grade school where you:to the::thing:like this but I don't remember the "rules".  Know what I'm talking about?  

Anyway, that's my philosophy on car interiors.  They're like grade school word games.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not "bad", and my Saab comment is a bit tongue in cheek, but like Saab versus the competition back in its day and BMW now, I don't think they hold a candle, **especially** since Audi and MB have updated their design language significantly.  Audi, Volvo, Mercedes, and Porsche have all drastically updated their interiors.  The new 5 series interior is just a refresh of the existing one.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Flying spaghetti monster" but as a political doctrine.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me of BMW.  So called "luxury" interior but honestly it doesn't hold a candle to the competition.  

A buddy of mine had a late 2000s 9-3 convertible.  Probably the best looking car they had, probably the best interior they ever made, and even though it got rid of those super ugly air vents, it still wasn't great.

Seats were comfy though.

And the ignition was on the center console for whatever fucking reason.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Complete waste of time. Horrible company.


Not sure who you're responding to.  No one in this thread made either of those comments.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah doing one thing cool 35 years ago is doing a whole hell of a lot for them now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice he doesn't actually own one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Saab

Always just the weirdest company.  Luxury car but all of them were ugly and never particularly luxurious on the interior to me.  Sporty cars but all of them underpowered and FWD.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst thing about Pontiac is how they specifically wanted it to die in spite of the potential for it to live on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  FCA screws up neither.

That's what I'm hopin FCA can see.  Someone somewhere made the right decision to not gimp the Giulia by putting it on the Chrysler 200 platform.  Somewhere, someone at FCA has to see how Maserati is fucking up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think MotorTrend said it was because the third pedal was cutting off people's feet in crash tests.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  /u/Doug-Demuro 

Do you think the current success of Alfa Romeo will bolster Maserati or kill it?


ed

Also if you can get your hands on the Levante I'd love to know what you think.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Grand Turismo.

And the GranCabriolet.  Both overpriced and probably have the same bad interior, but still.  I'd like to see *something* on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't that Lincoln pickup pretty good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAVAGE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porsche is beating them in luxury as well.  Internal styling for BMW is ancient by now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was it?  Something like 25k profit on each car now?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had money for the GTS but didn't get an allotment.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  hat being said, after they're done with EU4, I won't be buying EU5. What are they going to do, make the map prettier?

EU4 is, for all intents and purposes, EU5 at this point.  I imagine this will be a DLC thing for quite some time, at least until they need to overhaul some deep seated fuzzy math behind the game engine or something.  It eventually will need to not run like garbage.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  there's nothing about a turbo engine that would otherwise cause a reduction in emissions?

Not the turbos but the smaller engine.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I've seen a 50/50 split on opinions.

"Yeah the new ones are faster and you get that speed more immediately" is always contrasted with "yah but that sound!"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just glanced at the ugly rear lights and seemingly shapeless body (I'm partially red/green colorblind) and immediately went "996!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BOTW panoramic landscape  r/zelda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna xpost this to /r/zelfies.  :)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  Looks so good!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yes, I recall your username!

Are these really fetching 100k+ or are people just really optimistic?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you trade in to get this?  Or did you trade it in?  

2016 Spyders just absolutely shot up in value.  If you traded it in, I wouldn't blame you.  It's wild.  

I'd love to have one though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More pics!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're fine.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you can game the CAFE score in test environments.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
