<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Chairman Descends Into McCarthyism in Net Neutrality Debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Chairman Descends Into McCarthyism in Net Neutrality Debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So if you support network neutrality you are a red communist in the eyes of FCC Chairman Ajit Pai, who was former regulatory legal council for Verizon before taking the position in regulation capture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So if you support network neutrality you are a red communist in the eyes of FCC Chairman Ajit Pai, who was former regulatory legal council for Verizon before taking the position in regulation capture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup my moobs have been on the internets. We were out at a Maryland area hackerspace and had been drinking beer and liquor from noon to 7 when that photo was taken. We also had a hell of a foodie cook out / pot luck as well. Also a video of a fire tornado the hacker space made made several local news clips and the discovery channel as well. It was hella fun for all. We had lock picking tutorials, a 12 foot wide 3 foot deep inflatable pool as well

The stalker guys though who harassed my friends afterwards were what made it a sad thing though. The picture wasnt supposed to be posted but one punk did. I banned him since he kept posting it all over the place then he got a gaggle of his college friends from RIT to move a movement to have me removed so i was and i quit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes because portland wants the man who gave you the Baltimore Maryland International Reddit Meatup planning the event. My days of running community organization events for reddit are long done, unless reddit paid me that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spicer blames Obama for Flynns security clearance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So reddit meetup day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any plans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just popped in there whenever I read or hear the phrase ["You are not alone"](https://youtu.be/D2jSiY-Vo8g)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how this would work on a forward drive car, most chases happen with cars that are forward drive and not rear wheel drive like trucks typically are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not Kosher, but who cares .... life finds a way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, I don't know, you could just edit what things are allowed to be notifications in the app settings like rational educated digital device users do? I know that is asking a lot. I'll just accept my downvotes for pointing out simple end user responsibility, you know, simple logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they said the market would be self regulating!!!!!!!! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in this anarcho capitalist future child porn becomes the universal currency as well as bottle caps. No thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I interned for an agency that will remain nameless when I was in high school back in the early 2000s .... yeah totally "unnecessary". It's not like Edward snowden didn't leak out this information either - 

https://www.wired.com/2014/03/webcams-mics/

Oh also you never know what could get installed with what 0-days if someone really really wanted to target you with any semi-basic script kiddy level of netsec skills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The piece of black electrical tape I have is easier and cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um are these migratory birds i would assume. Ducks that fly south for winter. So maybe it was the summer locations to blame and not the winter ones? The lifecycle of the fish they might consume in the great salt lake might have ended the methylmercury absorption cycle if the source was ended what ever dumping occurred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you click links boy? I'm sorry I guess you can't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> based on the [selection of subreddits you group think on as mod.](http://i.imgur.com/mVHrWv5.jpg) 

Frak you!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong! More like negan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 08:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frak you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude is most likely at most 50 to late 40s. Meaning he was the age that skateboarding was at it's height of popularity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats thicker than a bowl of oatmeal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go Go Four Sword Rangers!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But wait. I thought the person on the Cover for Battlefront 2 is a woman, portrayed by Janina Zione Gavankar, one of the actresses from True Blood and now currently on Sleepy Hallow.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But wait. I thought the person on the Cover for Battlefront 2 is a woman, portrayed by Janina Zione Gavankar, one of the actresses from True Blood and now currently on Sleepy Hallow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know people who work in that office. They do a major crap ton of work for helping women either start their own companies from crafts / goods / agriculture they produce, help find micro-loan support for creating community endowments, as well as help with providing teaching and education on how women can be independent or to get husbands to let their daughters go to school even. They do an amazing amount of work in Africa and India. Kiva project actually was one of the joint projects with an NGO they helped developed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live on the train though ... and I have a french pastry shop, Thai food, tap house, Little Big Burger, and Coffee shop right on my first floor and it's cheaper than living downtown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An engineer is a applied science scientist. You have to know the science as well as how to apply it. You are doing experiments and testing just as much in the field of applied sciences which is engineering as in theoretical science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow there old man. Get the fuck over yourself. Homelessness is particularly caused by the shit poor quality of mental health care access. You refer to people as vermin, there is a special place in a lonely hell for your ass, bloody asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude I just want to be able to lay down and sleep from time to time. Being 6 foot 5, and having nearly 3 foot wide shoulders I just want to be able to go like "FUCK IT! Time to just sleep!" And if I end up homeless at least i have a van to sleep in!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also a I am the 1% joke since you know .... 99% of the world has speeds slower than 10mbps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they focused on apartment buildings and condos where they could get max penetration. They would actually bury lines they said but you would have to pay an arm and a leg i bet. But the property value of your house would be much higher given the tech community aspect of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orenco Platform District (Vector apartments, Rowlock, Hub 9) as well as 206 apartments on Cornell and 206 had it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus -- not CenturyLink or Frontier either! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Like a power glove](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SW8DgKm-7vs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um ... what data cap? I'm sorry you have one, but unlike you I have a local owned and operated ISP that doesn't have data caps.


so to repeat, I don't have a data cap! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone barely graduated middle school with that reading level i see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> speed megabit, data megabyte. We typically messure in megabit because thats 1 or 0. On off. light on light off, 5 volts / no volts. But we can also measure speed in megabytes which means if it it was 80 MB (megabyte) its actually 80 time 8 bits to make it 640 Megabits per second for the max steam download for games i have seen.

Video file video quality though is measured in megabits per second and a 4k HDR netflix video stream is 25 megabits per second but with their new video encoder tech they are able to make H.265 HVEC video in 4k HDR go as low as 5mbps when there is no action on the screen. 

To put that into context a UHD Bluray uses 28 to 50 mbps for H.265 video 

also my torrents typically only go 1.2 to 5 megabits per second but i throttle though typically to have it only go max 1mbps upload and 2mbps download with 6 downloads at a time and 30 uploads at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm able to have my fiancee watch Netflix 4k HDR show, download and upload torrents from my file server at the same time, and download games from Steam at 50 to 80 MegaBYTES per second. Steam actually maxes out at 80 MB as the servers can't actually send any faster it seems.

But it still leaves with with plenty of speed i have seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Canadian and I'm insulted on your behalf.     

Even though Trudeau is supporting tar sands oil I wish I was Canadian. I'm sorry though, I can't stand the cold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are aware this was the pcmasterrace when this was on the market? Apple Basic was significantly more powerful and had more graphics features and commands than Microsoft basic which was used on other computers. MS-DOS was only available on IBM machines wasn't even a thing per say for general home PC users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hate me with all your passion. I am the Portland area internet 1% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you luck into an apartment or condo with them I highly reccomend Fibersphere

I pay $60 a month for Gigabit internet

https://secure.fibersphere.net/coverage_map.php

Photo for proof of [internet speed](http://imgur.com/gallery/6xzPb).

I also verified with them, they are an 8 person team and don't keep logs. Also you are allowed to run any servers you want and they give you a static IP address too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punching Nazis in 1930 USA is what kept the party from growing in the United States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so you mean 4chan /pol/, r/The_doland, stormfront, and the alt-right then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take it you have never been to the "Third world" have you? Also It's not called the third world you dumb ass. It's called the "Developing World".

Third World / Second World / First World comes from the Cold War era as a way to define countries that remained non-aligned with either NATO (first world), the Communist Bloc (second world), or unaffiliated (third world).

Read a bloody history book about modern geo-political world development for bloody pete sakes you bloody tit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so we are going to need more pictures now just so you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is he sees these people as subhuman and ruining his property value. He called for a purge and called them vermin and trash in a post that the mods removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So .... this doesn't make you the least bit sad? Like I mean for the people who have to live like this? I mean are you just one of those uppity property value pearl clutchers? Because it seems your obsession with this and your post history shows you are kind of dick about poor people and people who have mental health problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah not so much in my opinion. It plays humor to a serious issue about racial inequality and made me hella cringe. The rest of the them were perfect but that was some serious yeeesh really face palm action for me for the Blackhole one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Progressive Protests always have much funnier and well thought out protest signs than Conservative ones. Also much more originality too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you are getting it, that was the Heritage Foundation / GOP plan all along! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if we tax corporations the amount they should actually be taxed they might leave the state!!!!! Oh no that entrenched infrastructure of major tech companies will not have anyone working on it anymore!!! /s/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How bloody original  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just shivered for 5 seconds out of disgust. This looks like something that would be left over from a monster spider liquefying the body of a victim wrapped up in webs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No SUV and Vans are entirely different base frames and are very different undercarriage body structure.

Now some SUVs have used Van / truck frames when they first came out but since then to deal with tip over and other issues the frames have dramatically changed.

The reason I want a mini van is I want to be able to take out the seats and have that flat easy to use storage space if I need it. Like an Astro Van.

Vans have flat floors remember, not a body frame that supports the seats up higher and then have dips for the feet. Van Seats are designed to have the raiser built into it so its about 8 inches to 10 inches off the ground with storage underneath if it is a bench or rotation if it is a single seat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight on my french brother! Resist the Jingoist Xenophobic Fascists! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't nihilism you tit. Simulacra and Simulation by Jean Baudrillard was empty and hallowed out when it was shown in the movie. The movie is in essence a trans-humanism / Existentialist hero journey. Neo is faced with the fact the One is just another means of control. But he says "fuck that there has to be a way to change it" He chooses to persist because he "chooses to" and does so for altruistic intentions. That is the very cornerstone of Existentialism. You CHOOSE to go on and find meaning in your life, its a glass half full look at life. 

SMITH, the villain of the story is the nihilist, he wants to be free and freedom to him means death. He hates his life so much that he will destroy everyone and everything around him to bring it all crashing down. He will swallow everyone up becoming the Superman in the ultimate climax for the purpose of destruction and  to bring about the black void of oblivion. No matter what the glass is always half empty for him because he is forced to be alive.

Ultimately through destruction and Neo under the right circumstances allows Smith to think he has given up. Smith thinks he won but Neo did the ultimate Autherian / Messianic sacrifice to fulfill a deal with the machines to save the machines and in turn save the humans, not just in the idea of human genetics or as a concept of the species living on but the for the right for human's to have to self determination of their future and have the machine system of controls removed. 

Again any Nihilistic texts referenced in the movie are shown as hollow and the villains being all Nihilists and hedonists are shown to be hallow and hate their own lives so much they live off the emotions and lives of others. Cipher was a nihilist who wanted opulence and to forget again. The Merovingian and his hoards of Vampires, Werewolves, and Ghosts. Also the very fact the Merovingian is displayed as a typical 1% rich asshole is very telling while the heroes are all hackers who build things from parts and trash and are using old outdated equipment to get by.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the paraphrased words of so many damn stupid Climate change deniers 

"TLDR, fuck off, jesus loves coal, hummers, and .45s and stop trying to oppress my minority complex in the nations majority religion of Christianity!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During the rise of cats memes you saw a rise of liberal progressive policy. Now with the rise of dog memes you see the rise of neo-feudalism / neo-fascism / and anarcho capitalist memes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sikhs are hella good bros. Anyone that ever tries to put down the Singhs will have to face Irish, German, Polish, English ex-catholic secular humanist fists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Electric Minivan ... how much longer for the USA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to lie. There are two cars i want to have sold in the USA. One is a Volvo like wagon and the other is a Honda Odyssey like van that are both all electric and have 200+ mile range per charge. Any word on any electric vans or station wagons?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fingers Hella crossed for Macron! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BNP are the Nazi party without calling itself the nazi party  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to the hobby lobby bullshit scalia decision  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UKIP is an ultra right wing, ultra jingoistic, ultra xenophobic, nationalistic party which is basically an openly racist party. Basically American Republicans if British and had no problems being openly racist, like if if they were from Florida.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ukip, party of the totally sane and not at all crazy people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Southern Strategy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Southern_strategy)   the rise of the [moral majority / Christian Right](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christian_right#History) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Son, 5k barely covers the shoes, the watch can go for as much as a 1.2 million dollars. 

The suit can go between 10k to 25k for a major label custom tailored suit.

Unless you go to Singapore or Hong Kong where you can get a custom 5 piece tailored suit where they come to your hotel room for only $500 with the same materials used by high end luxury brands and have it ready in a day to two days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K dad, i really learned my lesson! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Empty gestures would be hollow gesture. The point the people who use "Virtue Signaling" created it as the counter to "Dog Whistle".

The only people who use Virtue Signaling are ones who oppose typically things like diversity, affirmative action, gender identity issues, gender equality, racial equality, and issues of class / income inequality.

"Dog Whistle" means coded political language which always has racist or bigot undertones to policies.

Like if i said seeing movie about black female engineers makes me cry with joy because of the fact being a engineer it makes me happy to see zeitgeist popular culture have realistic depictions of not just female engineers, but of black american engineers, mathematicians, and computer scientists i get said oh that's just liberal Virtue Signaling. I fucking hate that shit because it just makes it seem like nothing you do is of value unless the the alt-right racist brigade supports its. 

And the only people who say things are empty are the ones who oppose it or are so gods damn bitter and cynical that the world is always shit and can never get any better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely hate the fucking phase "virtue signaling". The only people i ever know who use it are people on the alt-reich side to put down people on progressive side.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HDCP 2.2 encryption / DRM tech which is part of the HDMI 2.0 spec and needed for 4k video from UHD bluray, Netflix UHD 4k HDR, Amazon UHD 4k HDR, and VUDU UHD 4k HDR. If you don't have your entire device chain HDMI 2.0 with HDCP 2.2 4k video just wont show up as an option for the devices. Your best best to bypass this is HDFury

https://www.hdfury.com/shop/splitters/integral-4k60-444-600mhz/

but you can also use a 4k splitter with HDCP 2.2 and HDMI 2.0

http://amzn.to/2p9Tf2V

http://amzn.to/2ozxk21 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah the cause is calling out stupid and backwards people. If it hurts your feelings snowflake go find a safe space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats one shitty ass playlist from one shitty ass political party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, a truck that has ANTI-Republican posts .... i think that is a first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reason why is it can't be because of his old sperm that Barron trump has autism. It is the vaccines that did it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the Alpine Ridge chip which intel used until Skylake. Skylake included a Thunderbolt 1/2/3 controller so they could take the Apline Ridge chip off the SouthBridge in have it CPU core controlled instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TfadJj4d5K4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this mock the Gadsden flag or just some alt-right meme? Because If this was actual armed forces isn't flying this flag a breach of military codes?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PLANT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus/AntiChrist 2020!

"Bring the world together, in fear and penitence"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/p86IzjXPc_0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a man who can make such stunning documentaries about the very nature of the human soul and the beautiful  pointlessness of man's eternal struggle while seeking existential philosophy that transcends the follies of man just so happens to like watching WWE wrestling and shows about absurdity in life surmised down to simple fart joke humor.  

/* Read this in Werner Herzog voice */ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the pin is not stored on the card with chip pin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh i just smell young republican all over this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dictators are dictators, it doesn't matter what fucking political ideology they say they support. Remove all dictators and support democracy. Fuck sake this is some serious, "I just read Atlas Shrugged" bullshit tween shit posting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just do fucking CHIP PIN for fuck sake! 6 digit pin encrypted the entire way through the transaction so it never goes to the register, just the credit processor servers, just like bloody Europe does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about ism !!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what about ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of alt righters seem to like to post these </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There there now, lets go look at the pretty lights at the mormon temple in salt lake while talking about the horrors of LDS male youth pushed out so old me can have the women and also the horror stories of murders and massacres by LDS on travlers heading west. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically you are right, but that still makes you an asshole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were born in space jesus land!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE JOB CREATORS WILL BUY EVERYTHING!!!!!!!! trickle down economics will save us YET AGAIN!!!! /s/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Universal Basic Income. Look it up. It will be the future. A society of foodstamp fed scholars, youtubers, and fat obese people everywhere eating aggro-petro-pharma-chemical produced inedible corn highly processed byproduct.

personally I would want to have a star trek the next generation future but I know about 30% of the United States would be hopeless get rich quick types either buying into pyramid schemes or not going to public university. But i bet you if we had Universal Basic Income and legalized recreational Cannabis, crime rates would drop like a rock! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are saying that after the move from agrarian, to early industrial, to automated industrial, its almost like some sort of collectivist next step is supposed to take place? /s/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metropolis is a perfect analogy for this. It gets the perfect mix of Das Kapital from Marx, Futurism, and Post industrial revolution workers being made redundant by robots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um so ... if you are doing a job that a normal developer does you should get paid. It's against the law not to pay you. 

The following **six standards must ALL be met in order to establish that an intern qualifies to work unpaid**: 

1. The internship, even though it includes actual operation of the facilities of the employer, is similar training which would be given in an educational environment; 

2. The internship experience is for the benefit of the intern; 

3. The intern does not displace regular employees, but works under close supervision of existing staff; 

4. The employer that provides the training derives no immediate advantage from the activities of the intern; and on occasion its operations may actually be impeded; 

5. The intern is not necessarily entitled to a job at the conclusion of the internship; and 

6. The employer and the intern understand that the intern is not entitled to wages for the time spent in the internship. 


[Source]

- https://www.dol.gov/whd/regs/compliance/whdfs71.pdf

- https://www.propublica.org/article/when-interns-should-be-paid-explained

- https://www.thepennyhoarder.com/jobs-making-money/side-gigs/are-unpaid-internships-illegal/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senior Developer jobs Paradox. Where are the entry level jobs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I find this hilarious but where the heck do you find entry level jobs? Everything is Senior or Lead and I'm someone who is still working their way though Engineering school. I just want a entry level junior job but there is nothing just internships and Senior positions.

Is there special code words I should look for for junior level developer jobs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a Brocoder asshole who talks about the wonders of Ayn Rand's collective works particularly Atlas Shrugged? Do you do Yager bombs for a average drink at night? Are women only meant to be objects of sexual pleasure and any woman who is working is only doing so to find a man? THEN YOU ARE PERFECT FOR A JOB AT UBER!!!!!

Seriously though both are going to make you a slave for low pay. Go with Blizzard because you can get some free gamer shit and go to E3 or other game dev conf as industry or get them to pay for you. 

Uber I have had too many male and female friends come out of working for them in Dev / Dev Ops feeling dirtier. Their actual words about what it's like to work for UBER if you are not part of the Bro-Coder world.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPACE GOD!!!!!!!! TO THE PLANET KOBOL WITH YOUR 12 SPACE GHOST WIVES!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never wanted anything more in my life now than a Studio Ghibli Legend of Zelda Movie now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no Dixiecrats merged with Republican GOP with the move by the GOP called the [southern strategy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Southern_strategy) over to the republicans. With the splintering of the Dixiecrats this is where the modern Democratic party that was anti-KKK and pro civil rights came from. Basically all the racist bigots jumped ship and went to the republicans. You then had the start of the merger of Republican Politics post Goldwater who was very much against religious merger in politics and after that you had the rise of William F Buckley modern conservatism which merged christian protestant evangelicalism from Billy Graham but more so Jerry Falwell who created the moral majority, which evolved then into the christian right with the GOP and Ronald Reagan  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and walmart has shown it lowers productivity and actually made them lose money when they did that. Also the mandatory vacation wasn't the reason it was mandatory healthcare over 32 hours per week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Another!!!](http://i.imgur.com/Jun1onB.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since when the fuck was trust fund donnie ever sympathetic to student debtors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> National Review isn't alt-right they are neoconservative and the pinnacle of post 1960s conservatism with William F. Buckley Jr. as the beginning of Religion / Conservative Politics merger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so the alt-right has turned on him?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a tried and true Dixiecrat. A whore to special interests, likes his whites only country clubs, and thinks the black and minorities should be under his "heel of protection" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Private owned franchise shops and not retail ones are owned by ham radio geeks. They are treasure trove for anyone who needs surface mounted parts or tools for electronics out of the blue. But even they have been replaced by lady ada or element14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also tend to investigate local news stories as well not international unless the slant is it wraps up with Boston as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, Trump! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seize the means of production! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Education Secretary DeVos Withdraws Protections For Student Loan Borrowers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Education Secretary DeVos Withdraws Protections For Student Loan Borrowers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did i say it was? I was just saying this is what i think the reasoning is. They would rather you not use it at all and let it fully charge then have a mouse that isn't not always fully charged and get complaints over it not working at all because you keep not charging it all the way before you use it. 

Apple is fucked up in the last 5 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.wnyc.org/story/taxonomy-trump-tweets/

http://i.imgur.com/7rbUXJ0.png

http://i.imgur.com/9tlKp6H.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the reasoning for this is so that you can't use the mouse till it's full charged and apple doesn't want any wires so they would rather you not use it at all than have a mouse with a wire on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are an idiot little edge lord who only enjoys nihilism and the zero sum game of failing at life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone that promotes the idea of white pride and genetic superiority typically has none of which they should be prideful about or the genetics to create anything superior to even jack shit stacks in an outhouse.

example Steven Bannon, AKA the walking liver spot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are we talking nationalism or national pride because I feel the ball is being moved and the goal posts are also being moved from your argument. 

You can have community pride. I mean I'm from maryland so any time they are in then news for something good like banning fracking i'm proud. But nationalism is a whole other thing. Nationalism is unflinching. National Pride is something that means you can also feel national shame. Nationalism means you never see any shades of black to the star spangle awesome of your special choosen nation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://vid.me/qBMO

Sorry we are just not that cool anymore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And someone else would have enventually invented then. You antidotal example can easily be just that antidotal. Lightbulb was 10 years before edison. Edison just made a way so the bulb had to be replaced more often for making money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it came down to it i would rsther be i a fox hole with an anti fascist than a white nationalist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The quest for creation is beyond one of economic gain. But in seriousness read "the master switch" by tim wu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who voted to sell off internet privacy? I disnt see a single Democrat on that list. The issue as a whole though is democrats work as not one unified party but as a coalition which on a whole are fractured and have a mix of people. Some are liberal in the economic vein where helping Buissness helps people. But most are put your money where your mouth is and never takes private company's word as honest unless part of the deal brings something fo constituents. You can see it all the time and the false equivalency you believe in is the entire game plan of the republican party for the last 30 years. Ever since newt Gingrich wqs speaker of the house the skrink the government at all cost shut down the government if we dont get our way slash and burn and salt the earth make everyone hate all politicians and do as little work as possible has been game plan of the GOP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> National pride is great at all at the olympics but in truth national pride is something everyone should keep a distance from. I feel not seeing your self as a citizen of the entire world and thus the problems of one part where peoplle are abused and taken advantage of is also your problem. Like we blame mexico or china for pur problems when its really automation and private international companies who have. O reason to exist but to produce more money, no matter at the ethical or sociological cost. 


Companies are by the definition roving sociopaths looking to take advantage of some legal loop hole or ability to manipulate something or someones for a profit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For flag waving yahoos only. Im a mutt of conflicting cultures and nationalities and that is just "white" European western nations part </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a person who thinks national identity is a tool of oppression. It creates a false us vs them dynamic by people who live wherever they want. They only live in a country because it has some sort of stability, laws favor them, they love playing with the chess peices like they own them, or they are dumb and wont be rich for long.

When it comes down to it im a middle class citizen who demands universal education for everyone. Universal basic income for every person of legal working age. With it kept in the trust till 18th birthday for youth. And im for universal access to information/ internet. I am against trademarks, patents, and even copyright unless directly owned and used by its creator for a peirod of 10 years after publication with a court having to allow extensionss for only copyright until 20 years after creation. 

Even then fair use should be something the copyright owner has to fight to prove false. All copyright and trademark cases should be paid through a fund of lawyers that is established by taking a percentage of the profits from copyrighted work

Anyway thats another topic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was solved hundred years ago. Its called a water battery. Pump up the hill and then run it down at night to power turbines. Europe does this all over the place. If you dont have hills you use flywheels to store energy and if you dont want to so that use molton salt that is powrring a water boiler powered turbines when the heliostats are not getting sun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are staff lawyers. They are not retainer. If they were on retainer you damn well know they are getting paid first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont read "the master switch" by tim wu then because you are gonna pull your hair out from the level of progression held back by private corporations for greed and short term gains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Son you think countries matter? That very concept of nationalism is a tool of control by the rich and multinational corporations. They are not globalists but international abusers of the poor and powerless who like the united sates for the last 150 years bent over backwards to please them. The fact is private companies have too much power and run politics for the sale of making quarterly profit numbers. A presidential election like trump was cheap to keep they richest rich and the rabel fighting amongst themselves. Typically democrats will try to make something comeout of the tree shake to help the working class. Republicans shake the tree and direct what falls out to their friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> foreign Asian / middle eastern market and nondenominational representation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fascism is a ultra right wing jingoistic political ideology that blames the problems of the state of mythical foreigners as scapegoats while shrinking the services and size of the government but then giving control of government services over to tightly controlled private companies with owners being friends or members of the ruling party.

The origin and symbol of Fascism comes from the usage of a Fascis ( or a bundle of sticks) that was uses to beat people by the Fasci, or special roman soldiers, in modern era roman empire, to get them out of the way of ruling senatorial class as they made their way through the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i tend to see knives and guns at these kind of protests only be pulled by pro trump pro "white" nationalists though. 

https://twitter.com/MackShelle/status/853500603523227648/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> feels good man. Nazi Killing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoking pot, and drinking cheap Chianti from the bottle? Let me guess they voted Trump and complain about millennials not working while using social security and medicare but hate or complained about paying taxes their entire life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> going strong until ..... *cough* I might have voted for him but i knew it was better than Hilary *cough* LOL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nahhh my dear with a twisted sick thought like yours they either will die fast or learn to hate you with a fiery passion. And I'm like so glad you assumed my "whiteness" It hilarious that all this seems to be is a way for you to "not work" and have someone pay for you to bitch on the internet all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tut tut ..... Mormon ... Most Christians don't consider them christian since you know space jesus and 12 space wives and space planet kobal and black people who are actually jews punished by god because they killed jesus and well caffeine and such.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kolob </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Son, JFK was a black man being elected to office. That is how big a deal of him being Irish as well as catholic was you dumb fuck. Leave the playground and go back and read a book other than "my big comfy struggle" from your pencil mustached wank bank. You are just looking stupid with your edge lord "Social Nationalism" son. You look like your are angry at your Jewish dad because he won't let you eat mastaballs in bed on the Sabbath.

Shit son you must be the middle school flunk out if you have no context of history of what it was being a catholic in the 50s / 40s, 30s, 20s, and even post civil war reconstruction. Son you are like a bag of rocks that go hit by a larger bag of rocks. The amount of sand that comes out when you turn your head to the side must fill up a child's sand box, or at least 3 of your 5 cats litter boxes. 

Did you like know you were this stupid or did you like assume it you were smart this entire time because it seems you don't know about the DunningKruger effect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Travis County custody case, jury will search for real Alex Jones as Alex Jones's lawyers tell court not to take anything he says on his show seriously, because he's a "performance artist." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
