<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2991</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be honest here. Aside from how beautiful she clearly is, it's her wit and humour. She is dark and scathing and can take a joke. Finding someone like that has been like finding a unicorn.

We can joke and be very dark with one another one minute, and then talk about waffles the next. It's awesome.

Also she tells me what she wants for dinner when I ask her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except you won't know until you show up to hospital that there is a delay of a week, then after the week you find out the op has been cancelled. Then there's a surgeon strike. Then the price of surgery goes up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming from a government whom is setting the NHS up to fail so they can justify privatising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE 24 HOUR BAGEL PLACE DOES THE BEST BAGELS.

I'd recognise it anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of the time it's simply who shouts the loudest.

The far right (and far left) often make the most noise so that's reported, regardless of whether it's true or not. Just what sells papers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HOMEMADE] Skillet triple chocolate cookie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 23:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super easy:

500g self raising flour,
500ml beer,
50g sugar,
Teaspoon garlic powder,
Half teaspoon dried chilli's.

Mix in bowl till sticky and no flour left, then oven 180 for 45 mins.

No kneading, no hassle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] Chilli and Garlic Beer Bread. Crunchy outside and fluffy inside. "For Valentine's" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These look perfect, too perfect... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an oil version of fondue, and the Asian versions usually have a flavoured oil on top of the water (like chilli oil) that clings to the food you cook in it.

And cheese is kind of like an oil, so they must all be linked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but instead of cheese, it's a very flavourful broth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 09:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah like Lancashire hotpot etc. I was just as confused when I first learned about it!

Japanese have something similar called Shabu Shabu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pot simmers and people put their food in to it to cook to their liking. (Most things don't take more than a few minutes) and you take it out, dip it in a sauce or eat it on its own.

Very good and social way of eating! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at that girl on the left, I imagine they would still react similarly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah makes sense. Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
