<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7048</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we have some indicator of people from our friendlist that have been inactive for too long? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to assume there are other people too that want to clean up their friendlist but don't have spare time to check each profile and when their last game was played. 
I'm pretty sure there are plenty of inactive buddies here, maybe we could get some indicator of inactive players and having an option of excluding them right away?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... is RE7 Main Theme just a coincidence to this song?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but even belonging to the same franchise, those are two different types of games, with different proposals. While RE4 is more action-oriented, RE7 is all about horror and frailty (at least in the first half, before character growth), so you ARE supposed to be playing with an ordinary guy, and I feel like his lack of combat skills is intentional.
I wouldn't accept seeing Ethan performing combat skills and being like "Heel yea, that fits to the game", because it clearly would not.
Remember that Leon received training to become an agent from the government, so his action set makes sense. 
 
Of course, they could have refined overall defense mechanics in RE7 because it's understandable to complain about being able to almost deny an axe swing by just raising your arms. That is complete bullshit. 

PS: Leon's abilities were completely exploitable in terms of combat system, every enemy would just stop/miss attacks even though they hit, just so you could perform the action. That shit is even more nonsense. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not enough kill 7.7/10.... what?!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that the Molded were pretty good visually and to fight against! The problem really was the excessive amount of them in the game. Maybe if they had another type of enemy at the ship and salt mines it would have been much better of an impression.
You've got a point at the linear level design from Lucas Testing Area. I could see myself going back to those places in search of items, antique coins and Mr.Everywhere though. 
Could you please explain me about your thoughts on the combat system? How could it be better? It runs smooth as hell for me.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the first time that I got legit scared and felt an unnerving tension to keep up since Dead Space. I've beaten a good bunch of horror games and I must say that RE7 is currently the winning title for me, it takes the survival-horror genre into its core. 


I've loved every part of it. 
The Mansion had the perfect pace and right amount of backtracking, really taking us to a "RE1" kind of trip. Jack is also arguably the best character in the game.  

I really liked the Old House level design too and Marguerite boss battle was creepy as hell. The tension was well-built for that particular character.

The test field or whatever it's called was a bit linear but it made sense for me. The VHS exploit to get rid of Lucas trap was beautiful. 

The ship was awesome too. It sorta had a different vibe and atmosphere; feeling defenseless again and having to grab all the stuff made the second half really good. 

The mine was a let down, but understandable. Just wish it wasn't that linear and the final boss fight actually needed some mechanics. 

Would give a 8.8/10. Would need to play on Madhouse to be sure though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 03:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...it must be a sign for another game then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Achei que era o nico no Reddit de olho no Re7, pelo visto no mais! hahaha

Uma pergunta, acabou comprando? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also shoot the hanging pendants and immediately spam "X" or "A" to catch them while falling. And yes the clean pendant will be sold for a way higher price by doing so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting mastery 7 on champions should be harder... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best connection: Static or Dynamic IP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many things associated to the router in my house; it gets frustrating when someone uses the internet and my game starts to become laggy. 
I'm current using Dynamic IP, but not sure if it's the best configuration. 
Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't tried him out yet, but his damage is freaking annyoing.
I believe if I buy him he'll be the only AD I'll be playing afterwards, though.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was, in your opinion, the most rewarding Champion to play with at Season 6? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one gave you the most satisfaction and joy to play after a  brief recap of 2016?

You can interpretate rewarding from "easiest to kill enemies" to "most enjoyable skillset". It's entirely up to you what fullfills your enjoyment. 
Just make sure to be explanatory! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 18:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why, but I thought it was Jon holding a rubber sword. 
Don't judge me. 

"What has been seen cannot been unseen"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 02:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No TL;DR for a text like this is an worship for masochism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't think of a better name really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it really work? Because I did a small stone hut and managed to get one inside and he despawned from there. Going to try this one out.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am building something similar! I'm creating Winterhell, it's a really big city at the north, close to the mountains. The main gate and the wall is indentical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
