<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7495</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also committed fraud because campaigns are to get votes but in primary season they're apparently meaningless ie they can pick their candidate any way they darn well please. 

So would soliciting campaign contributions in primary season be tantamount to fraud. They say for votes but individual private citizen votes apparently don't matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't the federal budget or US taxpayer be considered victims of communism/socialism day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought sanctuary cities were supposedly safer because the illegals would feel free to report crime and turn in criminals. Uh huh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet another Nazi era comparison misused/abused. From Gruber no less who said they shouldn't tell the public the truth about Obama Care by calling it a tax. 

No one is in a camp because of a pre-existing condition. Maybe a clinic but not a camp. 

But high risk pools are a result emphasizing method of payment rather than actual care for those with pre existing conditions. Actually anyone who wants or needs health CARE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DNC Lawyers Argue DNC Has Right to Pick Candidates in Back Rooms, in Secret! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Republicans" tend to get the brunt of commentary when it comes to conservative issues as do the Democrats when it comes to liberal or leftist issues.

The problem is with Republicans especially they are not "the" conservative flag bearer they were decades ago. But many posters treat them like that which is why a "Republican" politician or policy will get negative feedback. 

The Republicans "don't get it" as many Democrats "don't get it". If the professional politicians want to remain the establishment they need to start 'getting it'. Living in an echo chamber of positive commentary will do nothing to increase positive policy conservatively speaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Savage: Yale Republicans host BBQ next to liberal hunger strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The current batch of Republicants have to at least start writing the laws to so funding can be pulled in the future if these programs and projects are not in line with national policy. If nothing else they have to learn how to chip away at these laws working towards and eventual phase out. Incremental reductions every time a budget comes up.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many in the US aren't thrilled either but until Trump's little girl and hubby actually fork another country on administration business what's the fuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I see and hear about the ex mommy bells and telcos it's not pretty no matter how you look at it. Greed runs on both sides in the telco union workforce as well as in the executive offices. 

Still feeling the effects of the break up of ma bell over 30 years ago. This is probably one the first generations of telco employees free of the mommy bell legacy employees   management but they had plenty of time to indoctrinate their replacements. The union still have to fight for the legacy employees as the company will fight the union. SOS 33 years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If not terrorism somebody rejected by the police or fire academy or had a spouse have an affair with a fireman/women. Shot multiple times that's anger. Stupid and disheartening no matter the cause.

Speedy recovery to victim and resolution to situation 

Peace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rather than trying to eliminate many of these programs cold turkery for appearances sake phase them out with incremental reductions in funding over the next couple of years.

Elimination of a program is 'you're against people' in liberal speak. Reduction in funding and scale  is streamlining government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exclusive, It Was An Invasion: How Hungary Managed To Erase Illegal Immigration In Just A Few Months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rationing based on the priorities and criteria of the government, not the patients or people. "Free" comes with a price that includes choice, wait times, location etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heads of State(politicians) and congress(professional politicians) are a lot tougher than finance and  construction executives. Helloooo, anyone home? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh goody

At least it's official now. Now about Jared and Ivanka... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, not even a visit to the US Embassy in their own country. Things like a passport or visa don't  work either? Hmmmm...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The classroom setting including the campus is all but perfect for indoctrination. Throw in social media   media it is the perfect recipe for a cupcake nation who will cry, moan and do what ever it takes to get their way. Their ends will justify their means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attention seeking drama queen. It's an insult to the people that actually have been raped. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rather than cave and play the either-or game put a phased in sunset on the ACA. To get it done by the end of his first term I say something like a 25% cut in funding a few years in a row should wake everybody up. One can negotiate with numbers. 

The either-or game has much less room and it will be played out in public as you are with us or against us OR perceptually as healthy or not for healthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flipper-In-Chief: Trump Caves On Obamacare Subsidies To Avoid Government Shutdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they want to pick and chose when to work with the feds or not.

 Just enforce the existing laws and policy first, then see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maryland/Baltimore have some of the toughest gun control laws along with cameras and yet they are losing control of the city. 

Even worse is that they even think or want the feds to solve their problem. How about asking the county sheriff or state police for extra help first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ivanka also wants day care for all. Wonder who is going to pay for that.

http://www.csmonitor.com/USA/Politics/2017/0224/Ivanka-Trump-pushes-500-billion-child-care-subsidy-plan-Who-would-benefit

I'm afraid the time will come will Trump will have to muzzle his daughter from speaking while in the White House. She's planting seeds that will be harder to kill than weeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Undoing or getting this liberal progressive agenda and/or thinking under control will be like getting a junky off  crack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ivanka Trump contradicts her father on Syrian refugees: Admittance to U.S. has to be part of the discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Otherwise known as mob rule

http://www.nationalreview.com/article/447067/ann-coulter-berkeley-speech-canceled-leftist-mob-wins-again

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title should read caved into the demands of extorting radical leftist and ANTIFA. Along with the cupcake college called UC Berkeley.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ann Coulter speech at UC Berkeley canceled after loss of conservative groups' support | Breaking News for College Students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Public transit police in most cities wind up being the B team when it comes to law enforcement and once a suspect leaves their property most don't give a hoot.

Here local neighborhoods have had problems with gangs of kids congregating   hanging out on railroad property at night/ground level which would turn into noise and partying including music, drugs   alcohol. We would call the local police and they say you need to call the transit police first. You call the transit police they say if it's that bad call the regular police ??? It took a fatality from kids horsing around for the railroad to landscape and place fencing in those areas. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More cameras are due to be installed until July. 6 of the 9 cars had  working cameras. I don't think they said either way what train car video they did or did not get.

And yes that bond measure for something additional and new when the existing service isn't what it should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confined space in which a crime took seconds, not minutes coupled with 'this can't be happening' or 'not me' syndrome.

 I can see most not being able to start taking cell phone pics. If it had lasted maybe 10-15 seconds longer yeh cell phone vidoes and weapons might have started to come into play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 phones, 2 bags in about 30 seconds if that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saturation along with things like local sports talk radio   internet make consistent viewing unnecessary. Gamblers are driving game broadcasts   coverage but other than that demographic do enough people really care at this point in the day and age of scandals and millionaire athletes. Actually the scandals but who cares what the millionaires do on the field.

Sad for those let go but it has been coming for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are already some hinting that the loss of some deductions   manipulations might not be a good thing-because they have become addicted like the accounting   legal industry. 

The problem now will be the states and cities will tax more aggressively. Local control is good but local control is more power and absolute power corrupts absolutely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe something like 'public endangerment' or  'risking a catastrophe'. They already admitted to letting things go because they considered it "mutual combat" so wouldn't they be criminal negligence if someone gets hurt. 

Right now civil litigation is the only recourse and with the courts in California I don't see it progressing too far.

The information must get out there such his advocacy of groups like BAMN or by any means necessary.  I think this msn link is as close to mainstream media coverage of the mayor in Berkley so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do they know they were juveniles. It could be 18 or 30 year olds with good genes. It's one thing to protect a juvenile once they are arrested   put on trial but until they are caught and age verified they should just be treated like any other criminal/suspect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most drivers tend to overrate the strength/durability of their car and tires. Some studies have shown driving over a pot hole is like putting a car in a 30 mph crash.

Also I saw a picture of low profile sport tires in the story. Low profile tires are crap and highly susceptible to flats. The weight and width of the rims do not help the tire or suspensions either.

Report road damage asap. Small holes become big holes. Road debris often gets dragged on the road acting like sand paper on grass creating small damage that eventually turns into a pothole. 

Also I've found coasting, no acceleration while going over bump or hole helps if I cannot avoid it. Avoiding holes and bumps is just as dangerous because one doesn't want to create an accident. Most drivers are zombie drivers not paying attention or thinking about driving conditions or situations.

DRIVE SAFE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's killing transparency period.

 Climate change is included but there is other data as well. If they felt the website or agency became too bias then unbias it but they shouldn't be throwing out the baby(the data) with the bath water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is transparency really that costly? 

It's one thing not to enforce or endorse certain regulations but to cut the public off from information is another. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL 

Nobody cares if they are offering free righteous indignation showers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French mayor whose town voted Le Pen says he may resign as he doesn't want to work for 'p****s' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the current President's own party does not make the cut off that says the voters do not want the same old stuff. 

He is there to serve the citizens and voters of the town. But he is not there to indulge or perpetuate his own personal political views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo. People wouldn't dump bags full of debris on another's property but seem to think or rationalize "a few" leaves or dirt as being acceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or mulch by raising the wheels/mower deck and covering the discharge chute. 

One of the problems with excessive blowing besides noise and air pollution is that they spread seeds of various kinds. Until we had a major storm several years ago most of the neighborhood did their own lawn. After the storm and a influx of contractors and insurance payouts many started having landscapers do their lawns. I can no longer keep weeds or other foliage   flowers under control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Large pothole on JTB leaves 10 cars with flat tires </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's getting lost is the customer. Setting aside the noise which is an issue ANY debris coming off their property even if it's airborne particulate matter is their responsibility as well. That is a point that should be emphasized more. The customer needs to think about what they are hiring the landscapers to do and how they do it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where ever the city actually owns the curb   grass it's in the city's best interest to keep cars and trucks off that grassy area to prevent damage to the curb itself.

 Every time a car let alone a truck or van drive over the curb to get on or off the grass it risks pushing over or dragging down the curb with the motion and weight of the vehicle. 

Too much weight on the grass/dirt causes depressions which could hold water while it seeps down underneath the curb, street or sidewalk causing further damage undermining what's above.

Repairs and replacements cost the tax payers money and inconvenience with blocked lanes, streets and parking spaces during work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. But scarily it's in addition to the particulate matter and noise. Small engines have few emission controls   devices on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is true but if people see vehicles parked there regardless of owner they'll assume it's ok or no one cares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People ignorantly assume no one cares about that patch of grass or that it's the government's being near/on a street. 

 It's taken me hours of tamping down, reshaping, placing new soil   seed to repair the mini trenches left by vehicles. Especially after some rain. 

Many contractors in particular have to realize that not only is there no curb parking in many locations a homeowner can file a claim for damage which in turn will have the homeowner's insurance company suing the vehicle owner's insurance for the money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just about parking on the grass. Every time a vehicle goes over a curb it can damage it. 

I live on a street where I started doing curb repairs several times a year. I've gone to reflective poles and rocks to stop people from parking on the grass between the sidewalk   curb and getting onto the side walk. It works. And is cheaper than bringing in contractors who to like to replace: not repair curbs and sidewalk slabs, 

 Others have planted bushes, trees, put gardens surround by 1 foot high garden wire/fencing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why arent drivers getting ticketed for parking on LA sidewalks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it went to a posting landscaper trying to justify and rationalize their tool selection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because that loud landscaping tool is producing a lot more than noise pollution. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cleaning up the aided   abetted film of dust, debris, particulate matter etc on a daily basis is work as well.

 If nothing else the blower user needs keep the debris on the property. That means blowing the debris towards the customer, not away or off the customer's property which should be considered littering, illegal dumping or an actual air pollution violation. A  landscaper's work should not become somebody else's problem. The customer needs to be reminded of that as well because it's their debris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The noise is bad enough but the dirt they produce from airborne particulate matter is much worse because you have to clean it up.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up to 5 pounds of particulate matter an hour can be produced by a leaf blower.

https://almanacnews.com/news/2015/08/31/air-district-report-leaf-blowers-present-health-risks

It's about noise AND air pollution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loud and dirty. That debris cloud isn't smoke it's dirt, pollen, insect   rodent feces particles, paint chips, lawn chemicals etc. 

The particulate matter that pollutes the air maybe worse than the noise pollution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caffeine, aspartame and/or artificial ingredients-what's health issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of that wasn't implying or telling Merkel dump the EU and these are deals we'll make with you?

 Merkel's EU responses might have been her way of saying Germany isn't leaving the EU for anyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, just want to be hipsters exploiting their Trump hate and protesting. A mandatory resume entry in many a clic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like walking through or having blown debris   matter blown on/at you. So much for fresh air. 

The makers of allergy medications love leave blowers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or more people would actually do the lawn themselves and neighborhood kids would have work to fill their piggy banks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be the same 6 part report Maxine Waters cited and pushed.

WHO is on the editorial board? WHO is advertising with the Times? WHO owns the LA Times?

Righteous Indignation run amok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just the noise it's the debris and particulate matter they blow around/put into the air.

Also perpetuates laziness, amateur landscaping and blows stuff   seeds all over the place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An CNN and MSNBC are still pushing this adnauseam. Any surprises? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. He even let Milo on his show.

 People forget he started out in the media with "Politically Incorrect" on network tv. He's arrogant and pompous at times but he gets free speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The city and/or police used the rationalization of 'mutual combat' during the protest as a reason for not intervening. I guess that means 'mutual combat' is acceptable.

http://www.berkeleyside.com/2017/04/19/berkeley-police-chief-people-exactly-asked-april-15-demo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could hear the sound of the bar lock hitting the victim. Most of those locks are not light either which means this fascist could've been drugged up like other fascist soldiers in history. 

Will this lead to criminal charges? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least they recycled. It's a green wire tap warrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet they cry about inherited wealth and a low inheritance tax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of tax and spend it's spend and spend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She loses this blame game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The left keeps on jumping on Trump for not taking responsibility for his actions, statements etc yet Clinton seems to have one excuse after another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Berkeley police dept is apparently following orders when it comes to violent protests. Basically rationalizing their inaction with things like 'mutual' combat, resources, shouldn't get involved or insert themselves into the protest.

http://www.berkeleyside.com/2017/04/19/berkeley-police-chief-people-exactly-asked-april-15-demo/

Also must give this agitator Yvette Felarca of BAMN( by any means necessary) a dishonorable mention. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it comes to unruly and/or violent protestors the police are following the chief's orders who is probably following the mayor's orders.

http://www.berkeleyside.com/2017/04/19/berkeley-police-chief-people-exactly-asked-april-15-demo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assange has US citizenship? Unless he directly paid someone to actually steal, not just "get" him the documents/information I don't see anything other than spying charges and as many people that want  to wave the flag just as many will say he did the US a favor. And Trump, the president even talking about wiki-leaks will be used at trial in court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vehicle found with keys in ignition- Could the vehicle have been stolen? And investigators left somewhere to fend for themselves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She works too hard on seed planting that grows into a lot of nothing. Facial expressions, cynicism, satire, inference and innuendo only go so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recycle, that's a leftist tenant. So they recycled the same intelligence report   analysis of the DNC hack 'probably' the Russians. See recycling really does work, sort of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Oklahoma RB Joe Mixon allegedly hit a girl in high school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police At Auburn U Force 'Antifa' To Remove Masks At Anti-Richard Spencer Protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UC Berkeley cancels Ann Coulter appearance, citing safety concerns after violent protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UC Berkeley cancels Ann Coulter appearance, citing safety concerns after violent protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thomas: Mixon will be NFL draft's most controversial pick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Obama didn't give away everything. If it's classified or private like Trump's grandkids I can see it although that should be available under a foia request. 

Guarantee you if the Reps lose in 2020 they'd be demanding those same records they are denying now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considered a security nightmare.

http://www.msn.com/en-gb/news/other/met-police-face-monster-security-operation-as-donald-trump-insists-on-golden-carriage-procession-during-visit/ar-BBzSiz7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seem to remember a time when not complying with "royal" customs as a reminder to any king or queen we are not royal subjects. It was a badge of honor to not do things like bow or dip the flag in front of the queen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump demanding ride in queens gold carriage during Buckingham Palace visit: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Wikileaks is doing what the mainstream media hasn't been doing serious investigations   digging for information </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than the occasional soccer mom type pursuing an issue most in a position to visit the White House probably don't have a low profile life or are conducting other than minor business. If one accepts the invitation or assignment of going to the White House that's on them. This is a public building, not a private residence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did and Obama eventually caved into a general release although there was still plenty a visitor meeting redacted or available by FOIA only. Still much better than this policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually in cases like the 55 mph speed limit instituted during the gas/energy crisis of the late 1970s it was public pressure that got the limit lifted. Public sediment tends to dictate if a community can use things like red light cameras.

 Are those things really a necessary precaution just as the release of visitor logs which were already being redacted under the old policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In classic professional establishment politician world they release the story on a Friday before a holiday weekend in a lame attempt to bury or hide the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The White House is owned by the taxpayers for the public servant called the president to conduct the nation's business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The professional politicians frequently use secrecy for nothing more than job security and status. If it's "secret" and something only "they" should know it makes them seem special, the only ones qualified to see it/do the job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a visitor log for Mar-a-Lago?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they laugh at assisted suicide? health care rationing? the Japanese  who frequently lead the world in suicides? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU: Trump won't release visitor logs because he has 'many things to hide' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'It kept coming back to healthcare' Yup, contrived audience.

That being said any politician needs to learn to debate the public and not just manufacture sound byte answers for the press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative and liberal watchdogs are railing against Trump over concealed White House visitor logs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'grave' national security risks and privacy concerns... Are you fracking kidding me!?!?

Make that double absolute horseshit

Well being the week of 'the' Donald Trump hypocrisy   contradiction I guess we should ignore his comment and accusation of Obama hiding something by not releasing ALL of the logs .

And that's the point there were still redacted names under Obama's policy for various reasons so what is the big fuss worthy of a policy change?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they just recycled the same analysis/assessment. I don't think they independently verified much of the 'evidence'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since it was early in the morning I wonder how long this bus was in service/engine on prior to the fire/explosion. Was this bus even on the road yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds right but what caught my attention they said when it 'burst' into flames it blew out windows. 

And yes heat with buses an issue since they are frequently idling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And part of the transportation infrastructure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wuh Oh

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bus explodes or erupts into flames in NYC near Grand Central station.

And yet barely a mention in/on msm. 

Gunman opens fire on train in Atlanta again barely a mention

http://www.reuters.com/article/us-georgia-shooting-idUSKBN17F2OS

Two high profile public transportation systems suffer incidents on the same day with little or limited information. 

Are terror incidents being covered up or minimized?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bus erupts in flames near Grand Central Station NY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The status quo trying to minimize a threat, competition or eek-the truth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the telcoms and catv companies had put serious effort into their copper plant 20 years ago the cry for fiber would be half as loud. I've seen the same conditions sit for years on end. 

I don't see routine maintenance from many of the utilities. I've reported downed wires   cables in the past and both the power and phone company said unless it's a clear safety hazard they won't raise or replace them until service goes out and they have a customer report to account for their time. Can't sit on problems like that because things will only get worse.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AT T CEO has been one of the ring leaders of telco deregulation for years.

https://www.thenation.com/article/atts-deregulation-campaign/

Comcast used it's weight and lobbying to push for the Comcast NBC universal merger which gave them control over content and not just the service. Comcast wound up hiring an FCC commissioner a month after.

http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2011/05/12/fcc-commissioner-approved-comcast-nbc-merger-headed-nbc.html

Verizon has been abandoning copper landline for years with some hoping for fiber deployment   replacement much sooner. I've heard stories of Verizon   others stalling or even halting copper repairs   replacement in the 1990s. Broadband forced some work but with fiber in the back of everyone's mind including the techs   engineers the number crunchers ensured that copper repairs/replacement and/or fiber deployment never got the attention it deserved   needed.

https://www.wirelessweek.com/news/2015/06/workers-allege-verizon-abandoning-copper-landlines 

Throw in the corporate profit and/or bonus motives telco, catv and/or internet service has not been adequately prioritized for decades, not years. Mega mergers did not and will not help either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an old hit piece from 2014 but it's still an issue because AT T, Comcast and Verizon are basically government sanctioned defacto monopolies who use public and private rights or ways to conduct their business with minimal benefit to the public other than service they over pay for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politicians from Tenn also happened to be some of the big backers of the internet privacy regs repeal bill.

A regulated market to the likes of ATT doesn't mean service quality it means limited competition.

Building out where there was no poles, holes or service? Can't believe if they had basic dail tone they can't run fiber through the existing underground infrastructure or find space on some poles already in ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The capability is there but it's the equipment that has always been a cost issue with the telcos in particular. I heard fiber almost didn't get the layout it has today because many felt the provider should pay for   provide the power ie just  like they provided dial tone. Cost and not having dial tone/service in a power failure similar to a pots line was detraction for some in the early days of fiber   internet.

Coax might be as good or more susceptible to trouble but it takes a lot less equipment. Look at what a fios hook requires compared to the average catv hook up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "hip", perfect description of many who watch it. They try to equate themselves as a connoiseur of sorts simply because they watch her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Com, not con crap. Comcrap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox and Msnbc in particular seemed to get a talking points memo from their favorite politician and run with it for the whole day if not week.

Maddow has to work too hard to set up her stories often prefacing a story for 10-15 minutes hoping the actual point of the story will have the impact of a punchline a joke. 

Step one put evil negative thoughts in audiences head. Let their thoughts/ worst case scenarios run wild with a biased lopsided background/history. Step two, reinforce negative connotation with facial gestures, satire, cynicism and exclamation points featuring innuendo and inference.  Step three, make the claim with more innuendo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not so much about profit from communication   information is how they do it on a daily basis-over, through, on or under private and public property. All those holes and poles are tolerated because the public is supposed to benefit. Same for the towers. High fees and the issues of a business having their plant on private   public property is not necessarily a  benefit the way it used to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer Concrap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too many look at a utility like the baby bells and cable companies as THE provider in their area. People still use/talk about "the phone company". They look at them as THE entity or only way they get service.

Point being they get away with a lot of stuff simply because they are a utility and people including local politicians assume that utility can and should(more scary) do what ever they want.

What utilities do or don't to the local roads for example when they dig up the street for repairs or projects never repaving correctly. Every time  a road is paved/repaved the utilities get a notice to raise their manholes. Many blow off those request and create pot and sink holes. The cable and phone companies seem to feel they run wire in any fashion they want, not just anywhere but anyway they want becoming a truck hook, sign blocker or droop more than somebody's grand mother. They damage sidewalks, lawns, curbs etc with the way they park. Won't even get into to usual creating traffic nightmares. 

Too many blow off negligent   ignorant utility behavior simply because they are utility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sssshhhh

The market still needs to match or have the ideal available jobs per degree ratio. Could educate and degree the entire state. Without a job opening to apply for it becomes meaningless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand the moderators wanting to keep the sub from getting out of control bashing but censorship is another. I just think they're too quick to ban or suspend somebody. That being said if one doesn't tow the company line-whack. There are mods trying to do their jobs and mods that follow Trump and establishment. 

Can 'concern trolling' be clarified a little more?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Distraction 101. Both the media and politicians will exploit this. Free covering fire for their agenda's next move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US and/or China need to ask the South Koreans what they want because they will suffer with North Korean retaliation. And that's if they're helping Trump with regime change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
