<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8607</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether a company does well or not really depends on who is in management. Ownership determines who management works for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't use Latin, you might scare the WASPs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  sharia blue

sounds like one of the markers you huff  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Temper Problem and his baby tantrums </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  

wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gross, Michael. "Inside Donald Trumps One-Stop Parties: Attendees Recall Cocaine and Very Young Models." *The Daily Beast* 24 Oct. 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump would go from room to room, said the photographer, who added that I was there to party myself. It was guys with younger girls, sex, a lot of sex, a lot of cocaine, top-shelf liquor but no smoking. Trump didnt approve of cigarettes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not on welfare! I just use food stamps!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get used to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The buck never stops here!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other way around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nationalize the energy sector please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demonstrators protest against air pollution on the first Earth Day, 1970 [5671x4550] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Save Our Cities; Save Our Soil; Save Our Air; Save Our Water" U.S. Postal Service, 1970 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas Parking Lot, by Thomas Struth [1280x847] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A brief look at the Pyongyang metro system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Starts Taking Steps to Dismantle Obama-Era Financial Regulations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has a centuries old superiority complex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need glasses?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have a black president to fume against this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tax cuts for the rich, budget cuts for the poor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we sure the Trump administration knows Alaska is part of America? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Triggered

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They might have been stereotyped, but under all segregation laws, they were white, also called Caucasian or "caucasoid".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically the Constitution didn't apply to most non-white people until the 1950s, and even then only reluctantly. It wasn't until 1954 that the Supreme Court ruled in *Hernandez v. Texas* that Mexican Americans and all other nationality groups had equal protection under the 14th Amendment. Later that month, the Court ruled segregation violated the 14th Amendment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [filthy](https://c1.staticflickr.com/9/8339/8242827628_5575d10665_b.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well she's clearly aware the photographer is there, but she's being photographed by the Van Nuys Call, a local newspaper that later became the Los Angeles Daily News. Whether the paper ever ran the photo or a story with it is not mentioned. The photo is part of UCLA's collection of Los Angeles Daily News photo negatives, and is featured in [Calisphere's "Migrant Workers and Braceros, 1930s-1964" online exhibit.](https://calisphere.org/exhibitions/57/hispanic-americans-migrant-workers/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans already control 32 of the 38 states necessary to pass a constitutional amendment. Under Article V of the Constitution, 2/3rds of the states (34) can direct Congress to call a constitutional convention for amendments, and most recently the Arizona state legislature (authors of the "papers please" law) passed a resolution telling Congress to do precisely that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The citys tourism agency predicted earlier this year that the number of international visitors would drop by 300,000 in 2017, **the first slump in seven years**  reversing a previous projection that the number would grow by 3%.

Will Trump *ever* stop ruining New York?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *taxpayer subsidies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1598 engraving by Dutchman Theodor de Bry for Bartolom de las Casas' "A Short Account of the Destruction of the Indies", a Spaniard who sailed with Columbus and became one of the first Europeans to condemn colonial atrocities in the New World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's saying "I don't know where Seattle is." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A woman in downtown Los Angeles pickets against illegal raids by the Bureau of Immigration and Naturalization, 1930s [612x768] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about professional porn actors who have an actual union? Or the amateurs on Xtube who monetize their channels? Or the escorts on RentBoy who chose their own clients, until Homeland Security shut them down? Are/were none of them "truly" consenting to sex, simply because they were doing it for money? Something about that strikes me as deeply conservative and paternalistic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a sex worker doesn't turn you into a drug addict, nothing about sex work creates drug addiction. The image of sex work as a profession of last resort for only society's most desperate wretches is just not reflective of the truth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American napalm bombing of a North Korean village in Kangwon province, 1951 [990x689] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [By being so gosh darn ethnically homogenous!](http://empathosnationenterprises.com/empAthosWebGraphics/AfColony.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex work wouldn't be generally coercive if it weren't generally criminalized by law and stigmatized by culture. If you take out the criminal element, most sex workers are self-employed, work on their own terms, choose their own clients, and want the same protections desired by all workers. Under socialism, there will be sex workers as sure as there will be doctors, teachers, musicians, and actors (none of which can be replaced by automation). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be no for-profit private employers in socialism, but there will still be workers and professionals, as well as rewards and compensation (i.e. personal appropriations of common property). Socialism is against private property, not personal property or being personally compensated for collective labor. 

 We by no means intend to abolish this personal appropriation of the products of labour, an appropriation that is made for the maintenance and reproduction of human life, and that leaves no surplus wherewith to command the labour of others. All that we want to do away with is the miserable character of this appropriation, under which the labourer lives merely to increase capital, and is allowed to live only in so far as the interest of the ruling class requires it.

...

 When, therefore, capital is converted into common property, into the property of all members of society, personal property is not thereby transformed into social property. It is only the social character of the property that is changed. It loses its class character.

...

i.e. There will still be specialized labor under socialism - artisans, builders, doctors, teachers, sex workers, engineers, etc. They just won't be exploited for the purpose of private capital and its accumulation. 

But the real problem is there is *always* an undercurrent to this question, every time it's asked, and that is, "is there something inherently wrong with sex work in particular which socialism must abolish?" And the answer is no, there is nothing wrong with sex work any more than there is with nursing or therapy or teaching or acting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socialism is not against work, it's against exploitation. "From each according to ability, to each according to need." Sex workers have both an ability and they serve a need. What's bad about that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Ships Go to Die, Workers Risk Everything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon wants waiver from U.S. sanctions to restart Russia oil venture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children take to Capitol Hill to protest deportation of parents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second ICE Detainee at Adelanto Detention Center Dies in as Many Weeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubtful. The Rio Grande Valley is a diverse community and one of the Texas Democratic Party's few strongholds. The people who actually live on the border overwhelmingly rejected the border fence, and now the border wall.

To them, fortification of the border is nothing but a political football used by outsiders (i.e. the Feds, most Republicans) who have no idea how ineffectual physical barriers are for "security", and who also don't have to deal with the harmful consequences of living with them. 

  "I probably have one more decade to live, and I had one decade of torture," said Tamez, 82. "I think if they start that business again, I don't know how much fight I'll have left in me, but I'm going to fight it until the end."

Eloisa Tamez, a woman who watched the federal government bifurcate her family's land that had been intact for over 300 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they give a shit about anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but the article's point is anti-fascists don't fight generic Trump supporters whose only engagement with politics is the voter booth  they are clashing with [white, militant extremists,](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C9g-RM8UQAA-09E.jpg) called Brownshirts in Germany.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't know what reporters are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Terrorist' baby faces US embassy interview after error on visa form </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Terrorist' baby faces US embassy interview after error on visa form </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Republican leadership" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Boo hoo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chances are high that if youre abused in immigration detention, no one will care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But diplomacy is so boring!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither would being polite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really more Democrats need to go into journalism and report on the shady shit and important shit Republicans and activists have going on in their locality. The national "news" media constantly recycling the same story in different perspectives doesn't help advance any actual politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowardice is a Republican virtue. Ultra-left New York City gets hit by the *deadliest terror attack in history*, and somehow land-locked *red states* (with zero minorities) are screaming their heads off about how terrified *they* are of muslims and foreigners. These crusader-types are trained to be scared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone send him that vampire who counts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The city of Kankakee elected its first African-American, Democratic mayor. West Deerfield Township will be led entirely by Democrats for the first time, according to The Huffington Post. Elgin Township voted for a complete changeover, flipping to an all-Democratic board. Normal Township elected Democratic supervisors and trustees to run its board  the first time in more than 100 years that a single Democrat has held a seat.

Nobody in D.C. is telling these people what to do. The Democratic base is waking up angry and they're mobilizing spontaneously, this is just the tip of the bottomless grassroots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'We turn towards you with eyes lowered in shame': Pope blasts migrant suffering in Easter prayer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Africa, Fight For Your Freedom" Czechoslovakia, 1960s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Free the GI's" Black Panther Party, 1969 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student Activists Spend Spring Break in DC Fighting for Immigrant Community </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If big bombs were the solution [Afghanistan] would be the most secure place on earth today." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Criminal Justice System Is Broken, And Jeff Sessions Has No Interest In Fixing It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber Created Fake Lyft Accounts To Track Rival Drivers In Program Codenamed 'Hell' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  allowing U.S. states to ~~block family planning funds~~ force induced pregnancies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump always polls well with people who don't know geography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But their children will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why he looked so flabbergasted on election night. He never thought he'd actually be held accountable for campaign corruption  and that's how Republicans want to keep it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that you would know without transparency </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe their lessons learned from Iraq weren't all lip service like Trump's were.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans need to stop licking the shit off Trump's shoes. It's bad enough he's tracking it all over the White House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops Carry Arrested Protesters Out of Trump Tower </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Light Wages  Heavy Tanks France, Mai 1968 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sexual Assault Claims At Private Immigrant Detention Centers Are Rarely Investigated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All they did was make a picture for this quote, and it's pretty above average compared to most of the amateur pics on quotesporn.

They're not the authors of the quote or even related to the author. They've also quoted [Ralph Waldo Emerson](http://i.imgur.com/jCaPtKq.jpg), [Matt Damon](http://i.imgur.com/91dCaCs.jpg), and [Isaac Newton](http://i.imgur.com/ECysIJX.jpg). 

People on this sub should really be taking design pointers from their porn-worthy quote pics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Once weapons were manufactured to fight wars." Arundhati Roy [1060x1334] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump *is* the swamp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans currently control [**32 state legislatures**](http://www.dailykos.com/story/2016/11/14/1598918/-Republicans-now-dominate-state-government-with-32-legislatures-and-33-governors), just 6 shy of the 38 states (75%) needed to amend the Constitution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The law center notes Tanton has written that "less intelligent" people should be required to have fewer children, that a "European-American majority" is necessary to maintain American culture and once warned about a destructive "Latin onslaught" of immigration heading to the United States that he feared would undermine Western society.

That's some Nazi doctor shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooner or later, Americans will have to reconcile with the history of their country. We shouldn't be misunderstanding history - allowing outright lies to spread - for the sake of some people's sensitivity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reconstruction. The Freedman's Bureau. Radical Republicanism (back when republican meant progressive) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Misleading title from a misleading artice, **sessions** announced a new crackdown on **Illegal Immigrants**, not "immigrants"

The "citizen" most pissed at immigrants can't even use capital letters correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the Aryan ones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Betsy DeVos undoes Obama's student loan protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeVos Undoes Obama Student Loan Protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
