<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7026</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would make for some good assassins creed climbing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Keeps crashing. Destroyed phone with brick and neighbor now has a black eye. 0/10, would not use again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be a good thing, seeing how every time I go to my local Barnes and noble there seems to be less books and more overpriced toys and other assorted bullshit..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he's watching a horse race that he has a serious bet on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check out the hp lovecraft literary podcast. They cover tons of the stories that hp mentions in this essay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say post modernism is already pretty much over. Post-postmodernism homie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My stamen just got hard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not good. Maybe more adults or already liberal minded young people who read an article about it being banned will check it out, but I doubt the average Arkansas high school kid is going to go out of their way to read a non fiction history book that's not required just because it's been taken off the curriculum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn bro you paint a sad picture, lol. I want to smoke bad too, I'm on day three (again)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the second sentence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is getting an award for being able to swim back and forth in a pool the fastest or whatnot more legitimate than getting an award for making a movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm extremely skeptical, but I'll try this tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 06:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, rum diary is still one of my favorite books. If any HST fans haven't read it I thoroughly recommend it. It's like a young and crazier and more funny Hemingway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing Is Quite What It Seems In Surreal, Unsettling 'Twenty Days' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP you just need to use this as a starting off point to your own "If on a Winters Night a Traveler" type adventure!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Foodie! Loves to travel! No hookups!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like all of reddit? I mean it's a pretty good story but it's no "I don't know what a potato is" story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe give that banjo a this machine kills fascists sticker. Fuck it maybe give the dog an AK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy ever make good on making an album with all the money everyone gave him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
