<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The IT guy's office. I think it's time to clean up... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 18:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Hera! I'm so in love... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 23:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 05:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't apologize for breastfeeding your son! It shouldn't matter if he's 2 weeks or two years old. That is your personal business and should be no one else's concern. You do it for as long as you feel comfortable doing so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two of My Favorite Things Combined Into ONE!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 18:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 06:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your kind words and sharing your experience. I know I'm only focusing on the worst possible outcome, but I can't see the bigger picture just yet. It will probably take a few days to sink in for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad has cancer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 06:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He called me two times earlier this evening on my cell but I didn't feel like talking so I didn't answer. He finally called my house and I answered.

It's prostate cancer. He used the word "advanced" and said something about it being in 12 different places. I was pretty hysterical so I couldn't focus on getting more info.

I feel like a piece of shit for ignoring his phone call. I hate myself for not wanting to talk to him. I don't know how I'm going to deal with this. I'm a wreck.

Things between us have been strained lately, mostly on my end because of his inability to understand the fact that I'm in a same sex relationship. I feel like an asshole now. 

I'm so scared. I already have depression issues that I've been managing quite well lately. If I lose my dad, I'm going to lose my mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 04:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Optimus PRIME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 02:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please PM me if you need someone to talk to. I've been through an abortion before so I know how it feels.

As for telling him, maybe you should hold off on that until you talk to a counselor first. I think that finding professional help should be your #1 priority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buying a toilet... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 04:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 22:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It actually works quite well as the conditioner makes your hair slippery so the comb can just glide right through.

Let me know how it goes! Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 22:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of brushing your hair before you shower, try combing your hair with a wide tooth comb in the shower; after conditioning but before rinsing. Curly hair should never be brushed. The comb is your friend!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 18:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing!!! LOVE the colors and your beautiful long nails. As hard as I try, I can never seem to get my nails to grow past a certain point. Very frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my girlfriend's puppies. Her dog had 4 of them. They are all adorable!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 02:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 04:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG! Me too!!! Congrats!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My best friend [32F] won't talk to me [32F] and I don't know why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 04:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last time I talked to her was a few weeks ago right before I went to Las Vegas. Things were fine on the phone and I had no inclination that anything was wrong.

I tried calling her several times and she didn't answer which was unusual for her. I got a little worried because she's been having a tough time, so I contacted her friend on Facebook to ask if she was okay (she deleted her Facebook).

Later that day she sent me a nasty text. "Dude, quit calling me and asking people about me. When I want to talk to you I'll call you." This totally came out of nowhere and I don't know whether to ask her what's wrong or just let it go. I miss her.
  
**tl;dr**: Should I contact her to see why she's mad or leave her alone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
