<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2165</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you're going to cast an idiotic vote, at least have a basic understanding who you're voting for.

Unfortunately, most people don't in my experience. On both sides of the aisle. Latch on to one or two issues and vote accordingly, despite political track records or other policies that might not be a great idea.

I've heard this used as an argument against compulsory voting, as well. Even more uninformed people at the polls, pulling the lever for whatever person shouted loudest the night before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  MAY cause someone cancer

FTFY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an avid non-smoker, and someone who takes every opportunity to convince people to quit, this is a foolish stance to take. Banning cigarettes altogether will just create and underground, illegal economy.

Tax the shit out of 'em, but don't ban 'em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 11:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend, I am pretty sure I gave the same guy five bucks about 7 years ago. Very similar, if not exact, story/description. I told him I didn't really believe him, but to take it anyways for the elaborate story. He said it was fine I didn't believe, said thanks and was off to his next adventure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen you before... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the Batman vs. Predator comic as a kid. Wonder if I can dig up a copy and see if it holds up
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Alto's Adventure* is my go-to relaxing game. Haven't unlocked all characters yet, but being able to turn on the zen mode is nice. I also have a range of noises I make for each trick. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Hopefully he doesn't have the opportunity to screw the union again. Guys I've spoken to barely have trust in their board members now, let alone the headcheese. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true. The only problem is, being okay if life no longer includes owning a home. They moved that portion of the finish line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As if anyone is going to listen to this guy now. He didn't want a vote on selling the local to Unifor, he wanted the CLC to open the union to raiding (which they did). He didn't consult the membership openly to see what everyone wanted. Kinnear was promised a payday from Unifor to bring the 113 into their arms, and since he didn't get his cushy position at the international as VP, he tried to make it happen. 

From what I understand, if 113 goes to Unifor, it nullifies the current CBA. There's no way Unifor negotiates a better deal with the TTC than what they have now. But the 'Mericans are running our union! We need to be more Canadian! 

Christ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know plenty of people who wouldn't sacrifice location for savings. It is frustrating, however, to then hear "My rent is insane!" and "Does anyone want to sublet my couch!?" Usually followed, of course, by "Drinks with ma girlz!" (Not to imply a gender bias, I had financially unsound male friends as well) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I was on my own in the city was in a one bedroom basement apartment for 750. Which was just under 25% of my income, at the time. Hard to find that nowadays (five years later), I'll admit, but I made sure my place was within my means. At other times, with roommates and s/o's, my rent was less.

(**edit** I don't presume that my specific example will work for everyone, it's just meant as a "for-instance")

I mean, it's about priorities, I suppose. If your goals are to travel, or save up to buy a place, you sacrifice in the short term. If you want to live "The Life", with all the expenses that incurs, more power to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always told if your rent is more than 1/4 of your monthly income, you're living outside your means. I don't know if everyone necessarily agrees with this, but 50% is insane. And as others have said, if you can't find a one bedroom place in the city for $1650, you aren't looking properly. Sure you won't get a concierge, a steam room, or whatever other amenities you need to complete you, but you won't be wearing out your welcome with everyone you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Lost in a Good Book, Jasper Fforde**

Picked up the first book for a dollar last year, surprised by how much I enjoyed it, and that I didn't know about these books earlier. Plan to carry on with the series.

**Forty Stories, Anton Chekhov**

Casually reading my way through. First time with Chekhov, we'll see how it goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All painters know the beautiful feeling of ripping dry paint out of a tray/can/pail in one go. It's why we get up in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a professional painter, this, and most of what I see painters doing on reno/home and garden shows drives me bonkers. Put that roller on a stick! Are you cutting out of a coffee cup?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, don't get me wrong, I'll be taking a pass on this one as well. Only a handful of acts I'd really be interested in, and weekends are worth their weight in gold these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For equal salary, hell, for a 20% cut, I might consider Queensland.

Tory: You won't leave.
Byford: John, its Australia...
Tory (looking outside at snowstorm): I give up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we used to go to Bonnaroo, one or two of the headliners not being in your wheelhouse just meant there were no lines at the craft beer tent/silent disco/ferris wheel, etc. Nobody minded too much. Not sure if wayhome has similar "extracurriculars" for options.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse than that, didn't you see she wore that hat backwards!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 12:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone likes *The City and the City*, and for me that's where, after 4 books, I got of the Mieville-hype train. I don't know why I couldn't get into it, but apparently I'm in the minority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Dammit today I am reading literature! I am picking a book gathering dust on my shelf and I will... is that a far-future dystopian space opera I see on Amazon? *click click* ....dammit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it went a lot further than just a propaganda piece. Excellent story. And if I recall, didn't a lot of people in occupied Europe say they identified with the characters in the book? Steinbeck nailed the feelings and moods of those living under Nazi rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This Census-Taker, China Mieville** Loved the Bas Lag books, disliked his short stories. Taking another crack at his longer fiction.

Just finished the final Last Policeman book,**World of Trouble, by Ben H Winters**. Very quick read, in a good way. More emotional than the first two books. Sad to see the series end.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I hear Malcolm say something about Revisionist History being in "seasons" in one episode? So maybe just break for research etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 22:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm 1000 km northwest of Yellowknife

Santa, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the kind of thing people line up for? If I roll up at noon will I be disappointed. I know beer lineups are a thing elsewhere, do we do that in Toronto now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respond to all fashion criticisms with "I'm a trend-setter". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that Azaria and Shearer can just go off the cuff with their characters. The others seem to just be doing bits from the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 11:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've fallen victim to one of the classic blunders! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 11:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched a couple episodes and it has its moments, but nothing hooked me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't want to get away from ATU, he wanted to work for the international he is bitching about. Didn't get the job, so now they're the bad-guy-American-overlords. Guy's trying to leverage himself into a cushy Unifor job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read 'The Stars My Destination' last year and was pleasantly surprised by it. Almost like a loose retelling of The Count of Monte Cristo' in space. Classic sci-fi themes that weren't classic in 1956, either.

Equal Rites was funny, but it took me a while to get into. Love the Witches now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically Bad History leaning more towards humour on purpose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fly? Yes. Land? ... No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're poeticizing my life :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay: Don't be a dick. Next question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 21:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This scene](https://youtu.be/V638eAp7QFc?t=53s) got me into the show. I could take it or leave it before Tina counting toothpicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're referring to Baader-Meinhoff? I'd explain it here, but you'll be hearing about it again soon anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straya Day, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the LCBO only refills their own growlers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody's a bit inventive until the have cuffs slapped on them for no reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can like and support good police and demand accountability for shit cops. I can do both because I am capable of feeling more than one thing at a time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit, Frank... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Goodreads link](http://www.goodreads.com/book/show/223380.Stories_of_Your_Life_and_Others) to the collection, for your perusal. I enjoyed it, especially 'Tower of Babylon' and the eponymous story (which Arrival was based on). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who did their open water checkout in a quarry lake... in Ontario... in October... This is the correct answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The image of Julia Child ringing up Pizza Nova is both excellent and sacrilegious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 23:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm more excited to become 21 so that I can buy alcohol for cooking, and not drinking

It's easy to say that now. Then you've got a nice bottle of wine open for cooking purposes and it says, "How will you know what the dish will taste like if you don't taste me?" And you say, "That's not a bad point, but tell me, how'd you get in that glass?" And the wine laughs. And you laugh. Everyone is laughing. And the next thing you know things are burning and pizza is on it's way.

(there are helpful replies in this thread...this has not been one of them) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like 330am and 445am because goddamit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 11:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely wrap them. At least for stealthiness, also in case someone else handles your bag. Dont want them dropping your hard-smuggled beer and ruining the trip. I usually jam the bottles inside my socks, then wedgr firmly between other stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 04:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the wonderful world of electric scooters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plenty of shit is done at night here too. Only problem is, it can only get done between 230 and 5am.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. I'm starting to remember. I was worried it was going the way of Desert Trip, where the GA was behind the more expensive tickets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you might like to try [Looking for Jake, by China Mieville](http://www.goodreads.com/book/show/499415.Looking_for_Jake). I don't know if any of the stories would fall under "sci-fi or horror" exactly. A few of them go supernatural and unsettling (The Ball Room, The Tain, Looking for Jake, and others), and might draw your interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, can you not get to the front anymore with a GA pass? I'm having trouble visualizing "separate pits". I thought it was just a shorter line/earlier access for vip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 18:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to your heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 13:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 'Hat' series seems like something Penny Arcade would come up with.

...and I want to play it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the lesson is that the fire extinguisher was inside us all along? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends where you are i guess. could grab a coffee/food and people watch at (top of my head) aroma - yonge near wellesley, lakeview restaurant - ossington and dundas, quantum coffee - king and spadina, red rocket coffee - wellesley and sherbourne-ish.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folks came back from Costco in QC with a sample case of Boreal and Unibroue, each. No complaints.

If this cold snap gets worse, theres some Ol' Fog Burner barleywine from Garrison that might get called up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found the Swedish version to be more nuanced. Plus subtitles mean I pay better attention :-p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 06:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who just started the series (first book, ~page 50), how fast will I get ahead of the show? I watched season 1, and I'm curious if it is like Game of Thrones started off (1st season, first bookish). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same at Jays games for whatever strikeout gets us free pizza. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Un-navigable is a perfect description. I've been in the same boat.

Maybe it's because Toronto's downtown has lost a need for a bargain store? Or maybe everyone in the area paying 1500 for a jr. 1-bedroom actially needs a store like Honest Ed's! Oh god...Well, when they pave Kensington for the Wal-Mart, everyone will breathe easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 04:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, it's a "you don't talk about fight club" thing. Let an in-joke be an in-joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP is referring to an area of Northern Canada on Victoria Island, not the Phillipine lake.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are oddly (really oddly) in line with many other countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 07:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who are stuck 100 years ago hate her because she's a woman who likes women, people in the suburbs hate that hydro and gas are getting more expensive, and I don't like her because she's selling government assets and won't loosen the liquor laws.

(all of these are of course broad generalizations, but they are the most common, from what I see) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 05:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell which part of your statement the /s goes on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 07:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would call it thorough world building, but still wouldn't fall under hard sci fi, imho. Great movie, great backstory, and McConnaughey is over the top amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IANAL, but perhaps we could make it so the driver could just submit a written statement? 

Because the taxpayer in me agrees the OT for sending a driver to court would be expensive, but the nervous streetcar disembarker in me wants people to get a fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not liking a headliner is the best way to do other stuff at a festival, I've found. I'm looking at you, ferris wheel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Badass poem. How did I miss that. Bonnaroo with the deep Rovert Service reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've still got a few tracks from their sunrise set (w/ Big Gigantic) on my phone. One of the most epic sets I've seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had a long ER wait the other night and finished Hugh Howey's **Beacon 23** in basically one sitting. Reading Warren Ellis's **Normal** now. Onward to 52! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked up **A Burglar's Guide to the City** by Geoff Manaugh last week, which should be interesting at the very least. **Guns, Germs and Steel**, by Jared Diamond has been in my pile for some time, along with the last couple books in John Scalzi's Old Man's War series. Then I'll just see where the year takes me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 06:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slartibartfast. Although he didn't win an award for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, are you using pot possession statistics from a blog post to make a point about stop-and-frisk stats in different countries? You aren't making the point you think you are.

And for Pete's sake, it's "should have", not "should of". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. I saw Sweet Jesus on the beer description, but it doesn't say where the beans came from. I assumed they were from Pilot.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why terrible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 03:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shit my uncle and his buddies used to pull would have you doing a few years now, I'm sure. And on a watchlist... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watched the trailer. For $2.69, I'm pretty much sold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Steam Controller and the Mac: Is it worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 09:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw the SC on sale, and figured why not. Spent a bunch of time updating/troubleshooting to get the controller working, and just now realizing how short the list of games that the controller works properly with (gets a lot shorter for a mac user). First couple tries, steam crashes. Don't know if that's a Big Picture issue or a controller one...the struggle continues. 

Long story short, I was hoping to get a controller I could plug in and play some games that looked like they would be more fun with a controller. I'm not a guy who tweaks settings and configs, or partitions things or any of the awesome stuff I see other people doing. Feels like no end in sight for the hurdles in getting it up and running.

Is the SC not for me? Should I be returning this particular piece of hardware? 

I welcome encouragement and discouragement equally, at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 23:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a kid, I always just thought I was terrible at it. As an adult, I understand it was the mechanic (meaning I still can't jump right in that game). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 20:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think UP could have been better done as well. Like having the station attached to Dundas West (TTC) as opposed to me having to walk down the road in The Weather. Do you think pushing to get it in for Pan Am was a detriment to what could have been a much more well-thought out piece of infrastructure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My surprisingly unpopular opinion of getting local politics out of regiobal transit stems from decisions like this. I for one welcome our new Metrolinx overlords (provided they get their shit together on Presto *fistshake*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume OP just dropped an astrix trying to italicize *was*.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 23:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you did spell "asterisk" in a horrendous fashion... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Mac user, thank you for including us :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might also have something to do with the perception that mouthwash has alcohol, even it is an alcohol-free brand. Some poor sot could chug a litre of that and just make himself ill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess too. No other self-respecting human would wear those hats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 10:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you aren't, but I've been places that keeps mouthwash under lock and key to stop people drinking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or your native French-speaking teacher thinks you kids are so far behind and speaks to you fluently while you try to guess what's happening....or was that just me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is how I get lost in wikipedia tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 23:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, I have to agree with Mr. Bannerman on this one. Unless Gildan has upped their game recently, they feel a little like wearing burlap :-) The gf and I had a great laugh at your stuff last night, and I'm really glad you guys are making it work! Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 08:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All my bachelor food is cooked for 5 minutes on high. Occasionally there is a flip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice save. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 11:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been to a few places that were over and above our usual price range, our outside our comfort zone for type of food because of these events. We've had some really excellent, well-prepared meals, Canoe being no exception. It's not like these places treat you any differently (outwardly). I'll keep going for prix fixe menus, and we return to the ones we really liked  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 13:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. But let's face it, 75% of the place where O'Connor hits another street is a shitshow :-p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 11:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was Woodbine and O'Connor not on Tory's hit list of intersections to fix? Or was that just Donlands and O'Connor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 06:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Recycles Mcgee". Amazing. Oh Tampa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One can hope :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a good point. Perhaps trying the first volume to gauge interest. You're right though. Would definitely require a larger amount of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm looking for a new bag, this seems to be what I need and looks affordable."

Amazon.com - $209
Amazon.ca - $667

Hrm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be interested in Norwegian Wood, since I've read the first 20-30, but stalled/been distracted by shiny new books. I've heard it's the most grounded of his books, and maybe it would be good for people looking to start in on Murakami.

I would also put my name in the hat for Proust, since I have a nice, big, long, daunting copy and let's face it, can't tackle it alone. I think there are probably others like me, and as a group, we can prevail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't read it yet, but last year I read From Hell for the first time and I know what you mean about dense description. As you said about characters going for walks, I started to zone out when characters went for carriage rides, where descriptions of the history of London's architecture could fill many pages. All very interesting, but holy crap!

Jerusalem is on my 2017 list, but kind of hoping for a secondhand purchase (applies to all books I buy, not a dig at Moore). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
