<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8234</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that common birth control injection may be linked to increased weight gain by activating brain regions associated with food motivation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 21:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 02:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A quick literature search didn't show many studies investigating specifically TBI and Domestic Violence. From what I can tell, it seems that most studies in the past have listed TBI as a potential health consequence of DV, but have not specifically investigated TBIs sustained as a result of DV. Here's one of the few papers on this topic i could find: http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002937803003582

It seems as though DV wasn't even considered as a public health problem until about 10 years ago- I think OP's study is important because it establishes a firm connection between DV and TBI, and it provides future policy makers and researchers in the field a foundation to build on. If research finds that TBI is often caused by DV, we may be able to better help women (and men) who are victims of DV by screening them for TBI, and giving them treatment for that in addition to what treatments are already provided. Also, considering that TBI is often comorbid with other disorders, such as PTSD, realizing that DV victims may have TBI could allow professionals a new perspective on how to treat the mental health symptoms that often accompany DV. 

Here's a paper that talks about the convergence of PTSD and TBI:
http://ajp.psychiatryonline.org/doi/abs/10.1176/appi.ajp.2009.08101604 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study suggests that differences in male and female complaints after a mild traumatic brain injury (e.g. concussion) may be attributed to differences in emotional regulation circuits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study suggests that self-harm may be related to basic psychological needs not being met </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually in a similar situation. I moved across the country to a school in a state I'd never been and it was a huge culture shock. I had trouble relating with people and I woke up every morning wondering why I did this to myself. 

My advice is to apply to graduate programs near where you're interested by the deadlines this fall (usually Dec). If that means retaking the GRE, allow yourself enough time to do that. Finish the school year where you're at, and if you still aren't happy and get an offer from somewhere you'd like to go more, then accept it and leave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 22:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://student.cc.uoc.gr/uploadFiles/179-%CE%9A%CE%A8%CE%92364/Davis1983.pdf

Wasn't able to find an online version but here's the original paper that proposed the test.

And here is an online copy of the actual test: 
http://fetzer.org/sites/default/files/images/stories/pdf/selfmeasures/EMPATHY-InterpersonalReactivityIndex.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for doing this AMA!

I'm interested in what you think possible medical implications of this technology could be. In particular, I think about people with disorders like locked-in syndrome. Obviously, the technology is still far off from being perfect, but do you think that an interface for people with conditions similar to locked-in syndrome could be developed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My home in Louisiana flooded and thankfully my department is being really awesome about everything. They told me to stay as long as I needed to and that even if I missed a few days of classes that would be okay and that they would work with me to help me with whatever I needed. Made me realize how awesome this department is and how lucky I am to be a part of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 09:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The medial prefrontal cortex has inhibitory control over the amygdala. Some recent therapies have been trying to integrate CBT into the treatment regimen for PTSD to try and control the fear responses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 21:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, thanks for doing this AMA. 

I'm curious if any of you are interested in potential applications this might have for neuroscience. I know there had been some difficulty in the past with treatment of glioblastomas. I guess I'm specifically interested in what this methodology could bring to the table with regards to this problem, and if any of you think it has the potential to impact treatment of brain cancer in the future. 

I would also be really interested in hearing any advice you have for someone looking to do a career in neuroscience and neuroimaging. I'm currently working in a neuroimaging lab and am really interested in pursuing this as a career path. Is Toronto somewhere I should look into? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Dr. Gu, thanks for doing this AMA. 

I'm really curious to hear your thoughts on perceptions/misconceptions Congress and politicians might have about your research. Have you come across any notable misconceptions?

I'm also interested to hear your thoughts on how science is perceived and understood by people in power. I feel as though research and science is vastly misunderstood within Congress. Is this true? Are there any people in particular that are the exception to this "rule"?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 20:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you've already played through GTA I would just go for the PS now because if you haven't played through all those games that you listed, you'd probably have more fun. I'd also recommend Witcher 3 if you need a great time sink. Fantastic RPG. Probably my favorite game ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 17:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's this series by Bret Funk that would meet your tastes. The books in the series are Path of Glory, Sword of Honor, Jewel of Truth, and Forge of Faith. Just a fantastic series that's relatively unknown. 

I don't know if you're into gaming, but the books that the Witcher series is based on are great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah at the auction the art dealer would've given you a tip. Considering you bought it for 20 crowns, 500 isn't a bad ROI.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 23:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you can sell that painting to the bookshop owner in Novigrad for 500 crowns right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 07:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 6 months  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 02:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really depends on where you're applying. A lot of graduate programs list some classes/work/experience they'd like their applicants to have. For psychology, mostly everyone was looking for research experience. I would start looking at the programs you want to apply to, and see if you would benefit from having the extra experience. I don't think it could hurt if you got the extra experience, and if you could get involved working with some faculty members in that quarter, I'd recommend it even more. If you're applying to Economics grad programs, being able to say on your application that you were an Economics major would probably help. I recommend you look at both the pros and cons of both, and consider which one would benefit you more. Also, try and talk to some faculty at your university about this! I'm sure they would have some more practical advice for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your issues with Witcher? I personally thought it was one of the best RPGs I've ever played </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 22:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then flipped him off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 05:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom and grandma always told me this but I thought that was just an excuse to get out of making it.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 06:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously amazing indie game. Only like 19$ I believe. Just incredible game, if you end up playing it, use headphones. Adds a whole lot to the experience  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 06:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call production companies in your area and look for jobs. Generally in my experience they don't straight up hire a FOH tech. Usually you have to start as a gopher or a grunt, but if you work hard and pay attention and always put forth a good effort eventually they start offering more to you, like assisting FOH, then eventually running FOH. That first foot in the door is crucial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 04:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was hurting so badly I took the ice over the pain haha
It was two years ago so I turned out pretty well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 03:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't feel my ankle by the time I got to the hospital  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 02:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once broke my ankle and had to get a friend to drive me to the ER in Michigan from Ohio (going to a hospital in Ohio would've been way more expensive insurance wise). To keep ice on it we gaff taped a bag of ice to my ankle. When I got to the ER 3 hours later the doc said that it was the best job of icing an injury he'd ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 01:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how do we know it's Darkseid? I was wondering what Lex was referring to at the end but my first thought was Brainiac  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 14:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revolution is one of my favorite breweries. I would love to see them expand to Michigan. Right now I try and go at least once every few months to their taproom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 05:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried downloading a playlist for offline play and seeing if that works? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 04:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I thought it was 16, it's actually 18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 01:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan, USA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 01:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where'd you get the Pulteney? I've been looking for it in stores around me and can't find it. I found a website called Master of Malt that will ship it though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 01:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm torn between Caol Ila 18 and Old Pulteney 21. I want to get my buddy a nice bottle for his wedding later this year and I've heard great things about both. Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 22:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Indiana I recommend Crooked Ewe or Evil Czech  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 06:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh. People here seem to love it but I'm not impressed. Honestly the biggest letdown is the story. I don't give a shit about Primal's story, where in 4 I played through twice, one for each storyline. Everything is subbed in primal so half the time I just skip the cutscenes because I can't see the screen to read the subs. It's more challenging than 4 but I'm not immersed by it like I was in 4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 06:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have tinnitus and get this sometimes. Thought mine was just because of the tinnitus but I guess not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 02:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KBS. I've been dying to try one for years. Gonna try and make the drive up to GR for the release party since I missed the online raffle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 13:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started in 2012. I'm graduating in May. Can't wait to go to grad school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 23:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> michigan
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 22:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a small (3000) private Seventh Day Adventist University  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 20:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate Kai Winn on Deep Space Nine. Every time she pulls an asshole move, she covers it by being condescending and calling you "my child".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 17:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The homepage is [here](https://www.andrews.edu) for the lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My university's marketing team thinks that one of our professors singlehandedly discovered gravity waves.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 17:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 15:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> March 12th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 21:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What'd you think of daredevil vs Jessica Jones?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 21:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Undergraduate psychology major who does research and is peer reviewing for a journal. Waiting for grad school acceptances. I do audio engineering on the side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 05:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do yourself a favor and pick up some Penrose or Revolution Brewing. I live in southwest Michigan and drive to Chicago sometimes just to get their beer. Revolution has a brewpub in Logan Square with incredible food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 01:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for wickr! Been using it for a few years and I love it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 07:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is anecdotal, but my uncle and his wife are in their late sixties and just got back from Spain, where from my understanding they stayed in hostels the majority of the time. They had nothing but great things to say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 23:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's not much, but this is my first time donating to any candidate. It feels good! 

http://imgur.com/MCuvNUr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 23:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try and hit Abita Brewing in LA for a tour. They let you try as much beer as you want, and you can even pour your own from their taps! All free too. Awesome experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 06:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psychology:

You only use 10% of your brain. This drives me up the fucking walls. 

Also, apparently if you're a psychology student you're automatically analyzing everyone around you at all times. Like I don't have more interesting shit to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 06:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a big fan of the new Project PAM by Founders. Also can't go wrong with Crooked Tree by Dark Horse, or Founder's Devil Dancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't heard a ton. I hope I do in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did any therapies help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing research for a class and found some really interesting stuff. For instance, the amygdala (usually associated with emotion and fight/flight response) shows heightened activity and the medial prefrontal cortex (associated with executive control) shows diminished activity in people with PTSD. Researchers think that there is an "alarm" system that activates in the presence of non-consciously attended fear, and that as a result of trauma, the amygdala is over active and isn't being inhibited by the medial prefrontal cortex. They think this is why people with PTSD tend to have violent fear responses all of the sudden- they're actually developing drugs and therapies to try and combat this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 07:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got done applying to neuroscience programs and I'm hoping to do my doctorate by working with vets. I've been reading up on PTSD research recently and I'm really passionate about research on this. 

My grandpa is a Navy veteran with PTSD, but he doesn't seem to put much stock in science or research when it comes to developing PTSD therapies/treatments. Do you think this Is this a general consensus among vets? I was kinda shocked when he told me that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 06:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you remember what cheeses you used the first time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 21:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're into craft beer Revolution Brewing is amazing. It's in Logan Square and they have incredible food and beer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 02:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on publishing a paper about this right now. Would love to hear about your research. PM me if you get some time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 20:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get in with a local production company and work your way up. Get some experience and be a hard worker and you'll get recognized eventually. Takes time but you'll get there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 00:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually referring to the pope's recent US trip haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 23:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you go to Andrews? That's where I'm going now and its terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 23:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most painful part is that no one really knows except my family/close friends. Everyone around here treats agnostics and atheists like they're contagious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 22:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a former SDA, I always found this really ridiculous. My parents used to say that they planted gardens so that when the end times came we could live off of the land without having to compromise ourselves by buying food from the government (something to do with the mark of the beast?).. Every time the pope is in town, they flip their shit and talk about how his calls for "unity" are indicative of a sunday law coming.. They actually tried to teach me in SDA school that there are sunday laws already in place in some states in the US.

Bunch of loonies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 17:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a question about the importance of GRE scores. I took mine and got 154V, 148Q and 5.5 writing. I can't afford to take it again. I have great research experience though (a paper I'm first author on is under review and have presented at 4 conferences this year) and some great letters of recommendation (I taught a week of intro classes for one of my professors last year because he got sick at the last minute), so I'm wondering if the other parts of my resume could offset my GRE scores.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 04:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've looked before but I couldn't find any.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 19:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had it, I thought it was pretty mediocre. I like Virgil's a lot more. http://reedsinc.com/product/virgils-root-beer/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 17:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Griffin Claw is from Michigan, so it shouldn't be too difficult to find it. Have you tried Penrose Brewing or Revolution Brewing from Chicago? I live right outside of Chicago and those are my two favorite finds so far.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 14:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only brews from Alaska I've had are from Alaskan Brewing Co. I really liked their Amber </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 06:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of these I think Dogfish Head's was my favorite. If you can though, get your hands on some screamin pumpkin by griffin claw. Fantastic pumpkin ale that gives dogfish head a run for their money IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 22:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you're on the right track. Here's what I've been doing:

Submitted a paper I authored to a journal that is under peer review
Working on submitting a second in a week or so
Presented at a major national (ASA) and regional (MPA) conference 
Tutored for statistics
Working as a research assistant for my department chair
Started a high level statistics class with my professor, learned R and SPSS

Basically put yourself out there for every opportunity you find and make opportunities for yourself whenever you can. If you can work as a coauthor with a professor, you'd shoot yourself to the top of the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 22:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start studying for the GRE now. Learn vocabulary, and review math. There's tons of guides and helpful websites. It's a tough one. I'm gonna have to retake it here pretty soon. 

Applications are good for me because I went through this process trying to apply for internships. Get with faculty you know and ask them for letters of recommendation. You've got a year, if you don't know them get to. Do some research. Shit is so competitive. You need a good CV and cover letter.

Also, save money now. GRE is 199$ here and each application costs anywhere from 50-100$. I'm applying to about 10 programs, so that's gonna cost me a good bit. 

Also, do some research into who you want to work with at universities you want to apply to. I made a table of professors I want to work with, their area of research, application deadlines and fees. Read their stuff and email them and ask them about their research and if they're accepting grad students. I did this with a guy out at Brigham Young, we're skyping this week and it's looking good so far. 

Honestly I would just say to prepare as much as you can. Don't slack off like I did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 21:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm a senior psych major applying to PhD programs. I guess I have another 5-6 years before I need to worry about finding a job..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 17:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are these people pursuing graduate degrees?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 05:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations you are now a moderator of /r/pyongyang  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 20:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what score would that be overall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 18:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah I got a maybe, which is better than I've done in a long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 16:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tinnitus? Really? How long did it take?

I ask because I've got it from working as an audio engineer for the past ~4 years. I've been more careful about ear protection, but it's still bad sometimes. Didn't think I'd ever get back to normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 16:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm working out or physically exerting myself, I can definitely feel it. It's not so much hearing it as it is feeling it beating, I don't really know how to explain it though. If i'm just resting if I focus I can feel it, but I usually check my pulse every now and again to make sure things are ok. 

The heart flutter thing is definitely real, while people may not be able to feel it beat regularly, when it flutters you definitely notice it and it's pretty scary when you don't know what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 16:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang in there man! I just turned 22 and even though I have one, it's not really as thick or full as I want it to be. I was only able to grow one starting about when i was 19, and it took me until i was 21 for it to not be patchy as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 16:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been working out 5 days a week and eating right, and have lost about 20lbs in the past two and a half months. Even now I'm starting to notice things. Still got a long way to go, but it's encouraging.

1. Fitting in movie theater seats without being uncomfortable. Before my belly would hang over the arm rests and it would annoy the fuck out of me to where i couldn't use them. I went the other day and discovered i no longer have that problem.

2. I've got a lot more confidence. I finally got around to asking out this waitress at this local cafe where I've been a regular for 7 years. Felt great.

3. I'm starting to notice little things, like walking up a long flight of stairs, isn't so difficult anymore.

4. I can see my biceps becoming more defined, and it feels great.

5. I've been getting less self-conscious, and other people have been making fat jokes a lot less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 15:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So here's what a recent study into little Albert found, according to numerous professors I've discussed this with. 

Little Albert was videoed, and some medical experts analyzed his behavior and noticed that he most likely was nearly blind and deaf. This is troubling, because in their paper, researchers say in the last paragraph that Albert was selected for the experiment because he was a normal, average child to which a population of children could be compared to. If he truly was blind and deaf, they knowingly lied about it. The head researcher, at the time, worked on the staff of a journal being published by the university he worked at- Watson and colleagues (2007) found some documents suggesting that he pushed the paper through without going through a peer-review process.

He was born by a single mother who was a wet nurse, which was typically not very high on the food chain, and was pressured into giving Albert to researchers for this experiment. If I recall correctly, she ended up taking him out of the experiment and moving, where he eventually died around age 6.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 22:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain to me why older conservatives are such staunch advocates of Israel? I tried to say something about Israel to my ultra conservative family members the other day and they damn near took my head off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 22:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abita has some really good brews. If you're ever in the area go do the brewery tour. Well worth it. It's free, about an hour long, and they let you try all the beer you want, and even teach you how to pour your own. Awesome bunch of guys over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 00:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shout out to /r/consoledeals
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 05:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her name is Helen Owen. Check her out on Instagram. She is gorgeous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 18:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find something pointy (maybe a letter opener?) that will fit in the hole on that knob. Push on it/twist it until you can see a metal pin where the hole is. Push the pin in, pull off the knob. From there, disassemble the plate behind the knob, and you should be able to find the latch attached to the door pin( should be a small protuberance that fits into the center of the assembly). Pull on it with a pair of pliers and it should open.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-26 02:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite on this album is definitely devil dancer. I thought it was a fantastic IPA

What'd you think of the Bells Planet series? I didn't get to try any, but I've got a bottle of Neptune I'm waiting to break open.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 16:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got introduced to sours through New Belgium's La Folie. Really solid sour. Bells has some other good ones, the Wild One and the Contrebassiste are really solid sours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
