<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I gained a new doggo fren. Rarepuppers, meet Walter! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scones and white sauce  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no point debating it, we have different view points and neither of us will change the others mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 12:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a sane person, I agree completely. However some people are more easily swayed / disillusioned with life.

If we take the stance "anyone who has gone there instantly is blacklisted for death" then anybody thinking about quitting or informing on them etc will think "fuck it, I've got nothing to lose, I may as well stay here for life and go out fighting." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 12:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's why people who go to prison get reduced sentences, plea deals, incentives for good behaviour, etc. If there were no incentives there would be no deterrents.  If governments don't bend, they break. I'm not saying that if people return they shouldn't be watched like a hawk, or if they committed proven atrocities while they were away they shouldn't be jailed - im saying that if, say, 10% of people who went to be jihadis went and changed their mind, wouldn't you rather they came back and we only had 90% to worry about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as terrorists - but as people who realise they made a mistake and want to go back to normal life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 09:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or because taking a hard line with those who return would discourage people returning and encourage more people to go join. It's a delicate balance.

It's like why people in jail get good behaviour rewards when, arguably, they're criminals and don't "deserve it". If you don't have a light at the end of the tunnel for people they're more likely to do fucked up shit without fear of ramifications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all friends here - you can be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One question - what line of work are you in? How do you afford having so many kids!?

Congratulations on leaving, especially on having your whole family on the same page. Hopefully being free of Mormonism opens up your life to many new and exciting opportunities without losing the comfort or security that religion presumably gave! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lawyer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why!? I'm in Aberdeen! I don't want to leave the uk either, I voted no before and I'll be voting no again. Why can't we all just be friends  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me sad. I want to stay in the EU  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems legit. Get down to the bingo hall, pop some viagra and show those old dears what's up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I couldn't possibly begin to answer that. You'll get one eventually, stop looking and just work on enjoying life and you'll stumble across someone doing the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, what a toxic relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say my root comment was sarcastic and an incorrect assumption - I wouldn't say it was hostile. Whenever somebody has engaged me in civil discussion I've responded in kind but, you're right, I probably should've taken the higher ground.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate gun control. I hate lack of gun control. I am a centrist extremist. Nobody is safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I genuinely don't know how Reddit works but I thought stuff appeared on the front page as a result of popularity? So if the London killings didn't appear, do we not only have ourselves to blame?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I retract my statement as it's incorrect, the shitty attitude of some responders still warrants an equally shitty response. All that was required (which some people did do) was posting a link to prove me wrong, not the inevitable circle jerk or hostility that ensued. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. If nothing else, I appreciate your balanced view! Changed my view on T_D members. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I personally wouldn't be so on my high horse about someone saying something without a factual basis when Trump is your fuhrer. 

[source](https://www.reddit.com/r/Impeach_Trump/comments/619c3b/lie_tracker_trump_has_been_in_office_for_64_days/?st=J0TCXRCZ sh=d0a3870b)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I said, I sorted it by date, note popularity. I blocked the donald from my timeline since I was blocked for posting my opinion on something - that's frowned upon, it seems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did scroll in terms of date posted and went back as far as 48 hours, admittedly I could've looked further </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand corrected - apologies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know what this means.

Also, my point insinuated (as proven, wrongfully) that T_D members are racist.  However, I only had to look 3 comments deep into your post history to find you calling somebody a "butt hurt Jew". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 11:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that either the left or right support murder. I do think the rhetoric of the_donald (the subreddit, not all donald trump fans) is fairly toxic in terms of its anti Islam and, to an extent, its anti minority views.

Edit: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 10:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to see the_donald's post condemning this terror attack! Oh, wait...

Edit: it appears they did - I wont delete my post as I made a shitty assumption.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checked your most recent comment:

"thanks for that valuable insight. whatever would we do without shponglefart (OP)"

You need a better hobby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You try tanning buckfast most school nights in a park in tropical Scottish climes and see how you get on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't how the internet works! Call him a dick and tell him he's wrong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he Scottish or are kilts big over there too? I wouldn't be surprised about cost, my kilt cost ~1300! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that green guy staring at me was really throwing me off my stroke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, some people don't view toplessness as seedy or sexual, maybe they fall into that camp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you go as far as to say it's mad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sky news knows what's up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 09:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, I love the joycon and have exclusively used that mode thus far, so your assertion that they're horrible is not universal.

Secondly, needing hardware to play a game on four player doesn't equate to that game costing more. As somebody else has pointed out that, if you're going that route, you'd also need to include the cost of the switch.

A similar example is "me and my friends wanted a kick about so I bought a football - but we then needed to all buy pairs of boots, shin guards and football strips! The cost of playing football is so high!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She needs some eyebrows - that's why she looks scary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too, hate my ear lobes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This photo doesn't do her justice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only been about a month into it and I'm halfway through making an app. 

I can't remember their names, and I'll go dig them out if you struggle to find them, but there's an Asian American, and a South Korean guy who make tutorials that are great!

The first of the two doesn't really use the GUI and does everything code based, which was quite daunting for me! Especially if you make a mistake it's hard to know when you've gone wrong. The latter guy is very easy to follow IMO.

In fact I'm being lazy, I'll go get you their links.

Edit:

[The Swift Guy](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC-d1NWv5IWtIkfH47ux4dWA) 

[Duc Tran](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCvPFGq6luCqAVGiFpzTvkIA) 

[Jared Davidson](https://www.youtube.com/user/Archetapp) 

[Let's Build That App](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCuP2vJ6kRutQBfRmdcI92mA) 

Between these 4 gents I've managed to learn quite a bit! If you're willing to put the time in to going through their tutorials you'll definitely pick stuff up.

I'd recommend starting with The Swift Guy or Jared as their tutorials are much more bite sized, Duc and LBTA are a bit longer and more advanced IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bare foot if I recall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would highly recommend it, I've travelled a bit and it's my favourite place thus far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it good snowless, OP? I went in winter last year and loved it! Can't decide if I should revisit in summer or go in winter again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he's like 20 that kid will just be walking along the street and he'll be like "waaaaait a minute " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did yelling them go? Are you glad you did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was there for my dogs last moments - hardest thing I've ever had to do, and most sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched it three times and will undoubtedly watch it a fourth in the distant future. 

Walt and jesses respective transitions are so poignant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The exude autism  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies, forgot not everybody would know who Zavvi is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies I was on the move at work and saw it in my emails, hence the screenshot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but this is the first Fully fledged RPG style Zelda. It fits the remit to reward exploration, and there's only so many unique items you can get (bombs, magnet, stasis), so there needs to be a system in place to keep things fresh.

You may disagree, which you're entitled to, but I think it's great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 08:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's good and is essential to make finding weapons constantly important.

If you found a good weapon early on and it never broke you'd never need to bother getting another one.

Also, it makes me excited when I find a good one! Everything I had is ~20 damage then I found a 36 damage weapon! I then used it to kill a giant I randomly found wandering around. 

I'm loving this game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 15:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love a copy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually the authority on these matters  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 11:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vaping still isn't cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I scrolled down and saw this I thought "shit! Is that what broccoli looks like on the inside?! TIL...!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people did in the comments section of the news report saying he had no money, linking photos to him with prostitutes in Thailand the week before, he saw and responded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sub is about them getting confronted, not specifically the uploaded being the one who did it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So orange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love great tits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also posted screenshots of the Facebook comments section of the news report of him saying he's broke and other people commenting about him going to Thailand a few weeks earlier and linking to his photos of him with prostitutes etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neve taking his catfish game to a whole other level  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was thinking about putting an inb4 but decided it was unnecessary...

...should have known </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to select what data to download off of firebase? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

In a nutshell I have data stored on firebase than I want to randomly distribute, but in order of when it was submitted.  For example:

People upload data (let's say a voice clip), I want to set it so on the app there's a download button and when a user hits it it checks for the voice clip at the front of the queue, checks it's not uploaded by the current user, if not it downloads the voice clip and adds "1" to the counter, and once the counter reaches 5 the voice clip is then put into a waiting bay, pending all 5 users who downloaded it rating it, whereby an action is taken.

I ask this as I've just realised that all logic needs undertaken at the front end and not the back end, so I'm trying to implement the sorting of voice clips in line with the download button.

When a user uploads an audio clip I'm thinking of having firebase store:

1. The clip
2. Clip name
3. Date
4. User Unique ID number 
5. Username
6. Number of downloads (set to zero initially)
7.  Score

Is the best way to tell firebase to look for the oldest date? And then check that the user id doesn't equal current user idea, and then if a suitable clip is found +1 to number of downloads?

Any input to this very general question would be appreciated!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know most probably don't have anything to compare it to as it's all relative, but hoping somebody has an answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: I know you probably have nothing to compare it to, but hopefully somebody has an answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my most recent one was a guy posting that he's hard done by cause the government gave him 1 penny a month in benefits and he posted all over Facebook and the local news picked it up, but then I also posted screenshots of his Facebook from the month before of him rinsing thousands of pounds on a prostitute filled Thai holiday! 

I've given up on trying to submit to this sub, the intricacies are beyond me haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 09:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rules of this sub are so weird. Whenever I try post stuff with pretty substantial evidence it gets removed due to lack of evidence, yet, posts like this are acceptable - even though we just have to take the OPs word for it that his google search turned up what it did, and that the "rapper" wasn't joking in his post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I 100% agree. I wasn't meaning compare Zelda to Nintendogs directly, I was meaning evaluate both games contextually and then tell me do you consider Nintendogs as good as ocarina of time? I'd say definitely not. 

Is goat simulator a 10 because it's the best goat simulation game there's ever been? Probably not. 

Did Nintendogs push boundaries, and will it be remembered for decades? Probably not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but is Nintendogs literally the BEST it could physically be, aka 10/10? Is there zero scope for improvement?

A game like Zelda is much more open to interpretation as it has a story and gameplay elements.  A game as simple as Nintendogs - whilst still able to feasibly achieve a 10 would, in my opinion, have to do a lot more to be classed as perfect.

I'm not comparing Nintendogs to Zelda like for like, I'm saying look at Zelda whilst considering the boundaries of RPG/adventure games and look at Nintendogs within the context of its' genre - are both games equally as accomplished/pushing the boundaries? In my opinion - no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes subreddit simulator just gets it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be that as it may, is it fair to award a game so small in scope a perfect score? I.e. Sitting ocarina of time next to Nintendogs, is it fair to say they're both perfect games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did Nintendogs get 10/10  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trickle down banging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today is my birthday   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't believe Bill Gates just answered a question by a guy called Dick Nipples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot native Americans spoke English  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies - I hope my worry is misplaced too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sure? He specifically said to me all staff had an update saying it's release date (not delivery date) was the 6th of March.

How is PSVR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think they still have any!?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed the pre order from amazon so went with Tesco as they guaranteed release day delivery. 

I don't trust cancelling and trying to get amazon now...I'll just have to be wit and see.

I'm just annoyed that he was trying to claim Nintendo official release date is the sixth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree but going by what he said, they're classing the 6th as their day of launch. So saying launch day delivery would still hold true... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sneaky Tesco pushing back release date </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered from Tesco on day one of pre orders as they guaranteed release day delivery.

I just checked my order and it says releasing 6th of March so I phoned them. The guy on the phone said "yes, release day delivery - the console is dropping on the 6th of March."

I said "no, the console is dropping on the 3rd of March?" 

He said "no, we have a staff notice that Nintendo are dropping it on the 6th and they'll do an announcement on the 6th telling everyone."

I said "I highly doubt they're pushing the release date back 3 days and aren't telling anyone until 3 days after the fact. Plus amazon, Argos, etc all still say the third."

He said "oh well there's nothing more I can tell you than what it says here."

What it looks like is that Tesco want to ensure release day delivery so they've just created their own release date, 3 days after Nintendos actual release date.  I'm going to be left with BoTW and no console to play it on.

TL:DR; Tesco can eat a great big bowl of dicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. Look at the company who made witcher, they started with a lesser budget, lesser renown and a lesser fan base and look at the games they produced.

Pokmon have the budget, the fan base and the means to make an amazing game. It's just a question of whether or not they can be bothered.

Also, the switch functioning as a handheld gives them an "out" to just give it the same graphics as they give their previous Pokmon games. 

I doubt if we see a Pokmon game that it'll be much different than existing Pokemon games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Synchronised Sealing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so shit. Kudos for (seemingly) handling it well, predators like this can sometimes make people feel trapped, scared and alone.

Hopefully this guy gets what's coming to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Papa smurf smurfed all over her! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also used the phrase "a pack of n*ggers".

Probably a regular old racist, too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 17:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if you live in a gun free house but some cunt comes over with an AK you're still fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate VFRs, it's like bowling with the gutters up. 

You may as well start every game with everyone announcing their role - where would the fun be in that?

I agree VFR is a valid town strategy, I just think it takes some of the fun away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now he's progressed to making girls his slave online.

You shouldn't have given him the fucking candy, Marie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has crazy eyes like from how I met your mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
