<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it. Got it. Thanks man :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohmagerddd . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh that makes sense. Thanks man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is M52 Use Field Spell Card 3 times in one duel bugged? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 08:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used fusion gate three times and then used a chaos zone field spell card three times as well and still didnt get it. Suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, all the duels I've done so far this card is the only one i've seen used to fish for the head piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Painful Escape onto a lvl 3 spellcaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Auto Duel PLZZZ!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heres a deck I made to make people triggered :D [Draw Deck](https://imgur.com/gallery/aphuA)  could use a BSG though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate when you equip Black Pendant then twister it in the same turn just to deal the 500 damage in auto duel. Makes no sense :p. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how it's not worth it to be honest. Not trying to be condescending but the only way to get more gems is to keep doing missions or pay up so there isn't really a choice if you want more gems :D. It gets harder to get them, the more packs you get the more variety in your deck you'll have and compared to where you are at now it won't seem to be all that harder. It's not like you have to face 3 mirror walls + 3 sphere koribohs every game like KC cup :^) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah they do, some run mirror wall, E-con, spirit kuribohs. One uses soul exchange to bring out a spellcaster 6 star that gets spell counters that adds attack for each spell card used, which is super annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it sucks :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk if my game is bugged but I had to play 60 games with dragons to clear the stage. Theres some fusion in there too, which seems to work for the mission if you do multiple in a single duel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's my Kaiba deck I used for M-51 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm stage 51 idk what you're talking about :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is everyone getting so many keys? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you guys farm NPC's to get the best out of it or is there any other way other than the card trader cause I used all my keys and I really wanna farm Odion but no luck :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [the fiend king](http://vignette3.wikia.nocookie.net/yugioh/images/f/f2/DarkRulerHaDes-BP01-EN-C-1E.png/revision/latest?cb=20120616113335)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HATE REX DECKS MAN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liberals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a zed sequence you might like idk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone got a good fusion deck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 01:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On mission 38. Hard to pull out fusion cards :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the principle of it. All my life i've done nice things for people and get taken advantage of for it. And now you want to belittle me for wanting recourse. It was $200 when i bought it, could sell it online for $150, it was Christmas and he wanted it for his son so i said he could pay me later, but he didn't. And you think i'm the asshole. Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this does make me feel less anxious that i dont have to resort to drastic measures. I'll look into this. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't own the receipt anymore i bought it a long time ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, i never have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do i do? Just keep asking nicely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zomg look what i pulled just now! :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 11:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I main fill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if you see a Muslim dude with a turban getting his ass kicked would you think to yourself, that poor guy is getting racially profiled and beaten up for no reason, OR would you think that he'd getting beat up because he's an affirmed terrorist. I wouldn't think twice about it, i would thank the guy for beating his ass. Don't come into the country looking like that. Go to Afghanistan with gay tight clothes and you'll get worse. Fuck off with your PC bullshit. Don't like the treatment? Take off your fucking hat you dodgey looking fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 09:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. "Good Connection" is 69m/s. Then it spikes to 300 every few seconds. Like idk wtf to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 09:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dang i thought there was a reset on it :( feelsbadman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you get a new account if you already have one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 09:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is true. When i was making another account i wanted to throw my computer out cause it was so boring. I would give advice to the NEW NEW guys like how to buy items, what to buy. And if someone asked me a question i would definitely help them. P3 Main </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 00:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clever. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
