<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1055</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off topic, but mods inserting their witty comments next to titles so everyone can see, just because they can, is my least favourite thing about Reddit. please stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some bands that make a tonne of effort to recreate their studio sounds in a live setting, with minimal use of backing tracks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't understand this - why would he be any less embarrassed at a later date? Surely this will just add fuel to the fire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope not, it'd feel more earned if it were every few weeks. Alec Baldwin's Trump is still entertaining but didn't feel as special when it was every week during the last few weeks of the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I can't stand her, Kellyanne Conway does a waaay better job at spinning everything than Spicer. There's probably a good reason that I don't know about but I was surprised she wasn't the obvious choice for Press Sec. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. This happens so often when a youtube personality gets into shit, like when that emo covers guy Austin Jones got caught trying to convince underage female fans to send him videos of them dancing sexually. Complete and utter sleazebag. He went quiet for a couple of weeks and then came out with an absolutely typical sad song that opened with a voiceover about how he tried to kill himself, and of course his female pre-teen fanbase completely bought it because they're young and impressionable. ughh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unbelievable. This is obviously one of the darkest events of this administration so far in terms of implications on children, and it seems like it's only going to get worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: On SNL (and similar shows) how is the live audience's laughing timed with the camera cuts we're seeing at home, when they can see everything happening on stage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 10:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always wondered this but an example is [the Sean Spicer sketch](https://youtu.be/UWuc18xISwI?t=416) at 6:57. When he gets hit with the water there's light laughs but a much bigger reaction when the camera cuts to Spicer with the super soaker, but wouldn't the crowd have been able to see him(her) with the super soaker before the camera cut to it because they could see the whole stage? Are they shown a screen with the camera cuts and told to laugh in time with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, you know, opinions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much. Whedon basically just told Jonah to play some better music because the girls wanted to dance, and Jonah joked "Don't you know? Girls only dance to shitty music, they don't like any cool music." He was obviously joking around but Whedon took it seriously and was outraged at how 'sexist' Jonah was, proceeded to shout at him and later tweet to all his followers that Jonah is a sexist pig. I like a lot of Joss's work, but if all that's true it really makes him out to be a huge ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pete Holmes' talk show was cancelled suddenly after 2 seasons. I found Pete's statement on this, about embracing gratitude in light of something that may feel like a failure, very inspiring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 21:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know which Hostful Jonah spoke about the 'DJ Jonah v Joss Whedon' incident on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was listening to old indoor kids episodes and this came up on an episode with Jonah and I think he mentioned that he spoke about it on a hostful aswell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoooooooooooly shit the sheer prospect of an Afterman II is the most exciting thing I've heard all week. Or maybe that's not at all on the cards and I just desperately want it to happen. claudio plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I check that sub every few days just to see how they react to things that are basically objectively awful on Trump's part, and of course they always just up the exclams and ridiculous phrases etc. I don't know why I do it, it's terribly depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 07:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that they're getting recognition here again, but I wish this weren't the only song posted, they have so many amazing ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 00:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that fast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the heavy reverb on Bill's voice in the MM podcast bother anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 14:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the show but it sounds awful. Not sure why it's there at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MAGIC - RUDE (post-hardcore remix) this kind of blew me away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 04:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually hate when people assume that someone's positive personality is fake, but Corden really seems like he's forcing how cheery and extroverted he is on that show compared to interviews from years ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the language that Tommy occasionally speaks to his family and the Lees speak in Season 1? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming they're the same language anyway. Is it some sort of Romanian Gypsy language? I'm still not even clear on whether the Shelbys are fully Gypsies or not but I guess if they're speaking the language they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John C. Reilly is about as far from the image I had in my head of Crepsley as you can get. The movie really captured 0% of the magic of the books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 05:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chill out. I get it. It was frustrating for a minute to have such trouble finding a podcast when most are available in so many places, and any other podcasts I like that are part of a larger network aren't monetized beyond sponsors, but I didn't think it was the end of the world. No need for the sarcasm onslaught.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really infuriating. They could at least remove the broken soundcloud links.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there anywhere at all I can hear the Farts and Procreation podcasts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 08:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SoundCloud Links on the website are all broken and they're not on iTunes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the set designers of 'Homeland' hired Arabic-speaking artists to decorate the set of a Syrian refugee camp with graffiti. Resentful of the show's depiction of Muslim Arabs, they spray-painted slogans such as "Homeland is racist" and "Homeland is a joke", which made it on to the show. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 05:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does using Charisma to ask for payment on quests affect how the quest giver will treat you in future? (Fallout 4) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically in relation to Fire Support (which leads into Call to Arms). It's only a small thing but there's a Charisma skill option to request payment in helping Paladin Danse and the Brotherhood of Steele. I did and he seemed annoyed but agreed to pay for help. Does using this option and succeeding in securing payment affect how Danse will speak to you in future in a negative way at all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 10:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand a lot of the posts getting to the top recently. This is not a showerthought, it's just a relatable thought that a lot of people think but haven't written down anywhere or shared. Weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 01:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just came home from seeing it. I knew going in that she'd be in it so I was ready, but god it was tough. It's a perfect final line for Leia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S2 Spoilers] Does the teen romance sub plot make parts of Season 2 unbearable for anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 05:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly it is so outside of the tone of the rest of the show, and just generally (imo) cringy and awful. It wasn't present at all in the first season (very mildly with Xander I guess) and it was much better for it. I genuinely just fast forward over the Dana/Finn scenes now, they feel like really poorly written scenes from a John Green book. The ordeal of sorting out the hit and run was interesting but the proceeding romance was just terrible. Or maybe I'm just a grumpy old man that hates love, I don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, how do I check that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Reaper recognizes it as a MIDI input, but when I enable it and then close the window, it says 'the following MIDI inputs could not be opened; USB2MIDI' (the keyboard) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I go to 'input devices' in Sibelius preferences, it recognizes a USB MIDI keyboard, but doesn't pick up anything in the sensor bar when I press the keys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate to ask such an obvious question, but I'm at a loss as to how to get my keyboard connected to my computer via MIDI or USB. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a stage piano with MIDI outputs (Kawai MP4), had been wanting to hook it up to use with Sibelius and Reaper for a while but hadn't a clue how. Asked in music shop and was told to get a USB to MIDI adapter (it's just a usb on one end to go in the computer with MIDI on the other to go to instrument, no kind of interface in between) and that that'd work, but it's not being recognized. I just can't find a straight answer as to whether I need to buy an audio interface to put in between it or if it can work directly in from the keyboard. At the MIDI end of the lead  there's a split with one midi (male) marked MIDI IN and another marked MIDI OUT. Do I just plug the OUT one into the midi out socket on my keyboard? Or both in to the in and out? 

Sorry again for the stupid questions. Just frustrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 07:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. Reddit wants to project this drama of a man destroyed by an evil woman so desperately that it's honestly just getting annoying. Of course she is awful for taking all of this from him but none of us really know what this guy is thinking or going through besides all that so I wish people would stop acting like they're inside his head or helping a fallen hero through a tragedy. I'll get downvoted to hell but god, it's annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Notating grace notes, particularly for vocals/a scat solo; should the grace note have a slash through it or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never notated a scat solo before but have to do one now, not sure which of [these](http://www.notation.com/ComposerDocs3/gracenotestemandnotestem.gif) is the right grace note to use, visually. Or if it even matters really. Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just noticed them along with a red and blue one, honestly had no idea that was a sound output but working perfectly now. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Jackson, 1982 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 00:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, get you - so if you were marking the key down next to the song name on a setlist, you'd write 'D Dorian'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you're saying, but I don't understand how it's more accurate on a practical level to say it's in D minor if the scale of D minor, or that of its relative major F, won't work at all over the song. After hearing just one round of the progression, the D minor (if we're thinking in that key, I know the original is in a different key) always sounds like 2 to my ears, and never like 1, so I think that's enough reason to say it's A minor. 

But this is all open to interpretation I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Michael Scott </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Thanks for the feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, labeling it F dorian seems like an attempt to simplify it that would only end up complicating it to no end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, thanks again. If you're interested in chiming in there seems to be a lot of support for the contrary argument [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/WeAreTheMusicMakers/comments/58dpot/question_on_key_centers_and_correct_labeling_of/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agh, you just put into words the perfect argument I was trying to grasp to back my point up in the room today. Thanks for the feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I should have thought of the running the F minor scale thing on the spot, could have clarified his stance a bit more. Like it seems crazy to me to label that song as F minor, because if someone's busking it, they'll think it's going 65 (if you're calling the chords as in the relative major Ab) rather than 21 for the verse and that's just disastrous. That's great feedback, thanks, I'm a bit confused now though since I just got another good answer claiming the bass player was totally right on /r/musictheory, but appreciate all the info nonetheless. music theory bein weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that clarifies a lot! So if you were writing out a setlist with the keys of each written next to each song title, you'd call this 'Fm Dorian'? Or just Fm? Just thinking in terms of what would be most easily digestible for a musician seeing it at a gig for example. And if you were writing out the parts, would you place the key signature as F minor even though there would inevitably be more accidentals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question on key centers and correct labeling of keys for songs with chord progressions that don't centre around the root. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I was talking about a song with a band I'm playing with in college, and the song starts on Chord 2 (i.e. if we're in the key of Eb, it starts on F minor). [This is the song](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Y6Nne8RvaA), the progression for the verses and choruses is mostly just 212121 etc. The bass player asked what key it was, and the guitarist told him it was F minor. I assumed he said that because it's the first chord and you'd instinctually think that'd be the key without putting much thought into it, but I mentioned that it was actually Eb or its relative C minor, since it starts on Chord 2 which isn't the root. I only corrected it because obviously F minor and C minor don't share the exact same notes so there'd inevitably be some weirdness going on if one or two of us were thinking in F minor and others in C minor. The bass player told me I was incorrect, and that the key isn't Eb or C minor, that I shouldn't base what I refer to as the key on what the key signature would be on paper. He said the 'key center' for most of the song was the F minor, so the key is F minor or 'F dorian'. Honestly I had never heard about this way of labeling (idk the proper word) a key before, I'm only in second year of my degree and gigging on a professional level for a few months, but this guy has had way more experience MDing in the past and knows his stuff so I didn't tell him he was wrong. Just wondered what others think, I could be very wrong but I just want to know.


Another example of a similar song whose key I thought was labelled incorrectly really often is Get Lucky. The progression is just 2465 i.e. DmFAmG if we're in C major. I would have said the key is C or A minor and it just starts on Dorian/2, but whenever I'd see the key next to the song name on a setlist it'd always just be down as the first chord in the song i.e. Dm and I'd feel the need to correct it.


**TL;DR**: if a song starts on and seems based around a chord that isn't the root or its relative minor, do you still call the root note the key, or do you go by the most frequent chord/'key centre'?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question on key centers and correct labeling of keys for songs with certain progressions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this is the wrong sub - 

Today I was talking about a song with a band I'm playing with in college, and the song starts on Chord 2 (i.e. if we're in the key of Eb, it starts on F minor). [This is the song](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Y6Nne8RvaA), the progression for the verses and choruses is mostly just 212121 etc. The bass player asked what key it was, and the guitarist told him it was F minor. I assumed he said that because it's the first chord and you'd instinctually think that'd be the key without putting much thought into it, but I mentioned that it was actually Eb or its relative C minor, since it starts on Chord 2 which isn't the root. I only corrected it because obviously F minor and C minor don't share the exact same notes so there'd inevitably be some weirdness going on if one or two of us were thinking in F minor and others in C minor. The bass player told me I was incorrect, and that the key isn't Eb or C minor, that I shouldn't base what I refer to as the key on what the key signature would be on paper. He said the 'key center' for most of the song was the F minor, so the key is F minor or 'F dorian'. Honestly I had never heard about this way of labeling (idk the proper word) a key before, I'm only in second year of my degree and gigging on a professional level for a few months, but this guy has had way more experience MDing in the past and knows his stuff so I didn't tell him he was wrong. Just wondered what others think. 

Another example of a similar song that I always thought was labelled wrong is Get Lucky. The progression is just 2465 i.e. DmFAmG if we're in C major. I would have said the key is C or A minor and it just starts on Dorian/2, but whenever I'd see the key next to the song name on a setlist it'd always just be down as the first chord in the song i.e. Dm and I'd feel the need to correct it.



**TL;DR**: if a song starts on and seems based around a chord that isn't the root or its relative minor, do you still call the root note the key, or do you go by the most frequent chord/'key centre'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I just wanted to confess before you guys find out from someone else." But the whole reason he's done this response is because everyone found out from somebody else? How fucking noble he is. There is exactly 0 chance he would ever confess to anything like this unless caught with undeniable evidence. ugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 02:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely amazing. 

Might be a bit nitpicky but I wish the monitor brightness would be turned down a lot, the camera readjusting its brightness/exposure(you know what I mean) every time it goes between Ethan and the camera is really jarring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 18:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearing Jon Hamm in White Christmas didn't feel out of place for me at all. I think as long as the tone and aesthetic of the show stays intact, nothing should feel too jarring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Howard Shore, best known for scoring the Lord of the Rings trilogy, was the original musical director for the Saturday Night Live band from 1975-1980, appeared in many sketches, and suggested the name The Blues Brothers to Dan Aykroyd and John Belushi. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 00:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 00:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite. (also double negative hah) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate these condescending types of comments so much. Please stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 19:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok. Always thought this sub was a nice contrast to the shitstorm of hatred that the Nigri sub has become because of Patreon drama, so it sucks to see a bit of that happening (patreon drama I mean, not hatred), but I'm sure it won't ever get that bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry to be 'that guy', but I'm completely out of the loop and just curious what's happened. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 19:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing all these posts in response to this drama but I honestly can't figure out what exactly happened. I'm stupid, apologies. Can anyone TLDR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 18:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gone With The Wind. 

"The weight of the world is resting on thin ice. When the surface breaks will I find paradise? As I freeze to death, left to reflect what a waste of time I was, in retrospect.
Id take a leap of faith, but Id lose my nerve. In the end, Ill get the hell that I deserve.

Im always gone with the wind, crawling in and out of my mind. God knows, I've lost all my faith.

**A sickness with no remedy, except the ones inside of me.
You ever wonder how deep you can sink into nothing at all?**
Disintegrate. Annihilate me.

Do you remember when you said to me,
My friend, hope is a prison.
Hope is a prison.

Of all the patterns that I could create, I built a labyrinth with no escape, to keep my self under lock and key. I am my own worst enemy.

**If I could silence all the doubt in me, accept that what is meant to be (Is meant to be).
You ever wonder how deep you can sink into nothing at all?**
Disintegrate. Annihilate me."

Do you remember when you said to me,
My friend, hope is a prison.

I'm glad that Tom had such a powerful platform to express his feelings and thoughts about his death. This reminds me of the way Bowie confronted his death with Blackstar. This is all terrible and I'm in shock. 

Rest In Peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billie Black - I Don't Need Another Lover [neo-soul] (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 17:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you implying American Sniper got away with the plastic baby? I heard that talked about more than any other part of the movie honestly, I don't think they got away with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're being needlessly harsh. Dirk is not a hugely popular property these days and there isn't tonnes of star power in the shower or anything so of course they aren't going to be given a huge budget to work with, it's not Max's fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Has he ever made a good movie"

Whether any movie (final product) he's credited on is good is a matter of opinion, but he doesn't make movies. He makes scripts, and some of them that are online are pretty universally loved. Judging a whole movie on the screenwriter's input is ignorant and stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I never knew that! I think if they really had no budget, they could have done a lot worse than that episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? If it were at all associated with a studio it'd probably be recorded with a better camera and more professionally. Max makes videos like this all the time, it's just him, and even if it were viral marketing (which it isn't) who the hell cares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you follow him on social media there's been a lot of other things he's talked about that changes have had to be made for (weather, location suddenly unavailable, certain crew etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently it was really loose and didn't adapt the best elements of the book or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I'm sure someone brings that up to him nearly every day. You're not achieving anything, you're just being an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually use an Android app called Snapseed. It's really amazing for editing on your phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ITAP from a ferris wheel of Grand Parade, Cork City, Ireland. (Messing around with some selective colouring lately) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 10:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Messing around with selective colouring lately. (Grand Parade, Cork City, Ireland) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not actually Max here but I'm sure he'll see your comment since he checks posts related to him sometimes I think! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first song I listened to off the Sound City soundtrack and I got so hyped for the rest of the album thinking every song would be of similar quality. Was pretty let down by most of the songs. (not because they were different styles, they were just boring in general imo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, I'd never seen that, I'm blown away. Seeing all those characters and scenes in Fox Engine is amazing. I'd love if Koj made CGI movies like these for the other games too, particularly MGS1 and an updated and modern interpretation of Metal Gear 1 and 2 (maybe skip MGS2 and 4, 2 is just the weakest story and 4 already looks really good). But yeah, it wouldn't fully capture the magic of playing through the games. Would be awesome nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this really fascinating because it's just something you never really consider as a possible factor when something bad or nonsensical happens in a good show. It's always assumed it's just a blunder in writing or effects etc., but I can kind of see now that this production-altering-story sort of thing could have play a role in a lot of what might've been considered bad parts of great shows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Max Landis, showrunner and head writer on the upcoming TV adaption of Douglas Adams' Dirk Gently, demonstrates how drastically key elements of a show sometimes have to be changed to suit sudden changes and shortcomings in production. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 09:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 03:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pete's podcast YMIW is absolutely hilarious sometimes, some of my favourites have been the three episodes with Chelsea Peretti, she's absolutely vicious to him and it's amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racist Stephen Hawking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MGSV Spoilers] If having the game be linear like MGS4 and not open world meant more cutscenes and focus on story, do you think it would ultimately be better for it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 08:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just been thinking about this since I finished it the other day (I was very late to the party, but wanted to wait until I had time to completely sink into the game). The gameplay was the best I've maybe ever played, all the complex systems were woven together amazingly, and the open world was a large part of it, but I think I would let that suffer if it meant more cutscenes and tighter story telling. 

Another idea could have been to just release Chapter 1: Revenge, and then a year or two later release a fully completed Chapter 2 (or 3, if there was ever an intention to make one, which evidence suggests there was).

(I'll just say my random thoughts on the game as a whole here in case anyone cares to read them as I have no one to discuss it with right now, ignore if you want). 

Overall it was a perfect **gaming** experience, and I truly think that in terms of pure gameplay (i.e. every part of MGS that isn't story), Kojima achieved everything he set out to when he made those claims early in development that this would be his masterpiece and the pinnacle of his career. I (like most it seems) felt differently about the story. I went in determined to finish the game adoring the story as much as I did that of 1, 3 and 4, and not agreeing with any of the criticisms I'd heard, but I just didn't feel that way when the final credits rolled (partially because I didn't even know if they were the final credits, and only realised when no Chapter 51 popped up). It had a few incredibly poignant and powerful moments, but it was overall sparse and disappointing in my opinion. It was bizarre, but not in a good MGS-bizarre way. Not Otacon peeing his pants in MGS1 bizarre, not Volgin's kink for General Raiden in MGS3, more just bizarre in that it kept trying to push Skull Face as something beyond a painfully shallow and cliche villain for an MGS game, whose big master weapon felt like a joke with no real weight to it. The parasites didn't feel any more threatening after listening to Code Talker ramble on the cassette tapes for two hours or so. It was heartbreaking to see how much the game fell apart after the end of Chapter 1. Seeing that of the 19 or so new missions that would come, only 6 were actually new kind of sucked. The recycled early missions with extra difficulty should be an extra option for those seeking an extra challenge, and not numbered chapters in the main story. I wish only the 6 new missions would have been left in, even if it left the game feeling shorter. Also, the way arguably the most important story mission (Escape the Hospital again) just sort of pops up without any fan fair felt weird, and the fact that when it's over there's nothing telling you that the game is definitely over felt weird too. I played for hours after beating the remaining recycled missions waiting for something more, some resolution to Eli's escape, some news on the real Big Boss, anything. 

For what it's worth though, I did like the twist after thinking about it, it was really the most powerful way to convey the message of Big Boss as a symbol and a meme, rather than a man. It's hinted at early on in Ocelot's conversations about how the story of Mother Base's destruction had gotten blown out of proportion, BB dying a martyr for a cause etc. The Phantom twist illustrated that point beautifully, and though it sucks to know that the whole time I wasn't playing as the Snake from MGS3 and Peace Walker, and just some random medic who had some hypnosis and some stunningly good plastic surgery for the early 70s (not to mention a luckily similar voice to BB), I feel like without it the story really would just have zero redeeming features. 

Some other random points;

- Ocelot doing literally nothing interesting other than the horse chase at the start was so disappointing. We didn't see him in action once, and that's one of the things I was looking forward to most. I wanted to see him kick ass on the field, not just bicker with Kaz back at base and show off his extensive knowledge of the plants of Afghanistan. 

- A deeper backstory on the "Medic" would have been nice and added a lot. Thought I like the twist, it's uncomfortable to know that the guy I've been playing as was probably some random that I fultoned during Peace Walker who just happened to be on the chopper with Paz and BB. In the cassette tape after the twist drops, BB asks the Phantom, "Do you remember now, who you really are? Your past?" I found it bizarre that this wasn't a cue for some backstory, but maybe that's asking for too much. It felt a bit like Darth Vader turning out to be Luke's uncle and not his father.  

- I think there should have been more about what the real BB had been up to since waking up, rather than a sentence or two alluding to him conducting a covert war on Cipher. How can they say that and then just leave us hanging? Of course we're going to want to know every detail about what he's been up to. 

- I know it's probably a bit immature to want it, but considering Liquid's presence in the game, seeing Solid Snake/ David would have added so much to the story for me. I know he got a mention in a couple of cassette tapes, but it's not the same, and I'm sure he could've been tied in somehow. Kojima's definitely no stranger to fan service so I don't know why he got no screen time. 

- There was so much buzz about Kojima wanting to explore taboo themes in this, and Ground Zeroes accomplished this with the child torture, the brutal stomach bomb removal from Paz, etc. Having played TPP, it feels very run of the mill and not as if it's breaking any new ground. It did in parts with the child soldiers, but there were scenes involving them in the trailers that weren't in the final game so I can only imagine many of those plot elements were cut (which would also help explain Chapter 2: Race barely exploring Race at all.)

- I really loved Kiefer as BB/ Venom Snake, if they were just looking for a less cartoonish David Hayter, they found the perfect guy. He sounded subdued and defeated but also strong with hints of the Snake we know. I didn't mind at all that Snake didn't talk much. I just think it was a missed opportunity to add to the big twist (obviously BB in Ground Zeroes being voiced by Kiefer nullifies this). Having Kiefer voice Venom the whole game, and then when the real BB is shown talking to Ocelot outside the hospital in the end, it's David Hayter. This could have maybe worked if he'd muffled his voice at the start, or the player's hearing was damaged so could only barely making out Ishmael's voice, etc. But I don't know, that's probably just me being too desperate to squeeze Hayter in somewhere.

- Huey was just bizarre in this game and had no character arc. The first thing we hear about him is "Huey popped up here, we think he was involved in the incident 9 years ago but he'll say he's not.". And that's Huey's entire storyline. And his cries of shame as Snake was forced to kill his men in the Quarantine lab were just irritating since it would've been blatantly obvious that Snake was doing it to save many more. Having Huey do that felt like a cheap and unnecessary way to make the player feel conflicted about BB's actions, when I already felt the emotional weight of it before it was dragged down a bit by Huey's cries. 

- Another couple of immature fan servicey things, but confirmation on The Third Boy being Psycho Mantis would've been nice (I know it's probably definite but I mean 100% confirmation), and Quiet turning out to be young Sniper Wolf would have been cool too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been reading about Ep. 781 but can't find it online at all, anyone know where I can find it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 16:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't find it on Podcast Addict either, honestly just curious at this stage because everyone's saying it's the cringiest thing ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
