<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4227</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most farm jobs pay $10 an hr. So that's a raise of $2.75. But you're right most Americans would not do hard labor at those rates but these are the rates that keep your produce cheap.

Ok maybe lazy wasnt the right word. Americans think they are too good for these jobs. 

https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2011-11-09/why-americans-wont-do-dirty-jobs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, for a typical seasonal farm worker, a 40 percent wage increase could raise earnings from $10,000 for 1,000 hours of work to $14,000  lifting the wage above the federal poverty line.

Ok I know we were discussing prices at supermarkets but I'm going to look at this a different way. What would be the price in the supermarket if we offered livable wages on farms since that is the only way you will get Americans working there.

I'm going to use Texas for my example as Texas contains the most farms for any state in the U.S. The livable wage in Texas is $10.67 ( Source: http://livingwage.mit.edu/states/48 ) (assuming 2080 working hours). But farms are seasonal. Using the above of 1000 hours, the per hour rate to reach the living wage would be $21.77. 

But that's assuming they only have 1 job. Ok lets backtrack and use the 14k from this 40% raise and assume this person picked up another job for the 1080 hours that they were not working on this farm. At minimum wage of $7.25 they would make $7830 if we add this to the 14k from before you end up with $21,830 which is still $363.60 short of living wages. And mind you this is all assuming you're only providing for 1 person.

Now for your price at the supermarket if we assume that you're getting paid living wages from the farm ($21.77) and that is your only job. From the original mark of $10.07 (avg pay from article)
this is a 116% wage increase. The 10 cent farm labor becomes 22 cents and the $1 apple becomes $1.22. 

This is all considering 1 adult trying to make a living. Add a wife who may or may not have a job or add a kid in the mix and this person is right back under the living wage. To top it all off what is being asked is 1000 hours of back breaking work.
 

Edit: Numbers Are Tricky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what I am trying to say about how illegal immigration suppresses wages for the working class.

Those low wages keep everyone from paying ridiculous prices at the supermarket for fruit and vegetables. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you need to have illegal workers to keep your farm afloat, maybe it needs to go under.

Following this most U.S farms would go under. Then when you go to your supermarket you will have 2 options.

Fruits and vegetables covered in pesticides. or Extremely expensive fruits and vegetables.

Our country would be screwed without illegal immigrants picking our food. These are back breaking jobs and honestly America has become too lazy to do it ourselves.

I'm sure the migrant workers are more loyal and work harder. They don't have a choice.

They absolutely have a choice. They came to work here. No one is forcing these people. They just saw a way to better their lives and are taking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He won because half of our voting age population didnt even bother to vote. Illegal immigrants per populace have committed significantly less crimes than U.S born citizens. Sorce: http://www.nber.org/papers/w13229.pdf

This dispute he has raised against illegal immigrants is much like hitler did with jews in the early term of his leadership. He is reaching out to the poorest of our country and telling them that this populace of people is responsible for their hardships when that is demonstrably false. Trump even took a page from hitlers book and decided to compile a list of crimes from his targeted populace and print it out.

But you are right he does represent a sect of our current state as a society and nation but it is not a representation that we should be proud of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. It's not free money.
2. Yes. If you actively use a law that you call unamerican but claim yourself as a true american you are a hypocrite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No hate on duck duck go. They're a very useful site. I just find it funny that right after Trump signs a bill to allow sites to sell your internet history the trolls over at t_d suddenly get angry at google and start promoting a more protective site like ddg. Yet they still wont admit that Trump has done anything wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesnt solve the problem of some votes being pointless. (Democrat in Alabama) or (Republican in California) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so I'm not sure how a second layer of abstraction allows for a more equal voice than everyones vote simply counting for 1. And below that you listed a bunch of faults in the system.... You might need that flamethrower.

Doesn't it just seem easier to make everyones vote count for 1 and just do populist wins. The low population centers still end up with representatives to send to the house and congress to represent their needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok.... That's how it was implemented... That does not state one point as to what purpose it serves now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that plan is to become more self reliant and not be held hostage by another country

I honestly dont think that is possible. The U.S has always been a consumer country and we are remarkably good at it. We like to buy and we like to buy cheap. Becoming self reliant would require us to stop the consumer culture and I really don't see that happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What purpose does it serve that could not be completed without it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep dreaming. All they know is Breitbart, Info wars and Duck Duck go. USA Today is wayyyyy outside their spectrum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah he claims he didn't know Bannon before this. 

https://www.nytimes.com/2017/04/12/us/politics/trump-steven-bannon-fox-business-news-interview.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  plutocratic kakistocracy

That has to be the best way I've seen to describe our situation. Its frustrating to see how many people voted for him believing that he was the change we needed. Its like lady liberty got into an abusive relationship but we cant just leave because some of our population still want to give him a chance.

it seems as if your democracy is slowly turning into a banana republic.

Yep. The propaganda waves have been hitting us strong. Even our fact checking websites have now been declared liberal media by these Trump supporters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up you Cassiopia main.

Edit: I'm retarded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bane did it better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk I might prefer bane as president over trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait.... isn't congress going on break? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Average US citizens memory concerning bombings is 2-2.5 years unless its done against us then we never forget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DO NOT PAY ATTENTION TO THE MAN BEHIND THE CURTAIN - Putin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's as if the act of running a country is a 24/7 job.

Who would of known running a country would be so difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was referring to his personal lodging and meals.

EXACTLY! Every weekend "vaca" he takes he's literally putting more money into his pockets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but he's only traveling to his own resorts so no lodging or meal expenses and I doubt he's counting these as a vaca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but when he travels to his own resort what does he end up paying? Ik that airforce 1 and secret service are covered by tax dollars + Most of his vacations to Florida he's counting as "working" trips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in this instance is that they're attacking an education system that is already underfunded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
