<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6932</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going for a different word. Pretty sure it starts with a 'c'. When people conspire, what is that called? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They keep posting that twitter video of an envelope with multiple Macron ballots, which is both maybe the easiest thing to fake ever if you have two french people and completely inconsequential because unless you request to vote by mail (which isn't really a thing in France for some reason, but then again they vote on the weekends so it doesn't matter quite as much) you use the ballots provided at the polling station. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seemingly unbothered that Trump endorsed Le Pen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wikileaks is not neutral anymore. And I'm not sure how they have any more authority on the issue than anyone else, seeing as they weren't even the original host. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how that proves the documents are real; if anything it furthers the idea that they're fake, or at the very least the story around them is fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit I just realized that dogecoin could be the basis of a literal meme economy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd be compressed the same way though. Besides, if he did show us the real ones people would just accuse him of leaving out the ones that were made up. If I post a message that looks like it's from you and claim it to be real, you turning over every real message isn't going to prove anything because I'll just say you left out the one I showed.

Edit: [proof](https://i.imgur.com/z7ZgoXA.png) that /u/rodental is involved in this and until he turns over all of his messages this is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a long one for Neil too. The landing was so soft that the shocks didn't compress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruh girly deodorant is the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I see. Is that not advisable?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo, /u/DeLaNope can I get a quick analysis of what went wrong here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well only just. Yeah they got their budget passed without really having to work too hard but the Democrats aren't technically in charge. But you're generally right; the adults in the room are governing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Honhonhonhonhonhonhonhonhonhon* s'il vous plat. Ceci est un subreddit francophone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They seem to have given up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> En: HAHAHAHAHAHA

Fr: HONHONHONHONHONHON </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  La stylo est bonne.

Le kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The picture is of a salt factory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #KEEP

#CALM

AND

#CHIVE

#ON </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  never this doc is fake and here's the proof.

Hey, this doc is fake and [here's the proof](http://observers.france24.com/en/20170505-france-elections-macron-lepen-offshore-bahamas-debunked) (the article title is crap though). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bbbb but the polls are rigged aren't they? What happened to muh 95% confidence that isn't the same thing as a +3% poll that definitely isn't he same as a +22% poll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dans mon pays ils ont gagn. 

Et ce n'est pas li, mais si quelqu'un a besoin d'un epoux je suis disponsable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oui, vraiment ils sont inspecteurs comme Jacque Clouseau.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mais non. Ils m'ont assur que tout le monde franais parle de a. C'est pourquoi le sujet est en haut des subreddits at sites anglophones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why sure, your real history is in there right next to it.

Why is is so difficult to believe that someone planted fake evidence in with real emails? People have been caught doing the same thing at physical crime scenes before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that have to do with this? I made a claim and provided something that shows it's true. It's on the person the claim is about to release everything to disprove it.

(Obviously this isn't true; that screenshot is faked. I'm making the point that the argument is ridiculous.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was replying to my comment with the picture and then realized it made more sense just to put it in my original comment. Hit save instead of cancel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really beyond belief that these are fake? The whole world is out to secretly get Le Pen with fake ballots or whatever the story is now, but nobody could possibly be out to get Macron? Your only activity is pushing this story, by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an opium importer. You have a friend who launders your money to make the sale untraceable. Until you release all your messages to disprove my claim I'm correct; and then I'm going to say that I'm still correct because you obviously just released the messages that weren't related to that.

edit: [my proof](https://i.imgur.com/spBWVuV.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird how evidence of a conspiracy is being so heavily downvoted. It's almost like there's some group of people that don't want this seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some documents in Macron leak appear to be fabricated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so easily faked though, and from someone with an obvious motive to do so.

And French voters don't use those informational ballots; they pick up ballots at the polling stations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a bunch of people came together to collectively lie in an attempt to influence the world around them. There's a word for that, isn't there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cryptocurrency based on a meme managed to sponsor a NASCAR team. The future is weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen buddy.

Listen CHAMP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say that. They're pointing out that this sub is being obviously manipulated, and people are swallowing it because this sub is dominated by people who blame everything on the globalists or the liberals or what have you and never stop to think if they're being used by the people they support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most likely scenario. Given the way the school handled it, someone probably told them that the kid was making some sort of threat and the school acted before they had all the information (which is unfortunately what they have to do). Once they had everything they dropped it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It shows an agenda sure, but that doesn't mean that it must be a dummy account. Ordinary people have agendas too. And what they said was true; the Macron stuff is being pushed by brand new accounts with clear agendas, all created at the same time and using basically the same language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They admitted to it you dumbass. God Paul Ryan is such a slimy shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still doesn't invalidate their claims.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I see now why he's banned from Ukraine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that means that McCain is going to vote for the Senate bill before it gets a CBO score. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not answering the question: are [these women](https://imgur.com/a/dMpqb) really men? Or maybe do they know better than you and they're really women? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. Okay then. That said, their claims were entirely accurate. The accounts pushing the Macron emails are mostly brand new and offering little of substance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And their claims aren't valid? Not that I can see them now because they've been removed, which sort of furthers my point that this sub is biased as shit even on the mod level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because he don't drop character till he doin that DVD commentary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is somewhat ruined by youtube compression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. She was a woman. You wouldn't go up to [these women](https://imgur.com/a/dMpqb) and say "um ackchyually you're a man," because that would be idiotic (and just generally rude). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what they thought in 2007/2008, but it didn't work at all. Banks didn't have the confidence to loan out the money so they just sat on big cash reserves and the economy stagnated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really not an achievement, it's community college for christsakes.

This attitude is so dumb. If you actually bother to put the work in and not treat it like a daycare, community college is just as good as any other college; you get the same degree and the same experience.

then again I'm retarded

Well I wasn't gonna say it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you give a poor person an extra $100, they spend almost all of it. Give a rich person that same $100 and they save almost all of it. Raising the minimum wage impacts poorer people most, which means that they start buying more. There's a limit to this, obviously, because eventually you hit diminishing returns, but it's a pretty effective stimulus, especially when minimum wage is so far behind inflation as it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the problem is he's trying to make exactly the same show he used to make, but with more complex and adult topics. And that format doesn't quite work as well for adults; the song and dance and whacky visuals are kind of cringy, but objectively so was the original show. It just didn't matter because it was aimed at a younger audience (that was usually at school so anything was preferable to a normal class). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy was actually the catcher. He just let go at the wrong time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you just walk the guy if you don't want him to land a hit. It's a bitch move, the intentional walk, but you don't hit a player deliberately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the scrimmage line was a really difficult technical achievement when they first made it, because it had to accommodate different color uniforms, different shades of turf, and different weather conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but that's realistic because reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit none of that works at all. The hacking doesn't work like that, the laptop dangling from the cable like that doesn't work like that, the roof on the car doesn't work like that, changing gears doesn't work like that because you have him go through more gears than the car has, changing gears doesn't work like that because you clearly show both hands on the wheel during a gear change but also show a clutch pedal in the footwell shots, the car could not possibly have gone fast enough to catch that aircraft, certainly not at anything less than top speed, the car wouldn't have enough torque to break the tires loose at near top speed, the plane would not survive a collision with the tower and keep flying, the car wouldn't have enough braking force to stop in time, and to top it off sliding sideways would make the car take longer to stop.

Yeah, Scorpion won that little game.

Edit: Oh, and they wouldn't have had enough runway to do that. At the stall speed of a jet that size (which the car could conceivably reach), you'd need a 7km runway to fly for the 120 seconds in this video. The longest runway in the world is only 5.5km. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that before or after Mama Diablo was kicked out in the Great Mod Fuckery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's no spaghetti, but it's pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The little squealing sound that you get from some audio systems when they should be silent. Drives me batty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the 40+ woman's KEEP CALM AND CARRY ON. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny when it's funny though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's something about [Too Young For Tragedy](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1xpbYoYZTzg) that just *gets* me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally made an account just to log in just to click on this just to upvote:

#*This.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard rumors that they do that shit on purpose. They try to out-stupid other writers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Did they really need the pickup shot?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watched that scene again. God that baby looks so fake. Could they not get an actual baby for that scene? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think it's suspicious that the userbase here seems to accept just about anything that demonizes people that they hate regardless of what (if any) evidence is provided (though that's kind of a normal human trait). There's such an overlap with T_D, which constantly votes up things that just aren't true, and are demonstrably untrue, and disallows any kind of dissent. And as another user here has pointed out, it's pretty obvious when this sub is being used to push a narrative (the Macron emails are being pushed by a bunch of brand new accounts) but the users who supposedly are aware of when a conspiracy is afoot never seem to notice if they like that narrative (again, kind of normal human behavior but it's so clearly partisan and manipulated).

I'm not sure if that made much sense; I'm just kind of tired of pointing this out and getting shouted down (even though someone saying that Soros and co are flooding this sub with liberal shills never gets the same sort of skepticism). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub gives almost exclusive weight to right-wing conspiracy theories, regardless of any evidence or how many times the same thing has been posted. And for what is supposedly an apolitical place, you'd think there would be less obvious political bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look it's either death or the newest iPhone, I think that should be an obvious choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying that this sub will run with what is clearly a politically motivated smear that follows a presupposed conclusion to any "evidence" rather than following evidence to a conclusion. But it will only do that when it implicates certain people, namely anyone politically left of Tony Blair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, an actual criminal conspiracy? I'm amazed this isn't way higher up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, edgy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their account is four years old. Not sure where you're getting 90 days from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would they be able to verify that? Unless they have access to the originals they'd have no way of knowing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pizza place with a logo that vaguely looks like a butterfly is enough to convince plenty of people on this sub that they're secretly at the center of a ring of pedophilia that only ever involves people that have spoken out against Donald Trump, but a candidate openly funded by a government that has been implicated in attempts to sway foreign elections as well as their own makes mention of something nefarious that just so happens to be in the leaks dropped shortly after doesn't warrant *any* suspicion at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watches. I don't drop obscene money on my collection, but I've got nine right now and realistically that's about eight more than I really need. But I'm not big on jewelry otherwise and I really appreciate the engineering that goes into them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus Indy seems to have a thing for any woman with a pulse. That first kiss between them was so bad; *YOU DON"T LIKE EACH OTHER DAMMIT!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real, I think Temple of Doom is really the worst Indiana Jones movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that kind of just leaves the "insecure about your sexuality" option. Again, weird but it's your choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey had a dream you jumped out of my closet an held me down on my bed while screaming. Now my divorce doesn't seem so bad in hindsight. Thanks penis-nosed monster! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so a link or two should be easy to produce. What sneaky gay shenanigans are in store now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that you seem to think that trans people all love to trick people into sex means that you seem to think that you can't actually always tell trans people from cis people.

And the fact that you say it doesn't matter what someone looks like; you're not attracted if they're trans means that you *choose* to not be attracted to someone, even if your initial impression might be that you are. That kinda comes across as insecure about your sexuality unless you only ever hook up with someone with the intent of having children, which would be weird but hey that's your choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, even better then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama is a private citizen. He's not Potus anymore; he served both his terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You quite confidently called them trans earlier.

1,2,4 Adams apples would give them away instantly

So which is it? It's super easy to tell or you actually can't tell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they have this magic (R) that follows them around that tells the other (R)s to make up any bullshit to justify their actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely would never be romantically involved with any if them because they are biologically male. It's not like being male is my only deal breaker

But it's not one you seem particularly good at identifying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that was just one blade, it would be kinda cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/gkpDykV.jpg

https://i.imgur.com/Cwg6t7Q.jpg

Happy now? What says she's different from any other woman? [](https://archive.fo/yrBju)

Edit: and while we're at it, what makes you think [these men](https://imgur.com/a/75JZb) are any different from any other men? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to just be making fun of people who claimed they were cats or got overly upset about a TV character being straight but then at some point it turned into just hating on anyone who thinks that racism or sexism or homophobia still exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not seeing an Adam's apple on any of those women. Especially on that last woman; her chin would be in the way anyway from that angle. I don't see one on [this girl](https://i.imgur.com/VK42edL.jpg) either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, do enlighten me on how you know this woman better than she did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda reminds me of [this guy](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=izTK9fnZOY0) but if he was absolutely insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Wait, so nipples have orgasms?" Okay, guess I better buckle up for this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little column A, little column B. It's definitely a different place now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at her eyes right at the start of the video. She's on something for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to say something to justify voting party line, and you can't very well say "I'm being bankrolled by people who couldn't care less if your children die and I'm too much of a coward to defy my party" so you have to just make stuff up instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's such a stretch that they would do something nefarious in order to benefit a candidate that they're bankrolling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you can tell so perfectly? What gives [these women](https://imgur.com/a/dMpqb) away then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. At some point the whole "no politics" thing went out the window and it just became a slightly more civilized dumping ground for T_D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am shocked, *shocked* I tell you, that Russia would try to influence a foreign election in such a way.` </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize it's illegal in France to report on the election in the final 48 hours, and has been that way for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, they love to target anyone on a bike, or in a hybrid/electric, or a Japanese/Korean import, or just any car nicer than their truck. Or anyone that looks at them sideways for driving a giant truck with a massive lift to compensate for their numerous insecurities. But they do love to pull away hard at the lights, which I find funny because rolling coal means you're running a sub-optimal fuel/air ratio with lower power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but it's just unimportant hicks, not anyone in any position of power. On an unrelated note, don't google Congressman Steve King. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's surprisingly poignant for a WKUK sketch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Rush*. Such a fantastic movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish it was just on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize that's one of his supporters' favorite insults, right? I'm really making fun of them more than him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but is there maybe a short snappier word for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so dumb but I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm okay with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, that's just an aggressive front camber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait are you saying that people who shout racist slurs online are dumb? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a word for that, when your wife cheats on you and has sex with other men? It's just on the tip of my tongue, but I can't quite think of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Excuse me?](https://i.imgur.com/3ur1W4T.jpg)

(This isn't really relevant I just love the picture.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it is, but has anybody really put them to the test? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He cheated on all three. And I'm pretty sure his ~~first~~ second wife cheated on him, going behind him to have sex with another man (there's a word for that but I can't quite remember it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that the guy that makes all those movies with violence and racism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss the old TiA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treating someone with basic respect isn't "meaningless etiquette".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know that. Either way she was a woman; unless you think we should tell all of [these women](https://imgur.com/a/dMpqb) "um ackchyually you're a man." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a big gap between *stopping sex and stepping away* (which is pretty much always okay) and *beating a woman to death*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's even less correct the "girl". "Girl" is kind of diminutive for someone nearly sixty years old, but "man" is just wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I guess it really says something about humanity that I was expecting this to end with the cop returning with a carseat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manners are just baseline respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you even managed to squeeze in the "but he held up a flag once" meme into that. That's gotta be bait, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At they Olympic level they require hormones be within spec for at least two years. Worth mentioning is that if you have a medical reason to be taking a "banned" substance, so long as you disclose it and let them monitor it to make sure you're within spec you're allowed to compete. It's called Safe Harbor in a lot of athletic leagues.

Also worth mentioning, at the Olympics so far as I know there have only ever been two openly trans athletes, and neither of them won anything. If there was no advantage or disadvantage, you'd expect to see about thirty participate every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chromosomes are not the only determining characteristic of sex. 

[Sex refers to a person's biological status and is typically categorized as male, female or intersex. **There are a number of indicators of biological sex**, including sex chromosomes, gonads, internal reproductive organs and external genitalia. (APA, 2012).](http://www.apa.org/pi/lgbt/resources/diversity-schools.aspx?item=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so [these women](https://imgur.com/a/dMpqb) are all actually men then? I guess by extension [these men](https://imgur.com/a/75JZb) are actually women too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in the top right of the page near the shortlink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you think it is acceptable to beat a trans person because you find out they're trans? Because that's what it seems like you're trying to say here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chromosomes are not the sole determining characteristic of sex. You keep acting like chromosomes alone are how we determine sex but that is just not true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real though, Amazon loves to recommend stuff that you've just bought and clearly would not need multiples of.

*Hey, we think you might be interested in these twelve vacuum cleaners right now.*

*No Amazon, I just bought a vacuum cleaner; I couldn't be less interested in another right now.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just blew my mind. I knew about Caeser salad but this is another thing entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a guy. A woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, chromosomes are not the only thing that defines sex. Saying that they are is oversimplified biology. Actual biology accounts for phenotype as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you use the victim to just back up an argument you believe... That the average Western man hates transgendered people and wants to hurt them

3/10 strawman. You presuming to know my opinion down to such a specific level based on nothing more than reddit is absurd, and the conclusion is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your submissions, which is wht I was referring to, the majority are supporting and positive.

Only in the last two, where someone was murdered. That is not typical of /r/news. It is typical of /r/politics. Obviously there's some crossover, but the two do not react the same way.

Also, just an observation, but I can't believe you're not trying to bait a reaction.

I did briefly try to gauge a reaction. There was a brief period where I posted articles and at  the same time posted articles about athletes who had been caught doping. I was interested if the people who insisted they were upset that sports were unfair would show up in any of those threads. That's not really baiting though; if I wanted that I could have found plenty of less objective hosts that would present a much more radical version of a particular story.

Fact is, trans equality is something that matters a lot to me, so if I see something about it in the news I share it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cappyboop is bigg but slower than pupperboop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're trying to represent it as a hate-crime

I'm not saying this is definitely a hate crime. I'm saying that when a trans person is the victim of a violent crime, the fact that they are trans is often part of the reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is of that opinion outside of a few disturbed individuals?

An alarming number of people. I understand that the comment sections on reddit are not representative of the population; there's massive self-selection bias. But that doesn't change the fact that there are many who seem to seriously hate trans people. When it's murder, that happens less, but when it's healthcare, for example, it's awful.

And I am not saying that men do not make up the majority of crime victims. I am saying they are not often victimized just for being men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The overwhelming majority are not supportive and positive. That, so far, only seems to be the case when someone is killed or nearly killed. When it comes to anything regarding healthcare, athletics, or discrimination, the comments are far more vile. Believe me, I'd love it if the comments were all nice but they aren't. Fortunately many of the worst are removed, but they hit my inbox first; I see them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say this was definitely a hate crime. I said that someone being trans is often part of the reason they are attacked, not that this it definitely was in this instance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can keep saying that as many times as you'd like, but it doesn't make it true. They are only one of several markers, and the one most rarely actually checked to boot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an issue that's important to me. I happen to be of the opinion that trans people shouldn't be put down just for being trans, and should have the same rights as anyone else. Trying to discredit what I say with a cheap ad hominem attack is a cop-out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, if you want to have the argument you're having, take it to TiA or Tpls, but don't drag a tangent out here where it isn't relevant. A woman was murdered and you're trying to make yourself the victim here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, like new evidence exists and so a scientist edited a publication to reflect that? Couldn't possibly be what's going on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say it was, just that it often is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, now you're making this into a whole different argument about how somehow society thinks it's okay to beat on men but not anybody else. You're drifting off topic, and still not providing any citations or evidence. Look, if you want to have the argument you're having, take it to TiA or Tpls, but don't drag a tangent out here where it isn't relevant. A woman was murdered and you're trying to make yourself the victim here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more or less true. There's still stigma certainly, but trans people aren't mentioned in the Koran so fundamentalist states like Iran don't officially have a problem with trans people. In fact they will assist in paying for transition in Iran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda. But it can also just mean somewhere that certain judgemental or vitriolic behavior isn't tolerated, even if that isn't the primary focus of the place in question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I thought that was someone in the comments here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](https://goo.gl/maps/uG8sKAFhthm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How on God's green Earth is that related? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't say that genitals alone determine sex, nor did I claim it says that. It says that they are one of many indicators, including chromosomes. None of these indicators are the sole definitive marker of sex, otherwise it would be the only one in the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do but not as much as it looks like here. I assume maybe the fade fades some and looks a bit more natural after a little bit. Or it could be the lighting, who knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, as a man, I'm 80% more likely to be killed for any reason by simply being a male.

But not *for* being a male.

It's like that "1 in 5

That was skewed because it only asked people from two campuses that were already known to have a sexual assault problem. The authors of that study have said that the results were only meant to be taken for those schools and not as a representative sample.

So I'd have to see the questions in this survey.

[Feel free to spool through](http://www.thetaskforce.org/static_html/downloads/reports/reports/ntds_full.pdf). The actual questions are near the end.

 "I'm going to claim something i can't prove and you can't either!"

I provided citations, backing up my claim. You have not provided any saying that trans individuals are not disproportionately victims of crime.

They are rarely where? What does this statement even mean?

I'm saying that men are rarely victimized because they are men. Trans people are frequently victimized for being trans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are hard limits to what is and isn't male or female, and they are called chromosomes.

Just gonna put a stop to that really quick:

[Sex refers to a person's biological status and is typically categorized as male, female or intersex. There are a number of indicators of biological sex, including sex chromosomes, gonads, internal reproductive organs and external genitalia. (APA, 2012).](http://www.apa.org/pi/lgbt/resources/diversity-schools.aspx?item=3)

---

We don't kill suicidal people to cure depression, we don't cater to the body dismorphia present in anorexic or bulimic patients, we cure the underlying disease or illness

That's because those have psychological causes and we can with therapy and medication correct those causes. The underlying causes of dysphoria or gender nonconformity can't be manipulated, but the body can.

This is societal pressure directly influencing proven science.

A claim you continue to make but have yet to provide evidence for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   It's not some permanent vibranium shield you carry around with you at all times.

Come on, one more sentence and you would have had it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the entire idea of "safe spaces" makes no sense.

It's just a place you can go where you don't have to be afraid of being harassed or judged. AA is a safe space. It's not some permanent vibranium shield you carry around with you at all times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize that there's more to violent crime than just homicides, right? Attempted homicide, sexual assault, domestic violence, etc. And men are disproportionately perpetrators of violent crime too; about 88% of murderers in the US are men. 

Transgender women were 1.6 times more likely
to experience physical violence, 1.6 times
more likely to experience sexual violence,
and 1.4 times more likely to experience hate
violence in public places within a population
of hate crime victims and survivors

Trans women make up a larger portion of victims of violent crime than they ought to given population. That's my claim, and it's not one you can disprove. While men also make up a disproportionate amount of the victims, they are rarely there because they're men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean a group of people that makes up roughly 50% of the population makes up more of a subgroup than people who make up roughly 0.15%? Trans people are incredibly disproportionately victims of violent crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excuse me I clearly said "fib". Gosh, it's like people don't even read the article anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to [Amnesty](https://www.amnestyusa.org/pdfs/toolkit_transviolence.pdf). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you ignored evidence every time I provided it. You try to discredit the word of major medical associations by saying they only caved under social pressure. Then you kind of skirted around the studies I showed you, just repeating the idea that being trans is nothing more than a mental illness. I'd be happy to show you more of what the [APA](https://www.psychiatry.org/patients-families/gender-dysphoria/what-is-gender-dysphoria) or [WPATH](https://s3.amazonaws.com/amo_hub_content/Association140/files/Standards%20of%20Care%20V7%20-%202011%20WPATH%20\(2\)\(1\).pdf) have to say on the matter but you clearly don't trust what they have to say so why bother?

The person here was not a "man with mental illness". She was a woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that time of year again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This image has been reposted to T_D without a hint of irony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man with mental illness* beaten on sidewalk dies.

---

When that's how you start a discussion about a trans woman, and simply keep repeating a claim that being trans is a mental illness and that affirmative treatment is "mutilation", while providing no evidence of that claim and ignoring evidence to the contrary, and calling me a Nazi for disagreeing (nevermind that gay and trans people were put to death in Nazi Germany), it's not a stretch to make that assumption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What in all fuck? [X](https://archive.fo/1BKXy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeff Smith? I missed something here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's often part of the motive. And she's part of a group that's disproportionately victims of violent crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which are undone by hormone replacement. If it took such a long time for hormones to change your body, nobody would use testosterone to cheat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that makes me feel old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Any racism that exists is allowed to exist remember that

Not under the law. You're also not addressing what I'm actually saying. Racial bias in policing and sentencing is documented fact.

idc what you have to say idk how i can be racist to blacks if I am black

I never said you were racist.

if you werent guilty you wouldnt be considered of a crime.

Overturned convictions are a thing. And they're not terribly uncommon.

You cant tell me 100% of the blacks in prison that take up most of prison space in the US are innocent 

I'm not. You're mischaracterizing what I'm saying completely.

you think its okay to assume anyone who isnt black will assume a black committed a crime

Again, not something I said. You're strawmanning here, and badly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what we do for diabetics? We alter the body to what it should be and add insulin to the system, not say that people should just be able to deal with not having it.

Look, you can go ahead and hate trans people all you want, but throwing around "scientific regression" and "genital mutilation" just because you don't understand something doesn't make you correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I upvoted because... YEA!

It's about time we stopped letting our species make a joke of itself.

You seem to be doing a good job of that yourself, Kill_All_The_Humans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LGBT caucus declares victory after Army nominee Mark Green's withdrawal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No; there's numerous rulings, both from academia and the judicial branch, saying that police departments in the US display racial bias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 91% upvoted. Not sure what you're on about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, because that's clearly not in any way caused by racist policing policies and statistically unequal sentencing for identical crimes. Never mind that pretty much all analysis of the issue says it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that evidence of physical differences in the brain corresponding to structures observed in the sex of the gender one identifies as is "social pressure". 

[Zhou et al 1995](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/7477289)

[Kruijver et al 2000](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/10843193)

[Gooren 2006](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16870186)

[Rametti et al 2011](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20562024)

At best you could say that the studies were funded because there was a social pressure to better understand something. Heck, the DSM used to list being gay as a mental disorder, but after enough studies they realized that was nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you think I feel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no outward indication that any of [these women](https://imgur.com/a/dMpqb) (or [these men](https://imgur.com/a/75JZb)) are trans. If you're attracted to someone on appearance and you change that because of something you couldn't otherwise tell, that's a choice. I can see why it matters in a long-term relationship, but not for some casual fling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not according to just about every medical association around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exhibit A: [thicc](https://i.imgur.com/yZ6rgjD.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well normally they have someone doing squats for eight hour shifts, but hiring enough people to keep up with production is expensive, and there's a high turnover rate because employees get such titanic thighs they can't fit into any of the smaller sizes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the APA's site. They're one of the biggest and most respected medical associations in the US. Save the ad hominem for a source that doesn't have that kind of weight.

^^^^sp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still it's just words you only give them power if you let them.

Or if, you know, the guy saying it pulls a gun on you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet they're super worried about Kansas too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This law opens more exploitable loopholes than it could possibly close. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I can do better than just one doctor: 

[Sex refers to a person's biological status and is typically categorized as male, female or intersex. There are a number of indicators of biological sex, including sex chromosomes, gonads, internal reproductive organs and external genitalia. (APA, 2012).](http://www.apa.org/pi/lgbt/resources/diversity-schools.aspx?item=3)

They do cite themselves, which I think is a bit immodest but then again if I had over a hundred thousand members I'd source stuff from in-house too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they don't have to. Since the ruling it can be taken to mean that gay couples are just as protected under the law without rewriting it, unless explicitly state otherwise. This would usurp that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
