<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8369</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But SM6, SM3, SM2 armed destroyers and cruisers have more range and between American, Koran and Japan there are 10s of Aegis equipped ships ringing China. THAAD is a more limited last resort system.

I wonder if China is worried about the precedent of a missile shield in the area or that it might destabilize NK. An NK who worried about the neutralization of their nascent nuclear deterrent might be more likely to lash out first. 

China is also full of shit as they built radar installations, airstrips and long range anti air and missile emplacements all over the south china sea in violation of international courts and treaties and aggressively violate other countries waters and freedom to transit international waters. 

Chinese "fishing boats" harrass other countries, poach fish, violate marine sanctuaries, over fish, and spy... and now china is building huge heavily armed "coast guard cutters" with heavy caliber guns and long range endurance. 

Korea

*Sejong the Great-class destroyers, Aegis, 128 missiles each, 3 active, 6 total planned, 8500-11000 displacement*


America

*Arleigh Burke destroyers, Aegis, 96 missiles, 62 active, 76 total planned, 8000-9500 tons displacement*

 *Ticonderoga cruisers, Aegis (more powerful than destroyers), 122 missiles, 22 active, 9600 tons displacement*


Japan

*Kongo destroyers, Aegis, 90 missiles, 4 active, 9500-11000 tons displacement*

*Atago destroyers, Aegis, 96 missiles, 2 active, 7700-1000 tons displacement* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, no one knows what it can and cannot do. American and Japanese aegis destroyers/cruisers around the pacific might have more power. 

China is worried this diminishes their nuclear deterrence and their carrier-killing ballistic missiles, but again it's unclear that US naval assets do not already have that capability. 

I think China just doesn't know the capabilities of the new system (maybe they forgot to hack the relevant defense contractor like they did with many major US weapons systems) and is worried about dealing with unknowns. Or they are worried that this will set a precedent for future missile defense shields like in Europe...

The situation is complex... China is a hypocrite because no one likes their long-range air defense installations and runways to project their power over the entire south China sea and economic zone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As if we are deploying the system out of the goodness of our hearts and giving it over the to the South Koreans... Allepo is still waiting for one of these free missle systems the US government donates to foreign powers.

THAAD is there to protect our interests as much as anything else... something Trump fails to comprehend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, most banks wont do business with him... it is why people want to see his tax returns... he got some shady ass financing for some of his projects through unusual mechanisms. Also, he is known for bragging about defrauding contractors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Companies, governments, politicians use social media and complex algorithms to deliver specific content, fake information, and marketing aimed at you... you think you make your own decisions while you are flooded with microtargeted ads and content follow you on the web.

Everything is about reducing people to consumers. Latest fashions for clothes you do not need, pictures of airbrushed models to make you insecure and buy cosmetics and sumpplements... everything geared to insercutiry, a constent need for more stuff to fill a void. 

Everything reduced to a torrent of short sound bites... people get used to this torrent and are unable to do complex long cognitvely intensive tasks. 

Pizzagate is a classic example. Its either an oganic outgrowth of a preconditioned popoulation or actively pushed narrative by some entity.

Basically snippets of information, intrigue, linked to together with loose associations. No time intesive cognitevely complex information.. rather just intuitive random associations. Add in the aura of mystique by adding in nefarious organizations and leading political oepratives. 

Tap into a national dislike and distrust of the hilary campaign. Also, emotionally charge it... pedophiles using innocent kids. 

Add in an an anti establishment pro trump angle... and people take this hook line and sinker. Promoted on some sites (infowars whose star admitted to it being an act) to some people in positions of power (flynn, aka russian agent)... and it gets credence.

Then 100s of people on the internet do "research"... aka image searches and simple good searches, and then spin them into the narrative.

All fun except this distracted from an election where trump describes walking in on changing teen Ms USA contestants and groping women without consent... where he has sold our country out to foreign and corporate interests. 

All fun until some ass shows upto comet ping pong with a gun... 

All fun until people's busnisses and empoyes suffer...

We got played and now coal companies can dump chemicals into water ways, big oil will get their pipeline so they can get canadian oil to ports to ship to other countries, defense contractors get more orders, healthcare to poor people gets cut, erdawans get licence to do what he wants in Turkey, private prisons get a break, marijuana is not getting legalized at a federal level while sessions is in charge, we bombed syria, companies and rich people will get tax breaks blowing holes in our deficit while poor people dont, and not action on climate change, social programs to help the opiate epidimic are under attack...

You got played r/conspiracy and some small independent pizza shops took the brunt (papa johns thanks you btw). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if people who take narcotics chronically just have less ability to tolerate pain, whether from lack of coping mechanisms, lacks of supports, how they process pain, biochemical physiological factors etc. or if people who take narcotics become worse at tolerating pain while on the narcotics, but ask anyone who work with this population and there is a shocking lack of any kind of pain tolerance in this population... from not tolerating small thing like IV placement to not tolerating simple mildly painful conditions like a laceration to poor handling of emotional pain. It might be anecdotal but it is a repeating story over and over again in clinical settings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Senior citizens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possible, I do not know that we know that for certain. Also opiod and alcohol dependence abuse are a complex interplay of social, psychological and biochemical elements. For sure some canabis crossover effects in the mu and delta receptors might play a roll, but its effects on other pathways involved in everything from anxiety to depression might play a roll as well.

It is not surprising that one sedating substance off sets use of other sedative type substances likely alcohol and opiates and we know that the latter have a high morbitiy and mortality associated with them. 

I am curious to see what the long term effects of marijuana are on a population level when substituted for other drugs. Do people eventually come off of canabis. What are the risks of smoking vs edibles. 

Do people remain in a status quo, the marijuana helps with a holding pattern but does not allow addressing the underlying habits, social and psychological issues that drove the substance use (although address the biochemical aspects)...

Basically, are we accepting modern life to be a level of shitty that requires some large subset of our population to require life long habitual drug use to function without spiraling into more addictive and destructive drugs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that one psychogenic substance, in particular, a sedating medication can displace the use of other sedatives is not surprising. What is interesting is long-term effects of this. 

Alcohol and narcotics have terrible long-term morbidity and mortality and health effects. 

The real question is cannabis better and what are the long-term effects. Also, compared to getting people off of substances altogether what are the downsides for cannabis as a long term strategy. Furthermore, does it decrease the number of people who get clean altogether? Is canabis a stable long-term subsitute or do people relapse?

Basically, I am curious as to the near term, middle term and long-term population effects...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there is some nuance. If you believe that society benefits from every possible fetus coming to term, or you believe that abortion is morally wrong... but recognize others do not share your beliefs then his position makes sense.

If you accept abortion to be murder, I don't get how you would stand by and be ok with it. 

I think the dirty secret is that the church does not actually believe this to be murder, otherwise they would be a lot more vocal than they already are... the cognitive dissonance is on the church's part... otherwise they would campaign to put women and doctors in jail as accessories to murder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, well off people with supports might also not feel ready for a child at that point in their life... basically, to her point that abortion is only for people in different situations comes across a judgemental. Abortion isn't just about your life being over because you have this kid, it is about being at a point in life where having a child makes sense individual women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see the establishment doing the reverse, upvoting various conspiracy theories in these subs to distract from real conspiracies. 

Promote chem trails while signing an executive order to allow coal companies to dump chemicals in rivers directly. Also planes are emmiting toxic substances... it's CO2 and our world is baking but no one here cares about how the republicans are going to dismantle any climate change initiatives at the behest of large fossil fuel companies. The sec state was the president of Exon mobil. There is a war on science and fact and this sub has totally missed it.

Pizzagate and Clinton foundation stuff while the government swamp is filled twice deeper. Sketchy Russia connections. Out in the open nepotism. Erdawan just gave himself dictatorial powers and trump congratulated him becuase he has towers in Istanbul... same with the  Philippines etc. Remember Flynn who promoted pizza gate was an actual foreign agent. Big companies gonna get tax breaks, pay people below living wages, government subsidies. Raethyon rpeobably jsut got a new 70 mil tomohawk order...

Right now democracy and freedom are at risk around the world. Erdawan seized control, dueterte is murdering people outright, Venezuela is in rebellion. Governments are generating fake news, monitoring communications, tampering with other country's elections.  Big companies run the show. People are dying from opiates while for profit prisons make money on millions of young men on weed convictions. 

But this sub has found the real deal... the earth is flat, democratic D.C. elite are torturing and diddling kids in ironically named pizza shops, planes are spreading mind control agents, the Rothchilds and elders of Zion are secretly out to neuter the rest of the world... the powers that be probably make upvote bots for these sites/forums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most states have systems to check who is writing pain med prescriptions, someone will check and he will get cut off from all of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, public understanding of needing opiates is driven by cultural expectations created by pharma to sell more opiates.

Opiates are appropriate for short courses for specific symptoms. There is always risk of dependence and addiction, the longer the use the more the issues. People on narcotics develop less tolerance for pain in general: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Opioid-induced_hyperalgesia. The truth is a lot of people never needed the opiates and now people expect them. Everyone thinks their need is legitimate and everyone else is dependent or an addict. You can be an addict whether an doctor gives you pills or toy shoot heroin in the street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Advil or Motrin (ibuprofen): toxic to kidneys (stay hydrated), and stomach bleeding (take with food), and long term use can increase stroke and heart attack (less proven). Don't combine with alcohol because of risk of stomach ulcers.

Alleve (naproxen): same as ibuprofen but less theoretical risk if strike or heart attack.

Tylenol/Paracetamol (acetaminophen): in large doses or long term medium dose use runs risk of liver toxicity. Don't combine with alcohol because liver toxicity.

2) high dose opiates work fur a little but then you develop dependence, opiate induced hyperalgesia and then you will be in more pain and opiate dependent. Past a certain dose risk of death dramatically increases because your tolerance for your brain not telling you to keep breathing  doesn't grow as fast as the pain effects.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone thinks their needs are legit and all the other people are addicts when opiates are simply inappropriate and problematic for and long term use outside palliative care and cancer treatment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they did you a real solid. No problems with that plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask any clinician that deals with chronic pain, opiate hyperalgesia is a thing: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Opioid-induced_hyperalgesia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, opiate hyperalgesia. Opiate users are less able to deal with pain in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People become less capable if dealing with pain. Opiate hyperalgesia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not worse than opiates in that opiates have terrible dude effects, mortality rate, and tolerance and are far more addictive and dependent forming.

It's not great either. But there is no silver bullet. First of all the type of chronic pain matters. For some types there are specific interventions that help. For all chronic pain counseling, improved social connections, employment, support networks are huge. Good mental well being helps with resilience to pain. Social isolation makes things worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the pain. 

1) counseling, psych therapy, helping people with th support networks. Resiliance and pain tolerance improve with better mental state, less isolation, better support networks.
2) depending on pain type there are alternatives, from steroid injections to Botox injunctions (migraines) etc.
3) Weight loss, diet, exercise in certain situations. Increased activity less sitting/laying.
4) changing cultural expectations of a pain free life, life hurts... other countries, including developed nations use a fraction of the opiates we do with better outcomes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well addiction/dependence is an issue and becomes a greater issue the longer the opiates are used. That line that opiates aren't addictive or dependent forming when used to treat pain/ used as prescribed was invented by pharma to get dics more comfortable handing out opiates... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically addiction has a specific meaning... it would be hard to know just from his description, but definately dependence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They create a problem in cancer patients too, just the risk benefit is different... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opioids aren't appropriate for long term pain, particularly back pain because of risk addiction and poor efficacy, as well as tolerance to narcotics, decreased pain tolerance etc. 

As for your friend if he had a fracture, he would get opiates but for a muscle strain or lacerations opiates are also usually not indicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I hope Alabama will catch on soon"

...just seems unlikely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or when even the mention of his negotiations risks recession and global economic instability and ultimately hurts Americans. Imagine being an American automaker trying to secure your supply chain and not knowing where you can source parts... modern supply chains are incredibly complex and rely on political stability... with the specter of trade wars companies are going to have to take much more conservative plans and hold on investments in new product lines and factories... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think depends. If the explosion is above the water, then being in the water might be safer if the pressure waves glance of the surface. If it is in the water than it would be oretty bad although idk how fast the pressure would drop off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again you missed the point, the panels aren't made of crap, they are designed not to kill you. The bumpers are designed not to kill you or pedestrians. If they didn't deform on impact they would be a problem. Also, they are far more resistant to corrosion and small dings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot Sessions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=joMK1WZjP7g

Honestly, just look at trends in motor vehicle injuries and mortality per miles driven... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=joMK1WZjP7g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's important not to make the same mistakes democrats did in the United States. Trump voters were largely misinformed... 

If I read another article about an Appalachian or Kentucky coal country trump voter talk about how they are dependent on obama care for life saving care and didn't think trump and the republicans would actually repeal it, I will have a minor stroke. 

But it is important to realize that there are many blue collar community in America that are hurting and it's important to listen for their issues... because in someways these groups are the proverbial canaries in the gold mine. 

Le Pen is a fascist. Her core supporters are fascists. But Europe is also having trouble with the shear rate of migrants, the poor assimilation of migrants, cultural issues (like women's rights). Walk around parts of French urban centers and you will get hastled and hustled by migrants looking to make a buck... it's unpleasant.

So while acknowledging Le penn and her core backers as a problem, not recognizing the challenge migrants pose, the escalating problem as Syrian, African, Afghany conflicts continue... will drive people into her camp... and that's how you get fascism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You start with a MOAB, although no one would fault you for starting with a tactical nuke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got ~~some~~ mom... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, why do we fixate on WWII culturally? 

Vietnam is a problem because it too close for man people. Still lots of people who served with lots of PTSD.

Also complex in that America did not win and the enemy was fighting for their independence from a colonial power... of course chinese and russian geopolitical aims further muddied waters, but ho chi min was a freedom fighter first, communist second. Ho chi min wanted US backing after Israeli independence but got turned down by french colonial interests. He then turned to Russia. Finally, America didn't achieve their aims despite leveling half the country and 10s of thousands of US casualities... oh and that image of the US helicopter over the US embassy and marines pushing hueys off of carrier decks to make room for refugee choppers.

Korea. Well again, muddied conflict, Mcarthur's hubris, and advance to the chinese border, chinese involvement, results was stalemate at the same starting line. Weapons marginally different from WWII makes it even feel similiar to a WWII game but with geopolitical baggage. 

Desert strom... too one sided. Bosnia... to soon, to much genocide, Western intervention too much overwhelming western firepower...

Falklands... talk about geopolitical shit storm, basically argentine conscripts and a few special forces against a run down British fleet... a politically limited conflict defined as much by weapons malfunctions and geopolitical realities as anything else. Malfunctioning exocets, mismanaged diesel electric subs that never entered the conflict, under trained and under supplied argentine soldiers, a jury rigged british flottilla of civllian and miliarty ships with an aging carrier saved from retirement... ultimately actually faily limited military action... yeah terrible game. Oh both the brits and argentines are still upset about the whole thing. 

Seriously, flaklands air war simulator... argentine jets running out of fuel, against harrier jump jets with limited engagment time, all subsonic...

Sierra Leone... genocide... not good video game material. Even WWII games dont have much concentration camp missions...

WWII, safe material, internationally accepted "good guys", far enough ago, in American and European cultural consciousness so people feel comfortable with the general hx... games generally avoid the holcoaust thing...

WWI... long ago, less clear "bad guy", but 'merica, and the germans don't feel as bad about it... also different enough tech and feel from WWII so different mechanics. Less genocide and away from the main theatre... safe game material.

Vietnam, korea... geo policital (and some racial baggage)
Falkands... geo political baggage, not much opportunity for material
Bosnia, sierra leone... genocidem to soon
Desert storm? one sided
Ruso-Japanese war? One sided, still sore spot, AMericans dont really care about it.
Spanish-American war? Americans dont really care
etc, etc. Companies do what is safe and easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, after all of the shit how can people still be surprised: 

Soliciting sex from congressional pages:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_Foley_scandal

Soliciting sex in airport bathroom
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Larry_Craig_scandal

Driving mistress to get abortion... oh and she was his patient (he is a primary care doctor), yeah he fucked his own patient and then wanted her to get an abortion:
http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/10/10/scott-desjarlais-abortion-pro-life_n_1953136.html

Disappeared from office to pursue affair with argentine office (couldnt be found... yeah public official went totally MIA)
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_Sanford

Affair and using campaign money to cover it up:
http://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2017/04/10/523328717/alabamas-governor-resigns-amid-scandal-over-affair-and-cover-up

And this is actually just off the top of my head... funny, all family values republicans. This list is also just the top of the iceberg. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, after all of the shit how can people still be surprised: 

Soliciting sex from congressional pages:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_Foley_scandal

Soliciting sex in airport bathroom
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Larry_Craig_scandal

Driving mistress to get abortion... oh and she was his patient (he is a primary care doctor):
http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/10/10/scott-desjarlais-abortion-pro-life_n_1953136.html

Disappeared from office to pursue affair with argentine office (couldnt be found... yeah public official went totally MIA)
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_Sanford

Affair and using campaign money to cover it up:
http://www.npr.org/sections/thetwo-way/2017/04/10/523328717/alabamas-governor-resigns-amid-scandal-over-affair-and-cover-up

And this is actually just off the top of my head... funny, all family values republicans. This list is also just the top of the iceberg. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not quite true, Sherman's and t34s could take on most German tanks with the mark exception being tigers and somewhat the panthers. The flak 88 guns where also a problem but allied artillery, Air Force, and numbers did the trick. 

But American agricultural output was enormous, yes Canada contributed but American plains states produced enormous amounts of grain and meat. American ships got it to Europe, America trucks carried it the front while Germans relied on horses for logistics. Not taking away Canada's contributions, just more awknolodging the juggernaut that was America. 

Also the British brains thing is offensive... Bletchley park, proximity fuses were helpful but American designs and tech were also insrumental. American generals were largely effective leaders, at the least as effective as their British counterparts. Not hating on the brits, but dismissing American technological, leadership and logistical contributions is inane.


America was backing England early on, although American companies individually worked with Nazis, Roosevelt was just looking for an excuse to join the war when the Japanese gave him Pearl Harbor. Lend lease and other programs meant american goods were flowing to largely England. 

America itself was untouched by the war. Her literally undprecedented and unmatched industrial and agricultural capacity set the next 50 years. Argentina who was agricultural export dependent and enourmosly wealthy until 1946 got wrecked by us agricultural output (and internal mismanagement and fascist tendencies). American had undeveloped land, farms, factories, and dynamic intact work force and intact infastructure.  

 No one wants to overlook or minimize British/ Russian/Polish etc contributions to the war, but the hidden lead is American industrial might, agricultural production and logistics allowed the allies wage war across 2 oceans and replace losses at an astounding rate.

Honestly, if Japan won at midway and butler succeeded in barbosaa, it's still likely that while the war would have lasted longer America still had enough industrial capacity to over whelm the axis. 

Also, one has to wonder, if the war dragged on and the US was further from winning would we have used tactical nukes? Like instead of fighting for Iwo Jima just nuke the island? If Hitler succeeded in barbossa would we have nuked Hamburg or Berlin or German panzer divisions? One wonders if the axis was lucky to have lost when it did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even when senator and reps mean well, law is very complex and corporations basic help write these laws in areas they dominate, usually big companies. Politicians and their staffs are rarely scientists or economists etc... and since scientists and economists are ussually occupied with research or other work, they don't have time to argue and advocate bills. 

But large companies like Monsanto have lobbiests that help write the bill. Thats how liquid coal gets labeled a clean energy. It's how cms links hospital reimbursements to pain scores (opiates). It's how gm gets light rail torn up. 

Worse yet I keep hearing politicians clearly operating on some Econ 101 logic... talking about how clean energy is subsidized and how markets need to decide... wtf? Econ 102 would explain how fossil fuels produce pollution and that this is not factored into their cost as it is borne not by consumers directly so fossil fuels are cheaper than they should leading to over consumption... not to mention that supply and demand don't give a fuck about long term health and environmental outcomes as capitalism is a tool for efficient economic resource distribution,  not a value system or in anyway concerned with average Americans quality of life.

 Basically, congress is science and economics illiterate, big companies write bills and executive orders... coal can dump into streams, no CO2 regulation, fuck neutrality, health care is somehow supposed to work as some hybrid of public good and free market, opiates for everyone, cars and planes but no trains, weed for no one, and once you get caught with weed private prison for you, god forbid you regulate sugar, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scooter Libby of this cluster... him or Flynn are going to take this fall... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with american logistical support, from tucks to spam. But yes, russians, particularly males born in the 1910s had a poor life expectancy in WWII... also everyone in eastern europe didnt do well. Hitler planned to wipe out eastern europeans after the war and settle the area with germans, the jews where just the start. So he didnt exactly look to preserve cities and villages like he did in France... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US factories and farms. My grandfather remembers how american spam and american trucks to move it kept them all alive... American logistical support was as important as the t-34. You got to give the Russian credit continuing amazing arms production, moving entire factories to the urals, turning out t-34s in stalingrad as the city fell... but american planes, ships, trucks, food, supported every step of the Russian push to Berlin... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, the rule was that outside extreme circumstance they were not allowed to directly act on enigma intelligence... so a sub hunter group might be moved to a general location with increased activity, but they would not use enigma to micro-target a specific sub. This probably cost lives in the short term but saved lives in the long term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that walrus probably poses for porn on a russian sub, that last pic with the officer looks awfully like putin and seems to have less than honorable intentions  towards that walrus...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Russian picture ever, awkward posing young russian male, walrus, nuclear sub, and snow... literally only missing vodka... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would be hard pressed to get anything... he was still convicted of illegal weapons possesion even while beating the double homicide charge, and the patriots would also only have to prove in civil court that he murdered odin loyd, which odin Lloyd's family will be trying to do as well... at the very least they dont even have to prove he actually murdered lloyd just that he was involved... a image concious organizations like the NFL and the Patriots will no doubt have clauses to get out of contracts in the even of any legal trouble on the players part... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no... from a league standpoint they will still have no difficulty not paying him. They might have to do a bit more legal work but there is no way they don't have some clause in the contract they can't use to get out of it. The NFL and patriots legal team will have no difficulty in a civil case proving Hernandez violated the terms of his contract.


Where things get more dicey is odin loyds family now has to prove a civil case against Hernandez' estate... they still will likely get it, burden of proof is less in a civil case, (preponderance of evidende, 50% probability vs beyond a reasonable doubt 95%) but they need to redominstrate proof Hernandez did it, and demonstrate damages, rather than just demonstrate damages alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, on tape taking about grabbing women because he can as a star... in another incident talking about going back stage at a teen talent show while the constestants were changing... I mean this is what he is willing to say in public... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having spent a decent amount of time in academia, I agree, women do get condescended too, hit on, and sometimes taken less than seriously. 

Although, professors and upper management some time condescend and talk down to everyone while appropriating ideas... it's a syndrome that often comes with being in power.

But it is frusturating when I hear colleagues complain that they are being mansplained to when in fact they are just wrong and someone was just trying to correct something... and I have often heard the term used to shut down discussions. 

Also, communication is important. I want to hear what the peope below me or above me think about a situation or idea or what lay people think... what is often ascribed as mansplaining is just people throwing out their theory or idea. If it's wrong? They should be corrected... it's now information gets exchanged... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is gangster lifestyle and serial murder, he fell into the latter category... sure there are people in the NFL who use their large salaries to do bad shit but they aren't killing multiple people... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mansplaining isn't always mansplaining. Sometime its how more awkward men exchange information by putting forward their understanding of a situation. 

Exchanging explanations or disagreeing on them can bring about better understanding for both parties.

Also, of everything men say is mainsplaining it probably isn't. Sometimes people need to explain things to each other and you aren't always right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caffeine in normal doses is fine. There are many case reports for caffeine in higher doses (pills in long term and short term overdose). A normal cup of coffee doesn't have enough caffeine to cause problems even in daily consumption. We don't disagree. 

Exercise and healthy diet are also reliably good for you. 

Trained properly aligned cardiac muscle is non pathological. It probably is physiologically considered hypertrophy but clinically when we say left ventricular hypertrophy it's usually in terms of pathology, like hcm, or in setting of heart failure. Athletes heart does not seem to predispose peope to heart failure like hypertrophy from aortic stenosis, hypertension, or hcm...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Athletes heart syndrome is not a normal athletic heart, it's inappropriate deposition of myocardium and requires detraining. If retrained it does not always reoccur but there needs to be evaluation for hypertrophic cardiomyopathy.

We do know long term exercise is good for you. Long term cocaine causes plaque deposition, vasospasm etc. Caffeine in normal doses is not potent enough to cause long term adverse effects but in very high doses can be deadly. Nicotine has long term effects as well. Basically, some stress is fine, normal doses of caffeine is fine, exercise is good as long as you don't have underlying issues, healthy balanced diet with plants and fewer carbs is good, too much food is bad... these are not terribly controversial... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We definately understand a lot more than indicated in the post... the ordered response to exercise, vasodilation, increased cardiac contractility, endorphin release... all under physiological regulation are different than the uncontrolled alpha and beta agonist effects of sympathomimetics like cocaine, aderral, caffeine, nicotine is pretty remarkable. Also a marathon runner or athlete don't have hypertrophied hearts... if they do they need to detrain and likely have a cardiomyopathy... furthermore caffeine and nicotine in their broad effects also cause things like plaque deposition. The body is a fine tuned machine. Think of it like this, you can use a mouse and keyboard to input info on a cumputer. Do so in controlled intentional purpose and the computer works. Mash the keyboard and mouse randomly and things will happen on the screen but the computer won't work very well. Drugs like cocaine hit all the butttons at once... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What MD are you? We definately understand a lot more than indicated in your post and you seem to have a weak understanding of biochem and physiology. The fact that you cannot differentiate the ordered response to exercise...   vasodilation, increased cardiac contractility, endorphin release... all under physiological regulation and the uncontrolled alpha and beta agonist effects of sympathomimetics like cocaine, aderral, caffeine, nicotine is pretty remarkable. Also a marathon runner or athlete don't have hypertrophied hearts... if they do they need to detrain and likely have a cardiomyopathy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy that on this site conservatives and liberals interact. I think it strengthens us that people from different regions interact, domestically and internationally. If we had more female and more older users it would be good too but I think that will happen in time. 

We don't benefit from a small vocal minority aggressively using Reddit to spread misinformation and hate filled dogma from white supremacy to misogyny. The ability of the internet to deliver hateful dogma and recruit people to ideologically driven fringe causes is a huge threat of our time. 

In other Internet communities it is how a small group of radical Islamists can convince someone in Paris or San Bernindino or London to carry out a terrorist attack with minimal investment. It's how hate material makes it to a kid who is unhappy and shoots up a church in Atlanta. 

Diversity and free speech are vital to our Reddit community, and usually freedom is more valuable than security, but it is a balance. And it's unclear how we innoculate our popoulation against the influence of these fringe movements. 

I only brought up Reddit demographics becuase I believe, racism, mysogyny, alt right ideology to actually be a minority, although growing position in Reddit. And that we as a community need to find a way to provide our youngest and most vulnerable and angriest resistors context against some of these echo chambers and campaigns of racism, mysogny, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what worries me is that the front page is largely videos and imgur photos, but, periodically, sometimes with some effort from the respective sub, some content will make it through to the front page, out of context, from some unreliable source. 

The concern is it an insidious way for the material to reach a broader audience, inocously mixed in with cat videos. And since early comments get upvoted the most, then hardcore users in these subs drive the top comments too.

So basically, you get users presented with a biased case, from a biased source, with biased comments masquerading as a legitimate story on a public forum (no immediately apparent political/corporate angle)... then people tell their friends, etc. Eventually, some story or some comment will debunk the claim/ story, but some fraction of those readers will stay and subscribe to that given reddit/ eco system. 

I beleive it was a big driver of the_donalds prominence during the campaign for instance... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, it is one of the reasons I don't really talk about Reddit, I pretend I barely know what it exists. 

For the lay public, reddit sometimes carries a less than desirable association with the alt right, PUA community, etc. even though the site is predominantly left-leaning, young over-educated tech savy users... lurkers, based on the people I know in real life who lurk, tend to be even more in that camp.

There are some out of mainstream threads specific to that demographic that can be problematic, and sometimes reddit can have a hive mentality that coupled with tech saviness can lead to problems... although conventional media campaigns like fox news gather the pitchfork calls have lead to far more problems imho.  

But generally, redditors tend to be more informed, non-violent, progressive than the public at large but a small vocal minority taints the site's reputation. Worse yet there is an element of reddit where alt right, neo-nazi, PUA types etc use reddit as a platform to exand to young tech savvy redditors to grow their numbers... so these elements are not simply an inconvenience to general reddit users but a cancerous growth...

The problem of how to address this without censorship that would degrade the sites primary function as a global internet forum and raise concerns as to who would vet the content and what is undesirable... The internet for all its good is also incredably effective at delivering toxic ideology to isolated angry youth, particularly young men... whether its ISIS, or its PUA, or its alt right. I think it is a question for our time as we struggle to share a national and global consensus on a factual base to help address pressing challenges of our time from global warming, to automation, to income inequality, to health care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean plain unadorned shells seems too serious for this was business.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean here is an example where we simply don't know and people aren't willing to wait and find out more.  

Take your example:
1) Assad gets 70-80% in rigged elections, and definatelty not in the area he bombed. Sadaam used to get in the 90s. Also, remember assad controls all the media in the country. Honestly, it's a useless propoganda number.

2) Assad has gassed his own citizens before. He is also willing to drop barrel bombs on hospitals... repeatedly.

3) Chemical weapons are a red line. Why risk Russian backing but so clearly toeing that line especially since Russia was supposed to ensure he destroyed his chemical weapons.

4) Russia and assads protestations are weak, we saw the plane take off on satellite. Russia was also at that base. So they know as well. I believe Assad did this with Russian approval. If they hadn't Russia would just compellingly debunk US claims and embarras the shit out of US... after Iraq and wmd fiasco they would neuter our foreign policy credentials. Also china would have joined in as they have Syria interests too. 

5) But it makes little sense why Assad would for little tactical gain shoot himself in the foot like that by risking a US and European military response. I think he did it to test US reaponse because he is desperate and needs a final push to regain control. 
6) But why Russia allowed him or didn't just give him mor conventional support is what's interesting. The response was predictable, the US danced the expected dance. 

Meanwhilw, The strike on the base was limited. The Russian knew and left ahead of time so at the least the Syrians would see the Russians leaving and probably move assets out. When we say we destroyed x many planes, how many were even flyable. In return trump gets leverage on the Russian connection story. It's a limited US response and in Washington less heat on Russian election meddling and sou rectruitment... maybe they decided trump was too close appearing to them and too weak to lift sanctions now, so for now they decided some distance there.

Also, I think more importantly they established an international redline. Conventional explosives to kill babies? No intervention. Chemical weapons? Intervention. As long as Assad stays behind that line no western intervention.

Finally, Ukraine. If Russia does a false flag attack in Ukraine with chemical weapons in a couple months the US won't be able to say anything when a 1000 Russian tanks converge in Kiev.

No, I believe a Syrian plane dropped a chemical barrel bomb and I believe they bombed the hospital and then I believe Uncle Sam danced his tomhawk laden jig, and I believe that someone, probably in Moscow popped the champagne to celebrate how well they played us.







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also there is an added challenge. People don't like being wrong. Critical thinking is hard and unpleasant. People don't actually know how to do research or check sources. And many lack a knowledge base to ground their research. 

So instead they just find a media and craft a media environment for themselves that reflects their own beliefs... for the really lazy it's bouncing around "facts" in a face book echo chamber. 

The more inspired watch Fox News or Alex jones or dr oz and do cursory google searches and cherry pick results out that match their ideals. What's interesting is it isn't even hard because these movements develop their own terms that enrich google results. Google the term and after a few results you get the crazy pages. Worse yet add 

Macedonian fake news writers looking to make a buck or fringe sites looking to make a buck or state actors looking to push and agenda and there is polished shit out there for tha public to consume.

But the most determined are the conspiracy theorists who sit their and "research" or basically scour conjecture and loose association driven theories on fringe sites and buy books and videos produced by either the mentally ill or people looking to profit off of them.

But even in more main stream media with cuts to newsroom budgets there are misinformed lay articles in major newspapers. Any professional will tell you after reading an article about their field that it's more complicated than portrayed and information is not quite right.

Or take bill maher ranting about gmos without information... that's the other issue, we let opinion news amd news shows drive discussions... and what's is mahers credentials? Why does coultere opinion matter? Who are all these panelists on CNN? They tell us they are experts but who knows.

We have lost touch with that news is actually not always exciting. 

That facts can be complicated. 

It can take time to develop a clearer picture. 

What a lay person intuits isn't always right. 

That a lack of a shared civic platform and basic knowledge base is undermining the integrity of our country. 

Fractured media markets make consumers vulnerable to misinformation.

Non experts, opinion news shows, and entertainers are not an adequate source of news or thought leaders.

The combination of social media, consumer culture and cable news is toxic.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a space x fan and I honestly, don't understand the finer details of rocket/ rocket engine design but recognize how space X has pushed the envelope in commercial space flight. That being said, the future of Space X is by no means assured or certain. Furthermore, it is not clear to me the feasibility of the Mars ITS or if it is the correct way forward. Furthermore, space X's contribution seems to be the reusability and landing rockets, not so much engine or aerodynamics design. 

I guess my point is that space X is a start, that can still fail, is not necessarily the only, or correct way forward and has its own blind spots and limitations. I think its is important the public support multiple players in a field, and in particular, we need to push the government to continue to fund Nasa. Musk isn't funding climate change satellites or europa missions and I find it concerning that people are so ready to outsource the exploratory vision of a nation to a single or even a couple of billionaires.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CEO clearly doesn't give a shit about the little people while running a company that has been bailed out by taxpayer money... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean...

2 of his former campaign staff/advisors and in 1 case cabinet members were retroactively registered as foreign agents (mannefort/flynn)

2 staffers/ cabinet members seem to forget talking to Russian ambassador come spy recruiter (Kushnir/Sessions)

1 advisor target of FBI surveillance of foreign agents with FISA court order requiring probable cause. (Carter)

Either they didn't vet anyone, or Russian connections was a requirement/ or positive on people's resumes...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He authored the GOPs Russia platform at the convention... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine if grad school, internship, and jobs are infinite... also it degrades the value of your degree. If a company hires people with 3.75 GPAs who can't communicate in English or know the expected material it will hurt the value of your degree. Academic integrity is a thing for a reason and grades are as much an assessment of your knowledge for yourself as an external marker to future employers. Professors aren't detectives but they aren't your moral instructors or parents... it's not their job to teach you right and wrong you should have learned in middle school. Even in high school cheating should get you a 0 and in some places expulsion. His job is to teach and asses your knowledge.  Not be your sensei. It advanced education with adult learners... you don't know shit then it's your job to figure out how to remedy that... cheating is a non option.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When applied to Newell or Musk it's with grudging respect... joking but a suggestion to the sway they hold among certain interest circles... particularly Newell in his control of steam (and steam sales) and half life 3 release (or non release). 

With trump I can see that idea of a fascist leader bringing society back from the brink and self destruction appealing to a certain sect of Trump supporters... if you believe Trump is playing 4 moves ahead and restoring American greatness from the threat or immigrant/liberal/feminist/minority one can see how that appeals to that minority....

Others on the other side use it ironically because they suggest trump is anything but in control or ahead but are concerned about the other side of the coin in his percieved fascist tendencies and self love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is what he meant by expansive, there is a lot of it. Lotr if you add silmarallion and the languages Tolkien developed has an entire cohesive world and creation myth with its own language... basically more layers if less content. Also he might have meant depth as in intellectual and thematic comllexity and individual character journeys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since when does Kim care about his civilians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regional at best, global huminatarian and economic disaster if Seoul gets badly damaged or destroyed resulting in potentially global recession, if Beijing or Tokyo get hit too shit be bad... 

unlikely because Korea is unable to project force and it's not clear the Korea have the nuke or missle tech to hit Tokyo or Beijing... they do have enough artillery trained on Seoul to do damage...

 in any event refugee boats would go everywhere but land refugees only could really go north since dmz is not passable. China getting 10 million refugees would be ugly too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Putin run prison until a time at which they might be of use... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By handling I mean the tone deaf tweet... harmless looking middle aged guy with patients to treat bloodied while thrown off of plane in a situation we can all relate too buy an already unpopular industry? Not going to win by blaming the victim... only going to get that video replayed over and over again on tv and social media... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With what recently happened to that Doctor on United, what are your rights as a consumer in that situation? Can they deplane you vs denying boarding? Do they have offer cash or are vouchers legal? Is there a minimum they must offer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am singling out how this situation was handled and the ceos tone deaf response that cost them stock price and brand image. 1st rule of dealing with any kind of client issue or pr issue is a sincere apology... you don't even have to admit guilt or liability... just an apology and a promise to address the situation. When you make more than 100x your average employee or the average American you don't get to make fuck ups like his... literally the worst feasible tweet he could have sent... show he clearly doesn't care about the little people... what a fuck...

Also, why is the link wrong, lines up with most of what I read regarding this situation... 

Furthermore, my experience lines up with United performance in surveys... shitty service, indifference to passengers, crappy inflight experience... will pay more to fly other airlines, they are the last I search.

They took US bailout, cut pensions, now when times are good still treat consumers like shit and clearly their CEO doesn't care about "reacomidating" the little people. What is the doc doing his transplant has been reaccomidated? First class passengers aren't he only ones with places to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he gained united... perfect pair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People comply because it's too much a hassle to fight for your rights and airlines use this. Recourse can be expensive and hard to come by... but basically, yes, airline often really on people complying when they don't have to because they don't know better.

http://finance.yahoo.com/news/uniteds-real-mistake-173844672.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't beat the shit out of a middle aged doctor after violating his rights and then drop tone deaf non apology apologies on twitter resulting in 500mill lost market cap.

The passenger had already boarded so not clearly bumpable, should have been offered cash, offered written explanation of his rights, it's not clearly an overbooked flight (employees)... but ok it's not his responsibility directly but the ham fisted response is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He needs to resign, why does he get paid millions to treat consumers with indifference when he has them deplaned unjustly and beaten... honestly telling me you can't find some guy at half the cost to do a better job? Keeping this asshole Oscar Munoz on as CEO for 7million a year is defrauding investors by overpaying this incompetent ass hole... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it supposed to be money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But now when profitable (using government subsidized fuel, airports, traffic control) they treat consumers like shit. 

As far as I can tell the CEO is confused why the little people are upset for being "reaccomidated"... as if he would be any less upset I. This situation... when airlines bump people like this other people's lives get messed up from losing vacation days to missing work and for some people flights are a big part of their pay check... people are sick of being used and abused and United can't even match the low expectations Americans have for airlines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It that people are sick of being treated like shit by airlines, partucularly united who fucks things up all the time. People get nickel and dimed for everything, fucked with change fees, and after spending a sizable amount of money not even guaranteed a place on the plane. People risk losing out on vacation or in this instance important work... add insult to injury it was employees and no another passenger. People's rage boiled over and they want pitch forks out and heads to roll. These fucking airlines get government bailouts in bad times and treat customers like shit in good times.

So is this more important than Syrian children, global warming, the nuclear option for scotus nominees, etc? No, but people feel like they can relate to this, are upset and angry with airlines and feel as consumers they can make a difference. 

So fuck united... an airline that despite not being particularly cheap, still fails to meet the very low basic expectations set by the American consumer base long accustomed to shitty treatment from airlines... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was bad to stay in terminal... also policy is for denying boarding and in this instance it was for employees not other passengers which seems kind of fucked up too. Honestly though united hands down worst airline to deal with in United States with american vying for close second... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> False, non accounts will see it unless their admin made it a default setting... say at school. People on their own home or public networks will be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube didn't even censor it. It's restricted under an opt in used for parental controls and probably insitutions like schools. 

Furthermore, maybe it's time people realized corporations aren't benevolent bodies... they have one mission, they are obligated, legally, and incentivized to maximize near term profits to maximize investor wealth. And since dividends aren't the main source of income from stocks, it's really about maximizing stock price. 

And our morals and sensibilities are limited to the collective willingness of us as consumers to boycott the convenience of a site like YouTube.

And, we must not forget, Scotus affirmed the rights to free speech of corporations so YouTube can pull and censor videos all it wants...

And if net neutrality gets fucked by this republican congress, your ISPs will start defecto sensoring content... good luck with that.

This is why regulations exist. Free markets don't always yield socially optimal outcomes. If it benefits companies in the near term to poison a river, especially if their customers aren't effected and they will be gone by the time the need to clean up? They will poison said river. Coal companies don't care about mercury emission or climate change. Oil companies only care about spills as lost oil... unless they are threatened with fines. If companies maximize profits in the near term by paying sub livable wage? They will do so. 

All sorts of negative externalities in markets exist when societal costs aren't proved into the good. Free markets are an effiecnt way to organize resources in the near term, but they don't have inherent values or principles... they are a tool that need scare and adjustment.

Idk how you fix YouTube free speech, but if the corporations buying add space feels they want this and American consumers are apathetic... then this will fly.

Also, don't forget, a lot of those future and current consumers are liberal, young people who feel alienated from the people on this sub and generally support sensible gun control... so they aren't going to care or support you on this unless you find a way to speak to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube is a private company out to make a profit... not a government agency... if it's bottom line is driven by viewers and advertiser willingness to pay for viewers it will do what it can do maximize those outcomes. As such your recourse is to not use YouTube and vocalize your concerns so others follow suit... otherwise YouTube, within the scope of the law, can do what it very well damn pleases.

And putting an opt in child filter on gun videos is ok by me...not exactly high grade censorship but rather let's parents have control over what their children view on YouTube... 

This is not some world ending event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isis aspires to dismantle our democratic institutions, freedom of speech, civil liberties etc. Trump is actually doing so. It's not
just lives, it's the survival of the institutions and principles that define our nation. We are not a nation of a certain ethno linguistic background or a long nationalistic history. We are bound by a shared belief in the rule of law according to the humanistic enlightenment principles laid out in the declaration of the independence, the constitution and the bill of rights. Trump, unlike Isis is actually ina position to do so. Trump, unlike Isis, posses a threat to our way of life.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odessa Jews seemed to think they were better than other Pale Jews... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kushner is Jewish. Whatever his feelings on communism - probably not very warm - I doubt he has warm feelings about the Nazis or other Belarussians for the matter. Eastern European Jews (with Ukrainian Odessa Jews being the exception) don't really identify as Belarusian or Polish or Russian but Jews because they were ostracized and limited to ghettos by czarist governments. Periodically murdered in pogroms.

Odessa Jews, Odessa being the cultural center of Eastern European Jewish culture and wealth identified slightly separately from the bulk of Jews in the Pale.

Jews in former Austria Hungary and Germany were culturally distinct enjoying more integration, freedom and economic/educational opportunities.

The Kushners are corrupt, kushner is amateur hour, and his actions are dubious but he is a) not a neonazi, probably opposed bannons alt right b) not pro Russia ideologically. However, Russia is antisemtic as fuck and don't consider kushner as truly Russian. Idk what ties trump and Kushner have with Russia but money, compromising materials, shady business deals are more likely to be the driver of the Russia/ Trump connection than ideology.

Kushner is a crook looking to make a buck and get some power... now flynn? Money or ideology? Unclear. Sessions? Who knows his motivation. Mannefort? Probably money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! Why risk US intervention? Why risk relations with Russia? It's seems like little gain while putting his regime and himself at risk for international military intervention? Something does not add up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has been murdering and torturing in all manner of ways and no one seariously tried to stop him. He has not used chemical weapons since the shit storm caused by their use in 2013 I think... why disrupt the status quo with such a small attack... ostensibly it causes him and his allies more problems than his enemies. He could have killed the same civilians just as easily with regular barrel bombs.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Hilary/Chelsea/Clinton foundation/Uranium mine/Benghazi... why is the lane stream media not talking about that... /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I considered it but for a few things:

1) it was delivered by air and we tracked the plane from the Syrian base.

2) Sarin isn't that easy to use, it must be mixed, and outside a closed system like Tokyo subway, you need a delivery system.

3) Responders got sick, it's hard to get that effect with non biological weapons. 

4) Russia would disprove this and make America look really bad.

5) Israel isn't going to tolerate sarin gas armed Isis or even rebels...

6) Why did Russian air defenses stand down? Shooting down tomahawks isn't like shooting planes. Either the airbase was empty or Russia wants this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 07:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, heirloom varieties can be delicious... heirloom tomatoes are amazing. Heirloom meat like pork or turkey breeds have distinct and amazing flavors. That's nice for home gardens or for wealthy people looking for variety. 

However, to think that we are going to feed 7 billion and growing with small scale agriculture and heirloom varieties is insane and misses the challenges of large scale food production and distribution. 

Mainting varieties of agricultural products is vital for tweaking existing large scale production to tweak flavor profiles, drought resistance, disease resistance etc... biodiversity matters. But we don't have the land, resources or climate to allow everyone to eat small scale locally produced heirloom produce and meat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 07:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Idk, why would he do this? Or more importantly why would Russia let him test America in that way? Was Russian testing the US? Did they know it would end limited strike with forwarning and wanted to test Russian radar? Do they want America to intervene and then create some event in Ukraine and use the same excuse?

Americas response was predictable. Russians knew ahead of time, so how many Syrian planes and choppers stuck around when Russians either inexplicably left or told them they what was to happen?

Honestly, more seems to be happening than meets the eye... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would Assad do this? Why would Russia do this? Maybe hope for limited US response? Then use false flag gas attack in east Ukraine and invade Ukraine? Or test Russian S400 radars against real tomahawk strike? The Russians had warning. Do you really think the Syrian planes and helicopters were still in the ground? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did Russia let Assad do this? Why would Assad shoot himself in the foot? Someone is playing a complicated game, and Uncle Sam is dancing to some else's tune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, why would Assad do this? He had to know it would backfire and he has other weapons. Why would Russia let him do this? 

1) Assad at Russia's behest or Russia launches attack knowing America will respond.
2) Russia knows it will be a limited attack and long term knows it can wait out the storm.
3) Weeks or months from now chemical attack in East Ukraine. Russia states red line was breached. Russian tanks poor into Ukraine.

Or 

Russia is using Syria to test weapons. Invites US retaliation so S400 middle system tests radar against real US tomahawk attack.

Or 

No chemical attack, US defense contractors want $70 million in missle orders.


Someone be playing trump like a fiddle... no one asking the real question... WTF was Assad thinking and why did Russia allow this... makes 0 sense. False flag, or sLeight of hand, someone is playing a complex game... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also why would Assad do this too? He had to know it was going to end badly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is my conspiracy theory, Russia convinces Assad to use chemical weapons, or even carries out strike itself. US retaliates. Russia creates false flag chemical attack Ukraine. Invades eastern Ukraine... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
