<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do my best to ignore them. Powerade Zero/Propel Zero has done the trick for me lately. Sip slowly, and drink regular water too. If it's really nagging, I'll do Keto hot chocolate (unsweetened flax or almond milk, cocoa powder, pinch salt).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!!! Asked my SO to get some HnH on this way home from work one day. He took the initiative to grab two quarts, one store brand and one name brand... BOTH were fat free =\ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 07:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anecdotally speaking, for me, artificial sweeteners always did more harm than good. Like putting a band aid on a gunshot wound. Yeah, satisfies the immediate sweet craving, but that craving just comes back later with a vengeance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 1 year old who wakes up at 3am and 5am on the dot for the last three days. Thank goodness for coffee with HWC!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love my zoodler and have zoodles at least 3 times a week. I need a vessel other than eggs to get bacon to my mouth. Zoodles carbonara is my go-to lazy meal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 06:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also had a job interview today. While getting ready, I tried on a blouse from the "too small doesn't fit" section of my closet just on a whim, and guess what! Totally fit! This was also after a two week stall. Hopefully this is the last interview for both of us!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any upcoming big purchases like for furniture or appliances? If so, the NEX usually had 0% financing on those big types of items if you use your star card. Also, IIRC, you can get a percentage off on gas if you bring in a NEX receipt with a purchase of $50 or more. Otherwise Air Force and Army give you 5% off on gas with the star card, which came in handy during our last coast-to-coast PCS move.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
