<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 11:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for expanding on that, I had no idea King Arthur was, at its heart, a propaganda tool.  I always understood why Tolkien didn't like it, but now I understand why he really didn't like it and that lends further to my theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with this is that LotR has a power leak, power is literally leaking out of the world and things grow weaker over time.  If the opposite were true, Gandalf and the Balrog, who are both from the first age, would have their powers set in the first age.  If a power creep happened over the course of the first age all the way to the third age, then the Balrog would be killed by the dwarves of Moria, Sauron would be stronger than Morgoth with the ring, but Aragorn would be even stronger.  Aragorn would end up fighting Tulkas, the god of fighting, in order to get a good fight.  

Reversing the power scale in LotR just wouldn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tolkien often lamented how the English didn't really have expansive, deep rooted myths and legends like the French and Germans.  The English had King Arthur but even that was a French translation (the original text is title Morte De Arturo).  This can be traced back to the Norman's conquest, where they tried and succeeded to destroy the almost all of the Anglo-Saxon's history and culture.

This sadnesses at the lack of myths and texts is often attributed to be the initial inspiration for Tolkien to write the Lord of the Rings and all its accompanying texts.  I don't think it's a leap at all to think Tolkien would be happy to have his world expanded on.  Fittingly, when most people I know think of British myths and legends, Lord of the Rings is one of the first things they think of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's learning!  Quick, kill it before it lays eggs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also can't really afford to take a day off work if I want to eat a proper diet and not default to cheap beer for dinner a couple nights, which is surprisingly filling.  So I end up in worse health if I go to the doctor.  Don't even get me started on the dentist and vision.  I'm lucky my four year old glasses are still in one piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right?  Zoe is straight up retarded.  They've never said it but Zoe has mental retardation from something like downs or something.  You could probably stretch say the more odd ones like Babby Bear or Oscar have mental disorders, but it's literally Zoe's entire character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they're just an uncaring asshole.  Actual sociopaths/psychopaths, which is really just a broad term for several personality disorders, fall into two categories: those who have it under control and those that don't.  If they have it under control then you don't know they're a psychopath, if they don't have it under control then they're the people that trigger your flight or fight response just by looking at them, the kind you subconsciously avoid because they're so obviously not right, mentally.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 04:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is a subreddit for flat chested porn?  Because I'm much more angry and confused if "flat earth" means you want flat chested women.  That's just wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 04:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I love how a large portion of the player base for the most popular game in the world know the two most popular programming languages in the world."

Gonna bitch about how we speak English next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MOHJEK RHUNES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was intimidating, I think.  He wasn't this imposing enigma, but lines like "Samuraaaiii, you can't hiiide, I can smell your blooood."  Were a beautiful mix of funny and terrifying that leant the original season's charm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say he doesn't.  In The Day of the Black Sun, Ozai shoots lightning at Zuko with full knowledge that Iroh has been training him and is likely complicit in the confrontation between the two.  It would be very stupid to shoot lightning at someone if you think they MIGHT redirect it back at you and Ozai isn't stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For round one, there are several.  I would say Doctor Facilier would be the weakest to beat Batman in a random encounter.  He's very clever and uses several layers of trickery, I could see him getting one over on Bats in a random first encounter.  He'd get his ass handed to him in every meeting after, though.

For round two, this is harder.  I can only think of one Villain who could survive a day of prep batman and that's Chernobog, a major Demon.  And I would only give this a 6/10 for the archdemon because the thing that defeats him might just be acquired in a day.  I'm not trying to circle-jerk Prepman, but all Disney villains who aren't human are defeated by Mcguffins.  Batman can find the shit out of a Mcguffin.  Chernobog is the only one we don't see defeated by a plot device, only banished by some divine spirit.  However, demons, throughout all of fiction, are defeated by humans and mcguffins.  You could replace Batman with Rational Man with a Shotgun and you'd run into the same problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got two.

Spaghetti noodles, cover with butter and garlic/garlic powder.

A really cheap, yeasty beer; bud light platinum is my choice, the extra alcohol makes me feel better about not having food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno man, there certainly is a lot to his classification of physiology--my grandfather was from Bavaria, Germany and I'm the spitting image of Homosapiens Alpinus.  The mental stuff is racist as hell but the physical stuff is pretty sound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there are a few different periods of time where Gohan can go SSJ2 and this wildly changes the outcome.

Cell Saga Gohan going SSJ2 would but up a good fight, but just doesn't have the raw states to take on Superman.  Saiyan Man Gohan is much closer, as Gohan got a significant power boost between the Cell and Buu sagas but he isn't that stronger than when we compare him too... Mystic Gohan.  This is where I can honestly say Superman loses.  Gohan goes from being below SSJ2 Vegeta to above SSJ3 Goku.  This Gohan is the strongest we've ever seen Gohan, though Super is still ongoing.  Up until Mystic Gohan, superman has kept the raw states advantage but I would say Gohan, always the stronger ki user thanks to his training with Piccolo, overtakes Superman in strength and speed handily.  Add a truly ridicules mastery of martial arts, Mystic SSJ2 Gohan is the only Gohan who could beat Superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/asmr  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nonsense, in a fight between Ziz and Glastig Uain (how the hell do you spell that?) I'd give it to our crazy Nordic girl since she absorbed Eidolon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bees only die when they sting us because our hairless skin is thick af (relatively).  Bees can still sting the shit out of smaller mammals, birds, and other insects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To fully grasp this you have to understand what Sauron was.  Sauron was a Maiar of Aule, The Craftsmen.  And he was a very powerful Maiar at that.  Despite joining Morgoth, Sauron retained his powers of making.  So Sauron is a much better inventor and builder than any person or nation that has existed.  Those drawings found in DaVinci's notebooks?  Sauron could easily build better.  Those amazing feats of engineering by Alexander the Great and the Romans?  Mud huts next to what Sauron could build.  It is impossible for men to design, craft, or build (with few very specific exceptions) than Sauron.  Those 50 thousand men might as well be small children with sticks trying to beat up a tank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the Link from Wind Waker isn't a reincarnation, at least.  The God of the sky and the god of the sea say so in the game itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, Jewish mythology has the coolest names. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, I thought Miss Militia was from Eastern Europe/Northern Asia?  Didn't her interlude take place behind the iron curtain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To understand why the unforgivable curses are illegal you have to understand what these curses inherently are.  To even be able to cast an unforgivable curse, you have to want to cast it.  You have to want someone to have no free will, you have to want someone to suffer, you have to want someone to die.  Not only do you need this want, you have to be convinced that you're just the strapping young wizard to get it done.  To put it in more muggle legal terms, just being able to cast the curse proves, beyond a shadow of a doubt, ability and intent on the caster as casting the spell is impossible otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cannon that Zelda and Gannon's spirits are constantly reincarnated throughout the games, forever locked in battle over the triforce.  However, it's also cannon that the different Links throughout the game have no relation to each other unless they are the same Link in different games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think "terrible PR moves" is a bit of an understatement.  I think the OP picture of a burning dumpster is a more apt comparison.  And I voted for Trump (more of a vote against Hillary but whatayagonnado?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America had a large pro-German minority before we joined the war, due to having the largest German/Eastern European population outside of axis territory (remember that the death camps and holocaust in general weren't known until the end of the war).  With our allegiance split between Germany and Britain in the OT, the emperor changing what side American joins would be child's play.  There's a reason we had to change the German names of so much of our food, we were a very German country at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most bullets have a point at the tip, or at least a rounded point.  Rifle bullets are very pointed and even spin as they travel through the air and punch into their target.  So i'd guess small handgun fire would bounce off and leave a scratch but a high caliber rifle would seriously hurt.  Kind of like a grizzly bear.  Is Diana part grizzly bear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing about Yoda is that he's the best.  He's a better light saber user than Anakin or Windu, he's a better force user than Jinn, he has a more stable mind than Plo Kunn.  There are many different second bests who are not far behind Yoda, but a Jedi who devotes their whole life to studying one aspect of the Jedi way is still second best to Yoda in any category.  This is why Sidious retreats.  Sidious is an opportunist, as his name implies.  He was being beaten down in saber combat so used is gile and words.  Sidious will come at you sideways even when he could best you in your strength, it's not worth the risk to him.  Yoda has no weaknesses, there is no way to come at Yoda that he isn't the best at.  So while Sidious is stronger than Yoda in the end, it's much more risk to fight the squirrelly bastard than it's worth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check who you're replying to and who is replying to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a glance, I wouldn't call that alt-right.  Arnold and Hitler were both Austrian, I think that's the joke.  Is it not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Roma gypsy grandmother.  She called herself and her family gypsy and took pride in the term.  Who the fuck are you to decide when a term is racist?  Some people use it a derogatory way and now it's a racist term?  This isn't a word used during chattel slavery, this is a term used inside and outside of Roma gypsy culture for good and bad.  Eat a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a kid, Odin would win because he doesn't screw around when it comes to fighting, he would impale a child and erase his existence before Richards could react.  Against adult Richards, Odin would lose.  Franklyn Richards is more powerful than Odin but lacks the practice to beat Odin until he's an adult.  Odin, along with all his cosmic power, is REALLY good at fighting and at war.  Adult Franklyn Richards beat three celestials at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 13:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psh, we all know your just posting this to try and give me attention, you're just an attention philanthropist.  Wait I think I messed it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 13:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure, people like Richards and Stark can prep like you wouldn't believe, but when people ask, "who would win, batman or superman?"  The answer is Batman***** (with prep, this specific version, superman not bloodlusted, this specific version of superman.). Odin beating hungry Galactus and stale mating normal Galactus has no asterisks, no "as long as" type statements.  Odin is just powerful af. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Single-handedly with no hax or mcguffins?  No, not really.  Most couldn't even beat Surfer without hax or mcguffins and he's only a fraction of Galactus's power (and Odin backhands him off his board).  Odin doesn't face Galactus with the Galactus Beating Sword or the Anti-Galactus Spray, he faces Galactus with just his raw power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few reasons.  One I can think of is that people just don't want to draw children.  You have teenagers in Worm and adults in Pact, but Twig features a cast of children who haven't even hit of puberty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odin is extremely powerful and above just about t any threats the Earth ever encounters.  Odin is able to slap Thanos around like a child and able to repel a hungry Galactus.  On top of physical, Odin is one of the strongest magic users in the universe.  Some feats:

Teleports every human on Earth at once

Creates a pocket dimension and imprisons a god in it

Blows up an entire galaxy in an instant

There was also the time he stalemates Galactus in a telepathic battle, got fed up with Galactus's face not being crushed inward, so he flew up and head butted Galactus and knocked them both out cold.  He also physically overpowered a being (Surter) who has the physical strength to destroy the universe.  Thor is a god, he's strong.  But Odin is a God with a capital 'G', there aren't many things as strong as he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pension?  You mean that thing that takes away from my pay checks that I have virtually no chance of benefitting from?  Must suck not to get that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/hucow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Implied.  I think it's supposed to be the same kind of slug that came out of Will and the Demigorgon is the only living thing we see in the upside down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree with the theory but I can see where someone would.  We see Barb is incubating Demigorgons and is in a state of decay.  But why would the Demigorgon use dead people to incubate its children?  A rotting corpse is no different if it's a deer or a human, so why only use people?  I think people are reading too far into it and we can just chalk it up to Rule of Cool storytelling rather than apply logic too it, but the theory isn't baseless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tolkien confirmed it was a strain of tobacco and not marijuana in one of his many letters he wrote about the LotR universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're messing up making the SAME thing instead of several of the same things.  There was a popular post a while ago where someone made almost 100 breakfast burritos.  I thought that was a fun idea but I changed it up, got ground sausage, beef, and turkey, got different kinds of each ingredient (jalapeo vs bell peppers, red vs russet potatoe, etc) and have been experimenting before I go prep out dozens of meals so I can avoid exactly what's happening to you.  It's not hard to dice and fry one kind of potatoe then another when you're doing it in batches anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but I think she's some sort of scizo.  And the closer you get to Ed Gein, the less you can be held to normal standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most coastal areas have very much less variance in their temperatures, SF being a great example where the weather rarely dips below freezing and doesn't often come close to triple digits.  

I grew up in northern Michigan where we had frostbite advisories--if you had exposed skin for 5 minutes you got frostbite.  I then moved to the south where we had heatstroke advisories--if you are outside doing mild physical(like walking) activity you risk heat stroke.  Also blizzards and tornados.  Fuck off with your "bad" weather, you don't even get hurricanes.  Yet.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This bubble is never gonna pop!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, I'm just relaying what I heard from hundreds of people in several Christian sects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my comment was misinterpreted.  I was retelling what I heard from different sects of Christianity in my area.  I know Mormonism is a world wide religion, though I didn't have those numbers.  I know Mormonism is a sect of Christianity.  But my comment was not my opinion, it was the average opinion I have heard from other Christian sects, of which I interacted with often during the 2012 presidential season for my own personal reasons.  I admit my comment was missing exposition to make this more clear but please don't fill in the blanks by assuming I share these ignorant beliefs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a bit different for Mormons and the rest of Christianity.  From what I've encountered, Lutherans, Catholics, baptists, etc, view other people as doing Christianity wrong or interpreting God's will wrong.  But Mormonism has books besides the new and Old Testament, have much different views, and are mostly isolated to the US.  Don't get me wrong, they still all dislike each other just the same, but Mormonism is definitely a league in its own as far as other Christian sects go.  My source is being in a large Bible Belt state during Romney's bid for presidency, so it could easily be skewed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just have to make your own fun.  Or, more likely, she was indirectly asking to be told what to do.  Poor choice, as every BDSM related thing in the bedroom should be hashed out beforehand, but this story sounds like a teenage fling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happens a lot more than hunters admit.  Happened to my cousin.  Shot a deer, felt really sad, never went hunting again.  Still eats meat, though, still eats game.  He just admits he doesn't have the mind for hunting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have numbers, but I can tell you from personal experience that no hunter I've met (and I've met quite a few) hunt just for fun.  Almost every person enjoys it for some reason or another or else they wouldn't be doing it, but I don't know a single person who hunts just for fun out of the dozens of people I personally know that hunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should I get the power bowl with no sauce?  ... Fuck it we're getting 6 gordita crunches again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right off the bat, we run into some issues.  The Tooth Fairy and the Sandman wouldn't be married.  They would, in all honesty, hate each other.  The Tooth fairy is a fae (duh) who are all about disorder, games, and mischief.  Sandman is a concept given physical form, as widely held concepts are want to do (the concept of conquest is someone you do NOT want to meet.). Sandman is sleepiness personified.  But a concept is about rigidity, strictness, and order.  A concept can't deviate from its progenitor concept because that's all it is.  In all the supernatural realm, you'd be hard pressed to find a more opposed pair.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outside of Abrahamic Religions, in more polytheistic religions, she does have the power of a god.  Most superheroes do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like glaistig uaine/Valkyrie going by silhouette alone--which isn't much to go by.  I think having a protagonist that starts head-and-shoulders above everyone else would be a good exorcise for Wileyhog as it deviates from his norm.  I think having Valkyrie as the protagonist would lend itself to Abbadin being the antagonist of Warm 2: Eletrical whalaroo, but now I'm building vague theories on vague theories when in reality it's much more likely the protagonist of Warm 2 is someone entirely new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro just make them watch the video and awkwardly leer over them the whole time while explaining every detail and reference they aren't getting overtop of the video.  It'll clear everything up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP but liberal =/= libtard.  A libtard IS someone who takes liberal values like women empowerment and socialism and takes it to an extreme.  As a libtard is a parody of a liberal, their a parody as well.  A libtard will support female superiority and flat redistribution of wealth because they are a libtard.  If you think libtard is something else then you need to take a step back and realize it's a amalgamation of the words liberal and retarded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You write off your premiums on your taxes, the government reimburses your premiums in your tax returns.  This makes it safe for consumers as all the other points turn healthcare into the thunder dome my removing regulations hindering competition and turning it into a virtually free market </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/iamverysmart  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be hard pressed to kill the grizzly with a low caliber gun, let alone with your hands.  Going by really life and movie feats, there is no way for Bruce to come out ahead.  A grizzly bear has thicker fur and thicker layers of fat that would cushion any blow made by Lee, grizzly bear's skulls can deflect buckshot and handgun rounds, grizzly bears have a bite strong enough to turn bone and flesh in to a pile of mush.  Grizzlies are so above many street-tier super heroes, let alone a real man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see Chichi getting with Piccolo.  Piccolo loves Gohan, is incredibly serious and hardworking, is a small business owner, and a minority.  Chichi would love Piccolo as a husband and a dad for Gohan.  However, she would eventually cheat on him and end their marriage because Piccolo doesn't have a penis.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing, you can't weaponize memes until you've weaponize autism.  It's like trying to weaponize nuclear weapons without rocket technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the speed and altitude it was traveling, it was only a couple mph between the top speed (speed at which it would break apart like toothpicks in a hurricane) and stall speed (speed where the engine locked up and turned into a big paperweight) so id say it was white-knuckle the whole way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 13:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Station to Station and before the Berlin trilogy, Bowie very publically quit all the illegal stuff (drugs, copious sex, flagrant vandalism, etc) and changed who he hung out with.  While he never said he was going to stop having sex with young teenagers, I'd say it's safe to assume he stopped having sex with young teenagers when he went clean and stopped every other vice, of which there were many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 13:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> East Russians are Asians, though eastern Russians, Khazaks, etc look different than what you think when I say "Asian" in the same way that Indians in India are Asian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ravioli ravioli show me the millioli! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an ugly, close minded individual.  But his rhyme game was on point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im going to use Arthur and Merlin from Le Morte D'Arthur for this.

This is a spite thread.

Round one.  Aragorn isn't a fighter, he's a ranger so this isn't an immediate stomp.  What's more, Arthur is fairly strong out of armor as he regularly runs around in full plate.  However, Aragorn is above peak human in reflexes and at peak human for strength and speed.  Arthur is just a really talented and practiced knight.  I give this 7/10 for Aragorn.  It would be closer to 50-50 but Aragorn fights dirty and Arthur doesn't.

Round two:  Right off the bat, Arthur comes out ahead.  Arthur has two magical swords, one of them Excalibur, a magic spear that always hits, and a horse that never tires.  Aragorn has Anduril, a sheath that keeps Anduril clean, sharp, and untarnished, a cloak that hides him from his enemies, and Mithril Mail.  This is a close one, as Arthur's gear is honestly better than Aragorn's but Aragorn is the superior fighter.  In a battle in a ring, I give this 6/10 for Arthur, but if the environment can be used in anyway, Aragorn gets this 8/10

Now for the spite.  Round three: Gandalf would win 10/10 against Aragorn, Arthur, and Merlin.  While he is limited in using his power during the war of the ring, I'm assuming he is unbound here.  Remember that Gandalf defeated the Balrog, unbound Gandalf is stronger than the Balrog and Gandalf isn't even a combat-based Maiar.  Gandalf is a minor deity.  Unbound Gandalf can speak words that are true because he wills it to be true, unbound Gandalf crushes spirits until the mortal who dared to stand against him is left catatonic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would go so differently for the Starks.  I could see Stannis betrothing his daughter to Bran or Rikkon, making the next King a Stark, thus giving the North their "King" that was their rally cry.  With things mostly settled down with the three kingdoms who wanted Lannisters dead dead, it would be easy for Stannis to keep order, albeit through force.  Is Stannis a good statesmen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you're making money somehow.  I don't get on Reddit often and miss a lot of the quality and entertaining pictures and memes posted on here daily.  You filter the shitty popular ones and repost the quality popular ones to be seen again.  While people always yell "repost" in your comments, I'm seeing a large portion of your reposts for the first time.  

You are performing a service imo, you deserve compensation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They claim that reddit's mysterious voting algorithm prioritized accounts with higher karma in certainly n ways.  I don't know if it does or doesn't but there is also a minimum karma to overcome a lot of spam filters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always assumed Jack was British too.  His name is Jack Slash, it's clearly based of Jack the Ripper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I have trouble coming up with names, I open my copy of the Silmarillion and go to the name index.  If you have ever read the Silmarillion, you will note that the creators of WoW did the same thing. For human men, a few quick ones I notice:

Anarion, brother of Isildur, distant uncle of Aragorn

Beren, cut a jewel from Mothoth's crown to merry a half-angle, half-elf woman, this lead to the creation of Aragorn's royal line.

Curufin, fifth son of Faenor, father of celebrimbor, called "Curufin the Crafty"

Dairuin, one of the twelve companions of Barahir on Dorthonion.

Ered, roughly translates to "The Mountain" from high Sindarin.

Firimar, roughly translates to "the Mortal" from high Sindarin.

Galdor, "Galdor the Tall", son of Hador, lord of Dor-Lomin, father of hurin and Huor, slaim by Eithel

You get the picture.  You can get the Silmarillion in most book stores or even rent it from most libraries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That truck was empty for it to tip like that.  Cars, cop cars especially, would punch through the side of that trailer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they say light load, they actually mean empty (or mostly empty) load.  It doesn't take much stuff to weigh down a trailer.  I unload trucks at work sometimes where we get high wind restrictions on trucking and our drivers have no problem as one pallet of cement boards (which is around 3x3x5) weighs over 2k pounds and will put a truck over the minimum weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://m.imgur.com/wcKAZcH?r </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're brave.  I love discussing religion.  I grew up in a religious family (great uncle is even a pastor) and I was lucky enough to have long conversations about religion that were civil and really helped me grow as a person.  I consider myself a Christian deist now, but I wish I could talk about religion somewhere on Reddit in a casual way that didn't devolve into mud slinging and logical fallacies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going out of character, raid bosses are always taken down by the players, but in lore it's always "So-and-so with a group of adventurers."  Arthas?  Tirion and a group of adventurers.  Death wing?  Thrall, the aspects, and a group of adventurers.  So in the story you have for example, Varian Wrynn fighting Onyxia with adventurers helping him.  Arthas, Onyxia, and death wing all have a reason to attack Tirion (the Ashbringer), Varian (complete her plan to rule Stormwind), and Thrall (destroy the Demon Soul).  They don't have time to turn and attack a weak Mage pelting them with frostbolts that simply sting.  In Lore, these characters are the tanks and their respective raid bosses rank them as target #1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fuck."

-Engineer, probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When a animal is in its death throes like that, don't go near it.  A mouse will bite your shit but a boar will fuck you up if he suddenly finds his legs and gives you a quick charge before he finally goes down.  You could shoot him on the ground but when an animal is on the ground flailing, you can't get close enough (because of reasons above) to get a clean shot.  You will probably end up putting it in more pain and making the meat unusable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://m.imgur.com/NCoOmdE,Y8oT6n8,bzh1zzh,KjSm8ip

On the emergency spillway, the concrete lip that the workers are standing next to?  That's your ass.  There is no bedrock under that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol @ over half of the 15 year old boys saying they had sex.  "I had sex, totally.  I even peed on her face after I put it in her butt." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people are missing the biggest clue in the smallest throw-away line.  "Sleeper was sitting on a porch, reading a book out loud."  Out loud.  Crazyballista dropped these two words for a reason that relates directly to sleeper's powers.  So why was he reading a book out loud?  Was he reading it to countless invisible servants, making him a master?  Were the invisible servants ghosts of people he subsumed?  Sounds a bit too Valkyrie-ish for me, but maybe.  Is there a reason he can't read things in his mind?  Does saying words in his head cause something to happen around him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nonsense, it is doing a lot of things and trying to do even more.  It's extremely bad and harmful things but to say it's not doing anything is stupid, it will make people think they can see back and let Trump flounder when he is doing so many things that need to be stopped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would compare this government to a monster truck on narrow roads than a leaky clunker; it's not doing nothing, it's doing a lot of bad things very quickly and hurting people along the way while rednecks cheer it on with earplugs in.  To be clear, I'm against 99% of what this administration has done except striking down TPP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, it's not function according to you (and me, should have mentioned that) but millions of Americans do consider it functional (millions out of 325 million, a far cry from a majority).  But not calling it function implies it's not doing anything when it is, in fact, very functional at doing bad things.  I feel like we're using two different definitions of functional.  Is it representing America's best interest?  Hell no.  But it is doing things, it is functioning, even if it's function is to do the wrong thing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, it's not doing what I want it to do either and, judging from the downvotes, I should have mentioned that.  But calling it ineffective is just wrong because it's doing a lot of shit.  A lot of DUMD shit, but a lot of shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most couldn't, as they don't have the varied climate to grow different ingredients or the sheer population to support the multiple styles, brands, and brewers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 15:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is very functional, its doing a lot of things very quickly.  It's just not doing what you want it to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americans do beat Belgian beer.  Sure, we have shitty beer that tastes like piss, but so do you.  Our shitty beer is just as shitty as your shitty beer.  But our craft beers are just too numerous for any one European country to compete.  We have a beer for every palate and preference.  And we still have a beer in whatever "category" you want to call your best beers that would rival or beat them.  The US has numbers on their side, a country 11 million can't compete against a country of 325 million. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show made more boat loads of money than the boat loads it took to insure them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happened pretty often in history in nobility, someone would die and a brother would marry their widow.  Hell, that's how Ned Stark married Catlyn, after the mad King killed Ned's older brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luffy does not beat Broly.  Luffy can't beat a single Z warrior at the start of DBZ.  In Dragonball, I could see Luffy going 6/10 with kid Goku during the first martial arts tournament but after that our lovable pirate stands no chance.  DBZ characters are just ridicules in strength.  A 7 year old was strong enough to blow up planets (Gohan on Namek). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a holdover, mostly.  Places like West Virginia and Tennessee, open carry makes sense because there are bears and wolves in the mountains, having a handgun could be life or death if you break down and have to walk or are even on the edge of the wilderness (wild animals love our trash).  It's open carry because the other option is concealed and that's worse for police officers and someone trying to draw the gun.  Brass knuckles or a long knife will just end up getting you killed against a brown bear or pack of wolves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and that is the whole point.  The women who had their nude pictures leaked are public figures with their own brand.  By leaking nude pictures this guy was ruining the brand of these women.  So while leaking the nudes of a McDonald's assistant manager could cause her emotional distress and embarrassment, leaning famous women's nudes could costs hundreds of thousands of dollars in damage to their public image, her person.  So this guy did tens of millions of dollars in damages.  18 months is a light sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something else entirely.  We find intelligent life, but the likely hood of one or both parties from being something completely repulsive about the other is astronomically high.  Say, for instance, we meet an intelligent race who eats vast quantities of their own children.  Children not unlike our own 3-7 year olds in mental and emotional maturity.  This species didn't have predators or hostile environments nor abundant resources like we did, so a conscious effort had to be made to curtail their population.  In this case, these aliens product a dozen offspring, nurture them until they develop the ability to communicate and move independently, then cull them by eating the weaker ones.  This, in their society, is seen as a honorable and good thing.  Never have they even considered not eating babies.  A direct translation from their language from ours for the phrase "to do good" is the same as "to eat babies."  Do you think we could get along with this species?

What if we're the disgusting ones.  What if we meet a species who are able to remotely feel empathy as if it were literally happening to them.  This species would turn toward our planet(s) and be appalled at the suffering and rigor of our lives.  "Why do we feel humans killing each other, why do we feel human life ending through lack of life sustaining material, why do we feel humans suffering a deep cut, why do we feel humans depressed, why do we feel humans disappointed, why do we feel humans frustrated with rigor?"  These aliens would not understand why people starve to death or why people get college educations.  Both make negative emotions.  They wouldn't get why we wouldn't change ourselves to never feel bad feelings again, like they have.  They would be horrified by how much bad and painful things humans feel on a daily basis.

I hope we never meet aliens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But your reply wasn't to one of those many comments you speak of (appeal to probability) it was to a top level comment paraphrasing what the specific woman in the picture said in a satirical way, in no way referring to all feminists as anything (intentionality fallacy). You assumed everyone here thinks all feminists feel this way (ecological fallacy) 

And it isn't an ad hominem attack if someone calls you a name while offering a argument, only when part or all of their argument involves the personal attack.  Like, say, if you failed to address what the person said and just started claiming someone was using an ad hominem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
