<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9063</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn what a dope interview </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, here in Ontario most campuses have special constables on staff who are real officers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I am insanely jealous, hope your night was fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is on campus they're not actual police. Campus cops can make your time in school alot shittier if you give them a chance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got mine a while ago, maybe you weren't accepted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 04:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of anyone getting in trouble for it, I know dozens of people that have been doing it as long as me aswell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea but you don't need one to order online and the dispensaries here usually just make you fill out a form  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you don't I've been doing it since I started smoking 6 years ago  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 15:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Il say it... Foreign drivers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 14:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> L3 same as ps4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 13:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just make sure you get a powered one that plugs into the wall not just into your laptop, with won't provide enough power if you plug more then a few into it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 18:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed you have that compassion pricing program for people who earn under 21k a year. Does this apply to students? I haven't made a dollar all year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long to stay residential before going commercial? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 04:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long would it take to build up enough experience to be comfortable with commercial applications? I'm finishing school soon and will be getting out in the field here in Ontario with a g2 and obt2(if I pass) licences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you need any certifications to install in the US? In Canada you need a licence to install any gas appliances </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks brotha, I've been working on that aspect alot lately. Trying to make stuff sound cleaner and more professional  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threw a Bone Thugs acapella over a beat today, made it all in maschine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 03:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea that's it sorry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should be R3 on console I'm pretty sure 
Edit: L3 not R3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GTA represent
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too it's not gonna be that bad don't worry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Algonquin?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow good ear! Little Ann - Deep Shadows... Thanks man I appreciate it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tupac Remix Made Entirely in Maschine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 22:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends how much you get I was getting hps of some of the best kush I had for 1100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks this helped alot!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2 pics I have up are recent enough that I look the same, but I am gonna take new pics when I get back to college. And that's 400km away so they'll be different matches  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 03:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, plus it's ideal for students because it's right there. You can go on your breaks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 02:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the movie cannabis kid on Netflix. It's a true story about kids smuggling drugs over the Canadian/US border by walking across  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 02:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gym at Algonquin is waay cheaper than anywhere else. 30 bucks a month for 4 months is crazy cheap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 18:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of underachievers stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 01:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, your right I just need to take some more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 01:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are pretty much the only 3 half decent pics I have that aren't with my ex. I have no idea what I'm doing because last time I was single I was 17 years old  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 02:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up! I haven't really tried around with too many Canadian vendors as Terra was one of the first Canadian vendors I found. I will keep those in mind when I'm thinking of getting more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Wasn't wearing the right outfit I don't think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 23:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy capsules yourself from most health food stores. Cap it yourself. Capsule vendors are usually way overpriced and the ones I've bought from have had extremely weak kratom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrabotanicals has amazing customer service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 23:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been using Terrabotanicals for around 6 months now and I have been extremely pleased with their services. It's by far the cheapest source (for Canadians) with some of the strongest kratom I have came by. Everytime I ever have questions my emails have been responded to very promptly, usually within 10 minutes. 

Recently I had a problem with one of my orders not arriving. I usually received my package within 1-2 days even without tracking or express shipping, but this package took over a week so I knew something was up. I sent an email and Terrabotanicals shipped another package the next day. This package also failed to arrived in and I had to email them again. I was expecting to just have to cut my loses and start paying for tracking, but they sent another package and we're super apologetic! This one was with free tracking as well. I received my package the next day and was extremely pleased with their helpfullness. 

If anyone is looking for a good kratom vendor I would highly recommend Terrabotanicals. What an amazing company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maschine comes with tons of drum sounds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't the mods delete shit like this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 06:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same boat 3 year relationship tonights my first night on tinder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 10:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alchemist is one of my favourite producers so I really appreciate that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you're a lost cause man, good luck with your sampling  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 18:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only use reddit on mobile, the rules are still there... You just didn't take the time to read them. There is also a thread on the front page of this sub called "no stupid questions". You could have easily found way more resources on YouTube a lot quicker. You didn't even state what daw you use...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 17:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 82 days in, still had an eighth left when I quit, still have an eighth left now. Also still have all my weed paraphernalia but that is because I knew I wouldn't be quitting for good. I just need a nice long break. Also depends on how much self control you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 17:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Servers are great tons of people on both regardless if you have premium or not. I hated hardline, it's really shitty. Just go with bf4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 17:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't this posted like last week? Or is this a new one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 09:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can sample anything you want  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 23:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool thanks, sorry for the stupid questions lol this is my first time. I guess I can delete this thread now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 23:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I was definitely just over thinking it it climbed up to 65 after a bit, on a side note, my weed smells like hay... Is this a problem or will curing bring back the nice smell they had when they were on the plant?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 00:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 00:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldnt trust any street lsd today. Too many research chemicals going around being sold as cid. Darknet is the best way to get high quality lucy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medical marijuana patients can grow 'limited amount' of cannabis at home under new laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 00:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just get this different cough from taking a big vape hit or dab as if its tickling my throat. A lot different from coughing from smoke cause it doesn't hurt really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Canadian medical marijuana rules open door to legal home-growing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty stoked on this announcement. I think it was bullshit medical patients couldn't grow their own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea time stretching is shit on the sp so you really have to work around the sample. Shorter chops help with this. I usually do the sample first on the sp just cause you can't really fuck with it to much. Once you get the bpm if your using a loop you can make the drums after  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you been drinking more since you quit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh the off beat drums are kinda better in my opinion they make it sound more natural and less robotic. Many producers do this on purpose in their daw to make it sound more human  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 15:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I'm with wind ive never had any problems. Koodo was fine before but way to expensive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been a Joey fan since his first mixtape, haven't really been feeling this one but I'm not saying he's selling out or anything. He's been really blowing up the past year he needs something they can play on the radio.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried so many different variations with 20 bookshelves all 2 blocks away can't seem to get level 30 enchantments. What am I doing wrong? Took me so long to get this much leather and reeds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I'm not complaining. This is my first grow so I'm still just stoked they made it this far and actually look pretty decent. Hopefully next time il be in a more stable and controlled environment where I can do this properly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea these pics are of two plants, the last few that are more amber are off the one that's looking pretty much ready to harvest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90+ days from seed northern lights auto. Have to cut them today or tomorrow because I'm moving out in 10 days. Used a 3-1-2 non organic nutrient until veg then flora bloom for flower. Started flushing about 10 or 11 days ago. First time growing surprised I got this far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90+ days from seed northern lights auto. Have to cut them today or tomorrow because I'm moving out in 10 days. Used a 3-1-2 non organic nutrient until veg then flora bloom for flower. Started flushing about 10 or 11 days ago. First time growing surprised I got this far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best trichome shots I got with my shitty microscope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me just really been feeling this lately. I think it should have more views </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeremy Talon  SP404 Live Set  LeMellotron.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope... The only way I could find is with the molecular relay mission. So if you already did that I guess you're screwed. Im thinking about just starting a new playthrough instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 05:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word haven't done that in pentatonic minor yet will try that next time! I usually pitch it up to tune it but I was being pretty lazy this time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 03:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really appreciate getting feedback on here. Definitely shoulda spent more time on that part. Thanks bro!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rough beat I whipped up real quick today in maschine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you didn't pay your deposit... Like me lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 02:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/8pRkJt8
Just gonna leave this here. This was posted 4 months before he was ever arrested and got down voted to shit. The guy deleted his comments once everyone started messaging him and shit about it. But he's definitely Austrian cause he's got tons of posts in /r/Austria. I know it doesn't mean much but for me this just makes it a bit harder to think he's innocent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need an interface just get an aux to rca jack and sample from your phone/ computer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 05:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could of rented a stone saw for 20 bucks haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried getting a pic but the microscope I'm using is making it real hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happening for me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. I should double check to make sure I'm actually checking nugs and not sugar leaves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if I'm using a non organic nutrient?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50% cloudy 50% Amber trichomes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 17:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thanks for the help!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had organic nutes in the mail but UPS fucked me over and let some random person in my apartment building sign for it and take them so now I've been using floranova, which I'm honestly not sure is organic http://generalhydroponics.com/floranova/ it was all my local headshop had. Ive only fed them 3 times throughout the flowering period though because it took me awhile to get the nutes. Would Ph have cause them to get crispy? Because I only started stabilizing the pH to around 6-6.5 on the last few waterings, I feel like that fucked with them. It's also been a really hot summer here with no ac.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 16:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/0TzxB tried getting a pic of the trichs but the microscope I'm using made it to hard. It's probably more like 25/75 orange to cloudy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trichs are around 50/50 but I just started flushing yesterday. Do I wait for the flush to finish or will they be "overripe". Do I harvest now and risk them not tasting as good. This is my first grow so I have no experience with the matter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> jeech beats ||  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up here in Canada I've seen multiple people lace their shit with angel dust just to get people hooked. A good friend of mine got really fucked over from it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make a group with 4 or 5 patterns in it. Change each one to 1 bar, 2 bar, 4 bar, 8 bar, 16 bar and just use that group to pick how long you want the scene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to use remote breaching charge on ps4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What buttons do I press to place them on walls/doors? All I can do is throw them like a coin and they don't do anything unless they're placed properly. I've seen videos on YouTube but I cant find a way to get the green box to show up to stick it to a wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> soundswaveformsbasic sine 
add distortion/saturation, filter, compress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn I'd be there if I wasn't away for school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 06:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I saw them at Boots and Hearts festival last year and they actually performed "We Dem Boyz" by Wiz Khalifa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 20:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any headshop I've been to has had it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 18:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The basketball mobile game on Facebook is pretty good practice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 03:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't even seen an ekan here in Canada yet... Slowly building a ratatta army </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 01:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pay off debt, probably none of it would actually go towards music  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 15:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get high off the seeds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 05:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ottawa here, level 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 05:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can download the apk online or use a us apple account. Playing in Ontario right now. They use the same locations as ingress so there's tons of gyms and pokestops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 05:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It uses the same locations as ingress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 05:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 04:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to find a time article on police codeming other police using excessive lethal force on the public and can't find it, can you help?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 17:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Took 12 hours for me, I think they say on there website it could take 24-48 hours
2. Thats what I had to do but that all depends on if the guys cool with it. Won't make it go through any quicker though, unless the guy is loafting on sending the request. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 12:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't suggesting that you need it. I'm just giving more options for sampling. I don't see any other way of sampling from a ps4. It'd be alot easier for me to put it right through my interface and sample that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 05:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can sample any game with an hdmi splitter from eBay. They're like 10 bucks. Some games have some really great sounds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I really didn't want to have to just trash them as I put in alot of work to get this far. I have some bubble bags that I've yet to use so I might just fresh freeze them and try some bubble hash.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup gonna try and hold out as long as possible but you are right! I definitely learned alot and feel alot better for my next grow. Il definitely be ahead for that one!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 06:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely ottawa, that's Rideau street. Plus his shirt says "I 3 Ottawa" 
Source: Ottawa resident </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 21:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moving out of my apartment soon and was hoping these would be done by now but they're obviously not. I fucked them up a bit by not taking proper care of them. If I harvest now is it even worth it? They're about day 60-65 from spouting northern lights auto, I don't even really smoke anymore and decided it's probably better to save growing to when I have more resources and an actually place as I'm a college student right now. They could obviously go another month I just don't know if that's possible with my current situation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't already his album late Knight special is awesome. All of it was produced and written by him on analog equipment only.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 04:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see anyone in this thread saying that cooking frozen chicken is a safety hazard?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 02:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I just have no idea what you're trying to prove/say and was congratulating you for actually doing your own research instead of just asking for other people's opinion over the Internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 01:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could have to do with the frozen chicken making the ceramic really cold, and then putting it on high might have been to much of a temperature change cracking it. Don't take my word for it though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 00:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 21:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea ramming him with an SUV seems a little much... Guy looks like he was about to collapse from being so tired </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 21:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup it's a real hotel in Berlin! https://www.tripadvisor.com/LocationPhotoDirectLink-g187323-d240273-i128062612-Arte_Luise_Kunsthotel-Berlin.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 19:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hardline and bf4 were both 5$ on the ps store a couple weeks ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
