<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4819</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. The company I just resigned from was JUST bought by another company before I resigned!

And here I thought my first instinct was to say nah tc you're crazy, but quite frankly...  you're right, that IS what's happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know the former but the problem with the latter is that while they were originally really good and funny in dinging legitimate problems with movies, now they kind of have devolved to just saying "guy wearing shirt, ding! credits, ding!" so I kinda stopped watching them. I do like how there's occasional crossover between cinemasins, honest trailers, and even how it should have ended. Rather nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, pen-and-paper letters? That's very intimate and sweet in this day and age. You've just reminded me of penpals from my childhood, incidentally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any fun youtube channels you enjoy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like:

- Honest Trailers for movies

- Dorkly for video game related humor

- How it should have ended (also for movies)

- TeamFourStar's DBZ Abridged and Hellsing Abridged for hilarious takes on said shows

- ASAPscience and/or vsauce for anything sciency related

- collegehumor's 2009-2011 videos for just generally fun silly type comedy

- smbc theater

The last 2 don't really update anymore but they have some classic stuff from a decade ago that I find rather hilarious. The others still update regularly and if you've never seen them before have a ton of archived content to get through. Each has relatively specific set of humor for whatever kind you enjoy.

I also enjoy dry humor but haven't really come across channels that do that, only webcomics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The automod automatically removes any query that starts with "is" or "does" without even understanding the question. It's pretty annoying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially if the question calls for a long answer, not just a simple yes no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are yes/no type questions not allowed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is a raven like a writing desk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially a religious culture with a "doesn't matter what happens in this world only the next afterlife" mentality that excuses any kind of behaviour... just makes one sigh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Throwing a glass bottle of beverage from a moving care into the street and seeing it shatter into a thousand pieces of sharp glass

- breaking bottles on the beach and leaving trash lying around where anyone could step on something sharp and get tetanus god forbid

- throwing cans and empty bags of chips/snacks into the ocean

- not cleaning up after a barbecue picnic in a garden and having hundreds of styrofoam cups, paper plates and tissue paper just thrown on the grass willy nilly when there's a garbage can ***right there***

Among other, worse things. That operational enough of a definition for you? This is only a taste of what I see in this country *every single weekend* for the past 15 years of my life. You just have no idea what it's like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess probably because like what has been already said, people can't see the danger if they can't physically *see* the danger... ah well what can you do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Maybe you should learn Farsi and move to Iran

Hehe sarcasm :P ? I can only imagine the instability and tyrannical regime there. But yeah China and India, as fast developing nations, are ones to create the most pollution. And they won't listen to western countries like america telling them to be more responsible because it would sound hypocritical (since it is)

I don't know what to do either. There really are no easy answers. I can only hope one day we can form a united front but until that day comes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately the populace IS the one that's wealthy... government gives monetary bonuses (as well as having no taxes whatsoever) to keep the people "happy" and more importantly complacent so no one actually cares about change and are more into a "don't rock the boat" mentality when it comes to a variety of social issues. But for my part I just care about the environment, I don't care about social issues or the other pressing matters that plague the region...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck, I just try to appeal to the self-preservation instinct that I'm sure all humans have, in that taking care of where you live means you can continue to live in it... I don't know, it's just really difficult with some humans, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I try to look at it logically, shouldn't their kind at the very least think "I don't want to live in squalor" since that what's it is in squalor, you're eventually gonna live in a garbage dump with waist high trash and a sky so darkened by smog that you can't see the sun so to speak. I just try to appeal to the survivalist rationale that ALL humans have, if you want to survive and be sustainable you have to take care of where you live... right? 

Just wish they could see it that way. But most people just think it's being preachy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah very true... That's just a case of ignorance, and something about developing countries where they don't care about pollution at all. Difficult to really explain or fix besides having a more educated populace. I'd like to think that ideally education can fix or at least be  a start to fix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 360 version of vesperia is the one that came out first... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't get it... what does that make me? Someone who was bothered by it since I was a kid? It's human to be apathetic and evil but not kind and conscientious?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we see that stuff every day. I don't know where you live but I'm tired of the smog and not being able to BREATHE outside from the smell of diesel, cigarette smoke, and all the fumes that large buses emit. I travel to places with mountains and forestry just to be able to breathe in the smell of greenery, which is all but non existent in arabia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends where you live. In America sure, people have become more conscientious of the environment. But in developing countries and the arab world? A majority of the population of man just don't care, even after made aware of the situation. Most remain seemingly ignorant about throwing their garbage in the middle of a park, and just damn jerkish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> explain tales of symphonia 2 being on ps3, as well as 1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't get it. I don't get most humans here and their lack of care for the place where they live, littering and polluting and scoffing at the idea of just taking that extra step to you know, NOT throw a bag of trash into the ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is caring about the environment something a majority of people are so averse to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is absolutely no reason we still haven't gotten Tales of Vesperia on ps4. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If nintendo can change up a zelda (drastically no less) and Sony can win a gen again after what happened with the ps3 and cloud can be in super smash then there is literally no reason Tales of Vesperia in english should remain only on 360. The rules have changed with exclusivity nonsense.

The fact that we still haven't gotten it when tales of symphonia, a gamecube game and tales of symphonia 2, a wii game was released on ps3 is highly suspect. I don't doubt microsoft paid for exclusivity, but like with gta 4's timed dlc exclusivity, that eventually runs out. Bamco namdai should have released this tales game like they have with all these other ones the last 6 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is absolutely no reason we still haven't gotten Tales of Vesperia on ps4. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If nintendo can change up a zelda (drastically no less) and Sony can win a gen again after what happened with the ps3 and cloud can be in super smash then there is literally no reason Tales of Vesperia in english should remain only on 360. The rules have changed with exclusivity nonsense.

The fact that we still haven't gotten it when tales of symphonia, a gamecube game and tales of symphonia 2, a wii game was released on ps3 is highly suspect. I don't doubt microsoft paid for exclusivity, but like with gta 4's timed dlc exclusivity, that eventually runs out. Bamco namdai should have released this tales game like they have with all these other ones the last 6 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fog is awesome, may you direct me to it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't the funny subreddit contain anything actually humorous? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is iron man's super power? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's always been great, but modern family has given more opportunity to show her incredulous look at something the family may have done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this forum's problem, what's with the 0 thumbs up arrows...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's everyone's job like and hours spent from day to day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did they make Aunt May attractive in civil war and spiderman homecomig? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which do people like more 6-pack or flat stomach? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thank you, same to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arabia. Maybe it's because you're all so close to each other that you had an agreement over what rapid firing guns would sound like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for us the sound of machine gun always sounds like "dov dov dov" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guns go bang not rat tat tat... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the hell does "ratata" equal gun shooting noise? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thanks appreciate it :D ! Wish I could claim it for myself but unfortunately can't, it was on whatsapp feed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many on this board are all vegan and/or vegetarian? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If vegans and vegetarians love animals so much why do they keep eating said animals' food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So darn true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just wasn't fun. The thing with the gta clones of that gen is that they're just not fun, and they always feel off compared to gta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thank you, so glad you were able to find this topic since it's a few days old so usually fall into obscurity at the last page of the sub... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because infamous's sequel was all over the place and didn't quite know what to do with itself. I think maybe they should have just dropped the whole "karma" system and focused on doing just a fun game. Either that or at least at the start of the game pick if you're going to be evil or "good" so you unlock the special exclusive powers and missions for the one you chose. 

Because other than its over the top Grimdark setting, infamous WAS a fun game. I liked 2 for having a better melee system, since infamous 1 was basically a shooter disguised as a superhero game and since I hate shooters I kept playing it as a melee game but got my butt kicked due to how tough and precise enemies were with their bullets. But I enjoyed the climbing mechanics (you can definitely see the sly Cooper inspiration here) and open world feel. I just don't think they planned for much of a story and hit a wall after coming up with the concept of the apocalyptic "beast" character as the premise of the game. Then didn't know what to do after that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't a gamer 10-20 years ago so I can identify with this hehe, never knew what L3 or R3 even were since the one or 2 games I did play never used them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should, especially if you like fun over an emphasis on edgy tryhard like that one franchise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They Um kind of weren't though, only sly was. Ratchet and clank is through and through a shooter (albeit a fun one with a great sense of humor and guns that turn enemies into sheep, fun stuff like that) and the less said about jak and daxter  the better, another shootery type. Sly Cooper is the only one that stayed true to its roots as a platformer and never lost sight of its fun Saturday morning cartoon look in an industry that was shifting away from fun and eventually entering the brown-and-bloom shooter gen with bald space marines who smoke spit and swear all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Frozen was rather sloppy with an obvious amount of a lot of rewrites. Plus at over a billion at the box office, I wouldn't say people didn't like it, the movie still made a ton and was wildly popular. The people who hate it because it's popular and not for real, actual reasons don't count.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 will subscribe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why aren't we allowed to feed the ducks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for saying what I was thinking, the ending credits are RUINED by whoever's unpleasant voice was singing moana's song. It's like, why not get moana to sing it again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had a threesome scheduled for last night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were a couple of noshows but I still had fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the top 5 Modern Family episodes to rewatch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wondering what everyone's favorite episode is and what they loved about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What benefits does the soil get from dead human bodies, if any? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does porn keep insisting on calling girls "bitches" ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the JRPG whose plot overall has the lowest stakes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Sly Cooper series is such a great set of platformers that seemingly never were as popular as Jak and Daxter or Ratchet and Clank. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Following a gen of annoying collectathons, the first Sly Cooper was almost a reprieve with its straight platforming with no added mumbo jumbo. Sure there were the bottles to collect but it was just that, the platforming was the core of the game. The thing that brings it down is those tedious minigames, which unfortunately plague the series for some unknown reason. But being a Racoon that climbs stuff was a fun gameplay mechanic. 

Then we have Sly 2, one of the best sequels that improves upon the original and is an open world mission based sneaking around game, best of which is it didn't devolve into a gta clone like a certain other Sony property. The best thing about the Sly series for people who love platformers is that it stayed a platformer throughout, as well as retaining its lightheartedness and sense of humor. 

Sly 2 is amazing, like seriously amazing, true there were some minigames but its the kind of sequel that really does rock. Love what they did with the Klaww gang and bringing Clockwerk back in that manner. The whole Arpeggio a bird who cant fly bit. Actually the entire Sly Cooper series has this sympathetic villains thing, I love it. This series isnt given enough credit, it really isnt. Essentially it's like a heist film brought to life in video game form, best way to describe it.

Sly 3 unfortunately was a step back, or rather just a stumbling sidestep before falling down. The game feels  rushed (released only one year after Sly 2) AND they wasted precious developer time on silly 3d. The blue-and-red cheap glasses in the box kind of 3d. It was basically Sly 2 but even more minigames and you barely play as the Sly so much as you do every other furry friend of the Cooper gang.

Sly 4 is a surprising, very surprising return to form. And by a different developer no less! Yeah they had a lot of good ideas here, and a lot of them worked. Only problem is I wanted more, they coulda done more, but I dont blame them especially after the stories I hear concerning budget and time restrictions.

Overall, it's still a fun series, and makes you wish there were more platformers of its kind with fun stuff like sneaking around, gorgeous cel-shaded graphics that give it a Saturday Morning Cartoon feel (you just don't see that anymore) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Sly Cooper series is such a great set of platformers that seemingly never were as popular as Jak and Daxter or Ratchet and Clank. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Following a gen of annoying collectathons, the first Sly Cooper was almost a reprieve with its straight platforming with no added mumbo jumbo. Sure there were the bottles to collect but it was just that, the platforming was the core of the game. The thing that brings it down is those tedious minigames, which unfortunately plague the series for some unknown reason. But being a Racoon that climbs stuff was a fun gameplay mechanic. 

Then we have Sly 2, one of the best sequels that improves upon the original and is an open world mission based sneaking around game, best of which is it didn't devolve into a gta clone like a certain other Sony property. The best thing about the Sly series for people who love platformers is that it stayed a platformer throughout, as well as retaining its lightheartedness and sense of humor. 

Sly 2 is amazing, like seriously amazing, true there were some minigames but its the kind of sequel that really does rock. Love what they did with the Klaww gang and bringing Clockwerk back in that manner. The whole Arpeggio a bird who cant fly bit. Actually the entire Sly Cooper series has this sympathetic villains thing, I love it. This series isnt given enough credit, it really isnt. Essentially it's like a heist film brought to life in video game form, best way to describe it.

Sly 3 unfortunately was a step back, or rather just a stumbling sidestep before falling down. The game feels  rushed (released only one year after Sly 2) AND they wasted precious developer time on silly 3d. The blue-and-red cheap glasses in the box kind of 3d. It was basically Sly 2 but even more minigames and you barely play as the Sly so much as you do every other furry friend of the Cooper gang.

Sly 4 is a surprising, very surprising return to form. And by a different developer no less! Yeah they had a lot of good ideas here, and a lot of them worked. Only problem is I wanted more, they coulda done more, but I dont blame them especially after the stories I hear concerning budget and time restrictions.

Overall, it's still a fun series, and makes you wish there were more platformers of its kind with fun stuff like sneaking around, gorgeous cel-shaded graphics that give it a Saturday Morning Cartoon feel (you just don't see that anymore) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thank you, much appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't say that about yourself! You're a good person unlike the unhelpful, sarcastic users who posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, I've gone to it a couple of times. It's a bit inactive but generally has generated some very fun to read discussions about movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's because in Europe, everything is tiny, so one forgets that in America stuff has bigger sizes and is more accommodating than pretty much all European countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds great, I like it when people at a store are nice and helpful. Monolith?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I mention it's not meant for a healthy active woman, but rather one trying to lose weight. Plus I personally am hesitant to rely on counting calories method in the first place  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does 2.5D animation look like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 11:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will they finish building the 9/11 towers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The r/movies board is so goddamn awful in that they just seem to discuss celebrity news gossip of blockbusters rather than talking about the actual movies themselves, and it's quite frustrating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I'm told the calorie intake for you should only be around 1400 to 1600... but I still feel counting calories is needlesly tiring and ultimately a hassle in the long run when most people don't and just remain healthy due to exercise and genetics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm maybe you're right. The ordering online thing definitely makes a lot of sense at the very least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's gonna hire or keep on staff an expensive employee unless they're in the upper echelons of management and have leverage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... clothes manufacturers don't sell beyond a couple of x's so how do they even find shirts and pants big enough for 300+ pound people?

Parking spaces are not nearly wide enough to park between cars and still able to get out if you're as wide as half the car itself... 

And if they work in an office setting, how would they even manage weaving and bopping between chairs and desks... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How exactly are the morbidly obese in America managing in terms of finding clothes, wide enough parking spaces, sturdy enough chairs, etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol so true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best place for talking about relatively unknown shows and movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it peach color? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What IS the color of Caucasian skin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither do we, it's a marketing tool more than anything else, something to put on the dvd cover or streaming blurb to get people who don't already know it's amazing to watch it. That's all really. I still wish moana made a billion dollars at the box office like frozen instead of half that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loool I'm glad I wasn't the only one who got finding Nemo vibes from the turtle. Half expected to seem him later in the movie as an adult turtle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So darn true, I've come across that so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the secret sign to get the barber to trim your nose hairs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How good is the upside down kiss popularized by the spiderman movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Such a classic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm rewatching it, at first for the nostalgia but now I'm legitimately interested in the lore and characters that I've always loved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet but I definitely saw paperman, which has the very definition of adorable in the woman in the short, she's so lovely. Also thanks for the video for I love watching that kinda stuff, making of videos and the like of disney pixar stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's why the ocean chose her in the first place after all, for her compassion and caring. I think that's what the scene was meant to illustrate, Moana's huge heart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What bothers me is why Disney released these 2 amazing movies back to back in one year? Why didn't they release Zootopia in 2015 so it could win the 2015 Oscar and Moana in 2016 so it could win the 2016 Oscar? Such amazing movies, they both deserved to make billions at the box office *and* win academy award recognition so more people see it and more people are inspired by such amazing films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true. AS a matter of fact, Disney did their research for A LOT of this movie, which is probably why it's particularly enjoyable and fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the actual movie itself is beyond fantastic. I've rewatched it thrice in the past week and keep singing the songs on the commute to work. This is one of those instant classic movies that I immediately fell in love with. It's just so amazing. The beautiful visuals, the story that hits close to home (the lyrics "find happiness right where you are" particularly struck a chord with me) and how it has a classic odyssey type adventure feel of a character going on a journey, overcoming obstacles and returning home changed, wiser, ready to lead, very classic "hero with a thousand faces" type journey done in a spectacular manner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a really good show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did no one watch Suburgatory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't peg this place, what exactly is everyone like on here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the age range of the users on here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally cried due to how adorable this scene is. It could have been a disneypixar short all on its own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moana saves a baby turtle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 10:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am rewatching the show and wanting to discuss it with people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who likes Disney's Gargoyles on here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 10:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know if you do, we can discuss all about it here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm apprehensive about bringing stuff back decades later, it usually never pans out. 

Perhaps it's best to be cautiously optimistic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think it was a running joke or something. 

I can't even remember how it ended, the last episode I watched was the musical where they sum up everything that's happened up to date.

I hear the show was canceled/ended on a cliffhanger and that makes me sad, I'd have loved to see more from it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh gosh me too, I remember I had toys of the gargoyles both in stone form and regular form. I'd constantly pretend they'd be breaking out of their stone form and then substitute it with the regular action figure while playing. Man I was so into gargoyles in every way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, **I** was thinking of going back to rewatch beast wars and reboot as well! I was enjoying gargoyles so much that I thought it might be fun to rewatch some other darn classic shows that are ahead of their time (and in the case of reboot/beast wars pretty much spearheaded the uses of computer animation for tv cartoons...)

How good was Reboot though, amazing right? You should make a topic about it, I'd love to discuss Enzo and the gang, the villains like hexadecimal, the works. Such a great show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10,000 thumbs up arrows for best food to use in a food fight? I mean... really now. Plus it's kinda wasteful when you think about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my gosh that's pretty much what I said regarding liking the song when it became all dark and sinister! So nice to see other people felt the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I much prefer biker mice from Mars in that regard hehe. 

I was also a fan of tiger sharks which part of " the comic strip" lineup:

https://youtu.be/3bTJaikGw_M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are silly questions the ones that get the most thumbs up arrows? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I particularly became amazed by was when I found out Keith David voiced Goliath, my childhood hero. Hearing Goliath's voice still gives me goosebumps, I love it so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even better. I love the show but I *particularly* love when they go back in time to the gargoyles age, since I like the fantasy and mystical elements more than the modern day setting (I've always liked the romanticism of castles with secret passages and dungeons with different colored potion vials, that sorta thing. Both as a kid and now carried into late adulthood) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah hehe.  I'm not much of a star trek guy or sci-fi in general so can't appreciate that they use a majority of the actors from said star treks to voice the characters on gargoyles. However I've always been intrigued by the fact that there are so many Shakespeare references in the show lie Macbeth and midsummer night's dream, calling Demona that name like in Othello's Desdemona, that sort of thing. Made me actually enjoy reading Shakespeare back in school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was downright obsessed with the show and would constantly imitate how the gargoyles walk and silly things like drape a towel around me like a cloak :p... 

I pretty much owned all the toys and action figures of the gargoyles as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rock eyebrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely let me know once you do and want to discuss any of these shows or their characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some dvds on amazon if you're interested. They were on youtube for a while, disney were having their own streaming service to rival netflix's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty good. I was recommended it myself and while initially on the fence I've grown to enjoy it immensely, and it's pretty much the best post DC Animated Universe show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And spectacular spiderman, the best iteration of spiderman in any show or movie to date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was feeling awfully nostalgic since I always talk about how awesome greg weisman is to anyone who'll listen (creator of gargoyles, spectacular spiderman and young justice) and how it's unfair that all his shows get canceled despite them being amazing.

Decided to get the entire series, and now I'm just watching it over the weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh my gosh yes! I owned it too, I remember disney released a vhs of the pilot, which contained the first 5 episodes of the series as one long movie. At the end they showed the board game with rules on how to play it. Good times...
 
Although, rewatching the show now has made me realize that they actually cut out quite a few scenes in the vhs tape release compared to the actual episode. It's little things, but these little things become very important plot points later on in the series, like the gargoyle eggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a classic simpsons joke, one I remember watching fondly with my old man so your post just put a smile to my face when I remembered it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean Roman Numerals? The first thing I thought of when I read that sentence was this:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Exiy5eVMzg4

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QEGwKTQrqmQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone here grow up with the show Gargoyles? I'm rewatching it now after decades. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the opening: https://youtu.be/CjI0TdvVbqI

It was an extremely nostalgic, bittersweet reunion to rewatch this show that's more than 20 years old, so many memories. 

I'm now in season 2 and am actually watching it because it's a really great show and I'm interested in the lore, not just the nostalgic reminiscence of my childhood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO true/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wow. AC 4 black flag is basically like if we got a pirates of the Caribbean game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wow. AC 4 black flag is basically like if we got a pirates of the Caribbean game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good one. 

There are some things that annoy me (regenerating health stupidity over having health potions like in the ezio trilogy) but I weirdly enjoy sailing when in 3 I hated it at the beginning. 

Also, the game's color palette is gorgeous. When I was in Havana I totally got vice city vibes. The sparkly crystal clear blue ocean... it's beautiful in this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup I think it might be so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the Romani people ("gypsies") supposed to be like Europe's bedouins? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Captain* Jack Sparrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does America still use the Imperial System, who keeps the Metric System down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can loot the medicine off dead bodies... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care about challenge,  I care about fun. I'm not expecting Demon Souls when I pop in Assassin's Creed. I'm expecting to just let off some steam doing parkour and assassination missions after a long hard day. To have fun and easiness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charlie Chaplin's smile in City Lights is one of the sweetest images in movie history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... and? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is much more annoying and tedious to run around like a doofus waiting for the health to regenerate on its own, and is too reminiscent of the shooter genre which I personally am not a fan of. 

Plus I feel being able to have health potions at hand is a consolation prize for all the bugs and glitches the ac series has, such as continually swinging at enemy for some reason doesn't seem to register as a kill despite said enemy stumbling and getting blood spurts and flesh wounds all over the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the opposite in fact, I believe you switched the description of the 2 movies as wreck-it ralph is the one that has an overarching story (not to mention an amazing twist that I personally did not see coming, don't know about you) while Brave was basically "oh rebellious teen, doesn't want to do what her mother/parents want her to do, bah" and the whole bear nonsense was once again, just that. I wasn't deeply metaphoric or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What even IS the legend of Zelda? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did they opt for regenerating health over using health potions after the ezio trilogy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would certainly make the bugginess and glitches more tolerable to have a safety net like that.

I'm just curious over the change when introducing health potions in ac 2 was one of the best improvements to the series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnny Depp is the one I would have thought would be bored of doing a caricature of a caricature. P3 was pushing it but then 4 cane into the foray and it's like, damn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Keira Knightley being in Deadpool 2 the reason why she didn't participate in the upcoming Pirates of the Caribbean 5 movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the point I was making.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest water, nature's caffeine. 

Also adrenaline shots injected directly into the brain stem, nature's *other* caffeine :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While the academy award has never been a symbol of quality, the prestige surrounding it is undeniable, and wreck it Ralph wining could have paved the way for a better utilization of video games as settings and stories for movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wreck-it Ralph was robbed of the 2012 Oscar in favor of Brave, and I'm still peeved about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here was an absolutely fun and emotionally heartfelt movie, with a really great unique story that lost to... a really bad generic one about turning into a bear (didn't disney already do that with the brother bear movie?)

It's a damn shame because Ralph had such a fun unique setting and is one of the very few instances of incorporating video games into the setting and story well. 

Just a damn shame the academy couldn't look past "ew video games" and most people didn't see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, I think op may have mentioned that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pirates of the Caribbean: The curse of the black pearl is one of the greatest movies of all time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of those movies that only gets better with age (in every sense of the word)

Back in 2004 it was just this fun movie that came out, but every rewatch shows something more to the movie, be it how amazing it looks to bringing back the swashbuckler type movie (really only it and the mask of zorro seem to be the only swashbuckler types in the modern age...) to just how damn funny the lines are. And yet at the same time can get super serious and dark for a disney produced movie.  Geoffrey rush's portrayal of a pirate is still 10/10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, the infamous one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wonderful, wish you the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thank you, very much appreciated. Are the two of you interested in doing creampies as well or not so much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True true, some good examples so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I wouldn't be surprised if I saw whichever version of power Rangers that was, do you know which series it was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh cool just tell me more when you're ready, I'm interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't sticking to them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a trope on tvtropes where a villain takes the child of the good guy to raise as their own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For any number of reasons, such as to stick it to the good guy, or generally want an offspring of their own but settle for the next best thing. 

Off the top of my head, I remember the show Angel doing something like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah so what do I search for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a matter of fact I can, tell me more : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *****Shudders***** lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have been my reason for liking it as an adolescent as well if I'm being honest...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one are you referring to with that pronoun?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why haven't taxis stepped up their service yet after Uber and such came into the mix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing. All the things I mentioned were and always have been distractions to make me not think about the fact that I have no friends, no one to simply *talk* to. And those things, electronics and whatnot, are no longer enough, I want more out of life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you even DO with life if you have no friends, no people to share it with, no companionship of any sort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one to talk about common interests and hobbies with (if you still have them and haven't felt it pointless to continue watching a movie/show, reading a book or playing a game, if you have no one to discuss the various mediums with) . Hell, no people that even speak the same language as you.

It's just such a lonely lonely existence. The kind that makes you tired of living it. So tired...

And once your youth and health leave you... what happens then? Truly I'll have nothing left, if I decide to live long enough to lose those last 2 things that I have through the ravages of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appreciate it. I've been there before, and the community is pretty darn nice and enjoyable to talk with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for the opportunity to talk to people about anything, about any show, book, movie or video game or any type of entertainment media that they might not be able to do so in real life? That's why I'm here, as someone who lives in the arab lands and can't find people that speak english, much less have seen a show like Happy Endings or a movie like Marty, a game like Ace Attorney or a book like the count of monte cristo. It gets frustrating not being able to share one's passion with others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they need to fall asleep, I wonder if they've considered melatonin, maybe some asmr sounds or even physical stimulation...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd definitely believe it when it comes to the Fox network. Not sure if I'd believe the 9/11 thing another user in this topic stated but I wouldn't put it past them either considering America was a very weird time post the events, 2002 was a pretty unfortunate time in America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this scenario, they have a spouse and a job that puts food on the table and see it fit to complain? What some people wouldn't give to have a significant other. To have the basic comforts and securities of life. 

I doubt the perpetually angry on internet kind even have anything resembling a relationship with real humans away from the computer screen they stare at... it would require all the other emotions like compassion, something they sorely lack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember making that joke too... moderately good times as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh that's what you meant. Sounds cool and very prophetic!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fixing movies: 2012's Spiderman should have been the Miles Morales Spiderman with Donald Glover cast as Spiderman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of remaking the same movie over again and putting the director who made 500 days of summer in charge (will never understand that decision) they should have explored an alternate venue, like maybe a spiderman set in the future where the original spiderman is a legend/myth and this new spiderman picks up the mantle. 

I dunno, just anything is better than those asm movies in 2012 and 2014 shudder. Plus it would be have been interesting to see Donald Glover play Spiderman, I can't *not* see him in the role now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you even talking about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is being perpetually angry on the internet not exhausting for those kinds of people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do internet "tough guys" not get tired of being constantly on edge in every post they make and aggressively mean when it's physically and mentally draining? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone identify czech streets 97 sylva/silvie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.spankbang.com/wyud/video/czech+streets+97+sylva+new+hot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember that show Dark Angel? With jessica alba </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good times. I used to watch this show in my youth and was really into it, but I think t got canceled (they always do)

Anyone remember it? Thinking of rewatching it, maybe spotting actors that went on to do other things, like Jensen Ackles in supernatural. 

And of course, Jessica alba had never looked better in that show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do a lot of culures view cats as... attractive/sexy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, what even IS r/all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does one get on R/all ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Privacy... window? Curious what that is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This automoderator guy is getting really annoying...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still is very specific to night time, what about during the day when there's light everywhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have it uploaded on the other sites like xvideos/redtube/xhamster?

I only ask because I can't access pornhub, live in the repression loving mideast after all : ( ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
