<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4399</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe u seen me do it. was it a synaptic with hotrod flames? lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have a negative kd. but i can get way over a 1 kd if i want. i just like to have fun and run around with crazy setups. 

i have screenshots of 40+ kills on tdm 2/3 deaths. 

the reason for that is when the enemy team shit talks my shity team and my shitty kd. lol i end up owning them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats offense to dogs. chill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the tickets are locked behind supplydrops. literally unwatchable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> doesnt work  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao. imagine porky pig...they they they they there's a guy cappin A.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you quit now, thatl be the end of it, but if you camp, i WILL find you and i WILL kill you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmfaooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd buy a VO pack if it was made by </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> morgan Freeman 

that moviefone guy

icecube

vin diesel

thor

also, I'd buy it all for a discounted price or maybe 3500 salvage for 1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> keep chin up , or i break it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hell no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> turista kinda looks similarly to combine from bo3. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i got this gun week 1 the game came out. never used it since. dont lile it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i sent a request. hmu lets run some matches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol word. im mostly a HC player. though i dabble in core from time to time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nyc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lookout for punannymagnet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats ur psn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> only u got this joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> queens Ny here. by jfk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> enemy ufo spotted above.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omle de fumage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hc is the best. its all i play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sick n tired people asking how is a weapon right after they got it.  bruh, u got the weapon. go test it out. itl be different if u were thinking about buying it with salvage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats because the population is LOW. i play only hc snd...i play with the same people everyday. believe it or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will intersteller travel become a reality within 50 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all codes have been redeemed. damn that was quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in no way am i a booster or condone that kind of thing but just standing there not doing anything doesnt warrant a ban also. how are you going to get banned for literally not doing anything? makes no sense. yeah, they might be farming keys but so what? you get free kills and nukes. i wish i can get into a lobby with afkers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is the new weapon implementation a conspiracy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, i get, SP holders get it free and reg users do challenges to get it. everybody wins. 


or do they?

remember when they brought out the first sets of weapons?
they had it as craftable, but it was soo early in the game, not that many people had salavge to craft them. 


skip ahead 4 months, now they're giving away the base weapons and everybody is applauding them for basically giving it away for free but dont even notice they added the BEST variants of it behind RNG, while a majority is sitting on a ton of salavge. I'm personally sitting on 9,386 salvage after crafting the flatline,chaos,bomber,cyclopean,corruption,invective and r3kt.


when exactly are they going to put craftable epic weapons? or they plan on stopping that, giving us base weapons and have the epic counterparts locked behind supplydrops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mw3
bo1
bo2
iw
bo3
aw
mw2
ghosts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a rusher. i have NOTHING againist people camping. i Camp sometimes when i play against good players. it makes ZERO sense to rush into the open with good players. other than that, if im rushing getting kills and my teammates are camping in a building with cryomine + c4, im happy, because i know they're getting less deaths and thats good for tdm because its helping OUR team. if its one thing i hate, is that when bad players give the enemy a warden, thor or apex. I hate when im single handedly winning a tdm match, but the enemy gets a scorestreak from my bad teammates and shuts me down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao. that guy is the bane of my existence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have MANY exploits and breaches i use to hide n kill enemies on alot of maps that was provided by infinity ward. i have no shame in using these exploits because it just proves these cockroaches activision scooped from the bottom of the barrel to call themselves infinity ward, cant code. everyday something new is broken. like the new key glitch. key progress doesnt show up in after action report. these roaches break more than they fix. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao what kind of FRIENDS give u shit for a low spm? 12yr olds? lol get some real friends kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its excellent for me. 1s1k everytime. i play hc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bro. u already got the gun without using any salvage. go test it yourself and see how good it is. if it isnt good, no worries. u got it free.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where do i Find CLANS for Hc SnD? ....i dont want to PARTY UP....yet..,but does anyone know any snD clan websites? I play hc snd 90% of the time....solo. Getting kind of boring. looking to change things up. any hints on sites? subs? psn community? or i guess if you play snd also, hmu. psn is in flair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> not sure where to go to specifically to... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i use only 3. lol and im MP12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao. i play snd only. i managed to get a vulture from CP on frontier. 3-0....whipped out the vulture, layed prone in the main hallway behind a headglitch and that sob chased after 4 enemies. lmao. with the final killcam too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i login. collect my bonus. i logout. i WIN everytime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bruh, thats what permanent unlocks are for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tell those guys to being back futurama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hop on. spawn in. guy shoots me in back. rage quit. 7 secs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have a shitty Kd because i rush and dont play tactically ( most of the time). i dont care about kd because it takes away the fun from the game. last week, ( i have proof if anyone want to see ), ran into a clan shit talkers with 2/3 kds out to get nukes. i simply said, you wont get a nuke in my lobby. they were laughing at me because i had a .8 kd. game ended. no nukes were dropped. i went 42-10 and i stopped all their nuke streaks. they called me a bitch and left the lobby. they rejoined a new lobby ( lobby shopping ) , they saw me and left. HC KC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i got dupes too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> repost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no. 1 bullet and move to the next victim. we don't waste time emptying a whole magazine in 1 player with bad hit detection. people say HC takes No Skill because every gun is Op. we dont get minimap or hud unless we EARN IT. Hc taught me to read spawns with no uav needed. when i jump back to core once in a blue, its ridiculously easy to drop a 50 bomb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i play pubs because i was adopted and my mom doesnt know who the father is. one of my friends suggested cod because someone is always fucking mothers here.  to my suprise, I've been told atleast 356 players fucked my mom so far. its kind of hard now, to pinpoint who my father actually is, so dna results is a must. in my continued endeavors to find my father, when i do, ill update this comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no wonder my propulsion feels iffy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i bought 2 ans they were all dupes. i got vid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> none. reimaged maps play shitty. its never the SAME feeling. just bring back the original, lile they did in ghosts with favela. wall run/advanced movement? fuck that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mission would work better. i loved hardhat btw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> anybody notice this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they changed the sound for the spaceship and rc8 gesture toys.


why tho? it was great before. sounds like shit now and it goes away too fast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hc snd? or core? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you recommend younger women doing what you are doing? 18+ of course. im sure the money is more than what a college grad would make.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i knew it from day one. but i guess common sense isnt that common.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i understand now. thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i see. i see. thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not certain what you mean by stack...?

but going by the games logic, if i earned 2 UK, I SHOULD'VE earned 2 MK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me figure something out about my medals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it possible to get 1 mega kill medal, but i earned 2 ultra kill medals? Shouldn't that mean I should've earned 2 mega kill medals as well?

mega kill - killed 7 enemies within short period of time. 

ultra kill - killed 8 enemies within a short period of time. 

pic: https://imgur.com/F9Tz8oB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HH would make people sign in and play everday. increaseing the population of players. better lobbies. more sales in SD. currently people just pogin for DB and sign off. no incentive to play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they do this every week.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what do u mean by FAIR? TIME ZONES is the same time for everyone. itl be respectively 5-7 for everyone. no matter where they live.  what does fair have to do with anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Hour - 5pm - 7pm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Infinity ward, why not have happy hour everyday, in which players will earn 2x keys,  2xp , 2x weapon xp or 2xp MT and just make that 5th day random rewards each match? or would that be too much work to make it random each match? or you could give us a random crate in QM which will determine what we will get that day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im not here to post comments to receive codes. im here to receive codes and give Op black eye if codes are not received.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah agreed. im still learning the editor though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh word? that guy is the coolest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's the first time I've ever used an emblem editor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 07:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> based off my favorite show. 

pics: https://imgur.com/a/B7it4

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im at mp11-32 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok so let me ask u something. why do they have so many game modes? some like tdm, some like dom, some like kc, and some like snd? snd is all i play. nothing else. im not going to put the game down just because they broke it and i stop earning keys. i bought the game to play it, to play snd. they broke it, they SHOULD compensate people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah i figured but i hope they compensate me for my missing keys. ive been playing since first patch and thats probably over 100 keys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hc snd removed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nooooooooooooooo. its all i play. playlist update. hc snd removed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> strictly hc snd player here. i can confirm all of this. im more pissed about the keys though. since first patch ive been playing ranking up mp11, and up to now im playing with no keys awarded. thats probably over 100 keys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool. what about the players that weren't earning keys since first update? any type of compensation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> new update broke the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> winners circle doesnt work 

and we stop earning keys. havent earned a key since update.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wha gwan popcaan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i thought the same thing. MP for months. ive probably banked like 7 prestiges in XP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> winners circle bug post patch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 00:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> patch error </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its NOT the studios property. its the property of their real life manufacturer. back in cods older days, they paid money for the names to be used. laws permit then to copy the same gun, but not use its real name unless fees are paid. they went the cheap route.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> licensing fees. its cheaper to name them something else than pay the fees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks to my post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fasle advertising  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very well thought out. but people fail to realize we are not talking about the gambling aspect of the situation. they are guaranteeing a prize that is dupe protected when infact its not. its like going to the casino and going to the machine that says, put money in me, and i guarantee you will win money but doesnt payout anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trust me. they already saw it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i will. i tried to contact and talk with GAMERGOLDIN, an Iw dev, and he keeps avoiding my questions and makes no comment on the current situation. instead, he tells me to stop all communication with him. i saw he replied on another thread, and again, i asked him if they plan on changing the description of the triple play and the Op of that thread says im berating him and to leave him alone and not to bother him. smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when are you going to change the description on the triple play bundle, unless you plan on milking the TP for customers who don't know they're going to get dupes until you " find a fix "? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mean my post. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> alohatube is better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> furthermore, I've never actually said , that i bought cp and got dupes. i said people are getting dupes becauses of false ads. read between the lines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. on my kids life, I've never bought triple play. I'm voicing my posts for other users. dont be so quick to judge and call people stupid. if you dont believe i have a kid, look at my post history from other subs way before i made this post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stupid? lol mortgage and creditcards are scams too. but if you signed up with a CC and it says 0% apr for 12 months and when u go to pay your bill ,you notice they did infact, charge you interest within that 12 month, you'd be pissed too. its called false advertisement. no ones arguing cp is a problem, but if they guarantee you something and they fall back on their offer. it becomes a problem. get your facts together before you run up in my comment section spitting your ignorant argument about people being stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> amen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lucky for you guys. song won't budge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> amen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the FIRST step of fixing ANY problem is first admitting there is one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reddit is a proper channel. calling them out is the right way. 

the key glitch was evidence of the players stealing from THEM. 

the triple play non dupe protected was them stealing from US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> didn't do the key gitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " sorry for any inconvenience this may have caused, we're looking into this " . And you never hear from them again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are missing the point. gambling is 1 thing, but saying something is duped protected when infact its NOT, is wrong. thats the point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a user was saying they did, BUT the camos still look like crap on most weapons. a good example is all the FLAG camos. all look like crap except the American one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes i saw , but people are still getting epic dupes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course. i agree 100% . my post wasnt necessarily for cod points alone. it was to make a statement in general about the false advertising towards the triple play bundle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/276QlkY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have no idea how IW   activision  are ripping off customers left and right  with false advertising and when someone is calling them out, youre defending this company? what they're are doing is very poor business practices and blatantly wrong to the players.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking about the rares. it says 1 dupe protected QM hack and 1 dupe protected mk2 hack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i havent gotten mine in 2 days. seasonpass holder here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infinity Ward, why is it OKAY for you to steal from US , but NOT okay to steal from you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perfect example is the key glitch back in december where players were exploiting your poorly written codes to get infinite keys and somehow you MOVED within hours to get this patched as quickly as possible and for damage control , you diluted the supplydrop system with 600+ items , not only punishing the ones  that did the glitch by banning them for a few days , but punishing your loyal customers by spending our hard earned keys on POORLY ported camos ripped straight from emblems. which by the way you have not commented if you're ever going to fix them. 


secondly, you put out this triple play bundle which CLEARLY states, each hack will be dupe protected. so what does your loyal customers do? pay for cod points and got duplicate items from your QM   MK2 Hacks. you've made no attempt to update and remove the dupe protected description nor tweeted out a compensation for those that purchased cod points. instead, you let your goons tweet at people who complained that said " sorry, its not dupe protected,  sorry for the confusion ". 


You people have no shame or integrity as a developer. 

i found the perfect CC to describe you scums. 

https://imgur.com/OUJF3VC

this clearly looks like eric hirshberg, ceo of activision 
scheming on how he can manipulate   rob his loyal cod community out of their money with by having their rng system 
described with FALSE advertising. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wouldn't work. you have to activate siri/ok google first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pregnant woman wakes up from a coma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 3 month pregnant woman falls into a coma. 6 months after she awakes and asks the doctor about her baby. The doctor said don't worry , you had twins , a boy and a girl. Your brother named them for you. She said oh no , not my brother, he's an idiot. What did he name the girl ? Doc said" Denise". Oh that's not bad she said, what did he name the boy? Doc said "de nephew". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how do u do that run? that jump run like ace? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you play HC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its NOT duped protected  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then why advertise its dupe protected. damn u IW.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no. dont u have a secondary epic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
