<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2408</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its fight scenes have amazing animation for sure, but aside from that it's pretty limited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chitanda

Constantly invades Oreki's personal space, acts like a hyperactive 5 year old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LotGH and Shouwa Genroku Rakugo Shinjuu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't Isao Takahata pretty well known in his own right? Not as much as Miyazaki of course, but he's not exactly an unknown director. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kaiba </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only seen the first episode but was disappointed with how the main couple's romance happened. I do like Yuasa though, so I'll finish it at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one I assume? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PN_CP4SuoTU ab_channel=OtaKing77077 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adding on to DocRocksO's list, from what I've seen of stuff by Kyoto Animation, they seem to employ show don't tell pretty well too. And  Shouwa Genroku Rakugo Shinjuu and the currently airing Tsuki ga Kirei has a lot that as well. Also, he mentions Miyazaki specifically but from what I've seen Studio Ghibli's stuff in general is better in regards to this than the vast majority of anime. There's also several anime which have badly written exposition as well as great visual storytelling such as Mob Psycho 100 and Evangelion and 3-Gatsu no Lion (which doesn't really have much blatant exposition but there's a few scenes where I felt dialogue was pointlessly reiterating stuff unnaturally).

I think it might be because a lot of anime are made as cheap, easy to consume entertainment and the main audience would rather watch something that spoonfeeds them information rather than having it naturally come out through the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2real :'C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 Centimeters Per Second wasn't really supposed to be about the characters but in the case of Your Name I agree with you. He puts more information in background content rather than the stuff the audience actually pays attention to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I wanna know too. There was someone who did it for the older episodes, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. That scene had other great animators too, I know it's Mitsuo Iso's most famous scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang. What is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, I meant that for 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He animated some other cool scenes in Eva too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched EoE first but I think it doesn't really matter. Personally, I'd go with the TV ending first, no particular reason for that but it was released that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
