<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject278</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Duterte says he would eat a terrorist's liver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas archdiocese severs ties with Girl Scouts and urges end to cookie sales </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOJ releases data on incarceration rates of illegal immigrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is right: Senate Republicans should kill the filibuster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She needs to go to someone. Hear Infowars is hiring...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad.
People may have not been a huge fan of Obama, but it appears he actually ran an honest, clean race outside the normal propaganda videos and PAC help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better buy a third tin and a punching bag because it's probably going to seriously disappoint the 98% of humanity waiting for this day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump knew that him getting in would require talking a metric ton worth of shit talking, bending of the rules, deployment of outside help, or a combination of all 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucked up how someone in a position of authority gets to decide when they get to tattle. If it were you, me or Joe Blow, we'd be held in contempt or jailed if we withheld testimony on purpose - or even on accident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did someone slap her with a gag order, or send her to a new home in Australia? Either way, she needs to testify and should be compelled either by a judge or through the Federal government to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, there goes my hope of seeing something special on SnapTwitter. Or is that FaceChat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, unless this is just a lengthy status hearing, it's hard to tell. Flynn may be more the topic of discussion than anyone else; one thing is for sure - the Feds will probably not give up until something is either found, or it becomes evident nothing *can* be found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Comey is getting flack from both ends, so I imagine he's probably ready to hide in Bali.
For one, the Dems want him to dig deeper - which they really need to.
For another, I'm willing to make a (small) wager that someone's palms are getting greased to slow this investigation down or dilute evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Hey now, hey now....don't dream it's over.. * </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need me a good Danish woman. So I suppose I would (loosely) agree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and just three hours after being detained, a new leader was appointed.

Do the Federales / military / locals actually think they're even putting a dent in this war?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, probably more like *"Nothing yet, but..."*

I'm just praying the end result is a deeper, more meaningful investigation into collusion and whatever else the fucktard GOP has done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So ObamaCare, which many want to preserve (with some exceptions), has an insurer who fired their CEO because of the GOPs failed attempts at repealing.

Well played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ObamaCare insurer ousts CEO who criticized GOP repeal plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Director Comey, NSA Director Rogers will testify about Russia on Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a huge fan of oil from what I gathered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Utah. Where the state's real decision makers are within the LDS church... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, although obstruction is a pretty kind word for *treason*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Putin is bi. Which would be awesome for the huge LGBT following in Moscow, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thought is this: The White House can make anything *not exist*, if they choose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia never interferes in others internal politics, yet feels such attempts from outside  Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chaffetz: WH Not Providing Flynn Documents Because They Dont Exist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the rich white America you speak of has moved to the tech sector, anyway. Or they're heirs to Walmart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the new saying goes, *haters are gonna hate* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erdogan - the "other" Kim Jong Un. Although even HE can probably successfully launch *something*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really think Saudis oil execs are clueless at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, UN Watch did no such thing. CNN covered this a week ago:

http://www.cnn.com/2017/04/25/world/saudi-arabia-un-womens-commission-trnd/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is newsworthy. From Daily Mail, no less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the NRA Has Been a Disaster for Black Americans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Doesn't Know Why the Civil War Began. Most Americans Don't Know How It Ended. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State suicide bombers kill 32 in Syria refugee camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump schedules another phone call with Russia's Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps Logic Could Apply Well Beyond Civil War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OPEC deal backfires: Saudis lose market share to Iran, Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, since you put things in a much more diplomatic perspective, I concur.
I would like to add that, in the spirit of such things as Brexit, anything is possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an already uncertain economic future, who would you rather have controlling *any* interest or property on U.S. soil: the British, or Saudis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Distortion of Trump's Civil War comment is reason few Americans trust the media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saudi took over the refineries, probably against the wishes of an already scarred OPEC. The other named countries may indirectly benefit, however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have other refineries, indeed. So you suggest we slow production down to save a buck?

They don't need a monopoly to create a price crisis. They only need ambition.

Solution: stop selling shit to everyone else. Period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or we perfect a hydrogen-based engine and tell them all to fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they suddenly increase prices for refining (since they now have 100% of our largest in their back pocket), you'll probably rethink your logic. That much they CAN do. After all, they own it.

Source: *Common sense.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.
Which still allows them to charge a premium for refining our shit in their refinery.
Otherwise, the purchase is irrelevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why refine their shit on our soil? Still allows the Saudis to charge a higher premium for using their newly acquired refinery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funding deal includes $68M reimbursement for guarding Trump family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What will happen now is the Saudis will run the prices through the ceiling. Not sure how we let another country come in and claim our oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudis take 100% control of America's largest oil refinery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct you are. It's like Obama rambled off some shit about getting started in the Oval Office, then nonchalantly slid in there *by the way, you pretentious fuck, I know about Russia. Enjoy the next 4 years, sucker!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I am, it's meth and other homemade mixtures that kills the most. I swear these officers are probably done administering Narcan to the same idiots three times a week (true story). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indian tribes fear Trump will be a buzzkill for their marijuana business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is Barack Obama Doing Now? Not Talking to Donald Trump, Apparently </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump unwinding Michelle Obama's school lunch program rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China is recruiting 20,000 people to write its own Wikipedia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. Of all the freaky things Philippine druggies have access to, they choose Fentynal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too busy eating terrorist liver? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justices order new look at fair lending lawsuit against Bank of America, Wells Fargo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. It was also my way of giving the chicks a 'good game' after a hard-fought dodgeball win high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it was only a few posterior pats. Who'd see the harm in that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony Blair announces return in bid to influence Brexit debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the same Duterte that would like to eat the liver of terrorists. Let's hope some unfortunate radical doesn't pass out near Duterte's quarters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New charges filed against so-called 'Spokane spanker' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably so. But then again, perhaps we ask the litany of complainants how they feel having their innocence stolen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rodrigo Duterte's drug war has killed thousands. Trump just invited him to the White House. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Africa's Jacob Zuma abandons rally after being booed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll never understand (maybe I don't need to) what pleasure individuals  find in praising/practicing a religion/ideology that literally defies sanity. Of course, given the longstanding issues within the Catholic church (namely handsy priests), I suppose every religion has its inner turmoil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans Want to Punish Students Who Shut Down Controversial Speakers on Campus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, alrighty then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just wondering why they can't peacefully assemble - Westerners, Europeans and virtually everyone else will not conform to whatever propaganda they're pushing. Nobody said they couldn't peacefully practice their religion - somehow, however, I doubt that any reasonably intelligent deity would want its followers bombing people and blowing shit up as a primary means to pay homage to their fearless leader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything that Trump is undoing and redoing will simply be undone and redid when he departs in 2020. Just hang on tight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump on congressional Republicans: 'I don't dislike any of them' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why radicalism is hitting London harder than other regions. Although it does look like these imbeciles are starting to terrorize Scandinavian countries as well. Remind me to colonize a completely isolated area of Mars when the time comes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three young women arrested in London under anti-terrorism laws: police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 Muslim men killed by mob over cow theft charges in India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers settle on hard-fought $1 trillion spending bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rights group: Trump should seek accountability from Duterte </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian TV executive shot dead in Istanbul, Turkish media report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP growing frustrated with Trump's trade threats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tear gas, over 200 arrests at May Day clashes in Istanbul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 11:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was literally the first thing that popped into my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Arabia arrests 46 suspects over Medina bombing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing KJU is capable of shooting is his mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is funny as hell. It's like a Yugo threatening to pull a semi out of a ditch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N. Korea threatens to sink U.S. nuclear submarine deployed to S. Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippines says Trump called Duterte to affirm alliance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Trump tweeted 470 times in first 100 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was reading through Yonhap, looks like the whole bullshit about us picking up the tab for THAAD is going back to the renegotiation table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says North Korea is maybe more important than better trade deal with China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says pre-existing conditions are in the bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the little boy in charge over in NK will find Mr. Mayagi and come to his senses. Developing a country's personal defenses is one thing - have this burning desire to create missiles that can hit California is ridiculous, especially since we've never threatened to do much more than sanction the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if North Koreans use Onion routers like the rest of the black market world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the whole failed missile launch is a ruse. North Korean isn't stupid enough to create nuke-tipped missiles without refining their launch apparatuses first. It's a big effing smoking screen. I cannot base this off facts, but it's a strong hunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump warns North Korea's missiles will get better </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Candidates invoke Trump's name, God in Alabama Senate race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police are 'tracking two further Islamist terror plots in London' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi commander says to complete capture of Mosul in May </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's for a used one, Mr. McDonnell. Without date.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There won't be much of anything east of, say, the Atlantic... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope to Catholics: get out, spread faith, help cholesterol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea crisis: Re-unification alone 'would cost $3 trillion' after war, professor says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Gov. McDonnell: I didn't know what a Rolex cost to be honest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S. Korean, U.S. security chiefs reaffirm no THAAD payment by Seoul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU leaders adopt Brexit guidelines at Brussels summit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 12:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Invites Controversial Philippine Leader to White House in 'Friendly' Call </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 12:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: "I will not be happy" if North Korea conducts another nuclear test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duterte - it almost sounds like a lost character in 'The Princess Bride". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Spends 100th Day in Office Whining About Media Coverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippines' Duterte urges U.S. restraint on North Korea, says Kim "wants to end the world" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very reasonable. It'll stop a nuclear holocaust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia backs Chinas call to stop N. Korea nuke tests in exchange for halt in US-S. Korea drills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Sotomayor Slams "Disturbing Trend" of Supreme Court Siding With the Police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare victory for persecuted journalist highlights Mexico's press freedom crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Broken by US power machine': Trumps 100 days prove his maverick image was fake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump names anti-abortion leader to high post at HHS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scared enough we're (from what it sounds like) 'donating' a THAAD? Damn sure isn't because WE need to defend ourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think the United States is about over it, S. Korea is scared shitless and China is still pumping out Walmart products like it's just another day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N. Korea fails in missile test: S. Korean military </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lithuanian scammer accused of single-handedly swindling Google   Facebook out of $100 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican senator from Arizona cites growth in U.S.-Mexico trade after NAFTA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonald's customer upset about coffee, lack of jelly arrested after racial rant, police say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Korean War-era bomb found in sea near Pyeongtaek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House and Senate Pass Short-Term Funding Bill, Avoid Government Shutdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UN Security Council hears tough talk against North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vicente Fox to Trump: Being president aint easy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Montenegro parliament ratifies NATO membership after US approval </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thai police obtain arrest warrant for Red Bull heir </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew that's what Trump was heading towards when he first announced he was running - turning America into a collection agency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump complains Saudis not paying fair share for U.S. defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite Populist Rhetoric, Trump Is Poised to Preside Over a Crackdown on Unions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. keen to try sanctions, diplomacy before force on North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What killing net neutrality means for the internet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems struggle with abortion litmus test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taliban Launches Spring Offensive In Weakened Afghanistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House GOP leaders struggling to secure votes for revised health care bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of all the mooning you've done in your life - it pales in comparison to the Moon that is setting over NK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malawi becomes the latest African country to ban child marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian police raid opposition office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then essentially the Supreme Court is the unnecessary evil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my idea was probably presented a bit vague, for which I apologize.

You'd be essentially cutting the 9th circuit states at an angle in thirds. I'll try and download a map and illustrate my ideology. 

But for purposes of time, imagine a very, very long "/" x 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone I think taking KJU snipe hunting would be a "blast". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd look like Psy with shades on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As large as California is, having it in thirds would further increase efficiency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Man, I don't know what you just said, but it touched my heart...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not consolidate duties? I mean hell, piss on these court levels (District, Circuit, Supreme) and just give every state it's own freedom to create appeals courts and courts that can handle Federal cases without having courts that do nothing but pass shit around to other courts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do agree when put that way.

This also creates more jobs, although it also creates a temporary tax burden to pay for buildings, people, equipment, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logically, I cannot see anything but long-term logjams with any judicial splitting. Maybe give each state it's own Federal district to hear cases and clear case logs faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what about Heidi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, did anyone consider this man was going to a circus tryout? Or a cooking class? Hell, Sam's Club always has someone doing knife demonstrations, giving away free paring knives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and we all know how Trump loves his bitches... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The statement was purposely facetious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man carrying bag of knives near UK Parliament arrested under Terrorism Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cruz was seriously butthurt when he lost to Trump. So he figures, I'd better succumb to his fascist desires, lest I become his punk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The largest of the 13 appellate districts, I cannot see anyone winning here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire Western seaboard would have no one to appeal to. Boo fucking hoo. Send your habeas pleas and tort claims to Pennsylvania Ave instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And although the presidential hopeful Moon made this remark, it stands to reason the cosmos controlling the moon are subliminally speaking through Moon, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cruz: Breaking 9th Circuit Court a possibility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in ebonics, it means *Kim Jong Un just got called out and thrown under the bus by his homies* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oversight committee: Flynn investigation to be launched by DOD inspector general </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moon warns N. Korea against conducting nuclear test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massachusetts Governor Proposes Bill Protecting Teen Sexters From Felony Charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have people who get the privilege of eating off the big kids table, if that makes them elites...  ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would very, very much like to be the head of that class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. This presidency has been more of a 'horse and pony show' than an actual administration of action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...does he even attend court hearings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Trying to Expand His Immunity from Lawsuits While Hes President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I believe sending the USS Carl Vinson team was smart. Think the sub was bit much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm Inigo Montoya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol.

Honestly, anyone who accepts $881,060 just to allow someone to defect is actually fucking with the government paying the bribe.

Hell, an MLB entry-level salary is what, $525k? Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree in part.

*Not The Onion* is increasingly divided on what is *not oniony*. And I'd rather not cop a Redditude over their choices of what is construed as 'oniony'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...which lends itself to why U.S. forces have every right to be in the Peninsula (or literally up Un's ass). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marco Rubio: President Trump Should Strengthen Americas Relationship With Argentina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you put in an email and it's all free. I see no portion of this site that requires payment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea releases video of missile attack on U.S. Capitol, aircraft carrier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at neighboring countries.
South Korea relies on us (and an often 'too' neutral China) to keep their freedoms safe.
The Cuban Missile Crisis was, in and of itself, a propaganda sham. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldman Sachs Alums Insist Trumps Tax Cut Is All About Helping Farmers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shit is spiraling out of control.

Can't let this Tupperware haircut fool keep bumping his cocktrap any more. Send it some SEALs, do their thing, and it's done. I promise the next leader of NK will be a little humbler, may even grant freedom of the press back to people... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who daily (or at least every other day) taunts the world with marches displaying their WMDs is war hungry. I mean, Putin's an asshole, but do you see him marching around the Kremlin threatening to reduce people to ashes? Hell, at least Saddam was all action.

The mere threat alone is enough to get people ready for war. If I tell someone I'm going to reduce their house to ashes, don't you think they'll be on high alert? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This Kim Jong Douche is no different than Hussein or any other war-hungry derelict on the planet. He's a little fucking mouse in a big fucking maze - he may have some 'toys', but the unfortunate reality (which will lead to his demise) is that too many countries neighboring (or within missile distance) have an interest in the United States. First time he fires at an American sub or even grazes an American soldier, Pyongyang will be decimated with or without warning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all honesty, he's a weak leader. His defecting constituents are increasingly telling the world this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korean elites increasingly think Kim Jong Un is a weak leader, new study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel uncovers ancient Roman history at Mediterranean port </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bernie Sanders lost to Hillary Clinton. So, can he be America's most popular politician? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers targeted as district politics shift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japans Shinzo Abe wants Vladimir Putin onside in North Korea standoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Damascus airport rocked by 'Israeli strikes' on arms depot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump tax plan prompts GOP fears about deficit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexicos Hillary Clinton Rips Trump Over Useless Wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think the relevance here is the fact a Missouri (or any governor) nonchalantly approaches their job like, "Look at me, I can do this shit with my eyes closed." It's an abomination to the Missouri government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri governor signs bill while taking Lyft to Taco Bell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four Republicans sign letter urging Trump to stay in Paris deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's rather hard to get good child care anymore. If it's not about the price, it's about trust....never have I seen trustworthy, moderately priced childcare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the most pontified stud I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That what makes the Popemeister a pretty swell guy. Patriotism seems to be a dying characteristic in America, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the problem. She barely has the capacity to sell her own merch, let alone try and logically deduce our current fiscal state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pope speaks free without compunction. Very, very softly kills people with words. I only wish I had a third of his patience and longsuffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
