<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3931</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... Meepo really isn't ranged. I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are shrines "very recent"? It's been almost five months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? When I complained about games being too long, le reddit told me games are now shorter than they've ever been. Hmmmm.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the single most versatile ability in the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something that's always fascinated me about Dota is how, despite the fact each hero has only four skills (well, a handful have more, but that's not the point), the majority of them have a lot of utility. One example is Keeper of the Light's Illuminate when you have Aghs: it provides vision the more you charge it up, it damages, and it heals.

Though since you can't heal without Aghs, that's cheating a little bit. What's a better example? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Low MMR players don't watch pro games. One reason I know this is because when I try to roam as Riki, they'll say "LOL RIKI ISN'T A SUPPORT" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old time phrasing in To Kill a Mockingbird? Haha funny joke? Try reading something from the Victorian era or some Shakespeare if you want something a little more odd compared to today's writing. To Kill a Mockingbird is very easy to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you consider those games "new", you're already behind the times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, it DOES feel like you're reading on a screen. Paper has this kind of grainy quality to it, whereas an e-ink reader looks too clean. I know that's a bizarre complaint, but eh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible Konami WANTS us to hate them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if so, what would be the logic behind this? They've made so many poor decisions over the past few years that I have to wonder if it's all part of a grand plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is the formatting of many Kindle books still so bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my second time trying to use a Kindle, and while this time I lasted a few months instead of a couple weeks, I'm not really much happier with the state of things. So many books - and I don't mean indie books, I mean professionally done books from Random House or HarperCollins or wherever - still have hideous formatting. 

Whether it's a space after every paragraph, books that still don't have properly aligned typesetting, or other smaller issues that I can't recall, I don't understand this lack of polish. The space after every paragraph is what disturbs me the most and has single handedly made me start going with used paperbacks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget MMR is even a thing. Don't even look at that number. You'll be much happier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/TropesAreTools

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blame? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get so fucking mad at this, too.  I try my best to heal everyone, then they rush into something dangerous, and immediately blame Widow despite the fact she's been getting picks all game and my team STILL can't win a fight. Just looking for someone to blame on their poor skill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Predictability is also a good thing. Do you really want some random twist just for the sake of being unexpected? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they didn't want aim to be a factor in your success, they shouldn't have made a first person shooter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that mathematics? It's a stupid multiplier Blizzard decided to put into the game, just the same as "performance based SR gain." Dota has it right with its flat 25 MMR gain or loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that loss or win streaks mean ANYTHING renders this game's ranked queue into a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But mechanical skill **is** a part of this game. If they can excel through mechanical skill, then why not let them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wouldn't be doing any of those things if you made a positive impact to the game, instead of jungling for 20 minutes while they're all dying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wondering the exact same thing, honestly. If the easy W+M1 heroes are so useful, is this really a game that can be taken seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is no one at this rank can aim with Soldier, either. There's no reason to single out a group of heroes when they can't aim with ANY hero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the actual goddamned fuck does SR work in this way? Why not something like Dota where it's a flat 25 MMR gain or loss? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I think I'm going back to Dota. Overwatch is some of the most stressful shit, feels like nothing I do has any impact. At least in Dota you can carry games largely on your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh they notice and they'll be like "what, are we throwing now? only one healer?" They get tilted very easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost yet another game to a Symmetra. She is honestly a free win at this SR, no one can aim. Fucking christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Soldiers, Reins, and Tracers are also shitty. Do you also say "fuck why did you pick Soldier?" Do you see how this logic makes absolutely no sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this community despise Hanzo, Widow, Torb, etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, the way this community treats "off-meta" heroes is so obnoxious and frustrating. And before you say "lol Hanzo main", no I'm a healer/support main. The condescending remarks to EVERY Hanzo, Widow, Torb, etc, is to the point I'm tempted to stop playing. I've never seen such aversion to certain heroes/classes in an online game. In Dota, the only heroes I know that trigger people into saying "what the fuck, why?" are Techies and Io. Two heroes out of 100+, whereas I'd say half of Overwatch's roster has its players whining like bitches.

I have to talk to my team like children in each pre-game, "Now guys, we've not seen them play yet. We have no reason to assume they're bad or throwing the game. Give them a chance." More often than not, I do get them to calm down, and hey what do you know, that Hanzo or Widow is actually making great plays throughout the match because the team didn't tilt them out of their minds!

It's just honestly the most goddamned stupid thing that people assume the worst before anything has even happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this community despise Hanzo, Widow, Torb, etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, the way this community treats "off-meta" heroes is so obnoxious and frustrating. And before you say "lol Hanzo main", no I'm a healer/support main. The condescending remarks to EVERY Hanzo, Widow, Torb, etc, is to the point I'm tempted to stop playing. I've never seen such aversion to certain heroes/classes in an online game. In Dota, the only heroes I know that trigger people into saying "what the fuck, why?" are Techies and Io. Two heroes out of 100+, whereas I'd say half of Overwatch's roster has its players whining like bitches.

I have to talk to my team like children in each pre-game, "Now guys, we've not seen them play yet. We have no reason to assume they're bad or throwing the game. Give them a chance." More often than not, I do get them to calm down, and hey what do you know, that Hanzo or Widow is actually making great plays throughout the match because the team didn't tilt them out of their minds!

It's just honestly the most goddamned stupid thing that people assume the worst before anything has even happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is a multiplayer game is so complex that you CANNOT assume the fight was lost due to one hero.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen attack Torb work. I bet ANYTHING that the reason the Torb failed, the primary reason, is you tilted him into oblivion by saying "fuck, really, why attack Torb, man, why you trollin???" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play heals 99% of the time, so I don't experience this, but I see it almost every game. I need to convince my team, no, that Hanzo or Sombra isn't going to throw the game. We've not even seen them do anything yet. I've never seen a game where the community is so averse to certain heroes. It's honestly enough to make me want to stop playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not played Dota much for a couple months - do I want to learn Techies or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd never really enjoyed Techies pre-7.00, but the changes they made to him in 7.00 made him fun as hell. While I've not been playing lately, I have been reading patch notes just in case. What is this about making a sound when you're near prox mines? You can already see them without sentries, why would they add this? Sounds like a straight up nerf to me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I thought you meant the in-game music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? The music seems absolutely random in when it plays and when it ends. Can you explain to me? If you can convince me it's helpful, I'll turn it back on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She rarely targets me first, which is the funny thing. She'll go for the dps and tanks and THEN me, because I guess Symmetras know these idiots try to run from her instead of trying to shoot her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a support player, what can I do to make sure Symmetra doesn't get triple or quad kills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in silver and Symmetra is a goddamned monster because my teammates are terrified of her, for some reason. I'll try to heal through the beam, but of course they die because of its increasing power. Their answer to Sym is ... to run away. They don't even try to shoot her, instead thinking they can escape to some safe place (???) This is even more frustrating because she's so easy to kill. I can take out my pistol as Mercy and get her down to 10% health, all I need is that little extra from my teammates.

But since they have no intention of killing Symmetra, what the actual fuck can I do against her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a support player, what can I do to make sure Symmetra doesn't get triple or quad kills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in silver and Symmetra is a goddamned monster because my teammates are terrified of her, for some reason. I'll try to heal through the beam, but of course they die because of its increasing power. Their answer to Sym is ... to run away. They don't even try to shoot her, instead thinking they can escape to some safe place (???) This is even more frustrating because she's so easy to kill. I can take out my pistol as Mercy and get her down to 10% health, all I need is that little extra from my teammates.

But since they have no intention of killing Symmetra, what the actual fuck can I do against her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait.. what? I thought the earth going round the sun was common knowledge in the 1800s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you don't get it. Hearthstone is Lost Vikings 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm low MMR in both Dota and Overwatch so my opinion may be meaningless, but I absolutely agree with you. I feel like in Dota, whether I'm Crystal Maiden or Faceless Void, I can find SOME way to carry the team if I'm just smart enough. In Overwatch, really I feel like it's random chance if I win. Whether I'm Mercy and my dps can't aim or if I'm Soldier and my tanks don't use their shields, it's just an absolute gamble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thing about sentries at 1k or 2k mmr, is that it's not uncommon the enemy "supports" will buy only 3 or 4 wards for the entire game. That's what the scoreboard tells me at the end of the game, anyhow. It's often a waste of money to buy a sentry unless you KNOW there's a ward because you just saw them walk up and put one down. And I guess being dewarded once breaks their little hearts and they just... stop buying any for the rest of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how that's possible when this sub keeps mentioning the same dozen books over and over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this why you broke up with her? I wouldn't blame you at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most amusing thing about this? You say that you can't fathom stars thousand times the size of the sun... but can you even really fathom *the size of the sun itself* in the first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fly is one of the top 5 episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean jeez, they extended the story as it is... the book it's based on is only 288 pages long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is incredible how this sub has no sense of humor. You took me so seriously you wrote out this long explanation of why my joke post is a bad idea. Fuck, I should just go back to /r/dota2 where "fun" is a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what is so frustrating about this game. Your individual skill means next to nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, hers wouldn't count.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I didn't even finish the first episode. Without that short introduction, I'd have taken it for what it is. But he says it's supposed to be for an older crowd, so I'm honestly a bit insulted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm curious, at what SR does Symmetra stop racking up triple kills? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at silver, and honestly I'm baffled how my teammates keep dying to her. Even tanks just melt under her beam. Part of it, I'm sure, is that they have no aim. At higher SR, can she still do this kinda bullshit once people actually shoot at her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cosmos was a bit sterile, but that's partly due to Tyson being uncharacteristically detached. It's weird comparing his lectures where he is so passionate and funny, to Cosmos where he's kinda sedated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeeeah I think this guy just browses the new section to find new outlets to bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The whole idea that "this isn't pro Dota, don't expect it to be", doesn't make a ton of sense to me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't ever hear someone say "This isn't pro basketball, don't expect it to be." If you're playing a game of basketball with friends or random people, everyone knows roles like center and point guard, even just for fun when you're not very good, and the teams work out amongst themselves who's going to fill each role.

So isn't it a little absurd that Dota, a "sport" in its own right, doesn't work the same way? If everyone knows the positions to any other sport, why don't Dota players? Is it the fault of the game's tutorials, the community, what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost certainly. There is no reason Schumer's special should be a 93% match for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the idea is to highlight the gravity of the situation, all the lame jokes seem to undermine the intention. How is any denier going to take climate change seriously when, half the time, Nye himself seems to treat it as a platform for humor in that first episode?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the idea is to highlight the gravity of the situation, all the lame jokes seem to undermine the intention. How is any denier going to take climate change seriously when, half the time, Nye himself seems to treat it as a platform for humor in that first episode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is those people are NOT going to watch a science show... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who have neglected science aren't going to watch this. Why would they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw someone mention it was in response to Schumer's special being lambasted - and at first I thought they were overreacting, but... I can't think of any actual reason that thing would be a "93% match" for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you care so much about this?  I'd think you would be excited that match quality will be (hopefully) higher, not wanting to see new toxic excuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have reason to believe you're muted, just type something in a regional chat and see what the console says to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Single Draft isn't in Ranked yet. I'd love that tbh, just change some things so you know what heroes your teammates have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you need a phone number for ranked, so you can play with new friends there - as you should, in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you refuse to take a break when you know you're not enjoying something... then honestly, you're pretty stupid and I guess you'll have to keep suffering for no reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... do I actually want to do this? For example, will the queue times be much longer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not true. I've left quite a few times this season, unintentionally, because of my computer crashing. Each time has been only a 10 minute ban. So for the people who DO love intentionally, really they have no repercussion. Either that or Blizzard can somehow detect that my computer crashed and let me off easy?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not true. I've left quite a few times this season, unintentionally, because of my computer crashing. Each time has been only a 10 minute ban. So for the people who DO love intentionally, really they have no repercussion. Either that or Blizzard can somehow detect that my computer crashed and let me off easy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 minute ban from competitive is not enough, though. That's pathetic for a "punishment." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> File under "Griefing" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like wishful thinking, but maybe you're right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does reporting actually do in this game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I report every leaver because I think a 10 minute punishment is goddamned laughable. There needs to be something more harsh. But what IS that more harsh punishment? What does reporting actually do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree for the most part, however it's hell in that people at silver/bronze simply cannot aim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... Valve is certainly not reading this. If you want their attention, head over to /r/dota2

Having said that, I agree All Hero Challenge should be ordered in ascending complexity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read The Razor's Edge as a teenager... I think that was my introduction to postmodernism, at least, I'd say Maugham being a character in his own novel is a bit postmodern. I've never liked that kind of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't even address what I said. Yeah, Mercy is hard to kill. What does this matter if your teammates can't aim at a stationary target? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I've played a ton of Mercy and in my experience all a rez is going to do is get them to die all over again - because if they were dumb ten seconds ago, why won't they be dumb now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you possibly solo queue climb with Mercy? Healing your teammates doesn't DO anything if they don't get any kills because their aim is garbage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the question after that - is there any way to get my team not to tilt the second they see it's not 2-2-2? This is the most stupid shit, people are so religiously dedicated to it, as if it really matters at silver or bronze what your comp is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This game is such a catch-22, fucked if you do and fucked if you don't. How do I make an impact? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like in Dota, you can really make an impact in any role. Supports can get shit done. In this game, that's not really the case. If you're a healer and your DPS can't aim, well that sucks for you, you've lost the game. And if you decide to go DPS, you're probably not going to get any heals yourself.

Is there any way to win Overwatch consistently without relying on your team? I know that sounds moronic, but it's not like I can trust my teammates to have ever played a shooter before with how accurate they are with their shooting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This game is such a catch-22, fucked if you do and fucked if you don't. How do I make an impact? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like in Dota, you can really make an impact in any role. Supports can get shit done. In this game, that's not really the case. If you're a healer and your DPS can't aim, well that sucks for you, you've lost the game. And if you decide to go DPS, you're probably not going to get any heals yourself.

Is there any way to win Overwatch consistently without relying on your team? I know that sounds moronic, but it's not like I can trust my teammates to have ever played a shooter before with how accurate they are with their shooting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some novels that were once considered classics that have been largely forgotten? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And more interestingly, what are the reasons for their leaving the spotlight?

You always hear about authors who died neglected and unknown, only to be revived later in history. Melville's Moby-Dick is a famous example of this. Surely the opposite of this has taken place, as well. 

Part of me wants to say Walter Scott might be a candidate for this phenomenon. He's not obscure or anything, yet I don't think I've ever seen him on a list of great works in the 19th century. He's a historical footnote, now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some novels that were once considered classics that have been largely forgotten? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And more interestingly, what are the reasons for their leaving the spotlight?

You always hear about authors who died neglected and unknown, only to be revived later in history. Melville's Moby-Dick is a famous example of this. Surely the opposite of this has taken place, as well. 

Part of me wants to say Walter Scott might be a candidate for this phenomenon. He's not obscure or anything, yet I don't think I've ever seen him on a list of great works in the 19th century. He's a historical footnote, now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... if they don't understand this, they PROBABLY aren't buying detection against you in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you "fill" in competitive, you're a piece of shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even watch this video? The whole idea is that he made things happen on his own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, exactly. All these attempts to help aren't telling me much I don't already know. I'm already right there with my team and they kinda just... don't do anything about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question: Do you tell them you're 5.2k and they're like "Aww yes smurf, easy win", or do you try to cooperate with them as if you were one of them [granted, much better than them]? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I said in the OP, I think Rein is the most boring hero in the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At what SR do players understand what a "tank" is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 1800 SR and almost every game, the tanks (especially Rein) are going off alone and not even trying to protect their team. I assume that many people see the extra health that a tank has and think "wow, I can overextend more safely like this!"

I know it's boring as fuck to sit there and put up a shield... but that's why I don't play Rein. If you do play Rein, why not accept that responsibility?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What am I supposed to do as Mercy when Winston is focusing me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The closer I get to gold SR, the more common this is, and it is the most ANNOYING thing. At least when other heroes try to focus me I can fly around and avoid them and it's rare that I die because their aim is quite bad. Winston is different. He can leap towards me just as fast as I can fly away, AND Blizzard thought it would be cute to give him lock-on aiming so he can't miss. '

What the actual fuck am I supposed to do against this guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... within your skill bracket... yes ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what world? If you lost, you lost. That is the only thing that matters. Anything else is delusional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The corpse disapears after like two seconds. Is this a glitch on my end or are they supposed to be there for the full 10 seconds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you feel about a performance based MMR similar to the one used in Overwatch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who don't know, OW has a system that factors in your individual performance as well as if you're on a winning/losing streak.

While I really like OW, personally I think the way this is handled is a joke. I asked their sub why this makes any sense and someone replied "Because you can perform extremely well and lose or perform badly and get carried." But in my opinion, all that matters is you lost. Who cares how well you did if you didn't get your team a win?

The other thing this does is really hurt support players. If you're not "on fire" (and as a support, you typically won't be), you don't earn as much SR at the end of a match. Imagine if Dota had the same, where supporting can already be miserable enough in some cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All that matters is you lost. Who cares how well you did if you didn't get your team a win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  lets say you do well in a game. but your team had 1 thrower. a disconnect. a troll. and 2 very bad players. wouldn't you want to lose less SR based on your INDIVIDUAL PERFORMANCE?

Sure that sounds nice but it's not the truth, so why sit and make theories about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This game needs an MMR system that is more like Dota, where all that matters is if you win or lose. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giving you variable amounts of SR based on your performance is, honestly, quite absurd. What is the logic behind this? Why not a flat number for each game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why trying to assess SR gain on a per hero basis is fucking ignorant. Make it like Dota with the 25 MMR win or loss for everyone the same across the board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually.. the most elegant solution would be keeping the bodies on the ground for the entire 10 seconds. I really don't think they are or I wouldn't be making this suggestion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, thats basically what I had in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not going to be an additional thing. It's going to be a replacement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would also be pretty cool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard story related missions referred to as fetch quests many times, so I assume some people feel differently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/chanzjj is right. There is no offlane at below like 3k mmr. Tell me how many times you've seen something ridiculous like Bristleback in the safelane, while Sven and Antimage are both in the offlane. And this is at 1.8k, so I can't imagine how fucking dumb it is at an MMR half of mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't help when there's more than one hero dead. And also you really shouldn't even need to do that. I'd love every hero on your team to be in the upper left just like in Uprising so you know the status of their ult and health.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the most enjoyable fetch quests in gaming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People really like to complain about fetch quests, but I don't think they're all bad.

One example of a fantastic series of fetch quests is obtaining the Masamune in Chrono Trigger. You have to go up Denadoro Mountain in 600 AD to fight Masa   Mune in a physical form, then you must go back to 65,000,000 BC to find a stone that can aid in tempering the blade, all the while talking to Melchior the blacksmith a few times in between - but never does it feel like padding. Everything feels like it's building up in anticipation. Every new quest brings you closer to finishing the sword, and in your bones you can feel that something pivotal to the story is going to happen because of it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instead of a skull, there should be a hero icon above a dead player. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are times in a desperate situation I'd like to solo res, but in a chaotic battle I'm not entirely sure if that's the Rein or Symmetra. One is much more valuable to revive than the other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The average carry at low MMR is also shit.

I'm actually convinced the reason players don't want supports is because games at low MMR tend to go on REALLY long. The longer you go, the less impact a support will have. Four or even five carries begins to sound more logical when you know the game is going to last an hour or more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least Rubick core has been done in the past... core KOTL? Wut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Old metas like Pudge Mid, Carry Bounty Hunter etc. still have some play? 
 

OK, I don't mind this on its own - the problem is if you try something that's not in the 1k-2k meta, they'll flame you. Forget trying to go support Riki, as an example, because they'll laugh and tell you it can't be done. The "old" strategies are so common in this bracket that if you DO try the new ones, they're going to bully you for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checked and the book on which it is based is only 288 pages... yeah, though I've never read or seen it, that sounds like quite a lot of padding.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checked and the book on which it is based is only 288 pages... yeah, though I've never read or seen it, that sounds like quite a lot of padding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's why Stranger Things is so good. The dialogue and acting are believable. So many times, kids and teenagers in TV/movies just make me want to burn something down. That show got it right.

Though this thread kinda makes me want to watch 13 Reasons Why for some laughs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like low skill Dota players actually know this, to an extent. Overwatch players, though... if you don't follow the 2-2-2 meta or if you choose an "off meta" hero, god damn do they throw tantrums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got it backwards. That "abridged" version is the original short story. The novel came after that. Most everything added to the novel is unnecessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, read the short story. The novel is trash and I wish it weren't the better known version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the book is too long, loses the effect of the original short story. Almost everything added to make it into the length of a novel is padding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah? The idea of a "TV channel" is ridiculous in the age of Netflix and Amazon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also do that in Dota, you get a rare chance to get skins. I'd much rather have the option to buy what I KNOW I want instead of leaving it to chance. Not like it affects the gameplay in any way, either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just give us the option to buy skins outright and make them expensive. Works for Dota with its $35 arcana skins. Loot drops are stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeeeah, if Dota has taught me anything, it's that you're full of shit. High MMR players may know a bit more, but they're still just as disorganized as lower brackets. Only pro teams are truly coordinated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in silver and we get two supports almost every game. Occasionally I'm solo healing. I guess players down here either don't know or don't care about support heroes earning less SR. It's something I'd like to see fixed, for sure, but I'm just having fun playing the game, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would love medals to be listed on the scoreboard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blizzard's whole idea of "hide KDA so players don't gloat about it" has drastically backfired, because people do the same shit with gold medals. Unfortunately, medals are even worse than KDA since *you can't prove if they're telling the truth*.

Why not allow us to see this information? Especially as a support player, I'd love to tell at a glance who is doing the best and who I should make sure stays alive at all costs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh I read all of this and still can't tell if you're agreeing or disagreeing with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is. It's from the  GameFAQs Music: Rock board, I think it's like over a decade old now. Fucking hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love when she makes fun of recent events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's an affordable yet comprehensive edition of Shakespeare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure this has been asked before, but I couldn't really find much with a quick search.

I'm kinda considering [The Norton Shakespeare: The Essential Plays](https://www.amazon.com/Norton-Shakespeare-Essential-Plays-Sonnets/dp/0393938638), however at $67 that seems a little steep. Is this my best option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I draw the line at communication. If you want to pick an "unusual" hero and make it work, that's absolutely fine. But if you're in competitive and don't have a mic, get the fuck out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're listening to Tool, just remember that they're not like other bands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're listening to Tool, just remember that they're not like other bands. Their music is incredibly artistic, almost to the point where you have to be paying complete attention to them to even remotely understand them. I remember listening to a song on Lateralus (though I can't remember what it was), where I thought a song was absolute bollocks during the listen. Then, I closed my eyes for a second, and all of a sudden the song had an entirely new meaning. It was insane the way Tool could just become something so different when you take a look into the music.

Another thing you should note about Tool is that it's easy to get a headache listening to them. Not because they're a bad band, but because of how many ideas their music is riddled with and how complex they are. Soon enough your head will fill to the brim and the rest will just sound like noise to you. Just turn it off and give it a listen the next day.

If you don't like the music, you'll definitely at least enjoy reading through the lyrics, and picking apart the song itself and all of the artistic values that go into making it the complexity that it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're listening to Tool, just remember that they're not like other bands. Their music is incredibly artistic, almost to the point where you have to be paying complete attention to them to even remotely understand them. I remember listening to a song on Lateralus (though I can't remember what it was), where I thought a song was absolute bollocks during the listen. Then, I closed my eyes for a second, and all of a sudden the song had an entirely new meaning. It was insane the way Tool could just become something so different when you take a look into the music.

Another thing you should note about Tool is that it's easy to get a headache listening to them. Not because they're a bad band, but because of how many ideas their music is riddled with and how complex they are. Soon enough your head will fill to the brim and the rest will just sound like noise to you. Just turn it off and give it a listen the next day.

If you don't like the music, you'll definitely at least enjoy reading through the lyrics, and picking apart the song itself and all of the artistic values that go into making it the complexity that it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'd say if your enemy is using three heroes just to counter one of yours, then you've already won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, sure. And if they're not, like I said, just accept that and don't whine about it to put your team on tilt before the match even begins. I've won more games when I just let the "stupid" Sym or Torb or Hanzo do their thing instead of whining to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I'm a Mercy main. But bitching about picks is not ever going to help you win. So why do it, what good is it going to accomplish? The only thing this does is tilt your entire team before the match has started. I've seen matches won where we were "supposed" to win.

edit: Something this community does not understand, that the Dota community has understood for a long time, is that counters ONLY matter at high levels of play. Sure, one hero counters another *on paper*. If you outplay your opponent, you're going to win even if they have three heroes specifically to counter you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're in solo queue, you should expect the unexpected and learn how to adapt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complaining about team comp when you're in solo queue is a little absurd, honestly. You cannot control your teammates. All you can do is play around them. You have no right to whine about any of their picks because that's what you signed up for by picking solo queue. If you think there are too many dps or tanks, or no healers, or whatever, you are just as capable as anyone else to make the switch.

You should expect the unexpected in solo queue and find a way to deal with it. Fussing about "team comp" for players that don't want to play nice is a wasted effort. Either find a way to win in solo queue or find five other players you can consistently team up with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're in solo queue, you should expect the unexpected and learn how to adapt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complaining about team comp when you're in solo queue is a little absurd, honestly. You cannot control your teammates. All you can do is play around them. You have no right to whine about any of their picks because that's what you signed up for by picking solo queue. If you think there are too many dps or tanks, or no healers, or whatever, you are just as capable as anyone else to make the switch.

You should expect the unexpected in solo queue and find a way to deal with it. Fussing about "team comp" for players that don't want to play nice is a wasted effort. Either find a way to win in solo queue or find five other players you can consistently team up with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was he a jerk? Or are you just one of those freaks who idolize him like a god and you were crushed to find he was a normal guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much filler for my tastes, would be substantially better if Harry Manback, Die Eier von Satan, Cesaro Summability, and Ions were removed. Useful Idiot and Intermission can stay, though should be merged into their respective tracks. So it should look like this:

* Stinkfist
* Eulogy
* H
* Forty Six   2
* Hooker with a Penis
* Jimmy
* Pushit
* nema
* Third Eye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't even make sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if the mockery worked, then I'd say the mods are to blame for allowing it to continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really hard work if you're an atheist? Hmmmm... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TV is an incredibly outdated construct, so I'd do no such thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many of you would name Undertow as your favorite Tool album? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The production on Undertow is so good, everything is so cavernous and echo-y, it feels both enormous and suffocating at the same time. Or maybe that's the compressed mp3s I'm used to listening to for them, not 100% sure... but I love it.

The lyrics are more down-to-earth, too. Lateralus got a little too mystical and preachy for me. I'd say the only thing I miss from the later albums is Maynard's more peaceful moments, but in general I'd say Undertow remains their best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The production on Undertow is so good, everything is so cavernous and echo-y, it feels both enormous and suffocating at the same time. Or maybe that's the compressed mp3s I'm used to listening to for them, not 100% sure... but I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn YES, all the quotes people posted in this thread and this is one of my favorites. I mean there's nothing profound about it on its own, but that song is great. That album in general is underrated. I want a Tool album that has the intricate music of Lateralus with the down-to-earth lyrics of Undertow. Would be absolutely perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not scary. I love that idea. Unless there is some hidden implication unknown to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're listening to Tool, just remember that they're not like other bands. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [this is from the GameFAQs Music: Rock message board, always thought it was fucking hilarious]

When you're listening to Tool, just remember that they're not like other bands. Their music is incredibly artistic, almost to the point where you have to be paying complete attention to them to even remotely understand them. I remember listening to a song on Lateralus (though I can't remember what it was), where I thought a song was absolute bollocks during the listen. Then, I closed my eyes for a second, and all of a sudden the song had an entirely new meaning. It was insane the way Tool could just become something so different when you take a look into the music.

Another thing you should note about Tool is that it's easy to get a headache listening to them. Not because they're a bad band, but because of how many ideas their music is riddled with and how complex they are. Soon enough your head will fill to the brim and the rest will just sound like noise to you. Just turn it off and give it a listen the next day.

If you don't like the music, you'll definitely at least enjoy reading through the lyrics, and picking apart the song itself and all of the artistic values that go into making it the complexity that it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of really cringy Tool memes... there's this one from GameFAQs, must be at least 10 years old:

When you're listening to Tool, just remember that they're not like other bands. Their music is incredibly artistic, almost to the point where you have to be paying complete attention to them to even remotely understand them. I remember listening to a song on Lateralus (though I can't remember what it was), where I thought a song was absolute bollocks during the listen. Then, I closed my eyes for a second, and all of a sudden the song had an entirely new meaning. It was insane the way Tool could just become something so different when you take a look into the music.

Another thing you should note about Tool is that it's easy to get a headache listening to them. Not because they're a bad band, but because of how many ideas their music is riddled with and how complex they are. Soon enough your head will fill to the brim and the rest will just sound like noise to you. Just turn it off and give it a listen the next day.

If you don't like the music, you'll definitely at least enjoy reading through the lyrics, and picking apart the song itself and all of the artistic values that go into making it the complexity that it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Also this one.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ctt87B6hU1M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've not actually listened to it in a long time, decided I'd check it out since I made this thread. God damn, Adam's solo at around the 7 minute mark still brings me to tears. Probably the best of all time. And while I like to make fun of Tool for Maynard's pretentious lyrics and wish they'd be instrumental... I can't help but appreciate the flavor he brings to the band, when I'm in the mood for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mostly making fun of all the threads with [Tool] at the end of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that you need to clarify you aren't BM'ing proves that gamers are VERY sensitive and need to chill the fuck out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I made the thread. I'm so pissed off every time I see [Tool] on the front page and it's another /r/GetMotivated post. For once, a quote from Tool. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maynard James Keenan said, "This body holding me reminds me of my own mortality. Embrace this moment, remember: we are eternal all this pain is an illusion. [Tool] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blatant advertising </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oddly enough I'd say he was better looking in the 50s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminder that this has nothing to do with Tool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play only competitive. People are really, really dumb. Pharah always dying to Soldier, for example. He counters her and can't even aim at her... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] Complex single player strategy game that isn't Civ or Paradox? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like something with a lot of moving parts like Overwatch but I HATE playing with other people. What is something that's very replayable where I need to carefully plan out what to do and think about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it also basic human decency to not waste someone's time? Why do people queue for competitive if they don't understand the basics of a team based environment? It's not my job to teach these people that you should stick together, that's the most simple fucking thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I feel like shit for losing because of them doing absolutely insane things. So why should I care if they feel like shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a healer in Overwatch is not fun. All your teammates trickle in one by one to die and none of them can aim. If this stupid game didn't necessitate a healer and just let everyone fend for themselves, I could choose a hero that actually does something so I can kill the enemies that my teammates are too stupid to aim at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More often than not, they *are* children. So there's that.

What am I supposed to do, anyhow? Politely ask them to stop dying over and over? If they don't have the common sense to understand going in 1 v 6 is reallyyyyyy dumb, no amount of kindness is going to make them stop doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that impressive when console has aim assist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That has no effect on the game, at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what is the point of that? There is already an option to mute chat on a per-user basis. If they don't like me, they can use that option already provided to them. Reporting should be strictly for people who throw or troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the end of the world in that if there isn't the obnoxious 2-2-2, people are tilted and throw before the match even begins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because someone needs to tell them they're not good at dps. Maybe they should tank or support, but stop wasting people's time on heroes that require aim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha ok so just being nice to them is going to help them aim? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, whatever. It's also a waste of THEIR time if our Soldier is so bad he can't shoot down a Pharah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not being toxic isn't going to help me win. My teammates are still going to be trash at aiming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this were quick play, then I would agree. But running heroes someone clearly cannot play in competitive is a waste of my time. Pharah should not be killing Soldier over and over, for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do realize it's a team game which is why this game is so infuriating. No one ever groups up after spawn, they ALWAYS run straight to the objective to die one by one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is with modern games that baby players with report systems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't like what I have to say... ignore me. Why put a system in place that can silence a player's communication for days at a time? Are we five year olds here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Communication muted for three days because of "abusive chat"... you can't be serious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If players don't like me whining that they should kill the Mercy instead of the tank, or that they need to learn how to aim, or whatever - then they can just ignore me. What is the point of muting my microphone for the GOOD teammates who will actually work with me? Might as well just ban me from the game for that amount of time if I can't help my team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then we have no healer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
