<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject16</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fading American dream: Trends in absolute income mobility since 1940 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title does not tell you much, but they interviewed him and this is a great piece about his first 100 days. 

Some nuggets:
He addressed the idea that his senior aides werent getting along. He called out their names and, one by one, they walked in, each surprised to see reporters in the roomchief of staff Reince Priebus, then chief strategist Steve Bannon, and eventually senior adviser Jared Kushner. The team gets along really, really well, he said.


-

More than 200 of Trumps campaign promises are scribbled in marker on a whiteboard in Steve Bannons West Wing office, which he calls his war room. Other pledges are printed and taped beneath a poster that says: Make America Great Again.

-

In Kushners office, just steps away, theres no Make America Great Again memorabilia. Instead, the whiteboard lists deadlines for bipartisan projects in his newly-founded Office of American Innovation on infrastructure and veterans affairs. Kushner often talks about the presidency like its a business, describing it privately as entrepreneurial and in beta mode. He often doesnt mind when Trump flip-flops, if its in the service of striking a deal.

-

As Trump is beginning to better understand the challengesand the limitsof the presidency, his aides are understanding better how to manage perhaps the most improvisational and free-wheeling president in history. If youre an adviser to him, your job is to help him at the margins, said one Trump confidante. To talk him out of doing crazy things.

-

But theyre learning. One key development: White House aides have figured out that its best not to present Trump with too many competing options when it comes to matters of policy or strategy. Instead, the way to win Trump over, they say, is to present him a single preferred course of action and then walk him through what the outcome could be  and especially how it will play in the press.

-

Of late, some Republican National Committee members have become deeply concerned about Priebus, who was party chairman before joining Trumps team. Priebus, who is distrusted by some rival White House factions and lacks the control previous chiefs of staff have had, has privately complained about the profound frustrations of the job.


-

Since taking office, Trump has 16 times tagged Fox and Friends, the networks morning show, in his tweets, and countless other times weighed in on whatever they were talking about on air. After Democratic Rep. Elijah Cummings went on Morning Joe and asked the president to call him, Trump did. After Republican Rep. Dana Rohrabacher defended Trump in an early Saturday morning Fox News hit, Trump called him moments later, inviting him to an Oval Office meeting. And after news segments, Trump will sometimes call his own advisers to discuss what he saw.

No slight is too small to ignore. West Wing staffers have even fumed about news coverage of the Easter Egg Roll. First, it was that Trumps White House wouldnt be smart enough to pull it off. Then, it was that no one would be there. And after the Easter Egg Roll went off without a hitch, no one wanted to give us any credit, said one senior administration official.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The education of Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is fumbling his real chance at tax reform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole article is well worth reading. Also it is not too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Trump voters ruining America for all of us?: Tom Nichols </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'All of us' obviously means all Americans. 

The title means that Trump voters do not just make the US worse for themselves but for all Americans including the author. 

You have to look really hard for offensiveness if you find it in the wording of that title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a garbage post. Pepple who upvote this should be ashamed of themselves.

The article goes a bit more into depth than your post. Care to elaborate on your argument? Why is it garbage and why should people be ashamed?  I might just take your word on it, but I am interested in at least some kind of argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noch nie wurden in Deutschland so viele Verste gegen das Betubungsmittelgesetz (BtMG) registriert wie im letzten Jahr. Delikte in Bezug auf das BtMG sind in erster Linie reine Kontrolldelikte, das heit, die Zahl der registrierten Delikte hngt vor allem von der Fahndungsintensitt seitens der Polizei ab. Dabei intensiviert die Polzei vor allem die Jagd auf Kiffer. Gem der Kriminalstatistik 2016 des Bundeskriminalamtes, die am 24. April 2017 verffentlicht wurde, stieg im Jahr 2016 die Anzahl der polizeilich registrierten Delikte wegen Verstoes gegen das BtMG im Vergleich zum Vorjahr insgesamt um 7,1%, bei den Delikten in Bezug auf Cannabis insgesamt um 7,9% und bei den allgemeinen Versten (auf den Konsum bezogene Delikte, Besitz kleiner Mengen zum Eigenverbrauch) in Bezug auf Cannabis um 9,9%. Der Anstieg ist deutlich strker ausgefallen im Vergleich zum Vorjahr. Von allen registrierten Delikten im Jahr 2016 in Bezug auf Cannabis entfielen 80,0% auf den Konsum bezogene Delikte. Noch nie war dieser Anteil so hoch, dass heit, noch nie zuvor wurden Kiffer so intensiv von der Polizei verfolgt wie im letzten Jahr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kriminalstatistik 2016: Kifferjagd auf Rekordniveau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Writers are so stupid these days.

Quite a blanket statement. Did you read beyond the title before you wrote your comment? If so, what exactly makes the writer 'stupid'?

By the way this is the author of the article:

[Thomas M. Nichols is a professor of national security affairs in the National Security Decision Making Department, where is also the Course Director for Security, Strategy, and Forces. A former Secretary of the Navy Fellow at the Naval War College, he previously taught international relations and Soviet/Russian affairs at Dartmouth College and Georgetown University. He is a former chairman of the Strategy and Policy Department at the Naval War College, for which he was awarded the Navy Civilian Meritorious Service Medal in 2005. He holds a PhD from Georgetown, an MA from Columbia University, the Certificate of the Harriman Institute for Advanced Study of the Soviet Union at Columbia, and a BA from Boston University.](https://www.usnwc.edu/Academics/Faculty/Thomas-M--Nichols,-Ph-D-.aspx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  minority of people that didn't vote for Trump

That is incorrect. Majority of people did not vote for Trump. He lost the popular vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the article? Care to elaborate where it is wrong or which statement consists of a character attack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the author of the article:

[Thomas M. Nichols is a professor of national security affairs in the National Security Decision Making Department, where is also the Course Director for Security, Strategy, and Forces. A former Secretary of the Navy Fellow at the Naval War College, he previously taught international relations and Soviet/Russian affairs at Dartmouth College and Georgetown University. He is a former chairman of the Strategy and Policy Department at the Naval War College, for which he was awarded the Navy Civilian Meritorious Service Medal in 2005. He holds a PhD from Georgetown, an MA from Columbia University, the Certificate of the Harriman Institute for Advanced Study of the Soviet Union at Columbia, and a BA from Boston University.](https://www.usnwc.edu/Academics/Faculty/Thomas-M--Nichols,-Ph-D-.aspx)

He worked for a Republican Senator. Definitely a wide definition of 'lib' you got there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is symptomatic of our celebrity obsessed culture and his voters support of him is indicative of that

You are totally right. This is not mentioned enough in all the post-election writing. 
Also, it may be extremely hard to change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great article. Thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole article is well worth reading. Also it is not too long.
An excerpt:

There is a more disturbing possibility here than pure ignorance: that voters not only do not understand these issues, but also that they simply do not care about them. As his supporters like to point out, Trump makes the right enemies, and thats enough for them. Journalists, scientists, policy wonks  as long as the elites are upset, Trumps voters assume that the administration is doing something right. He makes them uncomfortable, which makes me happy, Ohio Trump voter James Cassidy told the Toronto Stars Daniel Dale. Syria? Korea? Health care reform? Foreign aid? Just so much mumbo-jumbo, the kind of Sunday morning talk-show stuff only coastal elitists care about.

There is a serious danger to American democracy in all this. When voters choose ill-informed grudges and diffuse resentment over the public good, a republic becomes unsustainable. The temperance and prudent reasoning required of representative government gets pushed aside in favor of whatever ignorant idea has seized the public at that moment. The Washington Post recently changed its motto to democracy dies in darkness, a phrase that is not only pretentious but inaccurate. More likely, American democracy will die in dumbness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Trump voters ruining America for all of us? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Even if you had democratic Congress, this law would still get passed.

This is bullshit and you know it. Unfortunately we have no democratic Congress, so we have to make Republicans see sense. T_D has to bring this up to Trump so that we have a chance to preserve net neutrality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  stuck in a room of carbon monoxide

I guess those would be the best way. But this probably will not be done because of the optics. It looks a hell of a lot like the gas chambers. 

If you want the government to keep executing people, the last thing you want is an association with the industrialized executions in previous history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently you slowly lose the ability to breath while still being conscious. This supposedly is associated with intense feelings of dread. 

[Severe respiratory depression is impairing and occurs at dangerously high doses of depressants. At this level, a person's breathing rate becomes noticeably slowed down significantly which results in the feeling that one is not adequately moving air in and out of the body. Severe respiratory depression induces a powerful and overwhelming focus point of attention on one's breathing rate. In terms of how this feels physically, it can be described as the feeling that you are breathing abnormally, are short of breath, cannot breathe in enough air, and/or are forced to breathe manually in a conscious effort to feel that you are taking in enough air. Extreme sedation is present and if sleep occurs one may potentially wake up struggling and gasping for air. In cases of GHB overdoses, many reportedly experience an abnormal pattern of breathing characterized by progressively deeper and sometimes faster breathing, followed by a gradual decrease that results in a temporary stop in breathing called an apnea. Confusion and anxiety often occur at this level of heightened awareness, increasing the strong sensation that one's breathing will stop completely due to sleep or a lack of attention.](https://psychonautwiki.org/wiki/Respiratory_depression) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one of the two elite-billionaires from Manhattan are you talking about? Trump or Bloomberg? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you would have read the (rather short) bbc article before commenting:

The way the study, published in the British Medical Journal, was carried out means it is not possible to determine a clear cause and effect.
However, the effect was still there even after adjusting the statistics to remove the effects of other potential explanations like smoking, diet or how heavy people are.


There may be some third variables, but there was an effect that went further than the obvious ones you mentioned.

In the journal article are some of the things mentioned they controlled for:
Analyses were adjusted for sex, age, ethnicity, Townsend deprivation index, comorbidities (longstanding illness, diabetes, hypertension, CVD, cancer, and depression), body mass index (coded as categorical variable based on the World Health Organization classification19), smoking, dietary intake (alcohol, fruit and vegetable, red meat, oily fish, poultry, and processed meat), time spent walking for pleasure, time spent undertaking strenuous sport, time spent in light and heavy DIY, level of occupational physical activity, and sedentary behaviour. 

Also. It is not like the researchers did not think of that:
As is the case for any observational study, residual confounding is always possible and associations may not imply causation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way the study, published in the British Medical Journal, was carried out means it is not possible to determine a clear cause and effect.
However, the effect was still there even after adjusting the statistics to remove the effects of other potential explanations like smoking, diet or how heavy people are. It means the reason cycling cuts cancer risk cannot be down to weight loss in the study.

They have this disclaimer in there, but nevertheless treat it as causation. So they at least tried to control for some obvious confounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Brain Scientists Forgot That Brains Have Owners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im Mai 2016 hatten mehrere Mnner den Asylbewerber in einem Supermarkt gepackt, ihn hinausgezerrt und mit Kabelbindern an einen Baum gefesselt, weil er eine Kassiererin bedroht haben soll. Der Fall hatte bundesweit Aufsehen erregt. Gegen vier 29 bis 56 Jahre alte Mnner war Ende 2016 Anklage wegen Freiheitsberaubung erhoben worden, ihr Prozess beginnt am 24. April am Amtsgericht Kamenz.

Und jetzt wird er tot im Wald gefunden? Kann klar Zufall sein. Aber klingt schon etwas komisch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FEC report: Venezuelas state oil company Citgo donated $500,000 to Donald Trump's inaugural committee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puh das heit aber ja man muss jeden Hinweis darauf das man jemals reddit besucht hat von seinen gerten tilgen wenn man in die USA reist. Sonst wollen die am Ende die Passwrter hier auch. Dann wre es das wohl mit der Einreise gewesen. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think examining the brain for non lethal CTE damages is not something that would be done in an autopsy. There would probably be different kind of examinations necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question is, what happens when the list of easy wins runs out? Theres little evidence that Trump is operating with a coherent strategic vision, which means that he wont have thought-out criteria for knowing when to say no to the generals he clearly admires. For a true lame-duck president, that may not matter  when the Ws run out, hes out of office. For a first-term president who just acts like a lame-duck president, its another story.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lack of bills or legislative agenda screams of failure.

That is exactly what the article says?
Do not understand where the laughable part is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps Foreign Policy   Executive Orders Substitute for Major Bills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NFL will do their best that it can not be studied. Potential results are way too threatening to their multi-million-dollar-business.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
