<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2737</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got rid of tv, videogames and internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Text] "If you wanna ride a bike, you're gonna get hurt sometimes, even the most professional people get hurt sometimes" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I had uploaded this earlier but I messed up my post and need to redo it, but someone else had mentioned this same thing, so I just now went to look up the Always Sunny painting and it made me crack up, thank you lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Shepherd pup, watercolor, 9x12, Arches wc paper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even slightly joking that this will be the next book I buy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a double copy of Hell House and I Am Legend, and I Am Legend was way better. I really like his short stories, but though Hell House was a fun read, I wasn't impressed,

*spoilers*


 like literally they kill the ghost with mean words..... /sigh lol, I'm waiting on a haunted house book that's actually scary, hopefully Amityville Horror or Ghost Story will do the trick.

That being said, I love Richard Matheson and I have many of his books and his short stories are awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will now be picking up another Gene Wolfe book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a Gene Wolfe book recently, Fifth Head of the Cerberus, I wanted to go with something.I've never heard of before, so now I'm pretty excited about checking it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think up be picking up the trilogy soon, I'm interested in reading something in the D D universe, though does he write anything outside of D D stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I thought he was regarded as one of the best. Anyone other authors you'd suggest instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to keep up with a book a week myself, but I think I'm at like 14-16 this year so far, I kinda stopped counting because sometimes I do a book in a couple days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What R.A. Salvatore book would you recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never read anything by him and he has a ton of stuff. I'd like to check out longer of his books but don't know which one would be his best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After you've already found the book you're looking for </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.goodreads.com/book/show/18908205-dante-s-divine-comedy-in-plain-and-simple-english

Though I'd read the whole comedy because why not?

I listened to a YouTube audio book of Paradise Lost and really found it fun, maybe try that with The Divine Comedy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read a couple books a week now.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clive Barker, he writes dark fantasy and horror, but my god he's amazing, I'll probably be through every one of his books this year, I just can't get enough of him. 

Haruki Murakami as well, I don't think anything he's written is bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not like The Stand lol, it was such a disappointment for me and when it was over I very happy that I wouldn't have to deal with out anymore. I got sick and tired of then trying to build a council and regain laws and junk and I wanted it to focus more on the end of the world stuff. The third part was the best, but it was just like, "Hey here's all this stuff, then hey that guy has a bomb"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to read this pretty soon, like within a week or so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends lol

I read War and Peace (1400 pages) in three months, Imajica (850 pages) in about 2 weeks, The Thief of Always (260 pages) in 2 days, Flowers for Algernon (300 pages) in one day, Elantris (650 pages) in a week, The Shining (480 pages) in 2 days, and The Count of Monte Cristo (1300 pages) in about a month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this whole book in a single day and I loved it, and become one of my favourites </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have swan song, boys life and gone south, haven't read any yet.

I haven't read Brian Lumey, but I'll definitely check him out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mention them every chance I get, but I feel that people who are fans are like die hard fans lol, but I also feel most only know him because of Hellraiser. I bet they don't know he also created Candyman (the forbidden).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's on my to read list, I want to finish off books of blood first though, also Hellbound Heart is really good and I think in Weaveworld the cynobites make an appearance but there's called surgeons, I'll have to get back to you on this when I get through it though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, although they don't have to be read in any order, start with the first one because it explains what the Books of Blood are, which makes the rest great

This is the order


Books of Blood 1,2,3

Inhuman condition

In the flesh

Cabal


When you finish Cabal you can move on to Great and Secret Show, then Everville because the character from the last books of blood story is the main character in those books.

Also Imajica is amazing. Also lol what made you pick up Weaveworld? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read great and secret show or everville yet, those are waiting until I finish Weaveworld and Books of Blood, but, would Scarlet Gospels count since that detective is in it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely Books of Blood by Clive Barker, unless you consider The Thief of Always horror, then I literally just finished that, also by Clive Barker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just read The Thief of Always, what a fantastic book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 08:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So once again Clive Barker has moved me in such a magical way. This book was an absolute blast, it was a super quick read, really fun and pretty emotional at times. For all his dark gritty over sexualized writing, this book, this children's book he wrote, has to be one of the best stories I've read. I've had a smile on my face the entire time, and I'm busy in awe. It just goes to show how diverse of a writer he is. Such a good book and I cannot recommend it enough. Everyone, do yourself a favor, go out and buy The Thief of Always right now and just devour it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Thief of Always has pictures between chapters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think I'm going to be able to finish GoT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk why I can't seem to get pay this stupid book, I've been having at it on and off for like 2 years now and I just can't sit down and concentrate on it, I've only got like 200 pages left and it's just....idk, it doesn't fill me with any interest to see it all the way through, I really liked the show the though and purposely stopped watching agro I could read the books, but each chapter being another perspective and nothing really happening is getting to me. But I'm stupid because when the book is good, it's really good, it just hasn't been that good, and I know that things will pick up after I start book 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, I really like foreign films and I can't remember any Russian films that I've seen so this will definitely be added to my to watch list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only seen the movie w/ George Clooney, which I liked well enough, but I do want to check out the original if I ever get the chance, I believes it's in German or some other language, but I don't mind subtitles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my copy is a translation of a translation? LOL crazy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished Solaris, I really enjoyed it but I would not recommend it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a phenomenal little book, but there are too many issues with it to make it something I'd actually recommend someone to read. Sop I actually started this last year and got like 20 pages in and gave up, I picked it up again a couple days and forced myself though the whole thing, and just wow. The actual story is amazing, the problem is that the book veers too much in certain chapters into the what Solaris is and people's theories about it, and these couple segments really really really slow everything down and it gets so convoluted that you get to a point where you're just reading words and have no idea what's going on. So I think due to that alone I wouldn't suggest it, but the actually story part is very good, deep and emotional, inn really glad I read it and if anyone else has suffered through it, what were your thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how To Kill a Mockingbird isn't on there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well when I saw it the paper looked indented as if it was written in there by hand, so there's that, but it is what it is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of decent books about witches? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commenting for Clive Barker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commenting for Clive Barker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
