<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...probably because that'd be a funny prank. And a cool decoration for your dorm. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like an origin story? I thought you meant in the same time frame as the game, whoops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not alone. I, and many of the others here, can't stop listening the soundtrack. Even though it makes me wanna cry and curl up into a ball. As a lot of the other folks have said in these comments, this is the story of PLiSD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS. The mystery of the Tobanga, and the secrets it held, stayed a mystery. And while that's fine, I am super curious as to what they might have done with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All jokes and other issues aside, what would that game even be? Seriously, I don't think it would be that interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd seen the video, but I didn't remember seeing Rachel Amber anywhere in there.

*watches video up to about 1:10*

Ow ow ow ow the humor it hurts ow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not punny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't think too much of it. I think they just got a lot of positive feedback for those quiet moments, and rightly so, and decided that uploading nice cinematic cuts of those scenes would be a great way of keeping the game alive. Making us nostalgic and stuff.

I wouldn't be surprised if they continued with a sort of "Life is Strange: Highlights" series with some of the fan favorite moments like the quiet scenes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! That was the first thing I thought when I saw the Bay ending.

Okay, that's a lie. The first thing I thought was "noooooooo god whyyyyyyyyy Chloeeeeeee nooooooo" (*sob* *sob*). "What the hell is Larry David doing at Chloe's funeral" was the second thing I thought. A temporary blissful escape from the tragedy of the scene for me. Oh Larry, always there at just the right/wrong time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ERMAGERD! I'm downloading it ASAP, probably won't have time to play it straight away though. Again. Argh! Life is..poor timing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 20:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, that was an excellent edit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 12:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious which ending you guys got. I got the one where Kate discovers that she's the last survivor of Krypton and learns how to fly, and Chloe punches Warren in the butt and he dies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That line still gives me chills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The coward! Fighting the only guy thus far who was able to dismantle him in a devastating and some might say humiliating fashion, bringing his hype train to a halt!  

It sucks that Conor isn't defending his belt, but it seems pretty stupid to label it as cowardice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought most of the performances in Man of Steel were pretty meh, but hot damn was Michael Shannon good. His Zod was super intense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 02:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paddle backwards! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 20:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be personally interested in seeing Artem and Pendred going a few rounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 01:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because...Max and Chloe are super cute together? I'm a dude, and I'm Pricefield obsessed too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 01:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that, at least in my case, LiS did raise my awareness of some of these issues. I can't say I ever thought about these things before. Not just that, but I didn't think about the way they affected the people around me. Now I feel more aware of the fact that some of the people around me, even if they don't and won't say it, are affected by these issues. Like [EP2 SPOILERS](#s "Kate"). 

I don't know enough about the Everyday Heroes Contest to speak extensively on it. I just remember looking at when it was announced and thinking that I didn't have anything that I'd be able to submit for it. 

In regards to the EP2 Spoiler Question, I did, and it didn't really impact my playthrough. Like I said above, it impacted my perception in real life, but seeing as I suffered no consequences it didn't significantly effect how I was playing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 01:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw fuck, I wasn't here for the last one! ARGH. I've been slacking in terms of visiting this sub lately, that thing called "real life" has been knocking on my door. Thank you so much /u/armis for making 100 of these things, consistently, every day. They've been hella fun, and have been a great way of keeping us active and talking about Life is Strange (the irony is this coming from someone who has *not* been active for the last three months, lol). You're a boss. 

For my favorite Daily Topic, I'm going to go with the first one I found. [Daily Topic #3: What if Nathan had powers?](https://www.reddit.com/r/lifeisstrange/comments/3xa99d/daily_topic_03/). Nostalgia is a big factor for me, not to mention that topic was something a lot of people had been talking about pre-Polarized. 

My favorite moment from the game is the scene where you return to the original timeline ("the blue timeline") in Episode 4. I've talked at length about it in the past. It was the most emotionally affecting moment in the whole game for me. After all of the heartache and heartbreak and out-of-this-world feels trip that was the Alt-Timeline, seeing Chloe's blue hair again was the most relieving feeling in the world. I was ecstatic, and so excited to have Chloe back. I was grinning like a fool for at least 15 minutes straight after that. And the song, In My Mind, holy shit. That scene is perfect in every possible way to me.

I would try not to rewind, which probably means I'd forget I had the power and would end up accidentally firing it off at times :P

Thank you so much for all the Daily Topics /u/armis! Hopefully you'll still pop by when you can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 00:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so nice. When I see fanart stuff like this, it always lifts my spirits. It suggests that Max and Chloe are alive and well, and together, kicking it in someplace nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 00:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than a year after her first appearance, Alice continues to be the most adorable person on the planet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 16:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gravity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 12:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So meta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been away for a while, but I am SO glad to see that you're still here doin' work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing Life is Strange made me happy too. We seem to be the oddballs here.

I think what LiS nails better than any game is the balance between dark and light, between depressing and whimsical. And you know what? I'd willingly go through all that horror and dark room bullshit to spend just a few more minutes with Chloe Price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moments like this are super calming. I feel like I could just peacefully dissolve in the game's atmosphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One I love to talk about is when you first set foot on the Blackwell campus and the game gives you control of Max and all the time in the world. The ambient soundtrack, the way the light pours over the lawn, it's a very serene moment. It's not a still or frozen moment though, it's very much alive. It's like...active stillness. It's a very soothing thing, just existing in this space with all these other ~~characters~~ people going about their lives.

I also love the subtle changes in Chloe's voice. How she gets super excited when plotting their Portland road trip, or how her voice softens when her and Max are alone.

But the KING of subtlety in LiS is the facial animation. Specifically for Max and Chloe. There's so much subtle detail in the motions of their faces, especially in regards to their eyes. The subtle movements really sell the idea that these are real people and not a bunch of ones and zeroes. They say that the eyes are the windows into the soul, and that rings through here. So much of their emotion is conveyed purely through their eyes. And that shit was hand animated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it was very morally challenging, other times it was a split-second decision involving no rewinding. That's a very good thing. It shows that the game actually made me form preferences and made my version of Max grow as a character, but was still able to present me with difficult choices. 

Some easy choices for me were 1) take the blame for Chloe's weed, 2) kiss Chloe, 3) "shoot" Frank, 4) spare Jefferson, 5) sacrifice the town. I didn't need to think hard for any of those. 

Some hard choices for me were 1) answer Kate's call, 2) side with David, 3) stop Warren from beating up Nathan, 4) euthanize Chloe. The last one wasn't as much morally challenging as it was emotionally taxing. 

I did notice my own personal morals changed as a result of the game. Now I feel that the people close to me matter more than anyone and everyone else, regardless of the circumstances. But at the same time I try to be a lot kinder to everyone. It's just that in a foxhole, my friends come before everything else. I don't feel nearly as compelled to act for the greater good anymore. Sounds dickish, I know. I'm not going to bother elaborating further on why I feel this way and the logic behind it, we'll be here all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really did. First off, the LiS licensed soundtrack has become daily music for me. I always listen to it before drifting off to sleep, and I'll listen to it throughout the day as well. Can't get enough of it. Secondly, I can't go back and listen to a lot of my old music before. It feels weird listening to the Daft Punk, Mark Ronson, Pharrell Williams, Macklemore   Ryan Lewis and whatever other albums that I used to listen to all the time now. Just can't go back. My music taste changed in the way that I felt I *had* to seek out new artists and new genres of music to listen to. Now I'm a big fan of Fall Out Boy, Panic at the Disco, Halsey, (revived interest in) Paramore, and Lana Del Rey, among others. I don't think there's any real rhyme or reason to it. 

As far as games are concerned, I haven't had the time to play very many games in the last six months. I tried diving back into some multiplayer shooters and some action games I used to love and play a lot of, but they didn't feel that fun anymore. Felt like a chore. However I did have a really good time with the Uncharted 4 beta, so maybe it's like with the music and I just need something fresh. I also played Firewatch, and I loved the shit out of it. 

I'm also oddly more appreciative of movies these days. I've always loved cinema, but now I feel even more drawn to it. Don't know if there's any correlation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One man is to blame: 

*IDO PORTAL, AKA THAT DORK IN THE PARK*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 02:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting to see a wealth of body kicks in that fight. Especially with all of Conor's talk about Nate's "soft body" and "fat-skinny frame". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 01:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...kicks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 01:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I call efficiency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 01:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't gas either, for the people questioning his cardio. I was also expecting him to come out with a lot more variety of strikes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 00:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conor: "Nobody can take that left hand shot"

DC: "Bitch please"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 00:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody except Nate Diaz. 

^and ^Max ^Holloway  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life is Strange is a game that I feel I will sit down and replay at certain times in my life. I replayed it only once, on New Years week. Felt appropriate. I know what you mean though, about ruining the authenticity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are so many awesome shots from the two scenes where Max plays guitar. My personal favorite is the shot from her closet (symbolism woo), with the window in the background.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, occasionally I do. The OST is super calming, very zen. I can just melt away listening to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll bet they're adorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 22:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible that this is just a shitty translation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 00:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a PlayStation exclusive actually.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 21:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed it is. The mind is a strange and beautiful thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max - Hannah. Because Hannah Telle :)

Chloe - Stays the same. I love the name Chloe. Though if I hadda pick...how's Scarlett? 

Rachel - Daisy. Great Gatsby reference.

Kate - Mary. Biblical reference ftw?

Warren - Peter. He's essentially Peter Parker with no spider powers.

Nathan - Boo Radley. Nah, I'm just kidding.

David Madsen - David Radley. Same reference, not kidding this time.

Joyce - May. Spiderman reference, again.

Mark Jefferson - Mike Hunt. I'll let you figure it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journey. It has no dialogue or complex plot, but it's one of the most emotional trips I've ever taken in gaming. Like Life is Strange, it strikes incredible emotional highs and lows, and maintains a sense of wonder and serenity throughout.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you had to lose your friend like that; life is pretty unfair at times. "The moments between us were real. And they'll always be ours," is a line that breaks me every time. It's a heartbreaking yet hopeful statement. It reminds me a lot of [this](https://hylian90.files.wordpress.com/2008/04/calvin-and-hobbes-dreams.gif) Calvin and Hobbes strip, which drew from the death of the cartoonist Bill Watterson's cat (the inspiration for Hobbes). 

Even when they're gone, we can always see them again in our dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing. I love the yellow glow on her face, and the purple streaks in her hair. Beautiful work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 17:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, realistically it'd be a flyweight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You only get to play it for the first time once! Don't rush through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AUGH CUTENESS OVERLOAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props to you for putting this out there. Even more props to you for overcoming your adversity. The intimacy and relatable nature of the characters really made this story something personal, didn't it? 

For me, LiS was about friendship. It taught me a lot about friendship, my friends, and myself. I don't think I was ever *really* aware of love (but alas, I am still young in the grand scheme of things), but after Life is Strange I started to become aware of it. The feelings I have towards people in my life kind of started...making sense I guess. Specifically towards my best friend. 

But even just in general, after Life is Strange I feel so much more *aware* of who I am. It's kind of hard to put into words.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do we think Chloe would name the puppy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed candles on her birthday cake? Hell yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adrenaline dump. He threw everything he had at Nate in the first round, and Nate walked right through it. Not only did he exert too much energy in the first round, but Nate eating his shots may have mentally fucked him. It's probably why he slowed down, leading to Nate slapping the face off of him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's generally what happens when you get stunned on the feet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hardly. But it's nothing new.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 17:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think this is just McGregor being the crazy motherfucker that he is. Like the infamous belt steal. I wouldn't think too much on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 23:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conor did the same sort of thing, trying to push past Dana, with Aldo ([here](https://youtu.be/lKkSTYLyEiU?t=3m54s)). Not close to a brawl, all Jose did was hold up a fist, but it's a similar deal. I doubt it's a sign of anything in particular. Just Conor doing what he does.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 04:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Give it 5 weeks and you'll be good as new!

Maybe literally. I haven't felt the same since. Not in a bad way. Just different. "New". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 04:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't watch anyone's Let's Play fully, but I did enjoy Jacksepticeye's video on the game. Then again, that's just because I  think he's hilarious. I mean, I didn't watch him play Muddy Heights for the game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 04:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right there with you. Funny enough, two of the most impactful stories/experiences for me came out of 2015. LiS is one, the other was the movie "Whiplash". These stories really mean something to me, and they're always a part of my thoughts now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 03:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That shade of blue just made me braingasm. Great cosplay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 22:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultimate Fighting...Conor? 

Sounds about right I guess, considering that he's currently division-hopping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like one of the reasons Siver was able to last two rounds was because of his kicks. The straight leg kicks, the rounds kicks that made McGregor slip, the body and head kicks, they didn't do much damage but they did seem to keep Conor at bay for a little bit longer. That's why RDA and Cerrone fighting him is really interesting to me personally; those guys are great with their kicks. 

Uh, I'll admit I'm not too sure where I was going with this. Excuse me, I am dumb. 

Nate probably won't come out heavy on the kicks, but he could definitely keep McGregor at range with his reach advantage. I don't think it'll be enough, but I definitely expect McGregor to have more trouble hitting Diaz than most of his past opponents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 19:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the new footage, and my excitement for this game is through the roof, but I don't think this is actually a very good trailer. It's got some nice wide shots of the beautiful vistas and environments, but I don't think it's cut or paced very well, and I don't think the music is quite appropriate. But hey, it's more Uncharted, so who gives a shit. 

I know you guys all seem to love this trailer, but this is just my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 19:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful. I freaking love the orange and yellow hues, as well as the silhouettes of Max and Chloe at the bottom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 19:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming we see Amy Adams's boobs then. There was that shot in the trailer that started at *juuust* the right time for da boob to be obscured. If this is the case, I'm not really sure what to think. Actually even if this isn't the case I'm not sure what to think. "Batman v Superman: R Rated Cut" seems like a strange concept to me. Eh, whatever, I'll still watch it. 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 23:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes sense for him to get the Dos Anjos fight at 200. And Frankie is injured, Aldo isn't in shape, Max Holloway seems like the only featherweight for them to give the March 5th fight to. But that doesn't seem very likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 04:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's awesome to see a drawing of Max that's not meant to look exactly like she appears in the game. I love the style, even if I think it looks a bit too creepy for Max.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 04:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not surprising at all. Most of our impressions of these characters are greatly exaggerated. It's funny seeing people rag on fanfic writers when they constantly have Max and Chloe refer to each other by the same nicknames, yet them using "hella/wowser" in every other sentence is totally in character. For the record, I don't mind either. It's just worth pointing out that most of us (myself included) think of Chloe and Max kind of as cartoon characters (not saying they can't be complex cartoon characters).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 04:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The supporting character/sidekick/foil always steals the performance acclaim. Look at The Last of Us, Telltale's Walking Dead, any of the Arkham games, etc. The lead is almost never given the same recognition as the foil. 

In the case of gaming, this might actually be an indication that the protagonist's performance is actually really good; you're able to step into the main character's shoes to such a degree that you start to really see everything through their eyes. Hannah Telle, Troy Baker, Kevin Conroy, their performance stops being a "performance". The performance you recognize is therefore for the character you don't play as. In this case, Chloe. Until I actually stopped to think about it I never ever considered how good Hannah Telle's performance was, because I viewed it as my own inner monologue. That's my two cents anyways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you can rewind.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 00:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turned out better than okay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 00:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if they do show us Max/Chloe, they have to look different. It has to be one of those things where for a second you don't recognize them, but they look familiar. Then it clicks and you're like, "oh shit that was Max/Chloe/Max and Chloe!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 00:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The features are slightly off-position, but the shading is fucking excellent, and the individual features themselves look great. Don't worry about the positioning thing too much; it's hard to nail down the distances in faces right. This is a much more accurate drawing of this shot than my attempts have been! Keep at it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 19:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the words, "Release the Kra-can!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 18:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been super excited about Firewatch for a long time. Putting it off because I have exams for the next two weeks, but as soon as they're done it's Firewatch time baby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 18:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another bangin' soundtrack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 18:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad and all, but that's an adorable rendition of Max.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 18:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is...weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 18:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always a way to blow it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 18:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially if you take both endings into consideration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 14:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Although it means one of the endings did not convey dontnod's message.

Actually, they both work perfectly. Just the "happy" ending becomes a really sad and depressing ending, and the heartbreaking ending becomes the good ending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 03:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the first, not the last. Welcome brother. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 03:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think "Don't fuck it up son" is just a general statement from Sean to Nathan that expresses the way he looks down on Nathan. I don't think he's specifically referring to anything. He's just being a dickhole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 03:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ending I guess? How weird would it be if I couldn't remember a scene from somewhere in the middle of the game? You'd be able to put two and two together from what comes before and after, so the scene you get to re-experience would completely lose its impact. At least with the ending, it'd be in chronological order so you actually *could* re-experience it. 

But for the sake of a cool answer, I'd love to re-experience returning to the original timeline in Episode 4. It's my favorite scene in the game, and it didn't make me sad. So I'll got with that one. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 03:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that crazy, or that uncommon, but I'm reasonably accepting of the theory that Max has no powers and never saved Chloe in the bathroom. The whole game is her trying to cope with the feelings of losing Chloe, after never having called or seen her, having abandoned her, by creating a series of nostalgic, oft whimsical, and sporadically painful (reality) adventures that they went on in her mind.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 03:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These drawings are awesome. I love that first one so much! Nice work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 03:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could. It seems as likely a possibility as any when it comes to possible future seasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's something I'd like to get around to writing; a story that's just snapshots of Max and Chloe (post Bae) in 2016. Where are they, what's going on, how are they doing now, etc. What is that relationship like, what are their mental and physical states like? How have their appearances and personalities evolved? It's a concept I think about a lot every day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the photo. Good luck in the contest bud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ask me, Life is Strange is about a certain tone and style, and revolves around the concepts of relationships, coming of age, and identity. As long as they adhere to those core tenets, it's Life is Strange. It can feature Chloe and Max, established and well loved characters, or a new cast. It can be set in Arcadia Bay, Oregon, or Timbuktu. Whoever, whatever, and wherever the story calls for. Don't give us a new cast just for the sake of having a new cast and milking the IP, and *definitely* don't bring back Max and Chloe just for the sake of bringing back Max and Chloe and milking their already-established characters. 

I will say this though: if they make a second season with new characters, it can't have ANYTHING to do with Season 1. No Arcadia Bay, no significant mention of the storm (if any), NO REWIND, none of it. Just connect it to Life is Strange by those core tenets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does Henry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MMMMM YAASSSSS

Firewatch and LiS share several delicious qualities in terms of visual style. The yellow and orange light, *god*. I wish I could just bathe in that shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's just hard to let someone die when you could've saved them, regardless of whether you're going to rewind and undo it all later. Those people and their lives are *real*, regardless of alternate reality bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot damn, that's a beautiful looking website. I likes. I likes very much! Kudos to you dude, you've done an awesome job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 13:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wowser, a little bit of a trip down memory lane eh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 02:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks hella dope! I feel like you captured the somewhat childlike nature of Chloe in the face and eyes. Good work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 02:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Valentines Day to you too. You may be single, but I lurve and appreciate you very much. Can you have multiple Valentines? I'll take everyone from this sub please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 02:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 02:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Let 'em have their time*

*Sit back and let 'em shine*

*Let 'em rise and rise*

*Cause one day they're gonna fall*

*Let 'em soak in the sun*

*Sit back and let 'em have their fun*

*Let 'em spill their guts*

*Cause one day they're gonna slip on 'em*

*Well I could be angry*

*But you're not worth the fight*

*And besides I'm moving on*

*I've counted to ten*

*And I'm feeling alright*

*And besides I'm moving on*

*Let 'em play their songs*

*Let 'em say what's right and wrong*

*Let 'em do their thing*

*Cause they'll never be you and me*

*We got our own style*

*We got a way of livin' life*

*If they can't get down*

*Well we don't need them around*

*Well I could be angry*

*But you're not worth the fight*

*And besides I'm moving on*

*I've counted to ten*

*And I'm feeling alright*

*And besides I'm moving*

*Yes I'm moving*

*Besides I'm moving on*

["Moving On" by Paramore](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Xqcguy1YjI). A song that always reminded me of Life is Strange.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 00:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monday=Crabby Maxie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
