<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8477</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 07:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not at all. It just means you haven't made you intentions clear or one of the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pola X: Look, I will not lie. Incestuous, Dramatic, and unFuckingBelievable!! Watch it! Watch it now!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 06:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 06:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish that we could all get together and just discuss the films that we have seen, in person. DREAM COME TRUE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 06:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Departures was just a movie that..WOW...I will never forget it. Never. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 06:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this movie. I truly appreciate when a movie makes me feel. It's goosebumps and sadness and love and want all rolled up into one. This was one of the movies that helped me to realize that i just wasn't into the generic action genre any longer. If the OP reads this, I have many suggestions for your viewing pleasure; this is a favorite. [This](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0109424/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 06:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more saddening that you are so ill informed as to believe that otherwise is is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 06:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because...cptamericaref.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 05:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you are ignoring the jobs that were and still are being created. How can you vote for a man that will LITERALLY lie about anything to please the current audience? I mean he wants to take away choice for women! That's my SISTER, YOUR MOTHER, EVERY FEMALE IN THE USA. How can you be for someone that will stage fundraising events to charities that do not condone what he is offering because it make things harder for them, as a charity, to operate? He preys on weak businesses to cash in (Our economy doesn't look so well right now). How do you not see this? How? If you are against Obama because he is black, fine, say that. I would prefer you did. That would be far better than believing that you REALLY think Mitt Romney is the best choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 05:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, once upon a time there was a United States President that went by the name of....uhmmm..we'll call him George Dubya. He ran the American economy into the ground and left it up to his successor to fix the problem. His successor, being a man of pride an duty, worked hard his first four years against a backbone of a congress that despised and abhorred him. he made some successes, but could have had many more if the great monster, GOP, would have played ball. Now, here he is, going for four more to fix what has been wronged a restore us to a place of dignity amongst the international community. And there you have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 05:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this how you would like to represent yourself? With this statement?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
