<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4909</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 08:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I went for it but now other problems/stress </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vent Post: Process of Looking for Apartments/Moving Out, Fear, Doubts, Setbacks, "Good Faith Deposits," Intuition vs. Paranoia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have another vent, been stressing, doing research all night and didn't get any sleep (not that I am tired). 
Quick Background:
- Horrible Soul crushing living situation that brings me pain/fear all the time.
- Unemployed but have savings to last a couple of months if I find a place. Not looking for a job until I find and have a stable place.
- Been looking for sublet Craigslist apartments for months on months, as far back as March/April. It's been so long because I haven't been full-time/all the time. I've also been looking for sublets (between 2-6 months), somewhere I can clear my head, collect myself, get a job, save money, and eventually find more stable/longer term place. Lastly it's taken so long mostly because of fear/anxiety. Just looking at Craigslist housing posts used to cause stomach-aches. It still does but less and I know that I need to get out/have my own space.

My situation:
I found a place on Craigslist a week ago. I spoke to someone and went to see the place on Tuesday. There were 2 other people looking for the place too. BTW that took strength, I was soo afraid. My stomach hurt and I was nervous. Thank God my mom was there in case I had a panic attack. Anyway I like the place and I want it. The leasing manager/who is also an individual broker said if I want to continue forward with the process I have to do an application online. 
She emailed me the instructions and the application link. I filled out the application and submitted the required documents (I did everything online the same night). BUT THERE IS A CATCH. I must send a $500 deposit/closing fee to hold the apartment. In turn she will take it off the market. If I am approved then we will continue the process. I am assuming that means (getting/signing a lease). If I am not approved she will return the deposit back to me. Keep in mind that I haven't been approved, haven't seen or signed a lease, and I haven't met the landlords/homeowners.
Even so, I have am having serious fear, doubts about this "Good Faith Deposit" process. I am afraid as soon as I put in the deposit she is going to run off with my money and I won't have any way of tracking her. 
As I already said I am unemployed but I do have savings and good credit. I have enough savings to last the whole 6 months of the leasing term. Even so, I am not loose or risky with my money. My family has always been struggling with money my entire life and I don't want to make mistakes and do stupid things with my hard earned money. I also have a cautious/plan everything nature.

I did mad research. I looked up her name on the state department, I looked up the landlord/house owners property records. Everything seems legit. I looked up housing policies and it isn't unusual or illegal to do ask people for a holding or "Good Faith Deposit" before getting approved, looking at and signing a lease and meeting the landlords/property owners.
I really don't want to be duped. I can't afford to fall for a scam. I really don't want this to be a scam. $500 is a lot to lose for someone who doesn't have a job, and has hang ups about spending money. I can't even buy things I want without feeling guilty about it.

Right now I am waiting to hear back from the leasing manager. I sent her an email with a bunch of questions (such as asking for an electric copy of the lease and getting this "Good Faith Deposit" thing in writing with signatures) and I may meet up with her to see the place again later on today. 

In the meantime while waiting I am freaking out. I don't want to lose out on this place but I also don't want to be scammed/made a fool of. All this fear makes me question if this is my intuition talking or my paranoia. Part me wants to just pay the deposit and see what happens and the other part is like no bitch (like what if I get stuck in a bad leasing situation).

Like what should I do? How can I assure myself? How can I have faith? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change your outlook and perspective on yourself. I don't know if you have this in your country but watch/listen to the School of Greatness podcast (there is a channel on YouTube and a website). Watch Lisa Nichols videos.
Start a DAILY gratitude journal. Also tell the truth (figure out and write down all the lies you tell your self and tell the truth). It's a method by Lisa Nichols.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old are you? Listen to the School of Greatness podcast (there is a channel on YouTube and a website). Watch Lisa Nichols videos.
Start a DAILY gratitude journal. Also tell the truth (figure out and write down all the lies you tell your self and tell the truth). It's a method by Lisa Nichols.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
