<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3726</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone ever make posts on here and they turn up on your history page but don't seem to appear on the forum so nobody comments? This has happened to me a couple of times. Anyone know what it means?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a huge fan of French cinema (or at least I was before it stopped being all that interesting) and started to learn French in the hope that one day I could watch my favourite movies without subtitles. Well it's three years on and I can hold a (very) basic conversation in French - but I still don't have a ******* clue what anyone in French movies is talking about. I get 'salut' and after that I'm lost. :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need ideas for film club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about *2001*? Obviously the technology is not advanced by today's standards, but the sheer creativity of the ending manages to successfully communicate the overwhelming nature of such a transcendental experience. I would also suggest *Magnolia* and the rain of frogs. Through his camera work, writing and editing, Anderson creates a suitably monumental climax.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By chance I happen to have seen *The Cabinet Of Doctor Caligari* for the first time just yesterday! It greatly impressed me how many standard horror movie narrative devices and sequences are contained within this film from 1920. The exploitation of the uncanny - the monster at the window - the device of setting up a 'red herring' murderer who is caught by the police - the unreliable narrator - there was so much there that must surely have been a huge influence on later cinema. In fact to say the film was an 'influence' feels like an understatement. It pretty much invents the contemporary horror film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm - it did! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally. Gosling in *Lars And The Real Girl* - I don't understand how actors do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed the movie. I think Ford spent quite a lot time creating a sharp contrast between a sanitised, glossy and immaculate world of style, fashion and art galeries, and a dirty, messy world of human passions and suffering. The two worlds clashed most obviously in the many art works included in the film - housed in perfectly manicured interiors, but always depicting violent and chaotic emotions. Edward's novel is another example of such an art work. I would suggest that Edward has written a great novel, and that he was only able to do this as a direct result of the terrible emotional suffering Susan has caused him. Because of her, his comfortable city life fell apart and he was dragged down into the emotional dirt. He knows this, and while he may on one level be filled with a desire for revenge, on another he is grateful. Through his actions he finds a way to express both of these contradictory feelings towards Susan. So he gets his revenge, yes, but at the same time in dragging Susan down into a world of suffering he means to save her from her life and her world - a world she feels increasingly detached from and depressed by. Susan is searching for meaning, and Edward gives this to her. At the very last moment of the movie we see Susan's eyes and we know she suddenly understands what Edward has done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God yes - you immediately make me think of *Kasper Hauser* and the sequence with the carnival animals. I would also add Tarkovsky to a list of directors who specialise in beauty and wonder!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Em... well Toby Maguire just popped into my head I guess, but i suppose I was thinking of his performance in something like *Ride With The Devil*. If you want a really interesting example of the impact an actor can have on getting the audience on side, I would recommend watching (if you haven't already seen it) Haneke's *The Piano Teacher*. Isobel Huppert plays what should be an intensely dislikable character. She's destructive, mean spirited, narcissistic, and pathetic. And yet we are absolutely desperate for her to find a way out of her misery. The German actor Bruno Ganz is another good example. In *Wings Of Desire* or *Eternity And A Day* he delivers performances so underplayed it really is as if he's simply turned up and stood in front of the camera doing nothing. But we are on his side. I actually find the whole thing quite mysterious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's interesting you ask that, because the whole salting business is something I find really confusing. In this case I feel the salting *did* affect the texture of the final dish. Although the pork was delicious, I did wonder if the texture would have been better without the salting. Flavour-wise the salt worked well - as did the fennel seeds I added with the salt. I was surprised by how much of the fennel flavour had penetrated the meat. Although many recipes recommend the salting for confit, next time I will try the dish with much less, or even without the long salting beforehand and see what the results are. I'd make a post about it but I imagine it would be immediately withdrawn by the mods for being 'too general' (happens to me about once a week). Maybe someone with expertise in this area will read our comments and respond.....? :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might not be the kind of answer you're looking for, but I think a lot of this is down to casting. Good film actors (or at least those that tend to play sympathetic roles) have an ability to get the audience on side immediately, just by showing up and standing in front of the camera. I'm trying to think of the best example I can..... maybe someone like Toby Maguire? (Now a bunch of people are going to tell me how much they hate Toby Maguire!). Other actors have some particularly strong aspects to their character that make them people you immediately want to invest in. Jack Nicholson, for example, has this. Even when he's playing some crazy murderer, the audience *needs* to follow his story. At the risk of upsetting people, I would suggest someone like Leonardo Dicaprio is an example of an actor who doesn't really possess this quality, despite being a leading movie star. My point is that it's not a given for every successful actor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just personally speaking, la la land might have worked better for me if the dream world had been contrasted with an impression of the real environment of LA. The opening is a good example of what I mean. A song and dance number bursting out of a traffic jam is a fun idea, but I didn't really believe the traffic jam to start with. I don't know why exactly, but nothing at all seemed real in this movie. Thinking back, the only location I can remember that felt like it might have a connection to a real world was Gosling's apartment at the beginning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well - it's a little too late for me to change my plans this much now! Maybe I will try your method next time. I'm not sure about confit being a marketing ploy - as I understand it the technique is really very traditional - unlike sous-vide which is relatively new (I don't know very much about this - please someone correct me!). Anyway I gather from reading a few online articles the techniques amount to pretty much the same thing. I've read that experiments have been done using water instead of fat to confit, and the results were exactly the same. It's all poaching! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeh my oven's OK in that respect - I've roasted very low for several hours before - never for 12! Luckily I've got the day off tomorrow so if the pork needs longer I guess I can keep an eye on it throughout the day. Thanks for your comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pork belly confit overnight?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello. I'm about to attempt to confit a piece of pork belly (about 1.5 kg/ 3.3 lb - bone in) in pork fat. I've had the pork in a dish with salt for 24 hrs, washed the salt off, and now it's dry. The best looking recipe I can find online instructs to confit the pork in a low oven (150 C/ 300 f) for three hours. After a conversation I had with my butcher about 3 day confit duck, I'd really like to try the pork overnight at a lower temperature. I often roast a small joint of meat very low (75 C/ 170 f) for hours till the internal temperature is 'safe' (a brilliant way to roast any small joint). My plan is to try the pork in the pork fat at 75 C and leave overnight - so it would be in there for 7 hours or so. Can anyone tell me why this is a crazy plan?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *La La Land* puts a fair proportion of its energies into creating a dreamlike fantasy version of Los Angeles - a 'city of stars' where anything is possible and dreams can come true. In a way it's attempting to steal the 'city of dreams' identity from New York, traditionally the cultural focus for 'dreams can come true' movie narratives, from the Follies of the 30s to *New York New York* and *Fame*. 

*Rebel Without A Cause* is significant in that it was one of the first popular movies to focus on the social problems of Los Angeles - to 'expose' the real disfunctional undertones of the city that houses the superficial glamour of Hollywood. Since then movies that have been set in LA and in and around Hollywood have tended to follow this 'expose the underbelly' pattern, from *Sunset Boulevard* through *Day Of The Locust* and *The Player* all the way to the recent *Inherent Vice* (and incuding films that focus on LA gang conflict such as *Boyz N The Hood*, which are direct descendents of *Rebel Without A Cause*). 

Chazelle wants us to forget about all that - to forget this popular LA mythology ever existed. And so Mia and Sebastian choose to see *Rebel Without A Cause* - but Chazelle keeps first us, and then them from really taking the film in in any significant way. Mia first stands in front of the screen, obliterating it from our view, and then the film burns out, preventing the characters from seeing it out to its depressing conclusion. Chazelle includes *Rebel Without A Cause*, and then does everything he can to obliterate it. 

What does Chazelle *not* want us to see? *Rebel* ends with the murder of a young man on the steps of the observatory - a sad wasteful event born of street violence - an early example of an event that is a fairly regular occurance on the streets of LA even today. When the police cars have gone, a man in a suit casually walks across the scene, a 'respectable' middle class gent, comletely oblivious to the murder the location has just witnessed. The message is *this is happening around us, we just don't see it*. Mia and Sebastian may idolise James Dean as a glossy movie icon, but within the rhetoric of *La La Land*, the lovers function in every way in the manner of that respectable gent casually walking by the observatory steps. In fact they take his purpose several steps further - gleefully singing and dancing on the grave of *Rebel*'s troubled young hoodlum, just as *La La Land* itself dances on the graves of all the victims of social deprivation, the addicts, the drop outs, the porn stars and the hookers that people a city that has more commonly been presented to us a global heart of darkness. Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devil's Food Cake - should I tinker? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making a birthday cake for a party this coming weekend, and have settled on a Devil's Food Cake. I'm following Margaret Costa's recipe from the classic *Four Seasons* cook book. 

The ingredients (sorry this is in metric):
280g brown sugar/ 175g butter/ 3 eggs/ 85g plain chocolate melted in 150ml water/ 280g flour (+ rising agents)/ 150ml soured cream/ vanilla extract. 
The method is standard for a cake batter, with the ingredients added in the order given. 

First trial with this cake is a success. The texture of the sponge especially is superb - beautifully light and moist. My only criticism is the flavour. It's a touch on the bland side. I feel like it needs something - cocoa powder maybe to boost the chocolate. Is it safe to add cocoa (or anything else good that would up the flavour of the sponge) and not risk sacrificing texture? I'm not experienced with this old fashioned type of cake- is it simply the case that this type of sponge is best seen as a base for delicious icing (frosting)? Thoughts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What do you guys think about the movie?

I love it. Lynch's films are just so freakin' *weird*, I think not enough is said about some of the fascinating aspects of his work - his portrayal of women for example. *Mulholland Drive* is especially striking in this respect. Is it a feminist movie? A terribly misogynist movie??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly the greatest American film of the 20th century IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a font of wisdom. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I see- use common sense. I should have thought of that. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That pesky acid again! It trips me up quite often. Thanks for your comment- makes a lot of sense 

Edit: does the same apply to chickpeas? I never add salt as we're always told it will make the peas tough. I always add a pinch of bicarbonate of soda and to be honest with you I have no idea why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry- my question has nothing to do with Spanish cuisine! The recipe I was following just happened to be for a Spanish style stew. I wrote the question in a hurry. I'm an idiot! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's with Spanish recipes and dried bean instructions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I made kidney bean with chorizo and blood sausage following the method given by Patricia Wells in *Bistro Cooking*. It was OK, but I struggled to get the kidney beans to cook. It took about five hours (luckily I was making the dish well in advance!)

Wells instructs us to pour boiling water over dried kidney beans and soak for one hour, then to drain and simmer the beans in stock (wine) for two hours or more. I followed this (I very rarely use kidney beans so I don't have my own preferred method) and found the instructions gave nowhere near the amount of time I needed to get the beans to a pleasant eating tenderness. I fished the packet out of the bin and noticed the instructions advised soaking the beans over night (this is what I always do with chickpeas). Curious, I looked up some similar recipes and found alarmingly different methods - all the way from 24 hour soaking to one recipe which advised adding the *unsoaked* dried beans to the stew and *simmering for an hour*! Anyone fancy **hospitalisation** for dessert?

Can anyone shed some light on this dried kidney bean anomaly?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it looks like I'm wrong there. I recently watched an historical documentary film which included Kissinger, and the film maker showed some clips from *Strangelove* and suggested there was a link. Seems like it's a common misconception. I'll add a note to my original comment - thanks for correcting me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember liking this film a lot. Ozon is a highly skilled director - what I admire is his refusal to give the audience what they expected. He keeps us curious right up to the last minute, often pulling back from drama - so difficult situations are sometimes resolved easily (or rather the resolution occurs almost imperceptibly with the passage of time), while elsewhere crisis appears as if from nowhere. It's all a tricky balancing act Ozon has become wonderfully adept at. I'm not sure I agree with you that the Vacth character is a 'typical person in extraordinary circumstances'. To me she might just as easily by an extraordinary person in typical circumstances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes - I've heard about Werner von Braun - from the [song by Tom Lehrer!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QEJ9HrZq7Ro). That makes a lot of sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you are absolutely on to something with your ideas about Strangelove. The character was based (in part) on Henry Kissinger, who was born in Germany. Kissinger was actually a jew who fled Germany to escape the Nazis, but as a very broad satire, *Strangelove* takes great liberties with the inspirations for its characters. I believe many details of the characterisation came from Sellers himself, and so were borne of an ingenious comedic instinct rather than carefully considered subtext. Still, it's interesting to look into Kissinger and his controvertial political career as it will give you further insight into *Strangelove* in general. 

Edit: seems like I'm wrong about the Kissinger link- see discussion bellow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not 100% sure, but I don't *think* 17 was underage in New York in the 1970s (?). It's a technicality, but a significant one. Also, as far as I understand it, Allen has never been convicted of any abuse of children, and the allegations brought against him were all dismissed. I think you have to take these things into account when making your own judgements in this case. Having said that, I do find Allen's relationships with much younger women in some of his films 'icky'. *Manhattan* isn't really one of them though. In the 1970s there was an entirely different attitude to the sexuality of 'just legal' teens. There was something intensely sophisticated about the older man/teenage girl pairing - perhaps influenced by a European attitude to such matters, which still exists in some form today. I'm not sure I would support particularly singling out Allen in the respect - it seems unfair. You would need to start questioning the films of Roman Polanski and Maurice Pialat - and those two are just off the top of my head, I'm sure there are many many more. But of course, make your own judgement here, because each of us should. I struggle with the films of Klaus Kinski today for the very same reasons. I can't unknow what we now know about his treatment of his daughters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you saw my paragraph on Toni Erdmann also on this page. It left me cold also. I felt this was largely down to the actor playing the father character. I could not connect with him on any level. He seemed like a complete blank to me - I didn't understand why he did or said anything - he was like this totally random facade with nothing happening behind it. I also felt the film was ridiculously long - in no way did its content justify 160 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can acidic marinades actually toughen meat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Toni Erdmann** (Maren Ade, 2016 - up for Best Foreign Film Oscar) - very disappointed with this German odd-couple (Father/Daughter) comedy, after hearing a beyond glowing review on the radio. Structurally it's a fairly standard clash-of-personalities-learn-something-from-each-other narrative, with the gentle slacker practical joker Father showing his work obsessed daughter there's more to life than getting the contracts - kind of in the mode of *Pretty Woman*, except the asked-for prostitute is now an unasked-for parent. 

It never feels nice to single out an actor for criticism, but in this case I felt strongly the reason the otherwise quirky and potentially funny action failed to land with me was the Father, played by Peter Simonischeck. I simply failed to connect to this character, despite several obvious signals from the director that I was supposed to be strongly empathising with the rather pathetic but warm hearted joker. The actress playing the daughter, Sandra Huller, was, on the other hand, fantastic. At one point the Father asks 'are you human?' after witnessing his daughter in action at work. Ironically, I was thinking just the same thing about *him*. Huller so successfully communicates a vivid inner life, it is she that often ends up looking like the 'human' one of the pair. This imbalance jumped out at me from the off and for me the movie never manages to escape it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 15:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harsh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Figured this subreddit might get a kick out of this story.

Maybe if it had ended with you pushing him under a bus....? :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know - maybe there is not much point in searching American cinema for the kind of content you enjoy so much in European art house. For me, there simply is nothing in American cinema that can compete with Pialat - with Varda or Dumont. I get my Weerasethakul fix from Weerasethakul - I don't need Hollywood to provide that for me. If you really want to challenge yourself, why not try some cinema that Hollywood does better than anywhere else? I mean have you seen *Die Hard* (1988)?. I am not being facetious. *Die Hard* is a masterpiece of its kind (I do not joke) - and could only have been made in America. If you haven't seen it, watch *Die Hard*, and if you are unable to appreciate this film, well then I would probably accept that you will never really appreciate the very best that American cinema has to offer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many recipes call for more than a glug or two of wine :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good advice - thanks :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is actually quite a coincidence, because I *just bought* a bottle of Barefoot wine in the corner shop which I'm using to marinade a venison shin. Completely random purchase - it was around 7.50 (approx $9).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes - but here they don't tend to stock smaller bottles of wine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
