<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2699</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video shows drunken-driving arrest of Washtenaw police lieutenant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman says she suffered miscarriage due to excessive use of force by BART police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family files federal lawsuit against first responders in son's tasing death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia former policeman sentenced to life in prison in Taser death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cop says he fired only warning shots, admits he'd been drinking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this genius piece of legislation could be coming to a Red State near you. From [this article](http://www.free-times.com/news/local-and-state-news/sc-lawmakers-want-to-block-porn-as-part-of-national/article_f5a9b8e6-c540-11e6-9e4e-379a92121edc.html).

As is often the case with conservative bills, the bill is actually model legislation that didnt originate here in South Carolina. Its being introduced in about 25 states this coming year, according to Chris Sevier, a former attorney from Tennessee whos behind the model law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think plenty of people (especially groups like Everytown) take a more holistic view of gun violence, in which it's not just about the damage that is inflicted when Person A intentionally shoots Person B -- or in this case, Person A. Imagine going to a school where someone has committed suicide on campus, or where a gun battle happened in the parking lot the night before, even if it didn't involve students. Or where a kid brought in a gun and accidentally shot into the ceiling and didn't hit anyone. All of this has an effect on students, not just when it's a deliberate act of targeted violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta wonder: Do guns and gun violence only affect students when someone is bringing a firearm to the school with the intention of killing them? I feel like I would have been pretty shaken up if a kid had shot himself in the parking lot of my high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok must just be bad writing. Considering Everytown is only counting school shootings, why would they include the other one that happened at a home?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It happened at a home."

"Not a school shooting."

It happened at school, which would lead me to conclude that this was indeed a school shooting incident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, this guy is full of shit. I'm not going to go through every link to prove that he's full of shit, but I selected one randomly and here goes:

11/3/2016 Berthoud, CO Berthoud High School

Another student suicide. Everytown didnt pretend to care about the other one, because it happened at a home. Not a threat to other students. Not a school shooting.

Yet the [link](http://www.coloradoan.com/story/news/2016/11/04/berthoud-high-school-teen-found-dead-identified/93289106/) he provides clearly states that the kid shot himself at school.

If you're going to get high and mighty with an "audit," you better be accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Houston police chief wants body cameras that automatically record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Body camera helps convict Vermilion police officer of assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evansville, Ind., cops caught beating a handcuffed man, then lying about it. They wont face charges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYC To Pay Over $600,000 For Excessive Force, Unlawful Arrest,   False Statements by NYPD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bergen man sues cop who showed up at wrong house and killed his dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officer fired in 'poop sandwich' incident could get his job back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man sues after mislabeled DNA leads to mistaken arrest on rape charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa disbands state forfeiture team, OKs $60,000 settlement to California gamblers whose bankroll was seized during a warrantless search </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This [video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MappUyWPY5M) from Charlie LeDuff in Detroit is one of my favorites on this topic. At the 3:30ish mark, he's talking to beat cops about the dangers of the job. He asks one of them what he'd do if someone came rushing at him without a gun.

"That's just a fight," responds the officer.

Fighting an angry suspect has to be scary as shit, and it's certainly not a job I'd want to do, but is this not a risk that comes with the territory and that police are equipped and trained to handle? When did it become standard operating procedure for law enforcement and apologists/supporters to consider any physical altercation to be grounds for cops to use deadly force? Couldn't they bust out the nightstick and beat the suspect down? Didn't cops used to enjoy having an excuse to do that kinda stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio police officer accused of stealing more than $26,000 from a charity fund used to buy Christmas gifts for financially disadvantaged children has been ordered to repay $15,000. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social Circle Police Officer fired after profanity-laced traffic stop with teenager </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City pays Austin officer who killed teen $35,000 to avoid arbitration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The don't care either way camp would be agnostic. If you literally don't have an opinion one way or the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but there has been an increase in mass shootings. Just as there's been a decrease in overall gun deaths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S. Jersey man arrested in 'Pro-Trump', racist post-election vandalism in South Philly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still feel like the "don't believe in god, but could be swayed by actual scientific proof" people fall in the atheist camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio Judge: In God We Trust on Currency Does Not Violate RFRA, Free Exercise Rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleveland woman jailed 3 days while waiting for judge to accept no contest pleas to traffic violations, contempt charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LAPD officers who fatally shot homeless man on skid row were legally justified, D.A. says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DA: Man who smashed cars with baseball bat was just angry, not anti-Trump protester </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man whose $11K was seized at Cincinnati/Northern Kentucky International Airport gets it back -- with interest -- after settlement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 Los Angeles County Deputies Get Prison After Jail Beating Of Mentally Ill Inmate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois law enforcement takes in more than $319 million on forfeited property </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libertarian lawyer enters fight against Indiana's civil forfeiture law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore entrepreneur launches program to allow family or friends of arrested individuals to exchange firearms for prison bail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never suggested he wasn't dangerous. He stabbed people, cops knew that, I understand it was a tense situation. I don't know what you're envisioning, but this was not a case where the kid had a knife to a hostage's neck or something. The only people left to hurt were police -- humans and a dog. Considering they outnumbered a 15-year-old suspect clearly out of his mind and armed only with a knife, it seems like they could balance the need to "stop other people from getting stabbed" with the basic human desire, one presumes, not to kill a kid who has done terrible things during a mental break.

Instead of reflexively defending the officer's action, which again I agree was lawful, why don't we consider how a tragedy like this can be used as a teachable moment to avoid unnecessary loss of life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about a big weighted net...

I'm kidding, but honestly it seems like the non-lethal weapons and de-escalation tactics we give our police are lacking. We can do better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had time to use non-lethal force six times. And they are educated/licensed to kill people with ease. Why can't we all agree that we should shift some priorities away from killing and toward de-escalation, proper tactical confrontation, dealing with people in crisis, etc. to minimize the need to kill. Not saying they shouldn't be able to kill -- I agree that this case will be closed relatively quickly -- but we should all want to avoid seeing sad shit like this happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking hallucinogens can trigger a mental crisis though. Believe you me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Officer can't be blamed for operating according to rules. Real question is whether cops should have more options for dealing with someone in a mental crisis. Not just a matter of non-lethal weapons, though it seems like there are probably more devices out there that could shut down a situation like this, beyond what they had. But maybe serious psych help from a professional would actually work better than deciding that the proper way to respond to a violent incident is with further violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dirty doctor busted by DEA with doggy X-ray, undercover stripper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago Ald. Brookins Seriously Hurt When Squirrel Gets Stuck In His Bicycle Spokes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 19:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NMSU releases video of officer shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Affidavit: ABQ police have illegally deleted, altered videos of shootings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pen Argyl man cleared of felony for kilo of legal powder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems like a misreading of the [actual report] (http://www.aclu-il.org/wp-content/uploads/2016/11/civil-asset-forfeiture.pdf) which doesn't break down which forfeitures were civil and which were criminal -- likely due to shit reporting requirements. Still, safe to say a lot of this cash and property was taken through the civil process, meaning no need for a conviction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby died after jail staff ignored labor, inmate says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drain the swamp? Lobbyists were in Trump transition, now out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maine refugees to Trump: Tell us  that we have a place in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oregon schools reporting rise in racial attacks after Donald Trump election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driver says CPD made her wait several minutes before letting her take dying friend to the ER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wouldve put a bullet in womens heads, Weiser officer says on video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 18:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portland prosecutors drop more serious charges, for now, against 100+ anti-Trump protesters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea does not care who is president of United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mayor de Blasio urges all Americans to continue protesting Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 23:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 00:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've gotten away from the crux of the issue. These people aren't being jailed for crimes. More info here:

http://www.masslive.com/politics/index.ssf/2016/11/report_sheds_light_on_poor_inm.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't underestimate the power of a good moral compass. Also consider how factors that are outside of our control (family situation, wealth, mental health, etc.) make it easier or harder for us to keep these compasses well-aligned.

Anyway, jailing people for poverty doesn't make sense. I'm sure a lot of these fines could simply be forgiven without massive damage to the systems that have come to accept massive arbitrary fines as the cost of business. Or these places could work to create a more proactive method of getting people on a schedule that will allow them to pay when they can pay, or work off fines by other means.

Either way, the argument that laws must be enforced to bring people into compliance to avoid anarchy starts making less sense when the laws themselves are so often enforced in unjust ways and then amplified by further unjust means of getting people to comply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the fear of incarceration really what keeps you from breaking the law? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man arrested after filming a Portland police precinct from an SUV filled with weapons and ammunition has been sentenced to three years probation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what does incarceration actually accomplish? Does it keep people from breaking the law? On the contrary, evidence shows punishing someone with jail only increases the likelihood of future criminal behavior. Does not rehabilitate and does not succeed in actually extracting concessions -- in this case financial -- from the person. In fact, only costs taxpayers more to house inmates and pay for future social costs they're likely to incur. We need to completely rethink the way we use incarceration as a punitive measure. We cage humans out of some sort of cruel sense of retribution, which makes us treat inmates as subhuman both while behind bars and after they get out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why cities typically settle police brutality cases. No telling what will happen when you try to defend what the average person sees as indefensible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, the defense being the ones defending the cop from murder charges. Makes sense that they'd reject minority candidates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly all-white jury seated in trial of ex-cop who shot Walter Scott </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
