<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject754</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 05:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment isn't very funny and it will be immediately buried. What's the point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 04:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's often the case. 

For offensive wallpapers you don't even need full blown image editing, just the text tool. Unless you're photoshopping dicks onto people's noses or something like that. That takes a little more effort, but not much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 04:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is how [1024x536]](http://i.imgur.com/FaIgfPZ.png)

(Yes, I realize this is less than the minimum requirement for submissions, but it's the first one I clicked on in google. Fuck you.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 04:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, forgot that rule. I just added one, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 04:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a 3-gun competition this weekend, and these are what I brought. The bottom three are my competition guns, and the top three are my backup guns, in case something breaks or malfunctions. 

Bottom guns (used in competition):

* Remington 870 with 10+1 capacity
* AR-15 with muzzle brake (machined by yours truly) 
* Glock 34 with grip stippling

Top guns (backup):

* Winchester 1300 Defender with Blackhawk recoil reducing stock
* Mini-14
* Glock 27

I did very well in the competition for my standards. I got 7th overall out of 38 participants. In attendance was Craig Calkins who took 2nd at the World 3-gun competition last weekend, along with several others who were at the World competition. 


Needless to say, I was pretty darn happy with how I shot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 03:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The top three are my backup guns in case something catastrophic happens to one of the bottom three. 

Although there was a time where I did use the glock 27 in competition because I had nothing else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to a 3-gun competition? Better bring 6. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 03:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goodnight, Texas - The Horse Accident (In Which A Girl Was All But Killed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 20:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 19:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEAD ON, APPLY DIRECTLY TO THE FOREHEAD

HEAD ON, APPLY DIRECTLY TO THE FOREHEAD

HEAD ON, APPLY DIRECTLY TO THE FOREHEAD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 03:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What cute babies they had

http://i.imgur.com/AFlDUBn.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 03:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But this machine goes to 11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 03:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many dildoes is an obscene amount? One? Ten? One thousand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 07:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Works especially well for sausages](http://www.gifwave.com/media/46108/game-of-thrones-got-sausages-ramsay-bolton-ramsay-snow.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 05:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 05:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an introverted rock climbing engineer your edit is my worst fear.

I'm pretty sure it's 95% the reason my ex broke up with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 14:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rejoice, for you have found a righteous brother that will always have your side in battle.  


Unless he's a Collin... then offer a fake peace treaty to be held by the banks of a river. During the ceremony, the rightful Colins will rise up from the bushes and reeds and annhilate any Collins in attendance, driving them like mad cattle into the frothing, bloody waters to their doom. 

It's the only way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 02:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great singing and music. I look forward to hearing more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 06:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loosen lug nuts. Jack up car. Remove lug nuts. Remove flat tire. 

Assembly instructions are the reverse of disassembly instructions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 06:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And completely hairless. *Oh yeaaah* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 05:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you yell "Fuck the police!" every time you masturbate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 06:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Really slow music paired with dull lyrics. I think they took the airy indie style a bit too far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 09:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If readily available, coordinate with others to launch as many nuclear warheads as possible. 

Most people wouldn't be able to do anything, but the few people in the bunkers and nuclear submarines would absolutely wreak havoc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 22:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Make sure you arrange them correctly](http://static.fjcdn.com/gifs/How+to+arrange+pizza+rolls.+Tada_2dc945_5144040.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 22:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is a rabbit](http://i.imgur.com/QpCF0hs.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 02:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the bright side you've got a trials bike now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 04:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/sEGeTwW.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 02:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you doubting his ability to drive away all but 7 subscribers? I have full confidence /u/CowJam could do away with all but 3 or 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 05:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By raising the issue, you will inadvertently volunteer yourself to reprogram the entire system, upgrade all necessary hardware, and implement the new hierarchy without any downtime, with zero hardware cost, and while still continuing with all your normal job duties. 

That's why legacy systems run rampant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 09:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got me. It was taken with [this](http://www.digitallydo.com/phone/we202.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another glorious day, the air as delicious to the lungs as nectar to the tongue. [3648 x 2736] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 14:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 03:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I learned two things today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 03:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this one time my 4 one upping friends started one upping each other and I actually did punch one of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 06:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, that's not the normal procedure for hot tapping? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 04:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Pete and Repeat were in a boat. Pete fell out, who was left?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 14:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's more of a dingleberry than an apple </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 05:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Laughing with dead eyes](http://cdn.mos.totalfilm.com/images/c/christian-bale-american-psycho-2000-_148967-fli_1384789729.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 06:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is just for you](http://i.imgur.com/szsGcjs.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 06:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only kind of engineer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite road trip game: Add "Anal" in front of any trailer or RV name </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 15:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 14:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck them and their crafty ways! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 02:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! We contemplated hiking right up the couloir, but it would have taken much too long. We dropped in right at 11am, and any later would have been real sketchy with how warm it was on Saturday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 02:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's certainly a fun time up there. Lots of big lines. Just be real careful about snow conditions. 

For instance, we dropped in a 11am, and I wouldn't have dropped any later than 11:30. Things can get melty fast this time of year. Also during the early season weak layers can cause the whole thing to slide. Falling in the chutes would be a pretty quick way to get dead even if you don't get buried.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 01:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure thing, I'll come up with something in the next few days. Maybe not a full how-to on splitting your own (there are plenty of videos out there), but I'll show the mechanics of how it all works. 

Also, shoutout to /r/Spliddit. It's not the most active, but it sure is a fun sub to look at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 01:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this, I used his videos to help guide my build a few years ago. It's super easy and my board has held up great for the past 3 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 01:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, the skin track starts out at the Bear Lake trailhead and goes up to flat top mountain. It's not a bad skin at all, and it's way quicker than boot packing straight up the couloir. The only upside to boot packing is that you don't have to downclimb/rappel if there isn't enough snow up top.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dragon's Tail Couloir in RMNP. 1600 ft of vertical at 45-50+ degrees slope. Burly lines on a beautiful day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 14:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 14:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Album of skiing Dragon's Tail Couloir this Saturday](http://imgur.com/a/AV2b2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 06:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Dragon's Tail Couloir in Rocky Mountain National Park. [Here's an internet photo of the area](http://www.mountainproject.com/images/82/99/105808299_large_a37e28.jpg) Dragon Tail Couloir is the one directly looker's right of Dragontails peak labeled on the photo. I'll post up an album of the trip tomorrow. Edit: [here's a few photos of the couloir I took](http://imgur.com/a/qu2Al)

It's about 1600 vertical feet of 45-50 degree slope. Luckily there was enough snow up top that we didn't need to rappel the first bit, although we had harnesses and rope for it if need be. 

Burly lines on a beautiful day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-18 19:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Taken yesterday. Any love for splitboards and steep couloirs?](http://i.imgur.com/RHD2mZn.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 06:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> massterpiece 

ftfy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 00:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? That's super lame. I could easily make a backpack propeller for less than $2-3k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 06:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great advice, and it's how I got my current job. I got a job offer for an acceptable, but not great, job opening at another company. The company I currently work for informed me that they would like to interview me, and I told them that I would love to work for them, but that I also had a pressing decision to make. 

They took that into consideration and had me interview with 5-6 people at the office (normal is 2-3 rounds of interviews seeing 1-2 people each time). I walked in at 8am for an interview and walked out at 11am with a job offer in hand. 

If you've impressed them enough to get an interview then you know they're interested in you. Hiring people is a pain in the ass, so if they know they have a highly motivated candidate they're more likely to bend some normal hiring rules to get you in. Just don't be pushy or demanding, and show that you're interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 05:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. The street thug snowboarder style isn't my cup of tea at all. I think it's stupid, but some people like it. As long as they're having fun and not ruining things more power to 'em I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 01:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cutter is an [MH 871-MK 2](http://www.amazon.com/USCutter-34-inch-Vinyl-Cutter-Plotter/dp/B003D21SK8) and it comes with its own software </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 14:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some other stickers we made and clandestinely placed:

http://imgur.com/a/BdiVb

They include a Darth Vader head, a motorcycle, a few text stickers, and two ford stickers because our friend is vehemently against ford vehicles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I and 3 other friends are all into building cars. One of our group just got a vinyl cutter so he can make very large stickers. Nobody is safe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 14:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-12 04:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 23 and shave maybe once a week to chop down the one or two stray hairs that appear. [My face is a desert wasteland for hair](http://livinggreenmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/03/lone-tree.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 03:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, engineering school was *way* different. Hardly anyone wanted to go out and drink on a friday night.

I hear about keggers happening at 2am on a Tuesday night at other colleges and it blows my mind that it's even possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 06:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome to see some more Mines folks out there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 03:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://static.fjcdn.com/pictures/Please+tell+me_f3455a_3839869.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 05:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, 

I'm an engineer, and I don't think that's structurally sound... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 17:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 05:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you looking for this perhaps? 
http://www.bellyboner.com/


NSFW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 04:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nalgene](http://nalgene.com/) and [Kleen Kanteen](http://www.kleankanteen.com/) are some of the most popular bottles. Nalgene won't dent like the metal bottles will, and they can hold a bit more in them, so they're my favorite. They also don't taste like metal. But if you're not into plastic then buy yourself a kleen kanteen and stop worrying about water bottles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 21:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sit right down and I'll tell you a tale of the internet. Back in my day the internet was a wild frontier of piracy, lewd photos, and cat pictures. Trolls ran rampant and anonymity was the brazen shield that every user believed in. I've seen millions of dollars made and lost in the blink of an eye, I've seen massive attacks on public domains, and I've seen some of the most disturbing things you can see. Now son, now things are different... the internet has been rounded up, broken, and saddled. The wild, carefree days of casual surfing are gone. All that remains is the institutionalized mess we have now. Sure it works, and it works efficiently some of the time, but the days of posting on questionable forums, the nights of raiding, and the thrill of the unknown is gone. Dead and gone...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look at these fatcats, gloating about their opulent meals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 20:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 19:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at this fatcat over here, you have ELEVEN whole dollars in the bank, do you know how many lentils you can get with that? Enough to start a farm, that's how much. You also have two and a half beers, and a hamburger. That's a full year's supply of calories right there, and that's just from ONE friend! 

How's it feel to be sitting all high and mighty knowing you never have to worry about sustenance again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls love fast cars, and lifted trucks. Porque no los dos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 02:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 06:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, this modest proposal of yours seems very efficient </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 03:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Boom bitch](http://californiaoutdoors.files.wordpress.com/2012/02/bowfishing_indianheadranch1.jpg). Bow fishing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 02:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and why did I start masturbating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 05:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here buddy. I keep waiting for that perfect time when the clouds will part, the sun will shine, and I'll ask her out on a date in a perfect manner. Then 3 months later she's suddenly dating another guy and I never did anything to show how I felt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 04:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/eKi8C0M.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 06:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we *do* get to view all their public indecency. He's got my vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 06:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  embiggen

I don't know why, it's a perfectly cromulent word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 01:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's /u/POTATO_IN_MY_ANUS when you need them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 06:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went from 180 front/160 rear to 208 both front and rear. It cost me maybe a few grams of weight but GODDAMN did it increase my stopping power. The added weight of large rotors is negligible, but the gains are huge. So why not go with large rotors front and rear?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 06:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, that trick is like snowboarding 101. They didn't have you practicing switch 1080s on your first day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 04:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [However your fingernails are able to be digested into useful nutrients whereas your hair cannot.](http://i.imgur.com/krxVd.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 02:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Party on, Wiyne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 18:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, like a heathen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 17:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any other way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 17:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love cooking and baking. I also sew pretty well, but I generally sew [manly things](http://imgur.com/a/yxlot) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 17:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to the train derailment issue, there's the issue of aiming. Someone made a handy graphic just for this: [How to pee with morning wood](http://i.imgur.com/41gtr.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 06:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're looking for an answer for the question "how far can I go before I break" then steroids and drugs will allow you to answer that too. It will just raise the breaking point from where it is now. 

And quite a few athletes (even in minor leagues and college teams) use performance enhancing drugs currently, just take a look through professional cycling or baseball. Not much would change except that everyone would finally be open about their use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 09:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until he and Jon go out on patrol together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 08:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those. MONSTERS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 08:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Adidas Sambas](http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/0/08/Adidas_Samba_sneakers,_Originals_branch.JPG). Go!

*I've been wearing this brand for about 6 years now because they fit well. What does this style of shoe say about me to a random person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 06:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 05:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-AgyiM2exqXU/UyP0eYEUHyI/AAAAAAAAFT4/N_gmpHM3Xzg/w346-h207/Man+with+the+scariest+talent+ever.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 22:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get an internship, and work on projects for fun *and document them*. I like to mountain bike and snowboard (among other things), so I've built several mountain bikes, built a splitboard in my spare time, fixed engines, etc. and I took pictures of all the cool things I made, even if the project didn't seem all that hard to me. This shows you have real hands-on skills. A surprisingly high amount of people who go to college for engineering have never worked on anything before and can't hardly tell a nut from a bolt. 

The way I got my current job is by making a 1 page photo addition to my 1 page resume. I threw on photos of a trophy truck frame I'm building, pictures of a bamboo and carbon fiber bike I made, some SolidWorks screenshots of things I've modeled, and a few other things. This gives the interviewer something to talk with you about, and you can describe how you built the project and how some of those same skills apply to the job you're looking to get hired for. 

Also, software skills are important. Lots of companies look for someone who has experience with SolidWorks, Pro/E, AutoCAD, etc. And if you have experience with one type of modeling software then your skills can generally transfer over to another software suite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 03:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bigfoot's dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 15:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there's your problem, the floss goes in your teeth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 01:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That's one hell of a blow job](http://www.crh.noaa.gov/Image/top/events/toptor/torn.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 06:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Barry, does this make up for Framboise? It does, Other Barry. It sure does." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 04:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes some awesome sails for my sailboat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 01:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $3 for a drink *and* a van ride? My night just keeps getting better and better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 20:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like fishdicks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 05:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's long and it's hard to get through
](http://futanariobsession.com/content/No_Soul-epic-futa.gif)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 17:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually for this picture I installed the clock mechanism backwards which made the welds on the front. It's since been fixed, but you can see some heat affected areas on the front side still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 03:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. Until I assembled the whole thing I didn't think it would be hard to read, but I was mistaken. Future clocks will certainly feature black or otherwise colored hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 00:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several people have told me this. Perhaps once I buy a new TIG welder I'll throw a few up on etsy or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 00:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought about that right as I put it together. I might opt for black hands for the next clock. And yes, I TIG welded the gears together (although it wasn't hard, just two tack welds per gear) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just finished my first bike-themed clock. What do you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 22:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 05:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://geeknation.com/Content/Blogs/06_2013/games-recap-ep10-11.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 04:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was drunk at 2am walking alone through a bad part of town a few weeks ago. A large group of black guys all walked up on me and asked me if I could give them some directions, even though it was fairly obvious they weren't lost. I stumbled through the middle of them and mumbled something about getting home and just kept on walking. 

I had to walk home 10 miles that night (I fucked up and missed the last bus home), and until mile 9 I didn't really realize the many possible bad outcomes of that encounter. Maybe they were genuinely lost. Or maybe I walked straight through a mugging/scam. Cities be scary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 23:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was a legume-based fetish site </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
