<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4719</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes do it!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High school teacher here! I have my own classroom so i dont carry too much around
Backpack: Laptop + charger, lunch, umbrella, iphone and android chargers.  I make sure to have extra tampons for my female students as well. 

Sometimes i accidentally take dry erase markers and red pens home in my purse :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wear glasses and i keep adjusting them/touch my face without realizing sometimes. so i feel you on that! just a habit you gotta get into </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take vitamin C and D on the daily and wash my hands (bathroom and sanitizer) obsessively. Don't touch your face unless your hands are clean. Oh and get your flu shot! Preventative measures help, but nothing is 100% effective with all of these walking petri dishes! :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a colleague last year who would often times hold my students after class making them late to my class. She would even pull students FROM my class!!! From the students i heard that she found their senior paper more important than their math class. She was the english office chair and i was a first year in this school so I felt intimidated to say anything. 

She was fired in the middle of second semester last year because she wouldn't teach, she would sit and gossip with the students.... sometimes about things that are not appropriate for a student teacher relationship </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg how has no one thought of this already?! brilliant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! i'll try that app out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 15:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have yet to call off, a redbull keeps me going. I was weened off medication a few years ago, because my anxiety isnt as prevalent anymore so I dont think thats the path I'll go. I do think, however, going to therapy again is a good idea. Thank you so much, for the idea and the hope! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 12:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah:/ you're right,  that's definitely where I fell through last night!  I'll try my best tonight. Thank you:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anxiety about work- losing sleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 12:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second year here.  I had a sleepless night again. I was riddled with self doubt,  anxiety and a sprinkle of depression about my teaching abilities.  There's no trigger for it (unless thinking about work as I'm trying to sleep counts), I just feel suddenly insecure.  I'm doing well and I know I am- my department chair and vp said so post observations.  However, I cannot stop thinking about where I feel that I'm lacking. Maybe I set my expectations too high for my level of experience?  Anyone else going/went through this? Does it get better with time?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Feta :) I adopted her 6 months ago and she's fit right in since day 1:) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2nd full time! 3.5 counting maternity leaves :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to get a job in high school and it was my dad's idea to have me work as a teacher's assistant at my synagogue. She let me teach a few lessons. I then knew that i wanted to teach! I also had some amazing teachers in my high school career. I had one math teacher in particular who as spectacular and I found myself thinking "I want to be like him" and here I am! a high school math teacher :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WORD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can try to understand it, but i do not think it is universal. Saying we should have children to teach is ridiculous. Getting pregnant is not on my to do list for several more years - so according to their logic I wouldn't be able to work my dream job to several more years. Fact of the matter is, young teachers might seem to get "mad more easily" simply due to lack of experience and inability to de-stress outside of work. Older teacher with kids can get mad more easily because they're irritated and stressed with their own children. 

My teaching ability does NOT have anything to do with what's come out of my vagina. I can be a bad teacher with kids or a good teacher without. I can be a good teacher with kids or bad without.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 25, no kids. I don't get mad easily, if anything my patience is almost too high. I do not yell at my students. If I am angry with them I simply get strict in my tone. I don't consider myself strict in my teaching approach, but i'm not super lenient either. I believe I have a good balance with my students based on mutual respect. I honestly think the whole kid thing is bullshit. Maybe having children will improve my teaching in some way... but it will also add more stress to my life which can be a detriment to my teaching. I know older teachers (in their 40's) who are amazing - students love them, students learn a LOT from them, they are my goals - who do not have children and do not plan on having any ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> last year i had a student with a dad who wasnt really present, and when he was he was aggressively present. My grading system is weighted (i teach high school math) and although i've explained that the last time he sent an awful email to me, it didnt stop him from writing one again. This one was all about how awful of a teacher I am and how my teaching philosophy is ruining his daughter and so is the school's grading scale. I was hysterically crying at home because it was my first year full time and I really began to doubt myself. The next day at work I talked to the principal who helped me respond. Apparently this guy's been doing this to teachers at the school for all of his daughter's four years here and i just got caught in the crossfire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've kept a hand written journal since 2007. It's very helpful for the moment,  for self reflection,  and to see how much I've improved! I think I'll be doing this for the rest of my life  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  I have 1-3 covered to a T:) Ill see about 4 if I stay at this school longer:) thank you!  I think I might go see another neurologist soon,  it's gotten to that point again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so sorry for your loss!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brain fog is the most perfect way to put it! Mine last days or weeks  sometimes, so I feel you on that! Sending well wishes right back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get them every other day if not every day. I was diagnosed with acute chronic migraines and went through a ton of medications with a neurologist. I might try another doctor, but at this point i'm kind of hopeless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man, if i took off when i had migraines i'd be gone daily. I was unfortunate to get acute chronic migraines :( I agree with you - better to power through than to lose a day with a sub!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may try being honest next year, letting them ride it out again this year! thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Migraines   Teaching </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have chronic acute migraines and have had them all of my adult life (started freshman year of college). I've been to many doctors and neurologists and no one can really give me the proper help. Medicine works only sometimes and usually wears off pretty fast. I can power through them and teach - provided the right medicine  circumstances. However, my migraines cause my head to be all.... funky. I lose my balance, bump into the wall and desks, and trip over myself, which is easy to laugh at with my kids. My words come out of order and I mispronounce things a lot.I havent told my students about my migraines and i didnt really plan too,  but sometimes it's embarrassing. I teach high school math and I am very confident in my skills as both an educator and a mathematician, but when i make mistakes because my head hurts it makes me upset. Migraines are a fact of my existence so i've already accepted that it is what it is - and my students have accepted my weirdness. I often worry that they question my authority on the subject because of the mistakes I make ( I correct them instantly and always know I made one right after.... but still...).  
Does anyone else go through this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IBS here - probiotics and avoiding my trigger foods has been the best  way to deal for me. however, like you - i'm lucky to have the bathroom a few doors down and that often saves me cause i know i'll be able make it until I can make a dash for it once prep starts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I am recovering and i'd like to think full recovery is within grasp. I have been to DBT when i was 16 but i didnt take it seriously, i'm sure if i did it would be very beneficial to me! I had a therapist until 2 years ago, with whom i worked INTENSELY on all my symptoms. I've been off meds for about 6 years now and have been very much fine:) I have had relapses related to cutting, once every one or two years since i was 17. They  last literally a day and i snap out of it like 'wtf did i just do'. 
I think i'm at a very stable point in my life, depression and anxiety still get the best of me (might get a therapist for that soon...maybe), but other symptoms are pretty much gone/i have learned to deal without involving anyone or letting it out on anyone. I have a full time job in the career i've dreamed about, an amazing relationship- a HEALTHY relationship (never thought this was possible with our disorder tbh),  and i live on my own, all independent n stuff:) 
So I think i'm close. I strongly believe it is possible to recover with the right help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, first year is always ALWAYS be crazy like that. My first year was too. Try your hardest to make me time and remembering to do things outside of work. I did that by setting alarms on my phone and keeping a calendar with several reminders to do the thing i need to do (reminders to make appointments, reminders to go to them, when i'm seeing friends, to call a friend to make a date). 
I promise you that next year will be better :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your health is more important than keeping up with grading (at the moment) So I hope that you take the time to recover and worry about grading later. Maybe you'll fall a little behind, but you'll catch up in no time! 
I have emergency sub plans ready for when i am sick, which are usually ACT prep (i teach high school math to jrs and srs) Or some sort of basic review. That way grading them is just a skim instead of hardcore grading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
