<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4153</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Machinist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the shy away from a really satisfying ending to leave room for a sequel. Everything needs a universe now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a third person game, you usually have woman ass to spend the majority of your time watching instead of a man ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most cruel thing you've ever witnessed ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved that the show tried to stay true to the comics by calling the zombies "geeks" but no one stopped to think that it sounds weird and cringey aloud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one was foxkin, we talked about it later at the paintball field. I can't really hold a conversation with a mascot outfit long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's tons of metal that have great vocalists, and those are the ones i really listen to. I have a playlist called Bolts In a Blender that's nothing but growling pig squealing bullshit metal for my work outs though. Eventually my head goes somewhere intense where I forget I was listening to music or working out in the first place. I just feel my body hurt and realize I should stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hell is not the place you go if you're not a christian. It's the failure of your life's greatest ambition," </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to go out more with friends and family. Got shook up by a nasty loss and i let it take over my life for too long. Got a girlfriend that loves me that i need to treat like the angel she is. And brushing up on old hobbies I've forgotten.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> season seven started with a bang and if you weren't caught up people were so childish about spoiling it. But the new seasons are much more dark and real, I enjoy it. I just try not to hype past what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beer in general tastes like if you let a soda go rotten but it still retained it's carbonation. Double shot of tequila and a ice cold lemonade to chase it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moba communities make it crazy uninviting to get the hang of. I tried smite for a while for a friend but I could never really get into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's not a great show. But you really feel them pull out all of the stops in season five through seven. I liked season one and two but 3,4 kind of made me steer clear for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a local street gang in my city called the Colonia Chiques. Mexican gang refering to their Chicano pride BS. I would open up a bakery in the middle of Colonia and call it the Colonia Cheese Cakes, and make the most delicious cheese cakes ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost a brother to leukemia in 2012, I was always trying to be strong for him because he was fearless through the whole thing. I never got the chance to tell him I loved him one last time. We were always trying to be tough for each other and we didn't say it enough. Macho bullshit got in the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is something you never got the chance to say ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn.. that would kill me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohhh my god, you allowed it to breed ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly the I've always been into weird subcultures so i've crossed passed with a few furries. It seems that the weak minded ones have taken this new trend as an out. I was at a festival a few months ago and there was this guy in mascot fox outfit that had nothing to do with the festival at all. I wrote him off as a weirdo and went about my business having a good time. Than he approaches me and calls me by name. It was a buddy i knew from paintball that thought that that was his authentic self. That he felt like he was being who he actually was with a damn fox suit on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things that bother you, never bother, I feel happy and fine aha ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living In the Sunlight by Tiny Tim, also known as That one spongebob song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they never did though, RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's easy to write off pedophiles as some one that needs help until they kidnap your kid, fuck them for a few weeks, than kill them and toss them in a ditch somewhere. Spay and neuter the nonviolent offenders, and bring back the guillotine for the killers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He asked me to calm to calm down and there was no reason to have a gun out. I told him that there was no reason for him to be breaking my property and that he had no business trying to get into my house. I told him that i didn't want to hurt him but if he took a step towards me I would punch a hole straight through his gut. He dropped the piece of bench and a herded him out of my backyard. I called the police and let them know what direction he was headed and they picked him up a few blocks away. they took way too long getting here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sister wakes me up in the middle of the night and tells me there's a monster outside her window. I tell her it was just a bad dream and she insists that i look. A methd' out man with matted hair and dirty clothes was tearing apart my mother's bench and angrily saying something to himself. I had her lock herself in the bathroom while I called the cops. I took five rounds and loaded them into the rifle. He tried to open the sliding glass door to the living room, so i went through the garage and entered the backyard where I could get the jump on him. He had a big hunk of bench in his hand and was trying to get in. I put my sights on his chest and asked him to leave, he said something like "Fuck you, you wa -" than he saw i was aiming a gun at him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> quote the article, there may be other types of bodily fluid in there but it's mostly urine. what else is it ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but hey, plenty of people really like golden showers and it's nothing to be afraid of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a lot of information that suggest that the urination is caused by orgasm. but it's basically urine, do some research, plenty of people like golden showers. woman don't have some super secret sex gland and reservoir of "squirt" it's just that some woman can't control their bladder when they orgasm so they piss. 

http://www.netdoctor.co.uk/healthy-living/sexual-health/a2295/female-ejaculation/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> onions are good, combined with the sweet of the pineapple, spice of the jalapenos, and bacony goodness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pedophiles should receive more punishment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pineapple, jalapeno, bacon, and onion = perfect pizza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> use your blinker you insignifi-CUNT little fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An fling a while back after an amazing session was trembling asking for me to lay next to her. She grabbed my cock and said "You are magic, actual, factual magic" truth be told she was one of those lucky girls that has her clit perfect;y place so the balls rub them while she's getting it from behind. And certain strains of herb work like viagra for me and I was BLITTTZZZED. so just under an hour of that and she was a mess of her own home made lubrication.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is your favorite sexual accomplishment ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An fling a while back after an amazing session was trembling asking for me to lay next to her. She grabbed my cock and said "You are magic, actual, factual magic" truth be told she was one of those lucky girls that has her clit perfect;y place so the balls rub them while she's getting it from behind. And certain strains of herb work like viagra for me and I was BLITTTZZZED. so just under an hour of that and she was a mess of her own home made lubrication. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most you've ever sacrificed for someone else ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this kid's grades were bad, so his mom made him watch as I bought his WIIU, smash bros copy, controller adaptors for $40 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl bought me a drink a while back, random woman and nothing ever came of it. But it made me handsome and wanted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he totally is. he earned it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is the best thing about you ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Threesome with my gf and a clone of my gf, while a clone of me watches and jerks it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see that logic and respect it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are ? "Huh? A 9mm won't instantly kill you" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> read, where did I say it won't ? I'm saying that a .22 is still lethal and nothing to just write off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was talking with a budy of mine at this.. garage band house party thing. We were sharing some drinks, i saw his girlfriend in the background and thought nothing of it. I had no way of knowing he'd been banging her cousin over the last few months . She found out, grabbed a bong and pitches at his head missing us by inches.

I said something "what the fuck ? stupid cunt !" and I doubt she heard me at all because she was on him like a rabid house cat. Punching, kicking, clawing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shot a 45 long colt once. such a unique feel, very nice choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously. stupid easy to use, reliable, easily available, and crazy effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My gf keeps a youth aluminum baseball bat in the car with some tenis balls. the bat is feather weight but strong and easy to use, and the tennis balls give an answer to pansies and cops asking questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a 9 will kill instantly sure. But statistically the .22 is the highest killer in the US. Also a .22 is much more likely to break apart in the body and incredibly hard to repair since they stay in the body more often than not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have the muscle to be too good with a crow bar. hard to recover if you miss. But i'd feel comfortable with a claw hammer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also for what ever reason the .22 gets a lot of scoffs. as if a small bullet makes you any less alive than a big one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been taught not to rack a gun at some one, if some one makes their way in my home without my permission with harmful intent. I don't want them to know where i'm at till i've got my sights trained on them. But i respect the choice, most bullshit that requires a gun happens within 20 feet. and within 20 feet it's hard to beat a shot gun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got an 870 shot gun that just feels right to me as far as fire arms, I've got a cs kukri that has been my favorite campsite tool, and melee weapon. Never owned anything as easy and effective to swing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right ? after the first 100 rounds they start to jam up here and there. But before that it's a no recoil bullet hose if you have a good trigger job in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> respect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What weapon are you most comfortable with ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitch, watching people play video games live. Maybe I can make an exception for tournaments. But watching some on e else play a game is kind of bores me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously, dating apps are where it's at. for the same price as you pay for a lap dance OR CHEAPER ! you can hang out with an interesting person. and not only get to see the good stuff if all goes well. But you actually get to have sex instead of awkwardly getting erections with your bros.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What guilty pleasure do you keep from your friends and family ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A man used rape to take my sister's virginity. I used a knife to take his wallet, phone, and ring finger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohhhh to be young and from the south </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got the refference, now we can be friends. Just got done with the 7 mile trail at sycamore. It's feels like it's barely recovering from the fire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got back from Honneyville in Rancho Cucamonga CA. Bought a few water storage containers, some freeze fried meats, veggies, fruits, and some oats, beans, rice. Enough food and water to keep the gf and I independent for a few weeks comfortably. and some spare rice for barter, and charity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cousin ! I'm 30 minute drive from malibu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other day I was at a get together with a few friends. I was sipping on a drink and I over heard a few buds talking about their "zombie plan" and I said something like "dumb ass, we get earth quakes that swallow cities and your worried about zombies ?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Natural or otherwise, how prepared are you for disaster really ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your favorite back handed compliments ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 07:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tumblir, they may have been a time where I would have given them the time of day. But the hard core left needs to learn that they can be just as harmful as the hard core right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 07:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> links, no way this got that bad. over a cartoon ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear of the Dark - Iron Maiden. It's not just my favorite metal song, It's my favorite song.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a room that is basically free game to paint on the walls at my university. i used to do graffiti stencils and I want to pick a devilishly scary face to put up as you walk by or enter. The university used to be a mental institution so it has a long history of scary stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] If you were walking by a room and saw a figure standing it, what kind of figure would scare you the most ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bright white room with ne exits and no way to turn off the lights. Every time they try to sleep, blare awful noises over loud speakers. Throw food and water at them only when it becomes dangerous not to. Two - three days tops and you'll have your self a feral human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Espolon is my go to, the silver %100 pure agave is on par with patron for half the price. It's well known in tequila circles that patron is just swindling the laymen with sub par tequila. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> espolon is great bang for your buck, I don't really touch jose cuervo or patron. But if I feel like shelling out cash i like Don Julio, or Tres Generaciones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> specific doe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really care for beer. I can see why people like it, but it takes too much liquid to get me drunk. and it always tasted as if some one let soda go rotten but it retained it's carbonation. Triple shot of tequila and some lemonade to chase it and I am set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If your goal was to drive some one insane, what would be an easy way to go about it ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> git gud scrub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tequila  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, those guys are intolerable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why it's rated M, stopped a mom at target from buying it for her kid. I described the introduction of trevor in vivid detail and let her know that he was a key PROtagonist for the game. She put it back and he was staring teary eyed little daggers at me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am ZombehMoose on the social club, add me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pro choice. Sometimes I sneak into the dumpsters of planned parent hood and that's my dinner for the night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fathom, say it a few dozen times. it turns into nothing a lot faster than other words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> squeezing a child out out my dick hole. Damn thing would look like the end of elmer fud's shot gun after bugs put's a carrot in it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put up or shut up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PC ? my buds and I act as an impromptu esrb rating. We all have tanks and travel as a convoy. If you squeak, you get squashed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> incels, nuff said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's something else that has crossed my mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a dark recess of my mind where a distant memory of this movie lives. 90s personified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
