<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3287</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Dynamic Queue was announced, a lot of Redditors declared they wouldn't play ranked this season. Did anyone follow through with that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, now that the season is ending. I recall a lot of dissent over DQ (myself included) and many stating that they wouldn't play ranked or even quit the game altogether because Riot had "ruined it" and I'm wondering if that held through for anyone here or if Riot's attempts and remedying the issues and reaching out to the community brought people back. Did y'all play more or less ranked this year than in previous years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also he has a really sexy laugh

Relevant flair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 14:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frosk is also - if you see her post on Reddit (/u/thatchinesefangirl) and elsewhere, very eagerly open to criticism and takes that which is given to her onboard. She may still be subpar to several viewers but it's very obvious she had made an effort to improve and is continuing to do so. LS is very much the same analyst he was 2 years ago and does not take to criticism well - he often just goes on saying the same thing without considering what has been put to him (as seen with him repeating things after Alex Ich disagreed AND appeared to be right based on what happened in game). Goes a long way toward the perception of a person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Gnar, Azir, Kalista   Rek'sai - 4 champs who've been under recent fire for overloaded kits - were all released consecutively. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 06:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or rather, today I remembered :P.

Been seeing a lot of discussion in the community recently about how all four of the above champions have extremely powerful kits that cause them to dominate the meta and crowd out other champs in their roles if their numbers are even remotely decent (and often refuse to fall off even when they're nerfed because of the utility of their kits) and it made me think "huh weren't they all released in 2014" and then I realised all four were released within months of each other. Makes me wonder just what Riot was thinking with their design philosophy at the time and how it's shaped their philosophies going forward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> while i agree her comments can usually be pretty left-field i thought the drake comment was fine in the context of the series and all three casters previous commentary on it - RNG was playing reactive and passive all series up until that point and had been called out on it so the comment sounded more like an extension of that (ie: "yes they got mountain drake but it's not worth much if they keep playing like they have been") and just imo it would have been more out of place to say "i'm interested to see what proactive things they do with it!" when in context you wouldn't expect them to be proactive just based on how they'd been playing :p. you are right she probably could have segued that into a comment about how they could take advantage of their comp to start being proactive or smth though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggestion: Work the new solo/dynamic/team stamps into S6 Ranked Reward Borders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 11:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This year Riot added special markings to signify division in ranked borders, so how about adding something else that signifies the queue preference? Something like three little beads at the top for dynamic, 5 for team, 1 for solo etc, so you can tell how that person earned their rank - by being a good solo player or a good premade player or whatever. 

Probably won't further increase toxicity than the stamps themselves will and will allow solo players to feel rewarded for their SOLO achievement. While it won't do anything to improve the solo experience, it sorta helps diversify reward into two ladders (a big complaint is solo players feeling they're being disproportionately rewarded for their play).

Also, aware that people might just try to play the majority of their final 25 games in the season solo to avoid getting a dynamic border but if the player is truly boosted and doesn't belong at that level they will drop in elo over 25 games so it'll still be a more accurate mark of their solo ranking.

Obviously won't apply to bronze but it's not like a solo bronzie is going to feel any worse seeing that other people with premades are also bronze. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
