<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9825</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is that they only changed the time/location once they found out who was speaking. That is textbook discrimination based on speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally I would agree but Berkeley is a public university. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban - Lupin's Transformation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At what point did the Byzantines consider territories lost to the Arabs (Syria, Egypt, etc.) to be "permanently lost"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The territory of the Byzantine Empire fluctuated heavily throughout its history [1](https://www.alternatehistory.com/wiki/lib/exe/fetch.php?media=resources:byzantine_20maps.png), and it engaged in periods of both heavy territorial loss and conquest in Italy, the Balkans, and Anatolia. But at what point did they "give up", so to say, on the idea of reconquering Levantine and African territories lost to the Arabs? Did they ever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Progressives are the majority

Ok pal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the Communist Party USA wanted Hillary to win. Endorsements from shitty people aren't really a mark against a candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 1931 film "Frankenstein" begins with a warning to the audience about how scary the film is. Was this just a marketing gimmick, or was the film actually considered frightening enough to warrant a warning compared to other contemporary horror films? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the time Frankenstein was released in November 1931, there had been 3 other silent film adaptations of the Frankenstein novel. There had also been several other horror films released by Universal, including The Phantom of the Opera and Dracula. Was Frankenstein considered so much more shocking that a warning was necessary to prepare the audience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mind if I ask why you say that? Slavery was still legal in the UK for decades after the Revolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well considering how the [Declaration of the Immediate Causes Which Induce and Justify the Secession of South Carolina from the Federal Union](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Declaration_of_the_Immediate_Causes_Which_Induce_and_Justify_the_Secession_of_South_Carolina_from_the_Federal_Union) *only* mentions slavery, I don't think that's an accurate statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does that suddenly make it okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but the difference is that slavery wasn't the *reason* they were seceding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but the difference is that slavery wasn't the *reason* they were *seceding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BUT WHAT DOES JA RULE HAVE TO SAY ABOUT THIS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They were also fighting for states rights

The states right to own slaves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but Washington was fighting for an undeniably just cause. Slavery is not the same as self-determination. It's like the opposite of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. The right to own slaves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah but what he says doesn't change the fact that he *literally* is worth billions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Going to an Ivy League doesn't mean jack shit if you don't take advantage of it

He's the President of the United States. If that's not "taking advantage of it" what is?

I'm skeptical he's made all of that legitimately

Do you have any evidence for that claim?

Face it, trumps a con man

Correct me if I'm wrong but you need to be pretty damn intelligent to be a con man. 

This is why nobody takes these criticisms of Trump seriously. One minute he's an idiot and the next he's an evil calculating mastermind plotting to destroy the United States. One minute he's in Putin's pocket and the next he's about to start WWIII against Russia. There are legit criticisms you can make about Trump. Calling him "dumb" and "a puppet" are untrue and only distract from them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to be pretty damn smart to be a successful con artist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I don't know his qualifications but it's his word against Forbes. And I would go with Forbes 10/10 times. If he gave some actual evidence that would certainly help though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm not trying to insult you or anything, but I don't think you have the authority to try to argue against the findings of one of the most prominent business magazines in the world. Even if they were off by more than half of their estimate he would still be worth well over a billion dollars. I like evidence, and I just gave you some. You saying "no that's not true" isn't evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well [Forbes says he's worth 3.5 billion](https://www.forbes.com/donald-trump/#306b9f972899), so it's up to you to prove he's not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy went to an Ivy League school and turned millions of dollars into billions. He's obviously smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> User in r/PoliticalHumor tries to argue that democracy is a bad idea [+8] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what does Ja Rule have to say about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C I V I L D I S C U S S I O N.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **AIRHORNS** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real talk though that movie was dope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much warning did the Sassanian and Byzantine Empires have before the Muslim conquests? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Muslim invaders exploded out of the Arabian peninsula and made huge gains in Egypt and Mesopotamia in a very short period of time. Did the Byzantines and Sassanians have any idea about the looming Muslim threat? Or were the invasions completely unexpected? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Massachusetts so Catholic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Massachusetts is the most Catholic state in the US, with 44% of its citizens being Catholics. How did a state that was founded by and was a haven for Protestants come to be the most Catholic state? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Byzantine" is often used as an adjective to describe something that's complex and intricate. Were Byzantine laws really complex compared to those of contemporary states? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I hate the death penalty but..."

So what you're saying is you DO support the death penalty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AS A REMINDER, THIS SUBREDDIT IS FOR CIVIL DISCUSSION </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TFW 60% of the US was weak and bigoted in 1984.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the original 3 came out before PG-13 was a thing so I don't think that's a fair statistic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Palestine isn't a country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah but the government isn't giving the rich guy money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Then and Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You people are sick. Millions died and you just mock their deaths. Have some basic human decency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Millions died and they mock their deaths. It's sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point, I guess. I just suppose any amount would be "abnormal" for a site dominated by the West.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are there so many communists on Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like there are an abnormal amount of people on Reddit who go out of their way to defend communism. See [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/FuckUnitedAirlines/comments/64lzjm/united_airlines_if_you_upvote_this_it_will_show/) or [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/place/comments/62rbim/fight_the_communists_no_exceptions/) in the threads for examples. I just don't understand why there are so many people who feel the need to defend a failed and murderous ideology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton lost because she was too far right [SH] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude chill that ain't cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Youngledore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beasts 3: We Bought a Zoo

Starring Matt Damon as young Voldemort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RDJ as Aberforth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAME I commented there twice after the Nevada primary for some easy karma but after that it got too real haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am but I'd say there's a lot of T_D people here, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right? The left-wing echo chamber has become so encompassing it's the new normal. The instant one right-wing comment or post gets upvoted they think all of Reddit is becoming right-wing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  regressives

How is it regressive? Regressive would imply returning to what it was before (i.e. legalized).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Political ideologies such as liberalism/progressivism/socialism/conservatism have stayed widely the same over the years. The ideologies of the main two political parties, however, have not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well progressivism as an ideology has stayed widely the same over the years. Much like how conservatism wants things to stay the same and liberalism wants things to change, progressivism is based on the idea of progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I love that sub. Only the finest posts from here lol. 

And I don't know what you're trying to say about the Star Wars one. I made that when I was drunk and there's no posts in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prohibition exhibited many of the characteristics of most progressive reforms. That is, it was concerned with the moral fabric of society; it was supported primarily by the middle classes; and it was aimed at controlling the "interests" (liquor distillers) and their connections with venal and corrupt politicians in city, state, and national governments. 

Wow yeah that totally contradicts my point /s.

And fine if you want better links here's a paper by Princeton and the WSJ.

https://www.princeton.edu/~tleonard/papers/retrospectives.pdf

https://www.wsj.com/articles/the-progressive-history-of-eugenics-1456521508 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not really. Democrats as liberals/progressives and Republicans as conservatives wasn't really solidified until the 80s/90s. Prohibition and eugenics were *progressive* ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Library of Congress is...not reliable?

Dude.

And eugenics was the idea of progressives. JFK's dad freaking loved it and admired Hitler for implementing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol as if Democrats and Republicans were liberal/conservative back then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? If capitalism was so bad why did all of the post-Soviet states adopt it when they had the chance? If capitalism was a failing system why don't these states go back to what they had before? Because they know that it is better than the alternative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Prohibition](http://www.loc.gov/teachers/classroommaterials/presentationsandactivities/presentations/timeline/progress/prohib/) and [eugenics](http://www.discoverthenetworks.org/viewSubCategory.asp?id=1220) were part of the Progressive Movement. It's not "revisionist history". It's history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather there be haves and have-nots under capitalism than only have-nots under socialism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean those high schoolers? Yeah okay. Sure let's trust their judgement on this lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? That does nothing to argue against what I said. [Prohibition was a progressive movement.](http://www.loc.gov/teachers/classroommaterials/presentationsandactivities/presentations/timeline/progress/prohib/) The War on Drugs was an effort to merely enforce existing laws. It's a completely different situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand your point. I see a thriving economy with a system that has improved the quality of life for millions of people around the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That all sounds good to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/PanicHistory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no such thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Because conservatives hate progress

Yeah if it weren't for those damn conservatives we'd have eugenics and prohibition. What were they thinking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Carter was conned by Reagan with a back deal with the Iranians, blocking the release of U.S. diplomats being held as hostages during the election campaign. This affected Carter's numbers at the polls.

That's been debunked as nothing more than a [conspiracy theory](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/October_Surprise_conspiracy_theory). Its got about as much evidence as fucking Pizzagate (i.e. none). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Donald Trump version 0.1, Ronald Reagan, an actor who'd spent more time in front of a camera than behind a desk. A mentally damaged puppet controlled by greedy puppeteers, who drove home assfuckingly massive deregulation.

The hell are you on about? Reagan was a union leader and 2-term governor of the largest state in the Union.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drumpf

Oh shit. Has the Trump finally been stumped? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/killthosewhodisagree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's this one?

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/10/23/hillary-clinton-so-far-ahead-in-polls-that-doesnt-even-think-abo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That has nothing to do with Gorsuch's legitimacy, though. I don't see what your point is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there's your word.

And then there's Democracy Index's word.

No offense but I'm going to trust them over you. And they say that we have a democracy. So I think we're done here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't have an ID, then by the law you are ineligible. Whether or not that is constitutional is a different issue.

And I assume that you're just ignoring the fact that [the United States is among the most democratic nations in the world according to Democracy Index](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Democracy_Index#Democracy_index_by_country_.282016.29). Are there problems? Yes. But to say "we don't have a democracy" is asinine and fear-mongering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> democracy

dmkrs/

noun

a system of government by the whole population or all the eligible members of a state, typically through elected representatives.

We have a democracy. Stop acting like a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ASAREMINDERTHISSUBREDDITISFORCIVILDISCUSSION </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ASAREMINDERTHISSUBREDDITISFORCIVILDISCUSSION

Reported. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ghost conductor from Hey Arnold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In '96 it was the GOP that controlled congress anyway.

It was passed in 1986. Not 1996. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reported for incivility. Rule 1. Read it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ctrl+F: discrimination"

0 results.

Try again. Do you know what discrimination is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did I say the modern left? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you being serious? Are you legitimately equating gerrymandering with discrimination? Are you crazy? And for the record we do not and never have had proportional representation, so your "throwing out the window" rhetoric makes no sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes it an issue? Or at the very least detrimental? Not once since the GOP came into power in 2010 and redistricted has the Democratic Party been within a 7 seat swing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd like to see a reference for the Dems not enforcing the business provisions under Reagan.

http://www.pbs.org/newshour/rundown/todays-immigration-debate-rooted-reagan-amnesty-experts-say/

Bush 41 made his "read my lips" promise and it's somehow Clinton's problem he won? What Bush said is up there with Obama's "keep your doctor" pledge or "red line " in Syria.

Forgive me if you misunderstood. I didn't claim that it was Clinton's fault. I claimed that Bush made a promise, but then had to compromise on it, and lost badly for it. People don't want compromise.

Gingrich was and still is a firebrand. He shut down the government and it cost home for good reason. His "Contract with America" was a prototype for today's GOP platform. I.e., failed and partisan in equal measure.

Did it cost him? The GOP maintained majorities and got a Republican in the White House 4 years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what you said. You said MORE VOTES. That is an outright lie and you should be ashamed for trying to pass it off as a fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This modern trend of obstruction from the right only began with Gingrich, which he did because the left showed time and time again that they can't play nice. Obstruction worked, compromise didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said in any given race. Of course some districts are going to be more competitive than others. Don't be intentionally obtuse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  i don't think you understand just how fucked up it is that democrats get more votes than republicans nearly every election

On you mean like the [2014 senate elections](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_Senate_elections,_2014)? Or did you mean the [2014 House elections](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_House_of_Representatives_elections,_2014)? Or maybe the [2016 House elections](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_House_of_Representatives_elections,_2016)? 

Gerrymandering and voter suppression are very real and very dangerous.

Gerrymandering is a nonissue. It's something Democrats use as a scapegoat for their own failures. In 2012, for example, the new districts cost Democrats [7 seats](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/wonk/wp/2013/02/17/redistricting-didnt-win-republicans-the-house/?utm_term=.dd5e2b7e2719), or 1.6% of the House. Even if we used the former districts, they wouldn't be anywhere close to having a majority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell are you talking about? It takes 50%+1 to win any given race.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People dying is the most peaceful solution. [SH] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Are dems just supposed to roll over and let republicans literally steal our democracy out form under us?

What on earth are they doing to "steal our democracy"? They were all voted in this is literally the definition of democracy lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Republican party has metastasized.

Wins the House.

Wins the Senate.

Wins the White House.

Wins the Supreme Court.

"THE GOP IS CANCER!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is with the left. Our current problem with obstruction can all be traced back to the 80s/90s. In 1986, Reagan passed the Immigration Reform and Control Act, granting amnesty for about 3 million illegal aliens in exchange for the enforcement of harsh penalties against businesses that hired illegals. The amnesty happened, but Democrats in Congress stripped the enforcement against businesses. So we have Democrats refusing to compromise.

In the early 90s, HW is president. He made a famous campaign pledge to not raise taxes, but he knew that he had to for the good of the nation. So he did. He made a compromise for the nation, but he was crucified for it, and we got Bill Clinton. Once again, the left showed that they cannot act in good faith with compromise.

So in 1994 Gingrich refuses to compromise on anything because why should he? It never worked before. So the GOP gets both houses of Congress. They impeach Clinton and get W in the White House. They oppose the ACA and sweep Congress again. The GOP doesn't compromise because they know that it doesn't work with Democrats.

Basically had the Democrats actually compromised back in the 90s we wouldn't have gotten Gingrich and the start of all this obstructionism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I hope so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is "taxed enough"? The top 1% pay nearly half of all income taxes. Lower taxes across the board. For everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It literally hasn't changed at all from what it was when Scalia was alive. If a "hardline right wing" SCOTUS legalized gay marriage, I say keep it right wing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Now that the Supreme Court is hardline right wing for a generation? Now that the GOP unwritten platform comfortably allows Neo Naziism and White Supremacy and hacking of opponents and collusion and corruption? Now that Roe V Wade is in the crosshairs? Now that the rights of gay citizens to even exist without fear of imprisonment or live without legal discrimination is hanging in the balance? Now that public education is about to die and be replaced with corporate, right wing "education?" Now that we are going to something like 3 wars at once, the original goal of the GOP before 911? Now that climate change science has been suppressed? Now that the EPA has been hamstrung?

This is satire, right? PLEASE be satire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my God. I'm done here you're clearly not getting it. How hard is it for you to understand that a REPUBLICAN is more likely to closely represent the interests of people voting for a FORMER REPUBLICAN than a DEMOCRAT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the electoral college is undemocratic and needs to go!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, Democrats know that they're about to win big in 2018 and 2020.

Keep telling yourself that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not an assumption lol. Johnson LITERALLY IS closer to Trump than to Hillary.

You're still not getting this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying that Americans are taxed too much and the government spends that tax money on unimportant bullshit?

Welcome to the GOP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admit that some people may have chosen to not vote, but anyone who voted for Johnson and would have preferred Hillary over Trump obviously doesn't know anything about politics. Johnson aligns *much* closer to Trump than to Hillary, so Trump would indisputably be the "second choice", so to speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the electoral college is undemocratic and needs to go!!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is literally the definition of democracy lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He is a libertarian. Not the same thing as a conservative republican. When has a conservative candidate ever been pro-choice, for legalizing cannabis, etc? If Johnson was a republican he would be a moderate republican at best.

Well given these:

http://www.redstate.com/diary/southernconstitutionalist/2016/05/28/gary-johnson-and-william-weld-are-fake-libertarians-miseducating-the-public/

http://reason.com/blog/2016/10/14/evan-mcmullin-if-gary-johnson-were-a-rea

http://www.dailywire.com/news/8346/7-reasons-libertarian-ticket-isnt-libertarian-all-aaron-bandler

https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2016/jan/07/presidential-hopeful-gary-johnson-is-no-libertarian-hes-a-pro-pot-trump

http://www.alternet.org/election-2016/stop-pretending-gary-johnson-real-alternative

I'd say that your assertion that "Johnson is a libertarian" is a load of bunk. He's literally a Republican who likes pot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  your hypothetical is assassin.

Ok it's obvious you're probably tired or something because you're not making any sense. You should get some rest before you try to make any arguments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No, the republicans blocked Garland for a year.

[If you feel the need to lie to make a point, you don't have a point to make.](https://www.wsj.com/articles/president-obamas-supreme-court-nomination-of-merrick-garland-expires-1483463952) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you honestly don't believe that Johnson was a conservative then you're kidding yourself. He was a Republican until 2011 and his running mate was one until 2016. Do you honestly think they'd align closer to Hillary? Come on, man.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  WRONG: ~~Reid~~ McConnell was forced into that position because the ~~republicans~~ Democrats literally blocked EVERY APPOINTMENT to the ~~federal bench~~ SCOTUS. A RECORD ~~79~~ 1 block. The obstructionist ~~republicans~~ Democrats were determined to block every single ~~Obama~~ Trump appointment to the ~~federal bench~~ SCOTUS.

 So no, it is the ghost of ~~republican obstructionism~~ Reid's lack of foresight biting his party in the ass. Period

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But 3 million more said Hillary is a better choice.

*THAT'S NOT THE POINT!* The point is about their *policies*. Did Hillary receive more votes than Trump? Yes. I am not disputing that. But my point is, which you are still not getting, is that more people wanted Trump's conservative policies, as evidenced by the fact that conservative-leaning candidates received an *actual* majority of the popular vote in the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Column: Gorsuch and the ghost of Harry Reid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, it's *moot* point. Not mute. You're not off to a great start there.

Second of all, the preference is not black/white. You are allowed to like more than one candidate and dislike more than one candidate. If people liked Hillary more, she would have received 50% of the vote. But she didn't. Conservative candidates did. This *by definition* means that people liked Trump-ish policies more than Hillary-ish policies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're still not getting my point. If it were *solely* Trump vs. Clinton, Trump would have won more votes, as evidenced by the fact that *conservative* candidates got more votes than the *liberal* candidates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like those 3rd party people would go running to Hillary. If you only had 2 choices, all the Johnson/McMullin/Castle people would have Trump as their second choice. They would have wanted Trump more than Hillary. Ergo, more people wanted Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Diginic claimed that "the majority" voted for Hillary, which is an outright lie. No candidate got 50% of the vote. However, a majority *did* vote for conservative/right-leaning candidates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well roughly 750,000 more people voted for conservative candidates. So no, they did not want a liberal candidate like Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I don't get. The whole reasoning behind Democrats blocking Gorsuch seems to be "we need to punish the GOP for stealing the seat". But there was an opportunity to punish them. In November. We could have elected Hillary. We didn't. We could have turned the Senate blue. We didn't. Most people want Gorsuch to be confirmed. So it seems to me like Democrats aren't really on the popular side of this debate. So why are they doing it? They knew the nuclear option was going to happen so he'd get confirmed anyway. What's their endgame here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conservative candidates got 50% of the votes. Maybe people didn't want Trump, but they didn't want Hillary more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FDR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. 52-48. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I don't get. The reasoning behind Democrats blocking Gorsuch seems to be "we need to punish the GOP for stealing the seat". But there was an opportunity to punish them. In November. We could have elected Hillary. We didn't. We could have turned the Senate blue. We didn't. Most people want Gorsuch to be confirmed. So it seems to me like Democrats aren't really on the popular side of this debate. So why are they doing it? They knew the nuclear option was going to happen so he'd get confirmed anyway. What's their endgame here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Senate. Upvote this so that people see it when they Google "The Senate". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Senate. Upvote this so that people see it when they Google "The Senate".](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/4/41/Mitch_McConnell_official_portrait_112th_Congress.jpg/220px-Mitch_McConnell_official_portrait_112th_Congress.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I don't get. Their whole reasoning behind blocking Gorsuch seems to be "we need to punish the GOP for stealing the seat". But there *was* an opportunity to punish them. In November. We could have elected Hillary. We didn't. We could have turned the Senate blue. We didn't. Most people want Gorsuch to be confirmed. So it seems to me like Democrats aren't really on the popular side of this debate. So why are they doing it? They knew the nuclear option was going to happen so he'd get confirmed anyway. What's their endgame here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***DEUS VULT*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer the "Reid Rule". Rolls off the tongue better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   _  SCHUMER TAKE MY ENERGY   _  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Most voters say US Senate should confirm Neil Gorsuch to Supreme Court, but oppose 'nuclear' option </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Cannot win House majority: Gerrymander.

That's actually a common misconception. Even if you were to return to the previous districts the GOP would still have a sizable majority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AS A REMINDER, THIS SUBREDDIT IS FOR CIVIL DISCUSSION.

Reported. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jenner's a Republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you add up all conservative candidates (Trump, Johnson, McMullin, Castle), they received 50% of the vote. The GOP won the popular vote for the House. If you think conservative ideology is in the minority you're kidding yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loud and clear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The St. John's fragment (Papyrus P52) is the oldest surviving copy of the New Testament, containing parts of seven lines from the Gospel of John (c. 125 CE) [564  402] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the next comment says human rights. I linked this one because i wanted to include both comments. Don't be a smartass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A conservative-majority court will set human rights back decades [+202] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ajit Pai is chairman of the Federal Communications Commission. Maureen Ohlhausen is acting chairman of the Federal Trade Commission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, Republicans didnt just strip away your Internet privacy rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bullshit. The GOP did everything they could to stop Trump without literally destroying the party. They literally had the *previous nominee* give a speech saying how horrible of a person he was. Had Democrats nominated someone people actually liked (i.e. NOT HILLARY) we wouldn't be in this mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strom Thurmond took steambaths in the days leading up to his historic filibuster so his body would be better able to absorb fluid to lessen the need to urinate. They take this shit seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump raises pressure on North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rice at center of intelligence storm over unmasking flap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
