<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5867</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Distraint 2 - Official Announcement Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He created Eastbound and Down and helped to write all of the episodes, he also wrote Your Highness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'The Strangers 2' Starts Filming This Summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you deal with panic attacks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this is the wrong subreddit, but I was wondering how you all handle panic attacks when they happen. Mostly because I have been having at least two panic attacks a day because of being stuck in a college course where I have to talk/interview people every day.

So anyway, I was wondering what your strategies for dealing with panic attacks are? Any advice would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed the Platinum Dunes remake of Nightmare on Elm Street more than the original, it just felt more intense and real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zoey's Top 5 Games of 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you're the director for almost half of the Saw movies, I was wondering what you thought of Twisted Pictures and Lionsgate making a new Saw movie and if you're looking forward to it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone experience new voices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've recently been diagnosed as schizophrenic by a psychiatrist and for the past month, she's put me on Risperdal. For as long as I can remember, I've heard two male voices command me to do things. 

But the past couple of weeks, I've been hearing a female voice, but unlike the others, it's not yelling commands, it's screaming and asking for help. At first, I ignored it cause I live on a loud campus, but I was just lying in bed, watching a movie and I heard her scream for me to come help her. But no one was around.

I'm honestly kind of freaked out right now and I was wondering if anyone else has ever experienced another voice suddenly appearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video games like Fran Bow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently finished playing through Fran Bow and The Charnel House Trilogy on Steam. And since I only have Sanitarium and Phantasmagoria, I'll be out of "macabre games". So I was wondering if anyone had any game recommendations, PC would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any recommendations for macabre games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently finished playing through Fran Bow and The Charnel House Trilogy on Steam. And since I only have Sanitarium and Phantasmagoria, I'll be out of "macabre games". So I was wondering if anyone had any game recommendations, PC would be appreciated.

Sorry if this is the wrong subreddit to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 06:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone curious, Chance doesn't show up in the video until 3:52. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize until this year actually, mostly because I didn't know that was an actual thing. I realized while talking to my friends and roommates that I was feeling grossed out by them talking about sex. At first, I thought it was because of a bad experience with an ex-bf, but when I tried imaging having sex with someone else, I felt really grossed out. Then I went on the internet and everything made complete sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
