<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3805</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 14:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we do this? Pair up nosleep writers and have rap battles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 01:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bless your little heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 22:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 15:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely! I'm so glad I came to SC for college, because so many people look down on the South without having a chance to fully explore the culture and history. I took an intensive course in Southern Politics and History last semester, and that's one of the most valuable courses of my education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 15:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I'm going to school in South Carolina (the BEST one; I'll let you guess which one). I'm a Northern transplant.

I've always had a appreciation of the Southern Gothic, and I think that's what made me love True Detective so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 03:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Drink 1-2 beer, turn all the lights off, get naked, lock yourself in a wardrobe and start imagining the things that could happen. Know how vulnerable you are. How there is no way to escape...

That's my normal Saturday night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 16:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dearest butler, does [my story](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/1jai1j/does_anyone_know_a_good_plumber_i_did_one_of/) warrant an add? I know it's not a traditionally scary story, but I thought I'd give it a try. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 18:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boogie Wonderland
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 03:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yayyy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 15:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post it, and feel free to send me your story if you need an opinion. Just keep trying and don't let fear of reader rejection hold you back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 19:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, YOU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 04:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The happy plastic surgery family! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 14:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1.) Buttercup

2.) Fluffbutt

3.) Charlie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 22:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I write about trampoline booty sometimes, does that count?

EDIT: but seriously, I'd be happy to give you some writing advice if you want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for mods to make my game more...dangerous? Unpredictable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 03:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey y'all!

I find that the Sims 3 is a little too easy sometimes. I'm looking for mods that will put more unpredictability into the game, whether that be through dangerous situations or just strange occurrences.

I have Supernatural, Pets, and Ambitions.

Any suggestions? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 17:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "O Magical Mojo"...should've been my flair... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 17:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to message me your email, whoever that was! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 17:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm actually beginning a rather intensive edit on the "Dude" story. I'm not completely revamping the story, but I've been changing some stuff around. If you have any opinions on structure, organization, logic...etc, I'd love to see your opinions. Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 17:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, my week is crazy busy too! Thanks so much for your comments, I really appreciate them. I agree with all of your comments and like the new title change.

I've editing the story structure a bit, and then am just checking for any stray grammar issues that I missed. Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 00:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mean Girls: NoSleep edition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 00:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge believer in using baked goods to make people like you. It works!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 00:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HATE THE MODS AND EVERYONE IN THE SUBREDDIT! All of you are the equivalent of Satan to me.

especially bloodworth...what's up with that guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 04:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! That would be fantastic if you could PM me your ideas! And thanks for the website- I never knew that existed. I'm actually having the most trouble with the Dude series, so you're right on track! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 01:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> many thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone want to help me edit for my free ebook? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 20:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey y'all!

I'm planning to create a free ebook of my work. This will include stories from nosleep as well as some unpublished ones that didn't really fit within nosleep.

That being said, I want my writing to be as polished as possible, but it's a little tough editing on my own. I asked some of my friends to help, but most of them aren't writers.

Would any of y'all like to/be willing to read over some of my work? For example, I'm including Does Anyone Know a Good Plumber and Yo, Dude, Do You Own a Dog?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 16:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -Penpal by Dathan Aurbach (/u/1000vultures), as mentioned in the other comment


-Gillian Flynn (specifically her earlier books, such as Sharp Objects and Dark Places) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 17:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the recommendations everyone! Now I have plenty of great books to ready! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 17:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I loved Mystic River so I'll definitely check out his other works! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 17:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I wanted to give a touch of deviance to this character- I'm glad someone noticed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 02:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their name is Francesco  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 00:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read them- really enjoyed the 1st one, but not so much the ones after. Don't know why. Thanks for the recommendation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 21:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For all of the comments: 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Jv_XR6RMAI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a literary mystery/thriller- my favorite is Silence of the Lambs, to give you some context. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 21:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love mystery and thrillers, but I often find that they rely too much on "grizzled male detective with problems gets women and solve crime"

That's fine, but I want actual pathos to my characters. Some of my favorite media includes Silence of the Lambs, anything by Gillian Flynn, True Detective (the above statement done right), and Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys here's what happens on May 20th- too scary for /r/nosleep itself, so I had to post it here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 16:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Help me. Please, God, help me.

Its here.

The day is here.

I dont have much time, but let me explain.

I woke up this morning and although the day seemed normal, I emerged from my bedroom with a sense of foreboding a je ne sais quoi, as the French say. Do you ever wake with a small sense of hopelessness? As if your body is merely a shell for your own personal anxieties? Im sure you have, but today, I felt that sevenfold.

I felt a deep dread as I puttered about my apartment, going through the daily motions without much feeling shuffling to my kitchen; frying an egg; browsing r/TheRedPill. However, my feelings soon came to a crescendo when I looked at the clock

10:00 AM.

Suddenly, I knew. The reckoning of May 20th would begin at 10:30. I pushed up from the table, suddenly pouring with sweat. As if in a trance, I went to take my keys from the kitchen counter and exit my house. I had to get to my car.

As I approached my car, my physical symptoms became worse. My eyes bulged; my body felt like it was electric, nerves pulsing with a wicked form of energy. I stumbled to my car, dropping the keys countless times, fingers scrabbling on the ground to find the lost object. My world was inside out and the anxiety was like cocaine to my system.

I finally managed to start my car and begin towards my inevitable destination. I didnt want to begin that journey, but I had to. My mind was telling me no, but my obligation to a medical appointment was telling me yes.

You too will experience this one day. You will experience the fear, the disgust, the soulless humanity of my own personal May 20th.

The day of my annual colonoscopy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
