<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7749</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehyo Timo, Kurze Erklrung zum Wort Entschuldigung: Man kann sich nicht selbst entschuldigen, man sollte um Entschuldigung Derer bitten, die den Schaden haben. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk about life imitating art, that's totally a Tony Stark move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the quote:

Since it was revealed that Deadpools brilliant creative director Tim Miller will not be involved in the project anymore, I have undertaken some soul searching. Tim was the driving force behind Deadpool and me getting involved in this amazing project. Deadpool without Tim at the helm just does not sit right with me and that is why I have decided not to be involved in the second chapter.

Saying that Miller was the driving force behind Deadpool is the interesting part for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deadpool 2 Loses Composer Junkie XL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dieses passiv-aggressive Nachtreten tut als langjhriger Fan weh beim zugucken, das fhrt doch zu nichts auer tieferen Grben. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Der 6 Jahre alte Junge symbolisiert hier die Unschuld, das Unverbrauchte, das Echte. Er uert seine Meinung ber das Meer ohne von der Gesellschaft beeinflusst zu sein (Das Meer wird ja eigentlich nie wirklich negativ beschrieben, wenn es als Objekt dargestellt wird und nicht als Gefahr). Bukowski ist da aber auch sehr ambivalent in der interpretation :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 21:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I clearly remember it as Man-In-Blackstain, you must be wrong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was looking exactly for something like this, thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice job and awesome communication skills! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich finde die Kooperation sehr smart und sehe nur Vorteile fr beide Seite. Gute Idee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 17:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er ist vor ein paar Wochen in die SPD eingetreten, ja. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 17:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ich beie an. Bitte erlr mir den Unterschied zwischen Polizeigewerkschaft und Gewerkschaft der Polizei. Danke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Sonneborn: Erdogan, der alte Spavogel, hlt es mit uns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 15:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really enjoyed reading this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ist dies der lang erwartete r/de Trailer? Da hat sich die Community aber Mhe gegeben beim Meme zusammenschnipsel! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funk, das Junge Angebot von ARD und ZDF, sagt Hallo, Welt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 10:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We got lots of Wind Tetris in return, it was a glorious time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 15:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO VOTE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 21:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I wasnt the biggest fan of the game but still watched because of you guys ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  im Zweifelsfall Nein hinschreibt

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 13:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would guess it has to do with the chinese army! The number seven [is](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Numbers_in_Chinese_culture) a
 luck number and symbolizes "togetherness". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is knowledge ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Friend.
What is your purpose ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hier der [Screenshot](https://i.imgur.com/0zx9SAP.jpg) von Damals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was bietet euch YT fr den Wechsel auer der greren Reichweite? Werdet ihr speziell beworben als Deutsches YT Gaming Zugpferd? Ist dieser Deal zeitlich befristet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kann mir jemand den kausalen Zusammenhang erklren? Je weniger der Dschungelknig bekommt, desto mehr Medaillen werden gewonnen? Ist Unterhaltung gleich Sport? Wenn man die beiden FB Post die dahinter verlinkt sind liest, wird auch das eigentlich Problem angesprochen, nmlich Frderung, aber dann ist doch dieses Eingangszitat vllig nichts aussagend und realittsfern oder wie seht Ihr das? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "In einem Land, in dem ein Olympiasieger 20.000 Prmie bekommt und ein Dschungelknig 150.000 sollte sich niemand ber fehlende Medaillen wundern." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immer wenn ich den dicken Florentin sehe, habe ich Angst dass er in mein Zimmer kommt und mir mein Essen wegisst :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His Michael Caine impression gets me everytime - "Michael you can't do this in here. . . etc."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure he meant [this](http://cdn-9chat-fun.9cache.com/media/photo/a7mv52x03_480w_v1.jpg), sorry just found the small one, but I remembered seeing it and found it quite beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 01:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [NMS] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doppelpass alleine? Vergiss es! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hhhhh meinst du . . .  Wassereis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same for me! Anyone care to give some recommendations to similar stuff? I never really listened to Colins and there is so much stuff from him :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 15:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vorsicht, wer so edgy ist, kann sich selbst schneiden! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 17:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, gonna buy one and try it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the answers. The audio for the rift is coming from the USB, so that works fine. I guess the DP to HDMI is another option, but will that work, the DVI/HDMI worked for other people but not for me . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oculus + Multiple Screens [R9 390] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Guys,

CV1 Owner (+PC noob) here and I got some problems with connecting my Rift with my Computer. I have a AMD R9 390 with the following / usual setup:


* HDMI - Goes to my receiver for A/V (TV as second Monitor + Surround Audio System)
* DVI 1 - Goes to my Monitor
* DVI 2 - Not used
* DP - Not used

When I got my Oculus last week, I just used the HDMI slot on my PC and everything worked fine. Then i read somewhere that I can use a HDMI-to-DVI Adapter for the Video Signal to the Rift. I searched on this subreddit for this problem and found some solution, so I ordered [this](https://www.amazon.de/gp/product/B00ZMVGTA2/ref=oh_aui_detailpage_o00_s00?ie=UTF8 psc=1) and connected everything, but I only got a black screen on the Rift. I switched to the second DVI, same result. I dont want to change HDMI cables every time I want to play with my Rift. Now I'm a bit lost:

1. Is this the wrong HDMI/DVI Adapter?
2. Should I try to connect my Monitor with the DP Port, so that not both of the DVI ports are used at the same time?
3. Are there any options I just forgot to activate?
4. Are there any other viable solutions (I've read about HDMI splitter. . . )?

Thanks so much,

Karu



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Optimal Radeon Settings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 15:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Guys,

I recently upgraded my PC with a 390 and now I'm a bit lost with optimal settings. I made some screenshots and uploaded them to [Imgur](http://imgur.com/a/C0YtF), would love to hear some feedback on what the optimal settings are in terms of (gaming) performance.

Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 15:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, could you go into a bit more detail why its not gonna happen? I'm really interested! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 12:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I'm with you! After nearly 40 hours I reached Floor 5 for the 2nd time very and was very lucky to get my first dragun kill. Even when I was dying constantly on the first floors boss, the game is so much fun and I want to be better . . .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 11:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHich is actually a good thing, as it should happen to nearly everyone, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 18:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats the usual time it will stay on "Processing for Shipping"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 16:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much. Hows the internet structure, is it common to have broadband available everywhere?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 16:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Guys. I have some questions regarding Gaming in Lebanon. 

* Are Video games big in your country? 
* Is it easy to buy Consoles (I know South American Countries had some really delayed consoles for example) ?
* How about eSports? Any particular game or genre you guys prefer?

Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 11:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bei Fuball und Bier hrt der Spa auf! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 14:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its easy to forget that this letter is from 1960, so the time Kubrick just started to be a huge director with overtaking Spartacus. I find it interesting to see a fairly young Kubrick prasing Bergman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 14:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How strong is Tinfoil Man compared to Arthur Dayne? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 10:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hier geht es aber um fremd-produzierte content (HBO), im Gegensatz zu deinen Beispielen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 18:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, what a nice suprise :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 17:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warum nicht gleich bis Nepal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 17:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dark Souls 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 01:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe try Rockleesmile and Northernlion for YouTube content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 16:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halbwissen gepaart mit einer Priese Ignoranz bzw Arroganz. Das kann nur schlecht enden fr RBTV :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 15:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Large Guild Quests </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 15:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Duchess is not online, you can write me under the character name "Niobae" ingame! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 11:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up the Kenshin Manga, its a great read! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 15:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Es ist ja seine Entscheidung, aber irgendwie verstehe ich die Begrndung nicht:

"Grund ist die massive Berichterstattung und der damit verbundene Fokus auf die Sendung und den Moderator."

Ist das nicht genau das, was eine (satire) Sendung erreichen will, maximale Aufmerksamkeit? Der genannten Grund ist in meiner Meinung nach nicht negativ, bin etwas verwirrt. Vom Bellut (ZDF) gab es doch auch Rckendeckung zwecks Weitersenden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 14:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> valves cut is around 30%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 15:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die zahlt bestimmt auch keine Steuern, ey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 16:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can only dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 18:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anm. d. Red.: Diese Darstellung ist korrekt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 17:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Operation "Streisand" ist gestartet.

Mission: Accomplished

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 12:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to craft yourself a fishing boat or noble wagon. Its a nice challenge and will keep you occupied :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 11:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be so baller! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 10:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raw Sugar is a bit more expensive, so use Sugar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 12:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, BDO Noob here, quick question:
Is there any disadvantage into having idle workers? Im now in the situation, that I have more workers available, than nodes I want to gather resources from. Should I fire them? Does this reset their level? Also: Should I make a big web out of available nodes or is it okay to have separate areas (can they still transfer goods between each city, even if I dont have the nodes between activated?

Thanks for the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ich mag dich :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 22:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> und Rugby! Ich konnte net mehr vor lachen :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
