<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French cybersecurity agency probing Macron hack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jennifer Lawrence has changed up her hair yet again and added bangs! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eighty-two Chibok girls have been freed after successful negotiations between Boko Haram and the Nigerian government, a government official close to the negotiations tells CNN. The source said the the freed Chibok girls are currently in military custody in Banki, in northeastern Nigeria. They will be transferred to the capital, Abuja, where they will undergo medical checks and be reunited with their families. A total of 276 girls were kidnapped from the village of Chibok in April 2014. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boko Haram militants have released 82 schoolgirls out of a group of more than 200 who they kidnapped from the northern town of Chibok in April 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 35 Most Shocking and Funny Goal Celebrations in Football History [10:16] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are fiscal conservative opposed to single-payer healthcare? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Beautiful designs that can make your home living room paradise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This project has stable funding, creates sufficient jobs and guarantees the safety of investors money, one description of the project said.
 
Promotional materials made note of the Kushner family's "celebrity" status, but did not mention the president specifically. Organizers were also reportedly uncomfortable with media attendance at the public event and attempted to block access.
 
A Chinese investor who attended the event, Wang Yun, told The Post the family's association with Trump could go both ways.
 
"Even though this is the project of the son-in-law's family, of course it is still affiliated," Wang said.
 
We heard that there are rumors that he is the most likely to be impeached president in American history. Thats why I doubt this project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kushner family pitches wealthy Chinese on investor visas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Myanmar's Aung San Suu Kyi meets Queen Elizabeth for lunch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democracy for America will back Benjamin Jealous for Maryland governor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an extraordinary 1,800-word report Friday, North Korean state news agency KCNA said a "hideous terrorist group" conspired with the CIA and South Korea's Intelligence Service (IS) to "commit bomb terrorism targeting the supreme leadership" during major events including a recent military parade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea claims US 'biochemical' plot to kill Kim Jong Un </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 Fastest Goals in Football  Top 10 Goals  Guinness World Record </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama's mother died of ovarian cancer, and according to Souza "spent her last days worrying whether insurance was going to cover some of the medical expenses because they might consider her cancer a pre-existing condition." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama photographer trolls GOP over ObamaCare repeal vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Republican members who will pay the most severe political price for what House Democrats will gleefully call "RyanCare" will be those in the 23 congressional districts that voted for Hillary Clinton in 2016. Political analysts will also be surprised by the damage done to GOP members representing red or purple states with Republican governors and insurance commissioners.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vote to repeal ObamaCare spells doom for House Republicans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamas donating $2M to Chicago summer jobs programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cristiano Ronaldo Best Goals  Top 10 Goals  Real Madrid  Manchester United </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP, Dems put more money into Montana special election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said in an interview with USA Today just days after last years election that running for office would be a great opportunity to help people, so its possible. This past election shows that anything can happen.

The 45-year-old actor is reportedly registered as a Republican. He encouraged voter registration during a speech at the 2000 Republican National Convention  and also appeared at the Democratic National Convention that same year. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Moore calls for The Rock to run for president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Moore calls for The Rock to run for president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> tech executives predict significant job automation in the next five years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't change the title,Probably the site had change it.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She also criticized Republican lawmakers for attempting to defund the womens health organization through its healthcare plan, and said the bipartisan spending deal that left the organizations funding alone meant women narrowly averted a disaster with the budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres no question in competitive districts where youve got a potentially vulnerable Republican incumbent, this could make or break you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem rep: GOP playing Russian roulette with ObamaCare repeal vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton slams men in Washington rolling back protections for women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hearing comes one day after Hillary Clinton, the Democratic nominee for president last year, again blamed Comey in part for her defeat.
Clinton told a Women for Women International event that she was on the way to winning until the combination of Jim Comeys letter on Oct. 28 and Russian WikiLeaks raised doubts in the minds of people who were inclined to vote for me, but got scared off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Director Comey back in spotlight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Business wins, 'clobbered' Philippines environment chief says after ouster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Democratic congressman remembers the last time House leadership asked for a tough vote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yates' testimony May 8 will be the first time the former acting attorney general will publicly speak about the White House meeting. A source familiar with the situation says that Yates will be limited on what she can tell the Senate judiciary subcommittee because many of the details involving Flynn are classified, meaning there may only be a few new revelations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Acting AG Yates to contradict administration about Flynn at hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Best Goals Ever Scored In Champions League || Episode No.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German minister cools on support for migrant camps in Libya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rule calling for parity between defense and non-defense programs was born out of the pitched spending fight that nearly caused the government to default on its debt in 2011 and was reinforced by subsequent spending deals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan touts spending deal for breaking 'Obama rules' for defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the Anne Frank Center is taking on Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 314 Action founder Shaughnessy Naughton started the group after her two unsuccessful congressional runs in Pennsylvania. During that time, the chemist realized she wasnt getting help from traditional donors. Naughton tapped into her network of scientists and has kept building on that base to help other scientists run for office.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House GOPs new challengers: Scientists mulling campaigns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump said during the presidential campaign that he would be willing to meet with Kim Jong Un, explaining in June that "there's a 10% or 20% chance that I can talk him out of those damn nukes 'cause who the hell wants him to have nukes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If it would be appropriate for me to meet with him, I would absolutely, I would be honored to do it," Trump told Bloomberg News in an interview Monday. "If it's under the, again, under the right circumstances. But I would do that."
No US president has ever before met with the leader of North Korea, and the idea is extremely controversial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: I'd be 'honored' to meet Kim Jong Un under 'right circumstances' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: I'd be 'honored' to meet Kim Jong Un under 'right circumstances' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Dickerson pressed him, Trump said: "You can take it any way -- you can take it any way you want."
Dickerson: "I'm asking you because you don't want it to be fake news. I want to hear it from President Trump."
Trump: "You don't have to ask me. You don't have to ask me."
Dickerson: "Why not?"
Trump: "Because I have my own opinions, you can have your own opinions."
Dickerson: "But I want to know your opinions. You're the president of the United States."
Trump: "That's enough. Thank you. Thank you very much."
The president walked away from Dickerson and sat down at his Oval Office desk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump abruptly ends interview with CBS' Dickerson after wiretapping questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The political and legal stakes of replacing Kennedy would be higher than they were in fight to replace Scalia with likeminded Gorsuch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatives prepare for Justice Anthony Kennedy's retirement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
