<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9615</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the point of putting Sasha in the coffin?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved his comments during the gunfight. His comic relief is perfect for this show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao. You can approach him and give him 5 crowns after the fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How often does your Geralt refuse payment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask because I just beat up some slob that asked to let him win because he was poor. I feel bad, but I needed the crowns... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hope this community can keep my R6S teammate in mind. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good team member of mine got arrested last week for possesion of narcotics and alleged sexual assault. He and his family are facing a very tough time and so I am because my team is supposed to play a big local tournament in 1 month and he's like the best player in the team. I was just wondering if you guys could show your support for him in the comments so I can show to him when and if he gets out of jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm tired of my girlfriend watching crap shows. I want her to stop and I want her to watch what I'm watching. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that was horrible. I forgive it because I genuinely love the show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See you in 8x01 after the season finale this sunday. You know it's gonna be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you mean some stupid banter that he had with other guys that doesn't prove anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In *The Walking Dead*, Negan signifies the New World Order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our Lord's name shall not be used in vain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That didn't happen to me at all. I'm on Xbox though so I'm not sure. Is your game up to date with patches? Try /r/PS4, maybe someone has had your problem there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's filled with unnecessary open world filler content, even worse than Dragon Age Inquisition. 


Um. 


Are you fucking kidding me?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sit down. Preferably at night. Have some drink beside you, or drugs in general. Turn off the lights. Turn the volume up. Kick back and start up TW3. Enjoy questing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playing The Witcher 3 madee realize that this is the perfect series to adapt to TV. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets pretend Hexer or whatever never existed. Playing TW3, I've experienced a few awesome quests that made me realize that this would make great TV. Imagine if HBO, Netflix or even Sci-fy adapted this series into a 10 episode seasons. Oh my... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the rest of the game like this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got done with the Bloody Baron/Crones story in Velen and it was pretty great. My question is if the rest of the game is composed of these "novellas" and short stories. This is my first Witcher and I'm having a blast with all these stories. I know there's an overarching storyline but honestly I just want more stories like these </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world has always been messy. Used to be a man rode in from out of town proclaiming the Messiah has been born, or that the stars are aligning and doom awaits us all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel the need to recommend American Crime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This show by AbC is rapidly turning into one of my favorite crime shows. It is beautifully shot, the characters are complex  (there are no good people really, you will dislike something about each character) and the acting is downright awesome. I haven't started season 3 yet, but so far season 2 is gripping, and season 1 was very good too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although The Witcher 3 has an overarching storyline (which isn't hard to understand) my experience so far has been that the game is made up of a bunch of short stories and self-contained quests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not mustering the courage to fight back. They're gathering supplies, guns, and allies. Rick knows that his group alone can't beat the Saviors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I love The Walking Dead. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me start by saying that I recognize the fact that the show is inconsistent. But I have to say, I've seen *a lot* of TV shows over the past 5 years. I've seen stuff that is 10 times better written than TWD. But you know what? It doesn't matter to me. The Walking Dead creates these memorable moments that I never forget, and the characters are memorable too. When the show is good, *it is good*. Sometimes the suspense is off the charts, and I love that. Let's take last night's episode for example. Now I don't care for the no so good episodes this season because last night delivered. You can also really tell that the people who work on this show really love doing so, even if the directors and writers and producers make a lot of crappy decisions. 

All in all, whenever all is said and done, I will look back and remember the good times with this. And, in my opinion, there are many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glenn's dumpster fiasco  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass Effect Adromeda, The Witcher 3, why the former made me appreciate the latter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, I compared my inital 60 hours of TW3 vs my initial 60 hours of MEA, and I gotta say...TW3 takes the cake big time. But, I won't be too hard on Bioware. TW3 is just one hell of a game to top. Adromeda made appreciate TW3 more because </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could've made a good argument but you made this retarded post instead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a little lost on what Beeman and Aderholt were doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If zombies are the most unrealistic part of the show, then why should we care that Rosita was able to hotwire a car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Aaron's girlfriend dies maybe he can hook up with Jesus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate how little we see Rick now compared to earlier seasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 5 is not the final season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 09:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I a word
 




               I meant my mom as soon as i sit down ro play she lashe af me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Casual a good place to practice and get better at the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played a total of 50 ranked matches, Gold 2 ATM. However, I feel like I need more practice, and since I don't have a squad for Ranked, I play the majority of time in casual. I find that I can generally do good in rank most of the time but I still feel like I'm not very good yet. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you do? *What did you do?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Step back and think about the last time you died in this game. What could you have done differently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. It would be justified if that happened often but that was the first time in a year where they heard me that angry. Thing is, we break each others balls all the time and sometimes even cross the line. I don't understand why this particular instance was any different. They won't accept my party invites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I lost it and now my squad won't take me back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have said " i also ate your mom you fag" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the pacing of season 6. So many action packed episodes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys don't pick Caveira I want to use her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ak 47 n Glock pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since 2008 the CIA has hired 800 Muslims so idk what you're talking about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Git gud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why my squad has a clutch or kick rule </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you also like shooting someone and then acting like it wasn't you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys want to buff every operator lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sedativeity

Holy shit

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your rank,level, and how good are you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 02:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many games do you play a day? How many of them are ranked? How many of them are casual? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys can I play Caveira for a couple of games please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you abuse glitches you deserve to be hanged from a bridge with a sign around your head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dj vu  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cropped out the text </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kingdom people and Saviors point guns at each other again. Christ this is getting stale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any tips for avoiding hard ons while in clutch mode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this weird problem, when it's a clutch situation it seems all my blood rushes to my penis for some reason. It makes it hard to concentrate when my cock gets up like a fucking bamboo while I have 5 enemies closing on my location. Does anybody get this and if so how do you deal with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude back out and start it again what the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I'll look into it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
