<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3391</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 06:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chocolate dipped Ritz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit I haven't laughed this hard at something in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This can't be true. Supreme Leader Trump said that this all a Chinese Hoax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In trying to avoid certain death at the hands of Nazis, I'll give them a pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your spin about the Nazi collaboration is total bullshit. He was 14 years old at the time and was trying to not be killed by Nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 06:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grilled...the only way to go IMHO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elotes [1080x1080] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 09:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You drink water? Like from the toilet? Huhuh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 22:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm non-exempt. I've had conversations with management about this but it's fallen on deaf ears for the most part. I've pretty much just been waiting for a write up before I really make a case and go FLSA. They won't put anything in writing either other than some (intentionally) vague policy. It's just very annoying having to always think about this crap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 08:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late to this thread, but I've been having this fight with my employer for about 4 years now. I'm expected to be available 24/7 365 to physically respond to emergency calls unless I find another employee to "cover" for me. For example, if I intend to have a few drinks on my time off, I'm expected to ask a colleague to cover that time (even though I'm off the clock). I've yet to be written up for not responding (the few times that it has happened) so I haven't raised a stink regarding FLSA etc. It's quite ridiculous though that I even have to worry about this shit on a daily/nightly basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I got out of this video: Way to much gun violence in this country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.lapolicegear.com/lapg-urban-recon-pant.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 09:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just like, your opinion, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 10:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Shit. I know shit's bad right now, with all that starving bullshit, and the dust storms, and we are running out of french fries and burrito coverings. But I got a solution." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Branwdo - the thirst mutilator! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 23:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, going to a Krispy Kreme and Costco Business is like walking down a street in Syria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't cry at the end of "Hachi: A Dog's Tale" then you are dead inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simon says.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
