<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2697</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad part is it'll probably pass the House tomorrow. And because it does, the GOP is one very big step closer to killing a lot of Americans with whatever the insurers decide is a pre-existing conditions. The fact that protections for those with pre-existing conditions are removed has turned the vote into no less than a legislated, state-sponsored death panel.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hippo attacks, on the other hand...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool, I just WhatsApped my buddies to let them know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Expected to Relax Tax Rules on Churches Taking Part in Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Expected to Relax Tax Rules on Churches Taking Part in Politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whole article, emphasis added:

The House voted to approve a roughly $1.1 trillion spending bill which includes **more than $15 billion in defense spending and $1.5 billion in money for U.S. border security**. The measure is expected to come up for a vote later this week in the Senate ahead of a deadline to keep the government open past Friday.

The spending measure also contains nearly $5 billion domestic spending increases, **including $295 million to help Puerto Rico continue making payments to Medicaid, $61million to reimburse local law enforcement agencies for the cost of protecting Trump when he travels to his residences in Florida and New York, major priorities for Democrats**. The bipartisan agreement comes after weeks of tense negotiations that briefly broke down after President Trump insisted that the spending measure include money to begin building a wall along the U.S.-Mexico border. Trump dropped those demands, clearing the way for a final deal.

Among the bipartisan wins is **$100million to combat opioid addiction and money to combat wildfires**. Democratic and GOP leaders have boasted that the deal contains significant wins for each side but the partisan bickering is expected to begin anew in the coming weeks when negotiations begin on spending for the fiscal year that begins in October.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Thanks for the input.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House votes to approve roughly $1.1 trillion spending bill to keep government funded through September </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House votes to approve roughly $1.1 trillion spending bill to keep government funded through September </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House votes to approve roughly $1.1 trillion spending bill to keep government funded through September </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House votes to approve roughly $1.1 trillion spending bill to keep government funded through September </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see, that would make sense. But then, how would these individuals deal with steep ramps generally in the world? Surely a jetway isn't the only location where this type of dip would occur?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yes, but this happened on the jetway, not the aisle of the plane. Would the wheel placement/shocks or any other factors be significantly different enough to prevent this in a manual wheelchair?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm confused by something. How would a wheelchair have been better? Wouldn't the scooter have better control than the terrible airport wheelchair? Is it possible this is literally just an unfortunate accident? It doesn't seem like they were preventing her from getting a wheelchair, simply that they would provide it at the door of the plane, which isn't exactly shocking.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The anti-Centigrade hatred runs deep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno that this is news strictly because it's entirely plaintiff's point of view from a biased source. The allegation isn't great though.  

Edit: Wait hang on, this happened while she was on her own motor scooter? 

Because of the downward angle of the jetway, at one point the front wheels of the scooter suddenly and rapidly descended which caused her to be pitched forward from her scooter onto the ground fracturing her left leg above the knee.
All of this could have been avoided if the gate agents at United had only allowed her to use a wheelchair. There were available wheelchairs right there at the gate, said Remington.

How would being on the shittier United wheelchair have prevented this situation?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the masters program, really. The testing for it is apparently rough. And some of the best teachers get PhDs. 

Regardless, teachers don't necessarily all stay local. They're about as incentivized to move as anyone else. But just looking at monetary incentives, families tend to send their kids to the best schools. If they lack the means for private school, they will still do whatever it takes to get the kid to the best school possible, even if that means picking up and moving to a different district. Teachers, naturally, have the same profit incentives. However, this may be curbed by altruism or some other factor, leading them to improve a bad neighborhood, rather than maintain a good one. 

This, of course, means that there exists a demand for the best teachers. This is, in the case of private schools, compensated. In the case of public schools, it is not. This is because the immediate effect on the neighborhood is not clear. If they were doctors under the same public system, you'd probably make the same argument, that there's no value added to keeping someone healthy. You're just maintaining the status quo. After all a doctor fixes problems with people. Doctors don't just improve an already healthy person (so the argument would go, obviously a good doctor works to help patients improve their lifestyle). A good doctor would be worth their weight in gold, but they wouldn't get paid that. Why? Because a public egalitarian system has built in protections against a meritocracy versus a private system, in which the best performers advance. 

The problem is a little bit economic, but largely societal. We simply don't value teachers as much because they're teachers and we view it as a lesser profession. It's summed up in the stupid idiom, "Those who can't do, teach." It's stupid because passing on knowledge is arguably the greatest things those who can do will do so that society grows from past work. Perhaps it's, again, because it's seen as women's work (like the undervaluing of nursing as a profession until recently). The family benefits by having an educated child with more opportunities available than without the good teacher. But whatever the reason, there's an implicit bias against rewarding positive outcomes in teaching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desiree Fairooz has been convicted for laughing early in Mr Sessions' confirmation hearing after Alabama Senator Richard Shelby said that the future attorney general's record of "treating all Americans equally under the law is clear and well documented." She has been convicted alongside two other protesters who had donned Ku Klux Klan costumes during the confirmation. Those two protesters could also face up to a year in prison.

The conviction comes after a two-day trial in the United States Superior Court in Washington. Ms Fairooz told theNew York Timesthat she is "really disappointed" and that her lawyer are planning on filing post-trial motions to have the verdict cast aside. It is too early to discuss an appeal she says.

Was she in her designated free speech zone, out of earshot or impact? No? She must fry. /s

This would be laughable if it wasn't the Justice Department literally ignoring the Constitution to shield a racist from criticism. It's a confirmation hearing open to the public, not a court room. If you can't exercise free speech in Congress, where can you?

I mean, senators openly scoff at remarks made at these hearings. I don't see charges leveled against them. Joe Wilson shouted "You lie" at the President during a State of the Union. That's clearly disruptive, but it's different if an ordinary citizen quietly snickers at the bullshit claims of a nominee for Attorney General.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the most dangerous to humans?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh I disagree in terms of value added and hazard. Frankly, the only reason we value an amazing teacher so low is a societal issue. And I'd love to see you argue that being a teacher isn't inherently dangerous to someone teaching in my district. A good teacher is worth their weight in gold in terms of value to the community. You think parents don't want their kids in college? Or that they don't want their children receiving the best education? Entire families move so their kids can go to the best schools. 

And it's not like a good teacher doesn't attract money. Good teachers can bring attention to a district, leading to an influx of higher income families and therefore more money for the community to play with. The problem is that because it's publicly funded, people see both an egalitarian approach and a personal investment in the stake of the enterprise (in a way that Browns fans can't seem to grasp). Therefore, the entire "my tax dollars pay your salary so I can tell you how to do your job" attitude towards public education. If their child fails due to personal issues, it's blamed on the school, not any other issues that might arise in the child's life. 

The best teachers, regardless, should be paid more if the system you're arguing exists actually does, but they're not. They're just not paid less, unless the district feels that the schools are underperforming, in which case everyone suffers. Look at the example of private schools where teachers can make more with fewer credentials. Why is the lower valued individual being paid more? Simply because the private education creates exclusivity and therefore raises rates. It's not that one creates inherently more value than the other. It's just in one case, the government is setting the wage and standards and in another, private institutions are. 

I went to a public school where everyone had to have a Masters degree to teach. They were paid less than the lawyers. Why? Lawyers also get, effectively, a Masters degree (I should know, I am one). We have created a system wherein being a teacher is not competitive except in the top school districts nationwide. In those districts, you can clearly see the added value that comes from a good educational system. The problem is societal, which contributes to economics, yes. But it's not just value in versus value out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lemon zest in both the sauce and gnocchi seems a little overkill on lemon. Aside from that, looks incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, a welder gets paid more with less training. And I know teachers that get "hazard pay" because of the schools they teach in so it's not a danger factor. And teaching isn't by any means easy (unless you think it's easy to teach someone basic knowledge while they're still learning anything from fine motor control to emotional control). No knock on welders, they're dope, but the argument that teachers get paid less because they're less educated is frankly bullshit. Public school teachers have far stricter and longer education requirements than private school teachers and get paid less, so the correlation isn't there even within the profession. 

It's because we Americans as a society fundamentally don't respect public education as an institution. Arguably because it was at one point decided that it's a women's profession therefore worth less, but whatever the reason, it has nothing to do with the level or intensity of training.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's how I imagine his retirement from the force. 

https://youtu.be/8yO3OxB14uE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the pilot works for United so...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey says classified Clinton emails were forwarded to Anthony Weiner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey says classified Clinton emails were forwarded to Anthony Weiner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey says classified Clinton emails were forwarded to Anthony Weiner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puerto Rico Declares a Form of Bankruptcy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know me, occasionally I'll be quirky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Officer Who Fatally Shot 15-Year-Old Texas Boy Is Fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Officer Who Fatally Shot 15-Year-Old Texas Boy Is Fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officers Wont Be Charged in Black Mans Shooting Death in Louisiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officers Wont Be Charged in Black Mans Shooting Death in Louisiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton blames Russian hackers and Comey for 2016 election loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton blames Russian hackers and Comey for 2016 election loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton blames Russian hackers and Comey for 2016 election loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton blames Russian hackers and Comey for 2016 election loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton blames Russian hackers and Comey for 2016 election loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman: TAS might be one of the greatest shows ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oreo O's and SWAT Kats. Biker Mice From Mars, Street Sharks, Mighty Max, Gargoyles, X-Men...we had the best cartoons. Oh and obviously Micro Machines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Le Pen says capital controls an option during Frexit talks if she wins election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Le Pen says capital controls an option during Frexit talks if she wins election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Le Pen says capital controls an option during Frexit talks if she wins election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Le Pen says capital controls an option during Frexit talks if she wins election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officer Who Shot Walter Scott to Plead Guilty in Charleston </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was rock candy from a local Albuquerque shop?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the wine flavor noticeable?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably intentional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you are lost!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the guy's a cop, logic dictates that the cop has a gun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That goal was seriously amazing, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's honestly one of the big reasons I subscribed. I mean some of the best features they've done recently have been on how climate change has been affecting people around world, looking at individual stories. The new layout is great too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You...didn't read that before posting, did you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Executive Departs Amid Turmoil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Executive Departs Amid Turmoil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Executive Departs Amid Turmoil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox News Executive Departs Amid Turmoil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, Marie!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't have a rifle out preemptively. However, I do know the difference between right and left. And I'd assume that as a police officer carrying a rifle, I'd have some training in its use and effective use. For example, the best way to stop a car driving into you using a gun (assuming you can't get out of the way and a gun is your only option) is to shoot the tires or, failing that, the driver, not the passenger. Idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! Shoot the passengers! That'll stop the driver!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since when does a passenger operate a car? The kid that was hit and killed wasn't the driver, he was a passenger. How would killing a passenger resolve the situation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dwight Howard is gone. He and Harden clashed a bit personality-wise so it's probably a little easier now that there's a leader on the court.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, 100%. But he did want to limit it. It's the "they're coming for your guns" of its time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lincoln-Douglas was largely about slavery and states' rights, and from the beginning, Lincoln advocated for the 1850 Compromise model limiting the westward expansion of slavery. Limiting slavery *was*, as I said, tepid abolitionism. But I agree, he didn't start off wanting to end slavery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half smokes and mumbo sauce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't watch Season 4, didn't really get into the plot in Season 3. Worth it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a small grain of truth to what he's saying in that if the Democrats had won in 1860, the Civil War may not have happened due to the country's leadership being more gun shy about abolition/pro-slave-owning. This, of course, ignores that the election of Lincoln was itself a public referendum on slavery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The answer is slavery. It was fought over states' rights to own slaves and Lincoln's early tepid abolitionist stance, which was still a radical departure from previous presidents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He reads like an idiot and appears to be one, but there's a reason he's relegated to the Opinion section and isn't writing for the Science section.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, the Angst Vampire. The blood is a metaphor for youthful angst, sucking all the fun out of the genre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eric came here wanting to be a starter but accepted a bench role  because we told him thats what the team needed in order to be at our best. He didnt even question it. The majority of guys in this league wouldnt do that, believe me.

Nice to see him giving teammates this kind of credit. Really rolls against the perception of Harden. 

Houston, yall ready?

I already know.

Clutch City!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also demonstrates a lack of knowledge of history. Yes, the Spartans were great warriors and Leonidas is a fascinating figure. Plutarch is really worth a read. However, the same qualities that made Sparta so powerful ultimately destroyed it from within. You can't have a society where the servants/slaves are treated terribly and are a significant portion of the population without encountering problems. The increasing helot revolts and the loss to Thebes at Leuctra was the beginning of the end of Sparta. Alexander effectively finished the job and the polis was only important for its strategic location during the Roman Empire's dominance in the region.  

Sparta is a study in hypocrisy. They fought so hard for their independence from everyone's influence while being cripplingly dependant on slave labor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much the usual way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cooking. Cooking is getting to run biochemistry experiments in my home lab that I get to eat later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jordan Edwards, a freshman at Mesquite High School, was leaving a party when he was shot through the passenger's side window of the vehicle, attorneyLee Merritt said.

No officers were injured in the incident.

/break

Balch Springs police Chief Jonathan Haber said officers heard gunshots as they were responding to a call of drunken teens about 11 p.m. in the 12300 block of Baron Drive.

During an altercation, the vehicle backed down the road toward officers "in an aggressive manner," Haber said. An officer fired at the vehicle and struck a passenger, who was then transported to the hospital and pronounced dead, Balch Springs police said in a prepared statement.

Ah yes, firing at a car leaving an area where the officers heard gunfire. I'm surprised they didn't just open up on the house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trubisky fined for excessive celebration after being picked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or is the hybrid that is destined to unite or destroy the Vampire and Lycan races.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many iPads were sold in that time?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamas to soften stance on Israel, Muslim Brotherhood in policy document: sources </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamas to soften stance on Israel, Muslim Brotherhood in policy document: sources </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamas to soften stance on Israel, Muslim Brotherhood in policy document: sources </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamas to soften stance on Israel, Muslim Brotherhood in policy document: sources </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you live on Peachtree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And of course marking a man-made trailhead with a cairn is a celebration of nature's beauty. You don't like them, that's fine, but don't pretend that the reason is because you're trying to preserve the natural world from us intruders. If you truly cared that much, you wouldn't go at all and let those areas thrive without your human impact, but you don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo, it's been a minute. How do you feel about the retirement?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #S E N D  H E LP  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea Test-Fires Another Ballistic Missile, Heightening Tensions With U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea Test-Fires Another Ballistic Missile, Heightening Tensions With U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is, it's very clever. Already demonstrating that IQ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, my understanding is that the Republic doesn't really want the hassle and so largely sidesteps the issue. Meanwhile, yeah, NI is having it's own political problems that complicate things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When was the last time a sitting president was this blatantly, consciously racist? Even Bush and Clinton weren't this bad. It's more than the racism, it's the sheer stupidity of not hiding his racism and/or shit-eating self-confidence that he can't he hurt by saying it to that crowd. 

Speaking of, NRA wonders how they have trouble attracting minorities. Here's your answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh...how? 

Edit: Seriously, Pai is either cartoonishly evil or an idiot. 

Pai'sNPRM presents no evidence that the no-throttling rule hurts customers, but claimsthat the current rules were passed without evidence.The document seeks comment about whether the FCC should have any rules onblocking, throttling, and paid prioritization, but strongly suggests that such rules aren't necessary.

"Despite virtually no quantifiable evidence of consumer harm, the commission nevertheless determined that it needed bright-line rules banning three specific practices by providers of both fixed and mobile broadband Internet access service: blocking, throttling, and paid prioritization," Pai'sdraft proposal says.

Break

The NPRM also suggests that customers arebeing harmed by the ban onISPs charging websites and other online services for faster access to consumers. "Is there a risk that banning paid prioritization suppresses pro-competitive activity?" the NPRM asks. "For example, could allowing paid prioritization give Internet service providers a supplemental revenue stream that would enable them to offer lower-priced broadband Internet access service to end-users?"

The NPRM asks whether paid prioritization could "enable certain critical information, such as consumers health care vital signs that are being monitored remotely, to be transmitted more efficiently or reliably." But the document fails to mention that the existing rules have an exception that lets ISPssell isolated network capacityfor telemedicine services.

The FCC also askswhether it shouldkeep rules that require ISPs to make greater disclosures about hidden fees and data caps. The FCC seems to think the broadband market is so competitive that this isn't necessary. "We seek comment on whether the additional reporting obligations from that rule remains necessary in todays competitive broadband marketplace," the NPRM says. Pai has alreadyexemptedISPs with 250,000 or fewer subscribers from these rules.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carlos Boozer, Alaskan from Juneau. I'm down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid as Iraq!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? Obama fired him? That wasn't a fucking sign?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...when was the last time the Titans were the Colts? 

Also, FTC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It would merely state the obvious, i.e. that also a united Ireland would continue being a member of the EU," a source close to preparations for the European Council said.

"The EU does of course not take a stance on the possibility of a united Ireland. Should this question arise, it would be for the peoples of Ireland and Northern Ireland to decide in accordance with the Good Friday Agreement."

Is there any momentum for a referendum on reunification on either side of the island? I thought there was still some resistance from RoI on it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And not only did Chicago trade up for Trubisky, they gave up the biggest ransom seen in North America since the Louisiana Purchasetwo third-round picks and a fourth-round pick to move up a single spot, the football equivalent of hoodwinking 827,000 square miles from the French for $15 million.

I dunno, I think Os was still more expensive. Worth it, but damn.  

Edit: Also, remember the Redskins' ransom for RG3?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In2009, on her website Barr gave her detailed take on where each of the main characters from the show would be in a possibleRoseannerevival Roseanne and Jackie opening the first medical marijuana dispensary in Lanford; **Dan reappearing alive after faking his death**; DJ being published; Mark dying in Iraq; David leaving Darlene for a woman half his age; Darlene coming out, meeting a woman and having a baby with her; Becky working at Walmart; Arnie befriendingthe Governor of Illinois and remarrying Nancy, Bev selling a painting for $10,000; Jerry and the grandsons forming a boy band; and **Bonnie being arrested for selling crack**.

Glad to see they're going to keep it upbeat. Like Breaking Bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *lonely Starbucks lovers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thursday, fire, starting in my car 

Reaching a fever pitch and its bringing me out the dark. 


The entire song still works, but the message changes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh oh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, bodyweight fitness means no knees weak.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh holy shit really. Heroes. All of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.S.A. Halts Collection of Americans Emails About Foreign Targets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.S.A. Halts Collection of Americans Emails About Foreign Targets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.S.A. Halts Collection of Americans Emails About Foreign Targets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.S.A. Halts Collection of Americans Emails About Foreign Targets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.S.A. Halts Collection of Americans Emails About Foreign Targets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.S.A. Halts Collection of Americans Emails About Foreign Targets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.S.A. Halts Collection of Americans Emails About Foreign Targets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's actually data supporting this. Someone made a video about it. 

https://youtu.be/sIlNIVXpIns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a brrb brrb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bags of sand?!?! BAGS OF SAND?!?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chance easily had the best verse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well not only this, we're legit excited about Watson. Dude's what we need right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House passes spending deal to keep the federal government open another week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House passes spending deal to keep the federal government open another week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House passes spending deal to keep the federal government open another week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House passes spending deal to keep the federal government open another week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gold, probably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/_pBQ6eD3dyI

His stomach was not fireproof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I probably got a couple of screws up in my head loose

But no worse than what's going on in your parent's bedrooms

Sometimes I want to get on TV and just let loose, but can't,

But it's cool for Tom Green to hump a dead moose </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCKING FINALLY A QB THAT CAN PERFORM  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the End, Pacific Rim, The Rock, Patriot Games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like he's doing it because it's easier to kill than NAFTA and he just wants to terminate a free trade deal, he doesn't care which one. Truly showing he understands the nuances of trade agreements. 

The president explained that the process of termination of Korus is simpler than with the North American Free Trade Agreement. With NAFTA, we terminate tomorrow; if we did, it ends in six months. With the Korean deal, we terminate and its over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like he's doing it because it's easier to kill than NAFTA and he just wants to terminate a free trade deal, he doesn't care which one. Truly showing he understands the nuances of trade agreements. 

The president explained that the process of termination of Korus is simpler than with the North American Free Trade Agreement. With NAFTA, we terminate tomorrow; if we did, it ends in six months. With the Korean deal, we terminate and its over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: We may terminate U.S.-South Korea trade agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: We may terminate U.S.-South Korea trade agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pick's a pick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As is tradition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP is David Lindhagen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R. Kelly is the original [David Lindhagen](https://youtu.be/PfBuYlBqC-Y).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jumanji: Tron Edition  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All cats have a common ancestor. Big cats and small cats diverged at some point and formed different subfamilies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Pentagon watchdog launches investigation into money that Mike Flynn received from foreign groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Pentagon watchdog launches investigation into money that Mike Flynn received from foreign groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just let them go at it. It's better that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't tempt me Frodo!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically Lone Wolf and Cub?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll settle for Abed Nadir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it really be a barrel without one?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gone down before. See the 90s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socks always stay dry and warm without getting all sweaty feet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try this one simple trick in public. Tongue out for maximum effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have called them iPodcasts. Also, I'm assuming common use doctrine applies on the name podcast and Apple isn't trying to claim any kind of ownership?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear of sand leads to anger towards sand. Anger towards sand leads to hate of sand. Hate of sand leads towards *suffering* from sand.

Anakin fears *sand* storms in Episode I. 

Anakin kills *sand* people out of anger in Episode II leading to hate. 

Anakin mentions he hates *sand* in Episode II as well. For all intents and purposes, anger and hate were simultaneous steps here. 

*Molten sand* is lava. 

Anakin gets all burnt up from lava or *molten sand* in Episode III causing suffering. 

Anakin's fear of sand as a child leads to his suffering because of molten sand as an adult. 

Yoda was right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E.Lon. phone home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't even their final form.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. Although, "may have been" isn't all that on the level either grammatically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Materials scientists end up getting crazy specialized in their field. Are all of you doing the exact same thing? Because the metallurgists I know all do radically different highly specific things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can definitely tell the difference between people that actually work in metallurgy and those who got a degree. The ones who work in materials sciences understand how intense specialization goes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was just a prank!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like maybe just a little offense?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a puppy, actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do all four legged mammals play by splaying their forelegs like that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Euros are your bane... Ah, England.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Hardy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bermuda, Bahamas, come on pretty mama  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mathed wrong out of trickery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an inanimate fucking object!!!!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, an entire website filled with unofficial Li'l Sebastian impersonators.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're going meta way too quickly and obscurely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be surprised at the number of topics where there's only a handful of experts. Happens with something like metallurgy because there's not that many metallurgists in the world, for example.  

Edit: Yes, I get it, metallurgists Reddit. Talk to each other, how many of you are doing the exact same thing and how many of you are so specialized that there only a few, even among metallurgists, that can relate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blindfolding as </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [She's jumping as, bruh!](https://youtu.be/ZdVHZwI8pcA)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/SocketRience, do you like the Elton John song *Rocket Man*?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he hasn't been cut yet, so they can say one thing about hockey per week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bribe Cases, a Secret Jared Kushner Partner and Potential Conflicts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bribe Cases, a Secret Jared Kushner Partner and Potential Conflicts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bribe Cases, a Secret Jared Kushner Partner and Potential Conflicts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bribe Cases, a Secret Jared Kushner Partner and Potential Conflicts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bribe Cases, a Secret Jared Kushner Partner and Potential Conflicts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that or you're talking to a wolf trying to blow your house down. But, come to think of it, it takes effort to huff and puff to the extent you can blow a house down. So yeah, checks out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Vodka soda~~ Double whisky and white wine yes ma'am right away.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work next to a disability rights office. I see it all the time. I make a point to not use that stall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House unveils dramatic plan to overhaul tax code in major test for Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the better BBQ in DC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ann Coulter Says She Will Pull Out of Speech at Berkeley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ann Coulter Says She Will Pull Out of Speech at Berkeley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But is he such a good person? Allows an execution to proceed against the advice of everyone he knows and feels so guilty about it that he has a priest take his confession. Lies to the public about a major medical condition that can affect his ability to make decisions. Assassinates a foreign leader and creates more problems in the cover up. Blunders his way into a decades old conflict with centuries of backstory and believes he can create peace. Fires his chief of staff for telling him that this isn't a good use of his time. All because he doesn't really want to govern after his friends were hurt and killed. 

The man has a ton of problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah at least with Alaska we get a flag song some little kid wrote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, fuck it, this whole season is a mulligan. We're starting over so the Stars can have a fair shot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoulder and ribs too. But it's mostly brisket. Seriously though, we do dope pork shoulder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go figure. Could've sworn it was a municipal thing. I'll edit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations on being an engineer. You can't practice your trade in Oregon unless you're registered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have and this obviously gets a little touchy, but I think the show "pushes" gender identity as a theme more than letting it be a thing organically. For example, I think sexual orientation in the show is depicted much better as a casual thing (or even in something like Jessica Jones where it's present but not a focus). I think the transgender actress was amazing, but the actual depiction and storyline just felt forced. Sort of like the transgender brother in Orphan Black, you know?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it appears Oregon is one of those states.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federalist Pig.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federalist Pig.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my point is that he was reported by the city, but you're correct, the licensing is done by the state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is that the fallout from the things that happened in The West Wing does not compare to what would have likely actually happened to a President in a similar situation in the 90s. Clinton got impeached for lying about sex, you really think a Republican Congress or the Democrats would let Bartlett stay after assuming the presidency without disclosing a significant health issue that could affect his ability to execute his duties? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not *as* good as the best Houston BBQ. But it's a pretty damn good taste of the best.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #NEW HAMPSHIRE STATE REPRESENTATIVE ROBERT FISHER  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ~~city~~ state is clearly posturing to get him to fuck off, but they're also technically correct. He can't represent himself as something he's not and use that to lend credibility to an official correspondence. There's a reason licensing requirements exist, though the fees are clearly a racket. If he'd just presented the findings without alleging credentials, he'd have been fine. 

The fine is stupid, but it looks like a case where they're both wrong. Except about the traffic light. I think he's got a point there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunday's episode might be a top five for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if it were, it turns out Garrett was a bust because of his attitude and Sashi is a genius. Or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shut your beautiful mouth about Texas BBQ. Houston dry rub forever.  There's a place that does it in DC now and it's the best thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
