<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject832</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 21:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you say you do it yourself, what do you mean...?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 00:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Hed say a bloody nice welt.

A "nice bloody welt" in England would mean just that. A welt with blood.

Welt is such a weird word. Welt.

Welt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 23:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really didn't need the visual on that. Christ. I can almost smell it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does any such thing as a no wiper exist. You have to wipe to know it's a no wiper. And then it's not a no wiper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 20:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late to the party.

I was playing one of those social board games, where you shout clues and shit to each other.

As far as I can remember it had cards with stuff on like 'lives in the sea' and you'd have to say a bunch of stuff like 'shark' and whatever until someone figured out what was on your card. 

My card was 'evil' or something like that. After all of the obvious things like, murder and kidnap and stuff, with my family guessing 'crimes, I had a sudden image in my 15 year old mind of the embodiment of evil; being obsessed with lord of the rings, what could be more evil than the cloaked, black ring wraiths? On the same note- dementors! Scream from Scary Movie! They're all hooded, cloaked in black.

So to generalise, I just said "Black people," to the absolute dismay and outrage of my conservatively minded mother, father and sister, now convinced they'd raised a closet racist.

Not my finest moment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 10:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 'and my axe'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I wasn't even part of this conversation! Don't be like that. Let's hug it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My inferiors bahahahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excel wizards of Reddit, what sweet tricks can you teach me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like a 5ft cow isn't that impressive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 20:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much is 8 hours in dog time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 08:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also manboobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could have said your own biological children. You kinda made the adopted kids sound 'unnaturally born' like you grew them in a grow-your-own-baby kit from Walmart or something  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 10:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He shot himself in the foot. He said it further down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to the stereotype of men buying fancy sports cars to compensate for their small penises, the under-endowed male has better wealth prospects than average to well-endowed males. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 15:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 06:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, look! It's Jenna Marbles!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 01:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you'd have to taste it...

It looks like it would taste of cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offence, but *states totally non-offensive thing* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 17:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You couldn't care less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 11:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The love of my life coming back home and telling me it was all just a misunderstanding, and that he's never going to leave again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 09:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3meta5me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 00:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 weeks out of a 3.5 year relationship here too. I'm in the same boat as you.

Try and find things to do. When you want to cry, cry. Don't hold back. If you need space, take it. Take the time you need to heal, time heals all.

Thinking of you. Be strong. You aren't alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 08:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice cold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what my ex boyfriend would say. It's been a week and I don't know what to do without him. You sound like him. I don't know why I'm saying this really. 

I miss him too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 16:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I wouldn't really call it a story.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 20:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His eyes! Well I think he does anyway. *Adjusts glasses* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look a bit like Leonardo DiCaprio!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironinvelvet is right about your photography skills. You have a nice face but I feel the photography and the hairstyle let's you down..you look like a teenager, not a 23 year old. 

You should make more of your eyebrows:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it just means if you were to wear short hair then you would be hard to figure out. It's not a bad thing by any means. As a straight girl I think you look great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a really solid amount of savings. I'm not in danger of going under- I just want to make sure I have enough to stay in the black. I am planning on doing some dog walking (I love dogs but can't afford my own) to make a little extra cash and I have an etsy shop too. I may be able to negotiate the wage up too on this job because they are desperate to take me on. Thanks for your advice on the utilities too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 11:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no car and do not watch any TV so no licence required. This is a great help thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 14.5k PA enough to live on by myself in Sheffield? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 11:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My partner recently split with me and I am about to be offered a job. I have never lived alone and I don't know the full cost of living. I am a frugal girl who isn't into drinking and partying. I like to spend time by myself. Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't any one else feel like that smile could stretch all the way round her head.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the one in the blue scarf with the stripy top near the bottom of this album. That looks the nicest to me. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The expression really puts me off, sorry.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way you pout and pose for the camera tells me you think you are very attractive! However I personally am not a fan of the long hair look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl to girl- the eyebrows are a bit much in my opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 00:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Satisfied  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of these are symptoms of anxiety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps she'd pulled some dodgy shit before. You never know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 21:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you're still doing it! That's all in present tense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy I once dated had a full on dingleberry market going on back there. 69ing isn't much fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
