<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject513</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why not stop playing if you hate it so much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol whats entertaining is all you people crying on a subreddit about how unfair it is that dice is appealing to more gamers than you in your ivory towers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People that whine about the automatico need to realize its supposed to be good up close. But nope, they'd rather cry to dice about the things that kill them

downvote me I don't care. Someone has to call out the whining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As part of the wider audience they are appealing to I like the game and think all the changes you purists want would make it shit. No faster way to kill a game than to appeal to a small minority of its playerbase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dice wanted to appeal to more people so they made the game this way. I'm their target audience: Someone that has never really played battlefield before this and bought the game because it looked cool. I now have 350 hours in the game and I like it. Its great to hop on for 3 or 4 hours. 

I see this trend in all of you on this sub reddit that have played the older battlefields. You think your view has to be the correct one because you played old games. You think you just know in your gut what battlefield is and think we should listen. You don't seem to understand that games change over the years and its a good thing. I'd have never played battlefield if they'd kept it the way it used to be. I tried a couple times on BF3 and just thought this is too much.

I'm sure I'm one of those "Casuals" a lot of you hate but I really don't give a damn. Why shouldn't dice cater to gamers like me more than you, when there are way more of us? We're the reason this battlefield sold so many more copies than the last. Go find some indie developer focused on a small group of players if you want a "high skill" game with no good guns or vehicles. Because thats a lot of what you seem to want from your post: Battlefield without the fun/good guns or fun/good vehicles. Don't be such a purist. 

I totally agree with you about the server options though, players should be able to create custom gamemodes and its a shame they can't. I also agree about ammo 2.0, I think its a shit system.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The developers of the game clearly disagree with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love when this sub leads to fixes for the little things like this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cavalry class is already kinda bad, they don't need that nerf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use a fighter and you won't get shot down by AA often. Sure lots of people will whine at you but who cares if you're having fun? 

Also yes air superiority now please. Me and my pilot friends would be the Red Baron and his flying circus  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is the person getting punished isn't the support not giving ammo, it's the player that needs the ammo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem man, I didn't know until I was like level 30 with the pilot class haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to hold down the left stick to do it I believe. You can do it I have before  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do that already. It'll probably get you killed, but you can do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say find something better to do because I know I am. I'm not helping your little youtube channel on the off chance you get lucky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't set up a fair dogfight, I'm not doing that pre lobby dogfight bs without a minimap or hud. You may well win in that circumstance as I spot and use my minimap to know where my opponent is while I dogfight.

If I happen to run into you in a lobby we can try things but I'm not doing it on your terms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've went 129-2 soooooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gone 110-0 on St Quentin and won a 1 vs 3 fighter dogfight. I just checked your stats all you ever use is the attack plane, you only have 1 day in the fighter. Dogfighting without a fighter is hardly dogfighting. No wonder you think if someone gets on you then you die instantly, in the attack plane its true. Feel free to check mine if you want to see my fighter stats. https://battlefieldtracker.com/bf1/profile/xbox/oH%20So%20S3RiiOUS 

There is already a wide skill gap. I notice it plenty when I slaughter 10-15 planes a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're complaining because you aren't great at something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read your post. A rear view camera is ridiculous and it takes a lot of the skill out of dogfighting. So what a bomber killer shouldn't be able to sneak up on you and one shot if he catches you off guard? Because he couldn't with your rear view camera idea.

Now you're flat wrong that you can only go by sound. When they shoot, they literally show up on the minimap. Nevermind that if you're using the trench fighter, which who isn't, you can shoot flares. 

If you do have 11 days flying then most of them must be in bombers and attack planes because everyone I know that mains fighter enjoys dogfighting as it is and does a fine job getting people off their tail. The only thing that really stops us is 2 fighters vs 1 fighter. You're right in that its difficult to get a good pilot off your tail, but that is how it should be. As it stands right now in the time I've played maybe 1/20 pilots can consistently kill me once on my tail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't chastise me like I'm someone that doesn't know how to fly. I've flown for about 3 days of game time and think people crying about "whoever gets on your tail first wins" are bad at piloting. You seriously asking for a always active rear camera? Why don't we just show where all the planes are on the minimap at all times while we're at it? You should be able to figure out where the enemy is behind you based off his bullets (and the fact that he shows up on the minimap when he shoots) and "defend yourself properly". If you're flying randomly and depending on luck to defend yourself then you're one of the scrubs and deserve to get shot down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are downvoting you because they've all tried to solo a tank with AT rockets   AT nades and they know you're full of shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way, the double barrel shotgun and frommer stop auto would be everywhere if they did this. Dice has a specific range every kit is best at and this would ruin it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got 3 days in planes and I think the dart nerf is necessary. The AA Buff is too much though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy dogfighting in bf1 and I'd hate for them to change it. If someone gets on your tail you can get them off by banking into low yo yos. It's not impossible. You just have to be a good pilot. If the other guy can keep up through those he deserves to kill you. 

Battlefield 1 is more about how you move your plane rather than how fast it's going and I like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand the whiny people in this sub man. This sub is cancerous for the game as now Dice listens to these whiners over data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well considering in the base game 2 AT nades and 4 AT rockets isn't enough to solo a tank and is the standard we have now, I'd have to disagree and point out that you're just being a petty smartass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a blanket negative attitude towards people that just whine about the things that kill them, which is most of the complaints in this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't pat yourself on the back too much about being "top 50 in the US" BattlefieldTracker only tracks country leaderboards by people that register their country on the site. They don't just know what players are from what country. 

anyway the vast majority of people that play this game will never care as much as players like you and me. I'd like it if teamplay could be stronger, but the fact of the matter is changes like this will only make the game more frustrating as people continue to play the way they always have.

This game has been out for 6 months, players are set in their ways and a change like this is going to be infuriating. I have a feeling you play on PC as well and it clouds your judgement, as you've never seen casual like a battlefield server on Xbox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow all the capital YOURs really help convince me that your argument must be right. 

My problem is idealism about this game like yours. Players are mostly casual and expecting everyone to magically start running support and giving ammo after this change screws over starting ammo is ridiculous. You balance for the playerbase you have, not for the one you wish you had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was under the impression that they removed the "magic" ammo regen. 

And you should never depend on players to change. The average person playing this game is a level 20-50 with a PS4 that wants to chill out after work. He is playing to kill and runs stupid gadget setups, like limpet-mortar support. He isn't going to change. 

The instant repair going from 30 to 10 since release is quite the nerf. You just sound like you want an "I win" button from range against the tanks. A clever assault can take out a tank alone easily with at mines and at nades. If using only AT rockets it should take 3+ assaults to take a tank down.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It killed me the other day too, you basically have to never fly near the ground if the train or dreadnought are blasting artillery. Seems like any plane within 200m of impact gets pulled down   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, balance for the game you have not the one you wish you had  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This change will just result in a game where you have no gadget ammo most of the time and get pissed at all the supports not doing their job. If I had any confidence in supports I wouldn't mind this change, but I have none and I'm certain it will just result in a frustrating experience when spawning assault. Which is of course what most of the people asking for this want, as the assault class is hated in this subreddit. 

Tank nerfs should not be considered. They nerf too much too often and the last thing needed is yet another tank nerf. Tanks are supposed to be powerful. But an assault is also supposed to have the ammo necessary to take it on and after this change they hardly ever will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dice, Ammo.2.0 is ok but you should always spawn with the same amount of ammo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In every fps I've ever played it was a guarantee that whenever you spawned back in you'd have full ammo. It makes for a less frustrating experience. The whole sometimes spawning with different amounts of gadget ammo is a direct nerf to an assault class that has been targeted with nerfs more than enough already. In dices quest to make supports more important, they've completely tied assault players hands against tanks and taken away half the fun of the class. Because if there's one thing I know it's that you'll only have a support player willing to resupply you 1/3 matches and the rest of the time you'll get 1 AT nade and 2 AT rockets per life. 

This change won't make support better. It'll just make the other classes worse.

The cool down timers are good though, no need to change them. Just don't do the spawning with hardly any ammo thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a problem to you. But it's not a problem to a lot of us.

In six months when dice had nerfed and changed all the stuff this sub is begging for I'm not even going to recognize this game. They change too much too often and I'm tired of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full ammo like it is now. Unlike most of this sub I don't cry when an AT grenade kills me. It doesn't even happen often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're going to listen to all you people complain to them about explosives, and planes, and tanks, and automaticos, and shotguns, and by the end of it I won't even recognize the game I bought from the nerfed garbage it's become. I just want to play the game I bought without dice drastically changing things every couple months. I'm fine with the explosives. They're supposed to be powerful. And people are out to screw the assault class with this ridiculous nerf because of "spam".    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I would, I think it's an advantage of the assault class. I also don't like that the change would gimp AT rocket ammo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't agree with it. This change goes too far in dices quest to appease people spamming them over explosives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with Ammo 2.0 other than the whole spawning with different amounts of ammo thing. You should always spawn with the same amount of ammo. I've never heard of someone killing themselves for more grenades, its ridiculous. This is a solution to a non existent problem that makes the game more complicated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blinds/curtains dawg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might have a chance after the coming trench fighter nerf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As one of those fighter planes you just put a target on your back for me to come kill you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 2 or 3 guns I swap between per class but I don't feel the need to use the shitty weapons in the name of boredom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want idiots not to spawn in the pilot seat when I'm seat switching to deal with a fighter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish there was a "disable spawning" button while in a plane  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That price is a god damn joke.

Good thing my hatchet beats all these puzzle melee weapons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those guys you saw were likely in a squad together, and DICE spliting up squads of people that know each other in the name of "balance" would be foolish, even if they did it between games. 

I think you're wanting dice to forcefully switch people to the other team against their will during the match too, which would just lead to a lot of quitting. I'd be pissed if I went from kicking ass to suddenly on the other team getting pummeled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do you want dice to force people to stay in shitty games?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a game this big there are a lot of ways to play, even if you don't approve of them. And if you're buying those games you clearly enjoy that gameplay. But a Mario kart fan probably wouldn't enjoy the game if the developers nerfed all his favorite cars because whiners on the internet wanted him to play a certain way with certain cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People play in a way that is fun to them. Which is what you don't get. Its not necessarily about points or kills to them. You could make defending flags worth a ton and a lot of people wouldn't bother because its not fun to sit on a flag doing nothing but waiting. People don't buy games for developers to twist their arms into playing a way they don't enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah fuck them for trying to get the chance to use the dlc items they paid for. People play the game how they want which is something this sub doesn't seem to understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't like tank hunters running with medics and going MLG 1 shot quick scopes on people though. So I'd have to say no to this idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> l use planes all the time and as consistently as you can obliterate people in trenches they shouldn't be on this map </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You replaced one conservative with another so I don't really care. They are paying lip service to another healthcare plan, but they've given up and failed. It just came out today that Trump was moving on from tax reform too. nothing but failure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/iamverysmart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm enjoying watching him and congressional republicans fail at everything actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most People enjoy it on reddit. If you don't like it leave. That's all I've heard from conservatives about their areas for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt he makes 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All because they weren't willing to pay passengers more money to get off the plane. Being petty over thousands will cost them millions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "someone pointed out how shitty republicans are, quick mention Hillary Clinton!"

Republican shilling 101
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a complete fool or liar if you don't see how the democrats and republicans are different on this issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quits do not count as losses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just sound like one of those "omg battlefield 1 is so casual" whiners so I don't really care about your opinion. 

And so instead they should balance the game for the 20% of the playerbase on pc because they came first? That's ridiculous. You focus on where the people buying the game are playing.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I'm reading is someone that doesn't like a gun that is supposed to be good up close up close. 

I also see yet another PC elitist that doesn't get that the majority of this games playerbase is on console  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is /r/iamverysmart material  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got to be one of the biggest complainers on this subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You people just want the automatico to be shit because you get killed a lot with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roughing the passer flag in a spring game lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bryant could be a good wildcat QB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cooper may be Watson lite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't help that Watson spoiled us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy hearing Dabo talk about the team like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cooper looking good at the end of the half. Its going to be him or Johnson, with Bryant making a Stoudt like appearance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnson looks pretty good throwing. Don't know if that will get him the starting job though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either our secondary is playing phenomenally or Bryant and Cooper are going to the run too fast  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't stop Dabo from starting him lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bryant is not the guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Johnson keeps throwing like that we might just have a QB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spiers is god </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are those throws Bryant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inb4 a sack record is set at the spring game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you want to be excited for the defense but can't help but worry about the offense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to feel like we have a clear number 1 at QB by the end of this but I don't think we will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spring game is as good a time as any to start drinking for the day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Israel throwing the ball well 

edit: and he almost throws a pick right after I post that hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the QB was typically the player that signals the WR when to start running on those sweeps. Johnson may well have mistimed it. His first throw was a little bit ahead of his target. And he didn't really look great running. Its still too early to make major judgements but it wasn't a good drive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Johnson not looking too hot on the first drive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our team has too many great receivers to have a run first QB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could they at least make the white section on the scoreboard white?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see him limp. If he did then no big deal, he will be fine by fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kelly Bryant looking hurt already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can take him from Dabo's cold dead hands  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES oh this dline will be good for a long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 13:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deaths between operations rounds are not removed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The medic class is already iffy at best compared to the other 3, the last thing it needs is a healing nerf. One of the biggest advantages to the medic class is supposed to be healing yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your post is the one that convinced me never to buy this game. I got pissed enough getting weapons to X in ME3 I can't imagine having to get good characters up to X too. EA money-grubbing killing the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No ones going to do shit to us. We might get denounced by some diplomats but who cares.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put simply, what are they going to do about it? The most powerful force in the world just punished them for doing something evil. Its not like we bombed civilians, we bombed an airfield. 

I don't like Trump but I don't mind this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confident you're going to win lmao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah Infering dislike means you think you know how they should be playing. So take your lap and shove it up your ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really bothers me that you think you know the best way to play. We all bought the game and we all play how we want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you misunderstood me, I mean it's harder to take down the attack plane as the fighter when they switch to the Gunner seat. It's feels like the plane doesn't take as much damage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do attack planes tank more damage when the pilot switches seats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like the attack planes can tank a shit ton of damage after the pilot switches to the gunner seat. Is it just my imagination or is there anything to this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my only counter to dice putting me on a shit team so I don't mind  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The double barrel shotgun and frommer stop auto are too powerful to be giving out to every player like that. But I'd have no problems with use of the others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the system is great as it is and shouldn't be changed at all. There are mild annoyances but nothing worth worrying developers over.

Well except for the order squeaky swing sound, get rid of that shit lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone I know just had their SPM drop by like 100 so we're pissed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
