<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2800</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *There is no try. Do or do not.* Yoda (and now Putin) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It amazes me how much he sounds like my children sometimes. I wish I could put him on a timeout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We simply must  and we will  get this right. The Chairman and I agree it is vitally important that we do this as a credible, bipartisan, and transparent a manner as possible. As was said yesterday at our press conference, Chairman Burr and I trust each other, and equally important, we trust our colleagues on this committee that we are going to move together and we are going to get to the bottom of it and get it right.

I hope both sides buy into this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch the Top Democrat on the Senate Intel Committee Explain the Trump-Russia Scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did we say drain the swamp? We meant fill it with chlorpyrifos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan won't commit to healthcare vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The degree of the lying is new. I think people always believed they had to have some plausible way to tilt their comments such that they could be considered true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earth will be ok. It may just decide it doesn't want us around anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong! He know's that tomorrow is Friday, and he gets to fly to Mar A Lago on a plane, even though the gold trim isn't as nice as the one he was using before. People there will act like they admire him. Then he gets to golf. Meanwhile, President Bannon will give him some nuggets to tweet, that will make sure he dominates the Sunday headlines. He knows exactly what he's going to do next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They tried actually building consensus - starting with using a Republican proposal as the framework. In the end they needed to pass the bill themselves because the Repubs refused to contribute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Paul Ryan said it was going great. Of course, in shreds is where he wanted it. Heckuva job Nunes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He may go for the trifecta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've gotten a message that they can make up whatever they want, without consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the astonishing thing to me, that elected officials are actually allowed to lie without recourse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, for anyone who questioned which party was refusing to work with the other, here's your answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Op-Ed Do you live in Devin Nunes' district? Pick up the phone and call his office immediately </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should get John Oliver on this, he loves this sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Independent Counsel. Repeat until it's real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Koppel is a classy guy. Imagine if he really said what he thought Hannity was doing to America and in what position? And the fact that he won't even use lube when he's doing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do I think Trump Vodka is really just a bottle of hot air? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryan too apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And ignore the part of the process that involves congress passing laws and him signing them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there was this thing called an election last November. It was obvious which of our two corporately subsidized parties was more hostile to the country, but people didn't care. 

I'm all for people being outraged now, and I do call   email my Sens and Congressman, but I have a hard time getting past the anger at Americans for taking us here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hold up is them creating something else to distract the media. Now people are talking about Nunes and the holdup, which is what Trump's team wants. It's all about distraction.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure he should, but clearly that isn't the job he's doing. And clearly it is fine with his party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except right now I think he is succeeding at his job: Creating something else for the media to talk about while stalling the investigation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you know Nunes would fuck up the potato salad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's plenty of blame for both of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently it would take a different government. This one is broken, but it's warranty has expired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been obvious for a week. It was clear what his interest was when Comey testified. But once Nunes ran to the WH, refused to discuss leaks with members of his committee, and now shut the committee down completely it has become obvious that his objective is to do the President's bidding. Even more appalling though is the fact that most of his party continues to support him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, and the way the Republicans are acting now they will refer it to his committee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congress is supposed to be a check on the President. But the House is treating Trump like King. Hence, the checks and balances have been broken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one of the factors it uses in its assessment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget CAPPITALIZING and extra exclamation marks!!! SAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His Tax returns are public now 

**WRONG!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also called on Trump to release transcripts of Flynn's calls with Russia's ambassador. NR is conservative, but they don't like Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he won't say who his sources are. And he won't say what they told him. Almost like he was just creating a distraction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why the results need to be out in the open. And it is why cancelling this week's hearings look really bad.

FWIW, noted liberal source National Review suggested that Trump ask for the transcripts of Flynn's calls to the ambassador to be released - speculation of what they said is likely worse than the details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do we know this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Obama Congress was always happy to investigate. Benghazi anyone? You believe Congress is investigating Trump as aggressively as they did Hillary / Obama? You think they were briefing Obama on the investigation before they were briefing other Congressmen?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But congress wasn't helping cover up. Now they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are stalling, hoping they can delay long enough that something distracts people'e attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the scandal free ex-President? How about we look into the guy who seems to be covering up something trying to stop an investigation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is still a small piece of me that thinks there's still a chance this is Trump believing he's above having to answer to little people. Add in the embarrassment of a woman criticizing him in public.

I'm pretty convinced that behind the scenes Ryan and his band of traitors are scrambling to find a way of starting an investigation that they can claim is impartial but is really under control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, cancelling isn't even vaguely defensible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More a statement about the fall of his party than the rise of Graham. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goodwin's law usually takes more than 33 comments. Well played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the one. Suddenly the media looks pretty vital to our country, doesn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It worked before, but today it went very poorly. I think people in the media have finally caught on, weird random tweet means he's trying to distract us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schiff: Yates would have testified on Flynn at cancelled hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know it is a lie. But they have no shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do feel like that paragraph alone was worth clicking the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Trump, theres a very good reason Congress isnt investigating Hillary Clintons big uranium deal with Russia. Its because the story is absolute crap  as you well know.

http://www.marketwatch.com/story/trump-spreads-more-fake-news-on-hillarys-uranium-deal-2017-03-28 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's recycling these now, clearly. He recycled the times, Podesta, and Uranium today. Sad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cancelling the hearing this week makes it harder to avoid. The FBI is not going to allow them to hide crimes. One way or another, whatever happened and whoever is guilty is coming out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know things are looking grim for President Trump when he starts tweeting about Hillary Clinton again. Monday evening he sounded trapped and wounded: Why isnt the House Intelligence Committee looking into the Bill   Hillary deal that allowed big Uranium to go to Russia, Russian speech. Well, perhaps it is because she is not president, did not hold back her tax returns, did not constantly cheer for Vladimir Putin, did not hire a host of pro-Putin flunkies and did not have aides who lied about contact with Russian officials.

Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He clearly believes they can block an independent investigation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dems will not fight them on the debt ceiling, unless they try to load the bill up with other garbage.  But the scary thing is that there are forces within the Republican party willing to play chicken with the debt ceiling - so they could put something in there   dare the dems to oppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible Pence is going down   they know it. There's speculation that this is why they were discussing replacing Ryan last weekend, to keep someone on "their team" in line of succession. Strange times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly the intelligence community is working to keep the WH from changing the subject.

Independent commission coming up, it's inevitable now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or else Graham will... Do nothing. I get it, it's good that he   McCain aren't toeing the party line, but how about **action**? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, they're incompetent. Hence, worst cover up ever - cancelling a scheduled meeting of the investigative committee run by a partisan hack. Smooth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Department of Justice has advised that it believes there are further constraints on the testimony Ms. Yates may provide at the [House intelligence committee] hearing. Generally, we understand that the department takes the position that all information Ms. Yates received or actions she took in her capacity as Deputy Attorney General and acting Attorney General are client confidences that she may not disclose absent written consent of the department. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House sure looks like its doing a cover-up of the Russia story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now, we return to the WH being outraged by leaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is what Nunes meltdown was probably about. They were looking for a way to provide cover. Nixon would be proud of his party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems likely he's trying to discredit his whole committee. One has to wonder what Yates was about to say... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF is the world coming to when this is the voice of reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump tweets squirrel. The media runs after squirrel. Trump and Nunes laugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are areas where it's not doing well though. He could undermine it in several ways. I wouldn't but this past them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's embarrassing that he is happy about the idea of our health care system "imploding". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easy: When he is taking more than 4-5 of them per year. Or when the taxpayers have built a perfectly good   **SECURE** weekend retreat specifically for this purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not in question. Say it out loud: "Nunes has proven that he sees his obligations as being to POTUS, destroying any pretense of him being capable of running an unbiased investigation." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'know I was pretty sure the name was wrong but was too lazy to look it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Attorney General, who has recused himself. So it falls to his ~~Assistant~~ Deputy, IIRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was never about the emails. It was about a way of smearing Hillary. 

This is just another piece of evidence proving that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's reasonable. So Nunes was intentionally causing a diversion.

The Dems response needs to be a unified call for an independent counsel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sure seems like he was asked to provide a new storyline, and took one for the team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It Doesn't Get Any Easier for Republicans Now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure Nunes will change the mandate of the investigation for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump overturns Obama-era education regulations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd feel worse if he'd lost Florida. As it is, they get some ownership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should not be allowed to continue in his current position unless he comes clean with who gave him the info.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not very hard. Impossible. He flat out said he went to the President first because the President had been criticized. That leaves no question where his loyalty is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top U.S. Senate Democrat Schumer offers to work with Trump on fixing Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's hard to say, but I do believe that if an elected official on the left side of the political spectrum lied the way he does, I would disapprove.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't tie voting to being smart, but an overall better informed electorate would help - raise the mean rather than suppress the tail.

Vote by mail (Oregon) did a lot to increase turnout. FWIW, I was opposed to this initiative when it first was proposed, but in hindsight it was a positive. I would love to see nationwide voting standard for federal elections, but the argument is that it's not constitutional.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still wonder who these 36% are. Guessing they don't watch any news, and are big fans of the Apprentice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think smarter voters are a better solution. I hear you though, it's tough when what passes for News is often dictated by ad revenue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I get sad for the victims of the Bowling Green Massacre too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Trump Still Tweeting From His Unsecured Android Phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who knew him (and weren't currently being employed by him) were pretty consistent in their assessment: He should not have been elected. Somehow people weren't interested in this, cuz email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no shortage these days. Spicey will do fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wealthy Trump backers attend anti-climate change event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they do. But Nunes won't even share with the members of his committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You only get so many lies...

Unless you are POTUS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He and the Republicans agree that the Rich should pay less in taxes. This will be their make up issue. Then they will move on to a budget that fits with the reduced revenue from the tax cuts.

Everyone knew they had no health care plan, which was why people expected them to vote to repeal, with the repeal happening in 5-6 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there was a liberal woman who continually lied, he would be on solid ground. The problem with KAC isn't her ideology, it's her willingness to lie - and that is nothing but destructive to rational discourse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've thought the same about people like Ann Coulter for years. They will say crazier and crazier things since their objective is to be covered. The best you could do is ignore them, but sadly that isn't good for ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be ironic if in stopping the Republican Insurance Plan from becoming law the far right allowed improvements to a program they despise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that Trump being at the WH is considered breaking news should make even his supporters cringe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morning Joe Co-Host Believes Everyone Should Ban Kellyanne Conway From News Programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making Nepotism Great Again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do so love that photo. I hope it haunts him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he can. What I am saying is make him do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if the Democrats worked with them on that bill. Yes, it would destroy the right, and could actually be positive for the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that is expected, but I think people forget that part of the problem with Obamacare originally was the Repubs refusing to even attempt to work with Obama. It seems important to me that the Democrats continue the message that they are willing to work for the country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Just Happened?! A Review of President Trumps Ninth Week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Dems could reach out to moderate Republicans it would be an astonishing development, and good for the country. Seems unlikely though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see the Dems get out in front of this right away by making some real policy proposals. The Republicans will never cooperate, but it would allow the Democrats to deflect the criticism that they are only obstructing. FWIW, Trump's approach of blaming the Dems for his defeat will backfire, bigly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP senator: I'm ready to work with Trump, Dems on healthcare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Yet the media allowed Trump to claim that the details were on his web site. What was on his web sit was drivel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody pushed him to provide details during the campaign. All he talked about was letting companies sell insurance across stat lines.

He didn't talk details, because he is not a serious human being. He's a salesman. Unfortunately, Ryan was the engineer designing the product and he provided the salesman with a broken product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo. I read it back when it was released, and even though I disagreed with a lot of what he said he struck me as someone who was actually thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 22:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people don't love it, FWIW. Rather than voting repeatedly to repeal over the last 7 years, the Republicans should have been discussing actual improvements. Actual plans.

What you're saying is correct, and I'd hope that our government tries to improve our health system moving forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His supporters don't even require him to make sense, do they? It's the democrats fault that his party with a majority failed to come up with a law they could pass. Right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have little question that he'll have worse days to come. Hopefully the one where he's led away in handcuffs is the worst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll own even that though. They failed to repeal today, and can't blame the Democrats for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democrats are the party that says government will make you smarter, taller, richer, and remove the crabgrass on your lawn. The Republicans are the party that says government doesn't work and then they get elected and prove it.

P.J. O'Rourke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democrats are the party that says government will make you smarter, taller, richer, and remove the crabgrass on your lawn. The Republicans are the party that says government doesn't work and then they get elected and prove it.

P.J. O'Rourke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like **R**epublican **I**nsurance **P**lan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And last night insisted they'd hold a vote today. 

The country actually did win today, I'm not tired of winning yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's clear that they didn't start with an objective of what they wanted to accomplish. Less uninsured? Lower costs? A tax cut for the wealthy? Without being able to articulate their goals, it was impossible to craft a good plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it is dead for the best possible reason, the reason that undergirds all social progress: because a good idea defeated a bad one.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Obamacare Defeated Trumpcare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  TRUMP tells me in interview this is now the Democrats' fault, and that he anticipates that when Obama "explodes" they will be ready to deal

https://twitter.com/maggieNYT/status/845362688557486081

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting for them to blame Obama. Meanwhile, Obama's sitting back, drinking a beer and laughing his ass off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was right, I'm already getting tired of all this winning. I thought MAGA would look different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. So, Trump is moving on now, yes? I think he plans to fail at tax reform next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carter had some bad weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much for the ultimatum. Looks like they'll have to come up with something even worse to get the votes they need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't he be in the House listening to the debate? That's his job, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does have the benefit of being able to remove a leader who has lost the confidence of government at the drop of a hat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it needs them + 11 from the 32. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have an upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he WAS going to fly in to attend yesterday, until they cancelled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get the next one(s), I'm logging off cuz watching this is making me stressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11AM NYTimes update, 32 firm no (unchanged), 10 leaning no (+1 in last half hour). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYTimes already had him as a firm no. The real question is if their 32 firm no's hold, or if others join them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but when the AG had to recuse himself, and Flynn got fired for lying, that argument was lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note where I said the Republicans have no such constraints. The Dems were under the gun to to the impending loss of a Senate seat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had the votes they needed to get it to reconciliation, and were going to lose them. If the Republicans had been willing to work together they could have done something with consensus, but the right wing would never have handed that victory to Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up to 41. NYtimes is keeping a running tally today. Currently they've had the firm No's at 32 unchanged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fairness, the Democrats did ram through Obamacare. But the reason was that the Republicans had been given a chance to participate and decided they would do nothing but oppose, and circumstances dictated this was the only option left. The Repubs have no such constraints. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pro: We can claim to have repealed Obamacare.

Con: Our bill is abysmal for America.

I can see how they are conflicted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent branding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYTimes 10:30 update still has 32 Repubs as No, 9 lean No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patriot Act. They're good at branding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said this last night, when I first heard about the ultimatum. I believe they'll cave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His wife just died, visitation is today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYTimes has a count   list, but I doubt it's accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, ok. Yes, I've seen the 22 # for a while, but also seen 21 in some counts. I think it's 21 if Rush is present. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree, but I will be surprised if this actually comes to the floor an fails. Happy? Yes, that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was going to attend Thursday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could even be intentional, since visitation is today. Tough for him to be in DC, but I still wouldn't rule it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still believe that if they don't have the votes, they cancel at the last minute. This is a classic negotiating tactic though, and may work.

Remember, Dubya insisted he would force a UN security council vote on Iraq, up until it became clear that he didn't have the votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to be that guy, but they put the wrong picture in this article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened in Ottawa a month ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House will pass it. Senate will block. Trump doesn't give a shit about the bill just headlines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the Republicans will cave and vote yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Obamacare replacement cuts aid for lower-income people, makes more higher-income people eligible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, he is not impartial   can not lead an investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they would have a harder time and less excuses. The point has been made, even in places like the National Review, that the best thing Trump could do would be to get the investigation done ASAP. Release transcripts of Flynn's calls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who, then, is going to handle this keg of Kremlin dynamite? If a case proceeds, the first step may well be taken under FARA. And if that case goes to court, the F.B.I. will need an impartial overseer. But the ability of Congress to investigate fairly is dubious. Attorney General Jeff Sessions, who oversees the F.B.I., has recused himself owing to his own contacts with the Russian ambassador. The best answer may be an independent prosecutor, a step Democrats want but Republicans oppose.

And why do Republicans oppose it? Sessions has recused himself. Nunes has proven that his loyalty is to the WH, thus destroying the concept of separation of powers. On what grounds, based on Comey's testimony, can they oppose an independent counsel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The House Republican health care bill is a pure top-down document. It was not molded to the actual health care needs of regular voters. It does not have support from actual American voters or much interest in those voters. It was written by elites to serve the needs of elites. Donald Trump vowed to drain the swamp, but this bill is pure swamp.

And this is why it is going to pass. It doesn't matter what's in it. They don't have any objective other than having defeated Obama. What's good for the country never enters the equation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Willing to bet they pass it. This is how Trump negotiates, and as much as he's a POS, he's succeeded with this tactic in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, but it isn't clear to me which bill they are voting for. I assume it's the new one, but I'd like to see it clarified. There's been a fair amount of analysis of the impacts of the original bill, little on the latest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Thankfully mine are all in on this, I call and email them anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet he still won't supply his committee colleagues the information. He just blew any credibility that he had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Separation of powers my ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lieu urged Congress to appoint a special prosecutor and form an independent commission in order to investigate the alleged contacts "with impartiality and independence."

Yes. Please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem rep: 'We must pause the entire Trump agenda' until Russia investigation complete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This story doesn't say, do we even know which bill they are voting on? Does it include changes based on discussions over the last couple of days to make it even worse, or was it the version that was routinely panned earlier? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their supporters seem ok with it. Weird how they can pivot so quickly, Monday leaks were evil, by Wed they were ok as long as they were to Nunes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The # of Americans who have insurance now compared to prior to the ACA makes this clear. I still don't think the ACA was the best thing for the country, but it was a good faith approach to allowing more people access to medical coverage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is, although Bill and Hillary were actually trying to provide coverage. I was so disgusted that the Democrats couldn't pass legislation  while controlling Congress and Executive that I changed my registration to Independent  for the next decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly blow to Trump = Benefit to country. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
