<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4516</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a woman who has suffered/is currently suffering from major depression and an anxiety disorder I kind of find this post insulting. The guy fetishises women's anguish? And you wish to emulate this anguish to try and attract him. Please, tell me if I'm missing something here because I hope I am.

Edit: also, mental illness isn't a sexuality. People who have mental illness have a sexuality sure, as with all people and as with all people theirs is as nuanced and varied as anyone else's. Sometimes their sexuality will be affected by past trauma from abuse or sexual assault, sometimes not. Again, I'm all ears if I'm totally getting this wrong but it is really kind of offensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 07:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a behaviour therapist working with people who have intellectual disability, mental health, survivors of complex trauma and their carers. There is a lot of my practice that goes into my work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am also suffering with major depression at the moment. First thing I did was (after years of it mind you) get a mental health plan and began medication and seeing a psychologist. Then I began practicing magic, meditation and journeying again, began to set up a place of power, that I can draw from both in meditation and in waking hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a little slice of the white marble gravel from High Thira on Santorini, and a piece of smoky quartz, High Thira is a place where I felt tangibly in touch with the spirits of air, and the quartz is something I use when journeying to the higher realms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, the aboriginal cultures of Australia also have a rainbow serpent in their beliefs, which is very similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 05:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Outlander! So good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I immediately thought of the rainbow serpent who is a powerful creator god and possibly the oldest continuing deity or belief on earth. The rainbow serpent is deeply connected with creation, life and seasonal cycles, rain and water, thunder and lightning, blood, circulation and the menstrual cycle. I'm Australian and my power animal is the red belly black snake who I think is an aspect of rainbow serpent and represents ancient knowledge.

I'm not suggesting appealing directly to rainbow serpent, I'm not sure which country you come from, I imagine if you're in France, appealing to rainbow serpent might not do you much good. I just don't know about the cultural appropriation aspect. But maybe look into local indigenous mythology, or the mythology of your own people, you might find a snake god or spirit in your own backyard who will protect your animal companion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Then look for some porn that she might actually like, Erika Lust makes brilliant sexy and romantic hardcore porn, so does Lucie Blush. Or you could have a look at r/chickflixxx 

But no, don't go giving me guarantees of what you imagine romance novels to be like, I'm a woman, I'm currently reading Voltaire's "Candide" and on the side I'm reading a Mills and Boon called "Testing the limits" lol. I consider them stress relief, I have a very full on job. They are absolutely more nuanced than Fabio clones pursuing innocent housewives. Here's a thing, instead of making all these assumptions about your wife, find out what she's into. Maybe reading a couple of romance novels might actually be the key to your current situation.

Edit: my comment about the disconnect between your ideas of a fulfilling relationship had less to do with the porn aspect and more to do with the romance aspect. The fact you make these assumptions without actually finding out what she likes about romance. And let me just add that ALOT of women don't like the idea of porn, I love porn, certain types of porn, but there is a lot of porn out there that is utterly degrading to women and makes me feel quite ill. I have lots of female friends who like porn as well and we share the sites or filmmakers we love, but I also have friends for which it is an absolute no go. No amount of persuasion will change their mind. But yes, women like reading novels with sex in it, but it's is a type of sex that is rarely shown in porn. If you care to find out more, perhaps read Diana Gabaldon's "Outlander" series, that's the kind of sex a lot of women like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supermarket romance novels have sex scenes sure, but the operative word is "romance". Not an awful lot of that in most porn I've seen (apart from xconfessions). I really think there's a disconnect here in your idea of a fulfilling sexual relationship and hers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bunny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 03:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, maybe go back and read my comment when you're feeling a little less emotional about the issue. I'm definitely not "chewing you out". I have in fact been in a very similar situation to the one you describe and I'm merely asking you to look a little deeper than the surface issues in an attempt to figure out a solution. 

For the past few years I had been having issues with my partner, he would rarely initiate and would never reciprocate if I did, making me feel unwanted and undesirable, I gained weight, lost my fitness level, I blamed it all on the lack of sex, I became fixated in the sex I wasn't having. Then I was diagnosed with major depression. It wasn't the lack of sex and feeling undesirable that made me gain the weight, it was that I'd stopped caring about everything, stopped dancing, singing, going to the gym, all the things I had loved and had kept me physically healthy. I was suffering from the effects of personal and vicarious trauma due to the work I do. My mood was very low, I was prone to anxiety attacks and inappropriate emotional reactions. I finally got help, medication and therapy, and now things are starting to normalise, our sex life has returned, we've even done it twice in one day! Unheard of before. It turned out that my moods were affecting him as well. 

I'm not saying that this is the issue, all I'm saying is to look a little deeper and stop playing the games (like the one where you stopped touching her boobs altogether because she asked you not to while the kids are around-which, while it would totally not bother me, is a pretty normal and healthy boundary to draw) Start trying to see things from her perspective. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're young and sound pretty inexperienced with sexuality and porn, it sounds like this risky click has traumatised you somewhat, not surprising given your age. Just breathe, you won't go to jail for something like this, its natural for humans to be aroused by taboo things, this doesn't mean that we all act on our urges, you're fine, you're not a sicko, you just saw something you were a little young to deal with, and actually, I'm much older than you and have had similar reactions to risky clicks like this. You'll be ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a really good point, it really does sound to me that OP is more concerned about their own perception of the situation than about finding out the cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you're playing games with her instead of getting to the root of the problem. Is she depressed? Is there something else going on that makes her lose the confidence to initiate. Things aren't ever going to get better while you are playing these games with her and you could possibly be missing something incredibly vital by just reacting to the surface issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat lots of citrus fruits and strawberries if you can get them, and see if you can find some high strength propolis supplement, it helps with immunity, also a good multi-vitamin, I've heard that the pregnancy or pre-pregnancy ones are the best. If your immunity is low and you're working hard you will pick up everything, try to build up your immunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang in there I'm four sessions into therapy, the last one was a killer and I really thought I had lost my mind for a few days, but it is getting there little by little with the therapy and medication. Feeling much less depressed overall, and a lot less anxiety.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 12:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Don't you fret, M'sieur Marius
I don't feel any pain
A little fall of rain
Can hardly hurt me now
You're here, that's all I need to know
And you will keep me safe
And you will keep me close
And rain will make the flowers grow.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so so so fucking much for writing this. I needed to read this so badly. Thank you for your beautiful words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enthusiastic diner! I love that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm buying the full series now, while still reading Silent Sky. I love it! I loved when Djumbundji was waiting for this famous clever man/warrior and then the clever man turns out to be a woman! So rad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! I loved it! I need to read the whole lot!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been married for years to a guy that likes it, it's completely not niche, in fact I've read somewhere that almost 50% of ladies have larger labia minora, I do get how you feel though, I used to feel like mine were hideous, particularly before I lost my virginity, honestly seeing how appreciated the look is on r/labiagw helped me to accept mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 12:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I do enjoy mine, I'm mid 30's so I've gotten over any misgivings I had before, I just love them, they are a part of me, so close to the heart of me. Love your body, don't ever think you need to be different. The way you are is just incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truganini - I can think of no other woman who completely embodies "nevertheless she persisted"
One of my personal heroes. But I don't k is if her story would be too sad for elementary school kids, I wish I had learned about her in elementary school, but we didn't do much learning about the original custodians of our country back in the 80's.

Edit: for context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks awfully tasty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boo fucking hoo Trumpie, such a snowflake. Worst! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your boobs are exactly the same size and shape as mine and your nipple/areola shape/colour. Are you me? Honestly, your boobs are great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about HIM's "You're sweet 666"? I wanted to have Ville Valo's babies when I was a young whipper-snapper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I first thought! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 04:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 666 is the number of the beast which is some biblical crapola, but It's also a totally kickass song by Iron Maiden which you should probably listen to because it totally rocks like a mofo and Iron Maiden are pretty much the best band ever, but it has nothing to do with Wicca, it just means that your Uber cost that amount.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge closet Mike Oldfield fan and have been using his new album Return to Ommadawn in my rituals recently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father was English and of Norwegian descent, my mum is Aussie and her grandmother was an aboriginal woman. As long as I remember I've had a great reverence for nature and the intricate workings of the universe. I used to walk barefoot through the bush where I lived and animals would approach me as if they were tame, snakes and birds. I get messages in dreams and have been meditating and journeying since I was very young with guidance from my mum. As a teen I began to practice magic as well as yoga and set up a beautiful altar, practiced herb magic and connecting with the spirits of the four directions and other realms. I guess I really began to believe in my power when I started to have premonitions and warnings and the things I got messages about in my dreams and meditations began to always come true. 

For some reason I stopped my practice for some years, probably as I started building my career, but recently the universe is telling me in no uncertain terms that I need to pick it up again. Which I have, and people are noticing. I've been stopped in the street a number of times in the past week, asked if I am a healer, told I have an aura about me. It's like my spirits have rushed to speak through me again. The birds have begun to visit me again and eat from my hands, sit in my shoulders. A koala even visited me!

I guess I'm not really a pagan in the same sense of this subreddit, but I do what I do and it serves me well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One woman I worked with was virtually locked in after a devastating car accident that left her with a severe acquired brain injury, needed a wheelchair, non verbal, she still had movement but no actual control so her body would jerk constantly and she could not do anything for herself. I was convinced that her intelligence and personality was still alive behind her outward appearance and I don't talk to any of my clients as if they are stupid or childlike. It was incredibly frustrating working with her and emotionally draining, as she would cry constantly, but eventually I learned to close my eyes and feel the way. After that I was able to at least feel her acceptance or dissent to certain tasks and give her time or present things differently. Empathy is a very real talent that some people have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I know what that means, I have worked with people in this state, what I am saying is that non-verbal communication does not rely solely on what you can observe visually, but also what can be felt. Call me crazy, I am only speaking from my own experience which is all anyone can ever do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had to comment although it will be buried, she hugged and kissed him as he left like she would have when she was in full control of her brain and faculties, that must count for something? She didn't choose to get dementia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've worked for a large part of my life with people who have severe disabilities and I reckon you can get far more than just a Y or N answer just from being quiet and open and listening and observing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yass! That's what I thought! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 08:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 08:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub has really helped my recovery from major depression  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 10:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bunny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found Rae Beth's book "Hedgewitch: A guide to solitary witchcraft" helpful, I used to dabble in witchcraft as a teen and in my early 20's.  I also used meditation and lucid dreaming from a very young age for relaxation, centering and deep journeys of discovery. Somewhere along the line I lost my practice but never my spirituality. This book helped me figure out what's important to me and how I wish to continue in my practice. It has helped me pull myself out of major depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You go girl. I can empathise with where you are at, I'm currently struggling to get back from major depression and I had a back injury that set me back on my weight loss. You can do it, it may not mean much from an internet stranger but I'm cheering you on from my side of the world!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all about sun and flies and surf and nature. Winding down the old year and celebrating with family on this plane and the next. And it's alway really bloody hot, really really stinking bloody hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww yiissss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we do actually still celebrate Christmas in the height of summer, at least the majority of people do, but I tend to reverse the wheel so that it is more accurate and attuned to the seasons so I celebrate Yule when it is winter, Samhain in the autumn etc, otherwise it doesn't make much sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 13:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having just begun to see a way out of major depression, I'm glad I got help, because in hindsight I can see just how close I was to suicide.
But it was incredibly difficult to get that help, both because I was slightly in denial about how bad things were, but also because a lot of my attempts to talk to friends and family about it were brushed off, I think because I'm usually so bubbly and irrepressible that people simply didn't believe I was serious.

So, I would urge people to keep an eye on even their most fun loving friends, and believe them when they say they're not coping and offer assistance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I'm in the Southern Hemisphere I will be celebrating Lammas rather than Imbolc, and baking a beautiful summer fruit loaf and have a swim in the ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 11:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noted a few poles in my time. Well worth mirin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 11:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the sweatpants. They leave nothing to the imagination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember Maynard James Keenan said in an incident that Madonna could name an album "Bloody cum rag" and people would buy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 11:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a leaf on the wind.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 09:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog used to do that when I tried to bath him, does that mean I'm cruel to animals (I didn't bathe him for like years at a time as a result actually, he never really got dirty or smelly because he would regularly have a swim at the beach) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This gif is exactly what it feels like as well. I started some SNRI's a month ago and started seeing a psychologist, that's helped and I've also begun practicing meditation and magic again and that's really helped. You'll get there when you find the thing you need and are lacking and feed your soul with it. I think we will both get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am also going through this, it takes time, but believe me it gets better little bit by little bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mid thirties and don't dye my hair, don't think I ever will. I have a couple of nice streaks in the front that make me look a little like Rogue from the X-men, I can live with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just recently this is me too, my dead bedroom has really turned around since I started on anti depressants it turns out that I was probably the reason I wasn't getting any </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 08:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend was once nearly raped by emus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 08:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. Once had to jump a dry stone wall to escape a swan and hide behind a horse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 09:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And only in a corkscrew motion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 09:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sacchan is rapid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the packets of pre-cooked rice and quinoa and either add salad and rotisserie chicken or chopped zucchini and tomato and those pre-cooked frozen salmon fillets and heat it all in the work microwave, or make Italian meatballs with baby spinach and zucchini noodles, or make a taco salad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh mate. The other day I was just walking down the office corridor, then it was like I'd been shot in the calf, Charlie horse, I barely had time to say "I'm going down!" Before I hit the deck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could start your own cycling club? Or join some other social group? Do you have Meetup.com in the states? I wish nothing but the best for you mate, it's awful being lonely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in my class but my former creative writing professor at Uni was suspended after punching a male student in the face. 
She was well known to basically hate all men and would wax lyrical about it for ages at a time. I'm a feminist and I'm pretty sure punching much younger and smaller men is not the way to go about tearing down the patriarchy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys are the best. They are playful little buggers and they play pranks on humans and each other, if I had a dollar for every time a sulphur crested cockatoo flew too close to me screeching bloody murder I'd be able to live on the moon in a diamond bungalow. Natures little pranksters. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? That's what it's called, it's called a vulva. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "More youthful"? You mean that how? Like underage?

OP is a goddess and should do whatever she feels comfortable with in her own skin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mate if I could be naked and barefoot all day that is exactly what I would do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 03:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a thing for wrestlers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a cracker that one, me and my mates quote it all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vale Eddie Koiki Mabo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg can we be besties??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you for clarifying, I think the reason why I was so quick to get my defences up is that a lot of men (boys more like it) in other forums like to make this revelation in a very negative way whenever the subject of squirting comes (pun intended) up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 23:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your breasts are perfect. Don't do anything to change them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 23:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a flamingo!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember having to go to bed when big dog went to bed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 00:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What nationality are you?..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 00:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australians must live the closest to our ancestors then since we don't insulate our houses and don't dress for the cold in winter haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Passion.The first time he kissed me we ended up in a storeroom together because he made up a story about some thing he needed and couldn't find and I knew where it was, while I was searching for it, he closed the door behind us and as I turned he just gazed at me. I came up close to give him the thing, he took it out of my hands and placed it on the shelf then we just sort of melted into each other. We had to pretend we were doing something else when someone barged in. We were perfectly matched, our kisses were perfect, from the most passionate, push everything off the table and go at it to the most chaste kiss on the cheek. He would wink at me and stick his chin out and just point to his cheek and I would oblige, or he would wait behind a tree and grab my hand and pull me to him and kiss me passionately. It never went further than that, but the attraction was mutual and it was undeniably strong. It was years ago now and we have gone our separate ways, we are with other people, in different countries, but he still sends me messages like "One day I will come to you - or you will come to me" I doubt it will ever happen but it's nice to know he still thinks of me, and remembers that passion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fairly sure almost all of us girls who squirt when we come know that it has pee in it. It's not a downer and there's no shame in it, in fact I'm mystified as to why you thought it pertinent to bring this up.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this, I was a huge sillypants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some self care ideas would be good, I haven't done it in so long I think I've forgotten how.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Zooboomafoo?? Omg we never got that show in Aus but when I lived in the U.K. I watched it daily, it was like my religion. My favourite was when they had a wolverine on set and it just ran and ran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! Particularly if the joke is sexist or racist or discriminatory in any way. Just don't laugh, better yet call them out on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Means the same in Australia too. Happened to witness this once in my local, guy lost his eye, blood everywhere. Awful stuff. Finished my beer though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't just differ from state to state, there are multiple language groups in each state 
http://www.abc.net.au/indigenous/map/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And growing succulents is cheap easy and super fun! Start there and then get more adventurous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 11:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for caring, it really means a lot to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for asking. I'm doing a bit better, been to see a therapist and the meds are a lot better. I've found that I can't drink alcohol much at all, and I'm still sad and awkward and not feeling much joy but I'm not in nearly as much pain as I was, so it's getting better. Thanks troll, you rock! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
