<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9767</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game is far from dying on any platform. Just have fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That and we'll most likely get the new patch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one? PTR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They released soldier 76's short on a Sunday. It could be any day of the week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soldier 76 short was released on a Sunday. Don't let this guy crush your dreams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely bugfixes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn how many times have they updated it today? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No SR and no comp points  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't have explained it better. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're acting like a fucking prick and need to have a seat. Play on PC and stay on PC. Buying a console isn't a bad decision. Most people can't afford a high end PC. Overwatch actually runs really great on my PS4 and couldn't ask for better. Let people play what they want to play on and don't criticize them for it. 

Also, fuck you.

Toodles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They posted on twitter they're still testing it on the PTR. I'm assuming another week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just ended  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They posted on twitter they're still testing the server browser on PTR. I'm guessing they'll release it all at once sometime this week or next Tuesday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go for the ones that's more noticeable. Mercy's staff is larger so it's distinct when it's golden. Zen's is pretty neat. Mccree's is sick. Some skins on lucio though you hardly notice the gold. This is just me, do what you want though. I already have one for mercy now I can't decide who else to get it for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting very paranoid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to get checked out when my significant other gets home. For the past four nights I've had a fever and sweats. Fever reducers have broken the fever each time I've taken it. Today I wake up with a stiff neck and a fever of 103.9 but my temp is now down to 99.8. I feel a lot better than I did this morning the only thing remaining is the stiff neck and a moderate headache. Also should mention I have swollen glands in my throat. Is it possible I have meningitis? If I had bacterial meningitis would I be getting better or worse?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 03:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a much much easier way to provide a summary instead of the wall of text.

+ Good players will be good, regardless of the heroes they select
+ Bad players will be bad, regardless of the heroes they select
+ A team that consists of good players will defeat a bad team, no matter what their opponents are using.
+ The people who blindly 'believe in the meta' without understanding the reasons why are no different from those trying to conduct a holy war. Period.

You can say shit and still think you're right, have a good one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the server browser was what I was referring to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely would take a quality patch over them just releasing it. I'm just hyped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the chances of us getting the patch tomorrow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only one can hope :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that you have a flair bashing mercy mains is fucking ridiculous. People bought the game, they can play who they want. Any hero can be just as viable as any character. Just because it's not what YOU want them to play doesn't mean they shouldn't play them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still disagree. And we can see by votes on who agrees more with you and I. It's not high elo? It's higher than most. You don't have to be GM and top 500 for it to be considered high elo. Says who by the way? You? I'm not bragging and even masters isn't easy to get to even not playing mercy. She's not outclassed. Not everyone can aim with Ana and not everyone is good at Lucio. Just because it's not what the "pros" play doesn't mean it should be frowned upon playing mercy. Period.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong. Mercy can be very beneficial. I have a 60% win rate with mercy in comp games and I'm in masters. Depends on how good of a mercy you are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably no update today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooner or later yes. He will. Console? They're supposed to balance pc and console different. Of course we don't have as precise aiming, so soldier wrecks almost everything on console.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PTR or live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a new PTR patch. I don't believe we'll be getting anything probably until next week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already posted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will definitely get some sort of nerf. Especially on console. 

Edit: I'm getting downvoted because I'm voicing an opinion? He's getting a nerf. Deal with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say no. I have a feeling some of the hero changes aren't ready. They have a "when it's all ready" policy and bundle it into one patch. That's just my guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Exactly why I downvoted in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't care about it says the guy who opened this post in the first place. Okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can really see that you're an idiot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already posted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was already too late because they've already sent codes out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delete this post mods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already? Didn't think they would do that until tomorrow. I'm in the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for consistent gaming friends! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Hello, I'm Zach. 23. I'm looking for consistent people to play with. I'm a very laid back guy and easy to get along with. I'm very active on PSN. 

I play GTA V and Overwatch mostly. I also have mic and would prefer you do too. I really enjoy conversations, so feel free to talk to and add me! 

PSN: bigheartedboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 07:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean you get a new pair every year? I'd like to know how that works. I have the A40's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Event is over! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got a pop up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's not overpowered. Final.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 10:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for doing this! Happy New year to you! Good luck everyone! Here's to hoping I win!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 06:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you care about trophies, you can get my name is mayo for $0.99. All you have to do is tap X I believe it's 10,000 times and you get a platinum for it. Took me around 25 minutes to platinum the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 06:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I'm on ps4. PlayStation for life. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PS4] Looking for OW buddies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 03:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overwatch, Bloodbourne and Rocket League are must haves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 13:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted to say I appreciate you doing this. It's very kind. I just found out unfortunately that my ps4 has tore up and it's going to cost me dollars to get it fixed from Sony and I just don't have it. Anywho, Happy holidays to you and I hope you have a Merry Christmas!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for consistent gaming buddies! CT USA M22 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I'm looking for consistent people to play with. I'm a very laid back guy and easy to get along with. I'm very active on PSN. 

I play GTA V and Overwatch mostly. I also have mic and would prefer you do too. I really enjoy conversations, so feel free to talk to and add me!

PSN: bigheartedboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh no. Next season starts tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play on my brothers computer but would love a copy for myself on PS4 so I can play with my friends. It's nice of you to do this, even if I don't get picked. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unexpected server error? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else just get this?

Edit: I am on PS4. 

Edit: just let me log back in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 08:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4040 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 09:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for new gaming buddies! CT 22M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I'm looking for consistent people to play with. I'm a very laid back guy and easy to get along with. I'm very active on PSN. 

I play GTA V and Overwatch mostly. I also have mic and would prefer you do too. I really enjoy conversations, so feel free to talk to and add me!

PSN: bigheartedboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS4 patch is live! Version 2.00 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not PSN.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 20:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patch incoming most likely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you fuck off with your negative attitude? If people want to hope, let them hope. Nothing wrong with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 00:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Probably in preparation for new content going live tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 05:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I signed up months ago but didn't get invited :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 12:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would really like a copy. Me and my roommate would like to play together. We're college students and finally have a weekend to relax. If would be really kind if you would allow us to play together. Thank you so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 11:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was very nice of Blizzard to do something like this! I'm looking forward to any reveal from Blizzard. I thoroughly enjoy their games and can't wait to see what's in store. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people who actually like figuring this stuff out. Have a seat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut the fuck up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
