<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7913</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oic, thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't AD unnecessary now, even for solo, with the updated Holy Point Shot quiver? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya, especially if the rest of me was more visible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My eyes are somewhat asymmetrical, but not crossed that I'm aware :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Self-interest, the fact that they are handling something I'm about to ingest, is reason enough to be civil even if human decency proves insufficient.

I wonder how much spit the average asshole customer consumes annually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We gotta find a wizzerd can change em back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

Standard Strathmore white sketch paper toned a medium grey with vine charcoal. Used the vine charcoal and rubber eraser for most of the drawing, added finer detail with hard charcoal pencil and white chalk pencil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually looking for a nice skull   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You, I like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if you asked this in earnest, but you slayed me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I experienced the rare literal "lol" - thx!
Inspired to draw my own weird creature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self portrait from life, charcoal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you e ever tried S2/M2 it's ridiculously tanky, new S6 is similar (but more fun I should think). Also both builds are easy to gear (only 2 daggers possible on rare upgrade for DH). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All my meaningful ideas just kinda show up unannounced. I try to cultivate disciplines and exercises to encourage them and to be ready for them, but they come and go as they please. Sometimes there's too many ideas for me to keep up with, and sometimes nada for months. When I deliberately try to 'be creative' the results are definitely less interesting.

How do you work at creativity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Axe murder is actually fairly rare out here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The better technical skill and craftsmanship you develop the more free you are to discover a unique personal style. You want to be able to produce anything you can imagine. 

Besides, creativity can't really be 'worked at' anyway, so might as well cultivate technique while you wait for the muse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pixies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A suggestion on drawing practice, try starting out with a 'quantity over quality' approach, doing a lot of quick sketches. Trying to fully realize a drawing while your learning is likely to be frustrating and if you don't have a coach to help you it's kind of fruitless. Sketch until you start doing it well and then move on to more completed drawings, sort of like rungs on a ladder.

If you like that idea try vine charcoal. Tone the paper by rubbing in a medium value of vine charcoal, and then you can draw by both using the charcoal and by 'erasing out' the lighter shapes.

Also you'd do well to pick up a drawing instructional book. Most of them are complete garbage (How to Draw Dogs!) but something like Tony Ryder's Figure Drawing can really help you improve dramatically because he guides you in a systematic approach to drawing that you can use on any subject. That's the kind of drawing instruction you get in a good school or atelier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess folks already suggested to retake the photo earlier...but ya try again lol. You want to shoot it straight on, not at an angle because it distorts the image when it's foreshortened like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When drawing from a photo pick one with natural lighting or more dramatic lighting. A lot of modeling/fashion photography uses multiple flashes and flattens everything out (like this one). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kinda buried under a big project with a deadline right now, check me later if you like, I'll be around on here and r/painting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit I wrote like a long response and deleted it on accident lol. So...tldr version. I'm in a similar place, look at other areas of your life you can improve (even seemingly small things) and meanwhile force yourself stay on the grind doing the work. If you work the joy of working will return.

Check out Steven Pressfields (Baggar Vance, Gates of Fire) series on being an artist: The War of Art, Do The Work, and Going Pro. They've been encouraging for me and helped me stay at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's no moon...that's a space station! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What pigments did you use for the neutral greens? I imagine that accents the hands and face more in person than in the photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grazie! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 01:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fantasize about this pretty frequently. I'd do a lot of stuff along the lines of an older person who realizes too late how they could have enjoyed all that freedom more. Like one example: "I didn't have to sit through 4 years of high school?? I could have just taken a test?"

But then I start trying to think how to at some point get back on track to meet my wife and recreate my kids, which seems impossible. Assuming I could find and seduce my wife (likely enough) wouldn't the kids be new and different mixtures of baby batter? Not worth it. I like these ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I know what I'm about son."
Ron Swanson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ya, he definitely padded it a lot lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I appreciate critique - I think a lot of artists delay their development by not encouraging constructive criticism. We have to disconnect our work from our ego to improve it (easier said than done of course) ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I actually agree with the critique but I knew I would ruin it if I fussed with it much more. One of those unexpected challenges with drawing and painting: knowing when to quit while you're ahead ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being sensitive about constructive critique just slows improvement! I appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll gladly pass these instructions on to my wife (not the model). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya it's hard to stay out of that smile/grimace uncanny valley lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 00:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually agree that the texture is a bit 'tortured'. I started with vine charcoal, not really intending to realize it that far, and then when it turned out well I started adding more detail with a hard charcoal pencil. Probably would have been better to stick with vine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charcoal study, prep for painting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking I'll just use a tele staff on switch. I just have to stash up a few million gold lol, those tele charges are crazy $. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Art and Anarchy sounds very interesting, and still relevant definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 2 Sorcs in the mid 80's that I've been playing on 1.14 single player. I use GoMule for shared stash but nothing else. That's not by choice but because I'm stuck on Mac for the time being. I'll definitely switch to Plugy when I can for the Anni Torch option alone. But it's definitely been preferable to Bnet despite the limits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italian Renaissance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any buffs on the Italian Renaissance that can help me put a reading list together for myself? I'm a painter so that's my primary interest, but I'm looking for any stand out works on the general period whether on general history, politics, culture. Any films/docs or excellent historical fiction writing would be welcome too.

Kinda surprised there's no sub for the topic!

Mille grazie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad that we live in an age that has the highest number of humans ever with the relative safety and comfort necessary to reflect, plus almost unlimited access to information and yet most people have no interest in capitalizing on it. Because it is relevant, and people will realize that too late maybe when some horrible philosophy becomes widespread enough and acted on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely agree. I think practically all people use philosophy. It probably has more of a meaningful impact on the lives of those who didn't study it formally because they don't use it as a detached exercise, they use it to set and adjust their way of life. I just wish more people had a better grasp of the science of philosophy and reason, more tools in their box. Education and exposure to information doesn't really increase someone's capacity for thought, but it provides context and a broader horizon. For example, I've often found that people present well-worn ideas as an original thought of their own, just because they have no idea that it's 1,000 years old and not novel or unique to them. They'd be better off with more context, 'here's the first known proponent of that idea and here are 10 arguments in response to it.' Very likely they would have a richer and maybe even different view afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking from the experience of growing up in the US in public school I think it has a lot to do with education. I can count on one hand the number of times in high school I was expected to really think rather than memorize and regurgitate data. 

Whether people are aware of it or not philosophy will always be hugely significant. Everyone forms philosophies constantly, but today most people don't have the tools to step back and evaluate how and why they think the way they do. I think for most people they never will develop that, it is difficult after all, if it isn't prioritized and trained from a young age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh that's a good thought. I have a partly leveled Necro but lost motivation b/c I'm on single player with no Enigma. I have a Bliz for AT but need something for Chaos and WSK (ideally on 8p). I have a Meteorb going but I'm doubtful I can do high player in Hell with only +10 skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw some recommendations that a Treachery Armor / Reapers Toll sythe/ Guilliarms Face helm (spelling?) set-up was cheap and effective. Tried it out and it's been good for me. I also added some IAS with some socketing. The only item in the set that's somewhat rare is the weapon, but I got one off Hell Meph runs.

I use that setup on a Might Merc on both my Bliz and Meteorb Sorcs and he kicks ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best builds for 8P Chaos? Other than the standard Hdin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best build for 8p WSK? Standard Hdin or some others that stand out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like:
Pit - build
Chaos Sanctuary - build
Cows - build 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick Tips on Area-based MF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a sort of build grocery list, like "AT - Bliz Sorc" for all MF areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible the Trump administration is unaware of the existence of Indonesia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you max Fire Mastery? Or same goal of -175%? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mastery Meteorb Sorc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best split of points between Cold and Fire Mastery and why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Third Man, now on Netflix (in US anyway). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy! It's one of the best builds to get started on and learn the game because it's less dependent on gear. Are you playing on bnet? I'd be happy to help you out if you happen to be on US West Ladder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean you can experiment if you want, you get 3 stat/skill resets (1 per difficulty) so you can always change your skills later - but the most efficient summonmancer for later in the game is just skels, a certain kind of A2 merc, and CE. Amp damage is usually all you'll need once your skels are maxed, and Decrepify for bosses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guide is a bit outdated, but no harm done really. You can beat Normal and Nightmare practically naked so don't worry about gear. I would recommend googling "fishymancer guide" for a better guide - basically it's just max skels (skip the mages, they're dead weight in Hell) and maxed corpse explosion, you don't really need more than 1 point in anything else! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually the only really important item you look for in Norm play through is a good wand for summonmancer, you just want to get into Nightmare quick to get better chance of good drops.
How have you spent your skill points so far? Are you following a guide or building blind? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No question, best switch for you is going to be Teleport staff - for positioning your army and concentrating their damage on a specific target. The mobility is secondary. Also FYI, your +skills for summons function only when you cast those summons, so you will not lose your any skels or any power when you swap back and forth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 07:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couple examples of using it: I have a staff with teliport charges on switch whenever I don't have an Enigma, I also use a Life Tap wand on switch often when my Merc is lower level to help him survive. So in short, people use staff/wand on switch to gain spells their class doesn't have. The high-end example is Call of the Ancients that adds Barb shouts to boost health etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Style Mod </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a mod for D2 that allows you to 'transmog' and dye equipment ala D3? That would be sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow just realized Grief is fairly easy to make - but no life leech? Stack that on rest of gear I guess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was thinking, is there any weapon class that is better than others? Maybe swords for phase blades later on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I think hammerdins are considered casters though ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well fuck me huh? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melee Ideas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played quite a few years off and on but always caster types - any suggestions for Barb/Pally/Druid to try out the melee side? Playing single-player so looking for general leveling build + endgame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? TIL, makes me feel better about ole Azrkabahar dying to bosses all the time lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 06:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trav runs meaning just the council? Or clearing the level? What mobs there have an advantage for rune drops? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 06:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lightning Jav skills function as 'spells'? So you have to stack FCR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 06:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to be swapping from a Mac to Windows laptop sometime soon so have been wondering about transferring my Single Player items also, let us know how it goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From playing D3 a few years I definitely find D2's overall gameplay is more enjoyable. Leveling is more enjoyable, endgame is somewhat better, better skill system. I also prefer the art style, just because it's closer to D1's dark style than D3. I'm still somewhat interested in D2's world after all these years and it still has atmosphere, but no one ever cared about D3's story/world... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
