<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9619</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all, and he isn't. They've been switching to green lights for a few years now due to it being easier to make things out when in "night vision" mode. You need way less green light to see than red light to see the same amount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss my 1520 and Cortana, still the best most integrated DA I've had and she was much better at it while still being in Beta. Then MS would break her for a day or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird the incorrect guy got upvoted here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You listed two things, one that Obama didn't help that much because of the bad stuff he did and the second one only made things more expensive for everyone I know except some people that got to ride their parent's insurance longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green is great for preserving night vision since we can pick it up so easily, you only need a small amount of light/candle power to see stuff under a green light, especially compared to red light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really depends on what you categorize as progress though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green light doesn't lose contrast either, and works to preserve night vision, so they're better than the red lights used to preserve night vision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree with that. The real issue in the States is that we spend more on healthcare than if we let the government just run it all. Every family would save a couple of grand even after their taxes were raised to pay for healthcare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the best compensated soldiers

I know what you mean, but you try telling that to a guy living in barracks built in the 50s with no AC and having to buy his own ACUs when they switched over from BDUs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm for disarming the police entirely and have been for years (save a select, better trained, less used few). But I am also for civilians being able to buy more weapons, especially military type, because a fully automatic isn't much different than a gun with a spring loaded trigger that simulates autofire almost perfectly. Not a bump trigger either, that's slightly different and also can replicate full auto pretty well.  
  
I really want 3 round burst mode :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of that also has to do with the drugs. My step mother is a doctor from the UK and she said they prescribe the cheapest drugs, not the most effective or best like in the US. There's a big cost difference there alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most adopt a highway sites offer a service for a fee to clean the highway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. No because all memes sound dumb. But the fact that you and I have never heard it means it isn't much of a meme.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They usually just fall to the side. Keep their knees bent and when they hit they just fall over. That's what my dad was taught in airborne school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BABY HIPPO VS ANGRY ELEPHANT - UGANDA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is my favorite, demonstrates all sort of societal rules: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gHIKCoZmQII </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gHIKCoZmQII </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got one that says "I survived the big bad wolf" that ride was sweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're worried, you can get something like this : https://www.amazon.com/Otis-Tactical-Cleaning-System-Brushes/dp/B0000C52A5  
  
I have one that I can clean every rifle and pistol I own. They easily attach to a strap or molle web platform. As others have pointed out, unless you're in the mud or water (or own a kimber or something that rusts super easy) you shouldn't need to clean, but it's nice to have the ability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly enough, this was one of the major issues with insane asylums here in the US. Thanks Reagan I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once told my Grandma I wanted to join the RCMP and she told me they weren't honorable anymore, this was years and years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought some similar things on amazon, 100 or so and it must have been only a few bucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's with the "X" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They let their guard down? They built the 
[Maginot Line](https://goo.gl/fAf5UG) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know lots of people that laugh at Germany for declaring war on the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a temporary bridge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if it was attacking liberals or progressives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you've never listened to the show, I don't think he presents anything as "journalism". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need to last longer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best costume and stuff like that was deserved throughout though. And that was my issue. Best picture, etc as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That really sucks, yea I remember them saying they'll cover 5 or 10 K in accessories. Sorry they're dicking you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, that's what you pay for insurance for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  RotK won a shit ton of oscars including best picture.

Which sucked because the other 2 should have also won a lot, but the voters and organizers knew that the oscars for those 3 years would be "boring" and didn't, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two things, Joe Rogan says he talks and acts the same in real life, yet AJ said crazy stuff about JR ignoring him and the gov got to him, AJ had the wrong phone number or would hit him up last min for a show.  
  
Second thing, AJ usually says he just reports what he reads and hears and doesn't believe it all. So... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I've read articles about it, people masturbate too much and with way too strong of a squeeze, so normal sex doesn't feel right because they've gone too hard on their dicks and they can't cum from sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your story friend, I've had bad experiences as well with their insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least they don't force you to do all that, then go "Oh you need to use the mobile site instead because we hate that you claimed bankruptcy on and got out of paying us 3 grand, log in every same answer again" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  if you don't need them, you'll never be let down.

Yea and when you do it can be a pain in the ass using a service shop they recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different cards for different people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  mailed me a $1,500 check for no reason.

No, they did it because you put a claim in but didn't get it fixed. Same thing happened to me and my 1987 Blue Mustang LX Convertible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mayo Clinic researchers demonstrate value of second opinions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double that of the previous republican candidate, those are big gains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a friend, good price on 30 round Glock mags. He's got 40 cal Glock gen 2 so anything newer should work as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author of this blog whom hates Donald Trump, says he's not. http://slatestarcodex.com/2016/11/16/you-are-still-crying-wolf/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things like snoopsnoo and people that go through you comment history without reading the context to try to have who you are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 11:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about when they block of some city streets. The best rally racing has multiple surfaces in one race. You'd take that turn as part of the circuit. Go off an exit. Through surface streets. Then through a farm road. Then on some gravel if available. You cover it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/TvZXKnmNAZE
 Shinobi [PS2] [Gameplay] [PCSX2] - YouTube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are so many good places to do it to. So many highways to block for an hour so cars can fly through sideways on the perfect exit ramp going from 15 north to I-70 east bound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ever play Shinobi on PS2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know if it works for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Affleck across from Mark. It would be amazing. They're comparably the right ages/looks for an older darker rivalry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to log out. I have my laptop set up with two monitors and the laptop being the right side monitor. If you just disconnect it, it freaks out. Same when you plug it in. But if you log out it should be smooth. Sucky solution I know. Maybe even going to the lock screen could help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I owned that once on VHS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wowza. Entry please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the United States, mandatory retirement policies are actually illegal for most professions, though thats only been true fairly recently. In the early 1970s, about half of all Americans were covered by mandatory-retirement provisions requiring they leave their jobs no later than a certain age, usually 65. In 1986, Congress abolished mandatory retirement by amending the Age Discrimination in Employment Act

A few fields, however, are exceptions. Certain occupations that are either too perilous  such as military service or federal law enforcement agencies  and others that demand high levels of physical and mental skill (like air traffic controllers and commercial pilots) generally still have mandatory retirement policies. Some large and mid-size accounting firms also require their partners to retire at a certain age. (My editor's CPA was forced out due to his age not long ago, despite being perfectly competent.) And many states require judges to retire at 70 , 72 or 75.

https://www.forbes.com/sites/nextavenue/2015/08/02/is-it-time-to-abolish-mandatory-retirement/#5b4bde4f40db </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But with shipping I can go to some local store near me and get it, cause you know I'm in Texas and they're also charging tax, really kills this deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said whether he was right or wrong, I just pointed out why u/Nathan346 mentioned single soldier housing since u/smegdawg asked why it was relevant, all because u/sub_zero23 mentioned it in his post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shipping really kills this deal... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A single person in SD will be getting at least $1200 a month for housing, 

u/sub_zero23 mentioned it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was the girl from Stick it and the Reaper, and some Canadian cop shoe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea man. Just go out with them. At most by the second date you're fucking and you may have had some FaceTime sexing before that second date.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, but it makes since what this group is doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you hear this from? Kinda makes sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. Need to "disable" my car later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the rest of the windows are uncovered even the windshield.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh. Joker? Not talking about a wrecked car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do you put a T-shirt or towel in the door/window of a broken down car on the highway? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people put T-shirts or towles in the door or window of broken down vehicles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what this is about. They aren't going to jail for simply being here. Harboring can be done by citizens as well. The idea behind enforcement of laws is not only to punish the offender but to also keep people from committing the same crimes.  
  
We already pay for these prisons and these prosecutors salaries and for the courts and judges, you're "paying through the teeth" right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sub cred? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do. But they want to fuck on the first date.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just scroll up and read my other comments to you, and also still funny that you're so sad about losing. This convo is done since it's so obvious you lost that you're trying to attack me instead. Peace out, good luck being a fool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted the KARMA, baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's very funny how consistently wrong you have been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they all act like they want a relationship and shit, but they just want to fuck and maybe date. People are lonely thanks to the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find me those examples then, because I've never seen it upheld very far into court processes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my doubts it was so simple, I have no love for the cops, but they rarely if ever blindly attack someone. Usually there is some sort of build up, right or wrong of the actions taken, it isn't just a random choice of assault by the cop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One, people hardly ever stop to help anyone ever, so lets throw that away as reality. Two, it's all about intent, you wouldn't go to a trial and lose that case.  
  
Onto the harboring, smuggling last I checked was a separate crime from harboring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The funniest part is that article at the end tries to recover and back up your incorrect claims, while the author of the research that the article is about refutes it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he beat it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he beat it last I checked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still applies, they don't go to prison for just being illegal. Maybe a detention center that granted, sucks, but still not technically jail or prison. Harboring and encouraging is a different crime than being an illegal immigrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I've never had any problems with amazon with a non-working part or anything and them sending out a new one or refunding my money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Try to tell that to prospective jurors and you're likely to see jail time using Trumped up charges.

HAHA a funny, yet untrue and if you do it's lawsuit time, so either way a win.  
  
Someone was jailed for jaywalking in Sacramento a couple days ago. The charge was resisting arrest, although that was later dropped when people released footage of the officer dropping the suspect to the ground in the middle of the street before punching him.  
  
So not for jaywalking exactly, got it.  
  
I don't misunderstand mass incarceration. It's you who seem to want to jail those 'undesirable' to you. Did you go to the Spicer School of Communication?  
  
Read the article, I can tell you didn't because you would have said something else.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Merchants_of_Doubt_(film) or watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I took a cue from the POTUS, I don't pay taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried, reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here, read this: http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2017/04/10/how-we-misunderstand-mass-incarceration  
  
Jaywalking is a fine, not jail time FYI.  
  
So is the snake leash pet thing.  
  
All laws are subject to jury nullification despite what judges and others try to tell you last I checked in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All federal prosecutors, Sessions said in his slow Alabama drawl, must now **consider** bringing cases against people suspected of the transportation or harboring of aliens.   
  
Seems like the discretion is still there to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then don't pay your taxes :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screw those gals, you were going home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and it still runs.

That's what I want proof of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems par for the course to stack on the charges with any prosecution I've heard of. People do all sorts of illegal things that cost them their families and their freedoms. I have no sympathy for prosecutors, they can quit their job if they think it's so horrible. But just because someone wants to make their lives better doesn't mean you can break the law without repercussions. Yes immigration from Central and South America is stifled with problems of bribery and such just to get here legally, but that doesn't change the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much and what kinds of poison gases were used during WWII on soldiers/sailors/civilian pops not in concentration camps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Proof? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, fuck them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Redditor hoping for gold makes bland comment" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 25%, a bonus usually isn't anywhere close to 25% of your income, and if it happens yearly or quarterly your month to month fluctuation still isn't 25%. A quarter of your income changes month to month is volatile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought an adapter set a while back because I would switch between two or three phones that all had different sim sizes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what has he released lately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with the link for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If that's "highly unstable", they have a funny view of the word. A single bonus or customer invoice payment could be "highly unstable", not to mention simple overtime.
  
You clearly didn't read the article: "As employment in the service and retail sectors has grown, and dynamic staffing policies have spread, more workers depend on income from commissions, tips, and hourly work with fluctuating schedules." Your "insight" isn't very insightful.  
  
And the author is an NYU professor.
What did they think? Everybody got the same income and expenses every month?  
  
They tracked and reported, what do you want them to say? Also the frequency and volatility matched their income volatility which may have been surprising, rather than having smaller expense volatility.  
  
Also, there are lots of jobs where people do have the same income month after month and depending on where and how you live your expenses might not change. The percentages and wide swings are what's important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One veteran federal prosecutor told The Daily Beast these changes are a generating significant concern.  
  
Its fucking horrifying, the prosecutor said. Its totally horrifying and were all terrified about it, and we dont know what to do.  

The things they want us to do are so horrifyingthey want to do harboring cases of three or more people, the prosecutor continued. So if youre illegal and you bring your family over, then youre harboring your kid and your wife, and you can go to jail.  
  
I mean, harboring/encouraging illegal immigrants is a crime in the US. Don't know why it's so horrifying to prosecute it, I'd like to know which prosecutor said it so we can look at his record of what crimes he's prosecuted though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love his job, yelling "Fake news! Get out of my press room!" at CNN and MSNBC is a dream job. Not comparing Assad to Hitler (as a better person) seems like an easy thing to avoid.  
  
Seriously, should I watch his report, do it better than Spicer while recording myself and then tweet it to Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHA, why would the EU want to stop selling guns to one of it's biggest customers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't want to wife a cheap prostitute? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhh, most of the US is under 18 for age of consent. FYI! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone I've ever met off of Tinder or Bumble wants to fuck. To be fair, I have been told I'm good looking for a big (fat) guy, so YMMV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you didn't post a link or a message or nothing??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ROADTRIP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just proving you wrong at least twice, friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be technically correct, Sanders wasn't an alternative to Trump. I know because I voted for Sanders in the primary, but couldn't vote for him in the general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man. Where do I post the screen shots?  
  
She sent me messages all desperate. I replied back "anal?" and waited. When I said"ok no anal" she was in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BS. I've gotten on not one but two international fights in the same week with less than 30 min before takeoff and had luggage that got stowed. With an accompanying passenger both times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's marked not safe for work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't pay her lol. I wouldn't fuck her either. Cheated on my roommate with at least 5 dudes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A girl that used to date my roommate hit me up for money, $200. I told her I was only interested in sex, guns, and collateral. She said she didn't have any guns or collateral. Got her to agree to sex for as long as I wanted for $200. All my roommates and friends were laughing at her for agreeing to be a prostitute. She's a coke addict nowadays and we figured that's why she wanted the money. She gave me some BS story about car insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot, but you're not close to me unfortunately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll toss out $300 to start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty nice looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the shotgun, but you're asking what I can get for it new without a sale. If you want to drop the price I'm looking to buy a decent pump and I'm only a few hours from York. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know when you have some pics, I'm interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd just go for it, but I'm an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she's trapped? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spyware firms in breach of global sanctions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exclusive: Spyware firms in breach of global sanctions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is as far as I can tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure when I was there a couple years back I looked at the map as I bought my outer Banks beach permit and you could still make it back to VA from the northern part of the beach in NC. Not the whole thing, but you can make it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. There aren't enough for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just watched it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that. But you should have your representatives move to decriminalize it instead of fucking yourselves over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably did. And then they moved on. And then while holstering the firearm he discharged it. He fucked up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends how you're trying to categorize them.  
  
Cheney is clearly the smartest and most evil of them. But he did his stuff to make himself and his friends more wealthy. He wasn't just bought and paid for like the other two.  
  
That's the biggest thing I think why we didn't mind having a dumb president like Bush. We knew he could run a state and we knew he would have at least smart guys on his staff with lots of government experience. And it was just after the fun peaceful 90s, more or less.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ohio one would have made it so only large corporations could sell it. They wanted one where regular people could make money from it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's "pew" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shoot live ammunition while training.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as he hasn't been to a strip club he might do pretty well in the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F that. They wanted everyone to get more and more fuel efficient cars. They should have understood the ramifications on gas taxes. Large trucks tear up the roads, why should I subsidize their damage to the road any longer? Large trucks should bear the burden of road repairs instead of making everyone pay for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understood that reference (but I won't link the appropriate gif with Chris Evans). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://houston.cbslocal.com/2011/06/16/greedy-woman-steals-ball-from-little-girl/ Don't worry the little girl made out ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://houston.cbslocal.com/2011/06/16/greedy-woman-steals-ball-from-little-girl/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually you should be doing some distance looking instead of reading or anything else close up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Employee Burnout Is a Problem with the Company, Not the Person </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you get it cheaper elsewhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do your ammo sales taxes in your state not go to the public land? In MD they do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a blaze orange hat on clearance for $1.75 with free shipping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 19.6 cents a round is pretty good. Look around and see if you can find it cheaper with shipping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magtech Sport Ammunition 9mm Luger 115 Grain Full Metal Jacket $179.99 or $0.18/rnd 1000 rounds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting a link to some .18 cent. Now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you tempt me so, you son of a bitch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this website just for MIL/LE/etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why people downvoted you, it was back in stock when I looked as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says available </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of these people would have remained quiet in line though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the other ones op posted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never thought of that. Offer em $60.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll probably show up on the government auction site. You need to be an ffl to bid though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so wonderful that quality 308 has been so cheap this month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 12:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one of these. But I bought it for like $180 bucks. This is much too high considering how often it's in that range.  
  
Also mine is pretty good, on target and my friend and I used it to play PIG.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need commission lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's Zelda! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://goo.gl/fyfVfZ
Scientists Discover How to Identify People From 'Anonymous ... - Wired
https://goo.gl/koyrX9
You are not as anonymous as you think online: Hiding online is ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prvi PPU 308 Winchester Match Ammunition PP321 168 Grain Hollow Point Boat Tail 20 Rounds $14.85 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, when I said this post I meant the reddit post not his linked one. Ppu is a Serbian bullet. What kind of accuracy were you getting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just providing data on the 168. I didn't mention the 180 because it wasn't relevant. The 168 is faster than the 175, offers less recoil and is flatter in those shorter yards as well if I recall correctly. So with the shorter flight time and less recoil people perform better with it. In reality you should probably shoot both types.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I can find this is good ammo. Good find you should post it, or I will ;)  
  
Also this posted bullet is the Sierra Matchking bullet and the PPU cases apparently aren't the best and some people get a few FTC with them. Other than that I might buy some of these as my cheaper target/hunting and save my Federal.  
  
This ammo is also 175 gr vs the 168 PPU in your link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://rifleshooter.com/2014/12/308-winchester-7-62x51mm-nato-barrel-length-versus-velocity-28-to-16-5/  
  
That link is for data. But 168 gr 308 ammo will stay supersonic at 1,000 yards out of almost any barrel. The longer the barrel the faster it'll be at 1,000 yards. Other bramds ammo might drop out of subsonic around 900 yards according to other people I've read online, but I have seen no data for this.  
  
Your biggest issue will be with down range wind, the 168 gr will move more in the wind. But 168 performs better sub 800 yards. Especially at the 300 and 600 ranges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you lived in reality you'd see that people in power don't really care about the people. They care about staying in power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, good luck! And let me know after you count it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean almost everyone in every country. OK  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got 400 from the last two times 168 grain was on sale at a different site or I would have bought some too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't see the forest for the trees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah the ICC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He went to jail already, evasion failed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the one saying it causes problems with the population.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In r/gunsforsale people will sell ammo. How much are you looking to sell it for with shipping? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in MD and usually it's UPS delivering it to my door.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany seems fine. Japan is doing well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would cost me more than I got 168 from two sales here even with shipping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are they not? Their work supplies the military in some capacity, their government is running the war, their families are the soldiers. You can find some isolated examples of people outside of the countries politics or military or business and tax infrastructure, but that's the exception. You can try to argue a school or hospital but they're healing enemies or enemy support and they're educating them with their propaganda, but it feels like a shitty move. It stops wars sooner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a good price on a Springfield XD 9mm barrel. I've got it in 40. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your objection was that civilians are not targets. They have been since the Napoleonic Wars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $17.99 Federal 308 Win Gold Medal GM308M2 175gr Sierra Matchking BTHP Match 20 Rounds - Heavier grain than the last sales of this ammo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Armies don't go to war against other armies anymore. And really since Napoleon introduced the concept of an entire population supporting the army we really haven't stopped having total war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stell cas is garbage along with the light grains in your link.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Still, though." what? Cause it's a lighter round people are complaining on the price? 308 costs more, 30-06 too. Lots of us shoot those rounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called total war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't have the mexican stuff in 1 litre bottles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's considered a good price on 8mm mauser ammo? Brass in case I need to start reloading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. The glass bottle from Mexico on sale is a buck usually. $12 for a dozen but I can definitely get 12 American cans for less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blowing up civilians isn't a war crime. It wasn't when Truman dropped the bomb. It wasn't when FDR was president and Eisenhower bombed German cities. And it wouldn't have been during the Korean War either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be very incorrect. We have nukes small enough to only take out a city block sized area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know who says that unless they're the idiots I argued with in r/politics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they didn't have a supply for a war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know how many nukes we set off? We had a very blas attitude towards nukes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
