<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9117</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not true...your interpretation of the data is inaccurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nowhere does it say it is a cure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "To our knowledge, this study is the first to demonstrate the effective
excision of HIV-1 proviral DNA from the host genome in pre-clinical
animal models using saCas9 and multiplex sgRNAs delivered by an
all-in-one AAV-DJ/8 vector."

It's kind of difficult to have HIV infection if there is no viral DNA to replicate and make more virus
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  as shown in Figures 4 and 5. So, saying that it "eliminated HIV-1 infection" is way overstated.

Actually, the title says eliminates..which it does, it does not say completely eliminates. You pulled it over semantics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is definitely as awesome as it sounds, from a technology standpoint. it will be some time before we will see it in practical use curing disease..but most scientists believe it's only a matter of time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theoretically yes. But there still remain a lot of practical obstacles.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a former malaria researcher, I can tell you it is VERY hard ;)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to take a number of years..but its getting there. CRISPR clinical trials for other diseases like cancer are set to begin this summer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anything, they would try to use CRISPR to make more deadly biological weapons..but it's certainly not easy. Saying its a massive threat to humanity is a bit if an overreach ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a cure yet....but it's certainly a step in the right direction. The work was done in mice..but what are called humanized mice..in which their immune systems are reconstituted with human immune cells...making it a much more biologically relevant model. That being said, it still needs to be tested on humans.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, as of yet there haven't been any reports of CRISPR mutations and/or resistance. It's probably due to the fact that those pieces of DNA don't last very long..they do their job and then the cell will usually degrade the excess DNA  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It certainly not out of the realm of possibility....however, researchers are jus beginning to understand the molecular mechanisms surrounding CRISPR technology...so I think that level of understanding is still a ways off.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The researchers used transgenic mice that allow them to be infected by the HIV virus...a well-established animal model for HIV research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/IjHUeOM.png
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
