<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1178</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the witcher? It sounds like a job "
'what do you do?' 'I'm a witcher mate - you know, making witches' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Precisely. Ah well. Anything planned for your weekend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 13:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working every night this weekend then off Monday. 3 12 hour shifts in a row next week! Fucking bastards! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sitting in bed eating chocolate biscuits. Hooray for being an adult! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 12:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooft. That sounds sexy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 12:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of ice cream? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 12:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a cinnamon swirl as big as my head. And a pain au chocolat... Cos I'm a fat bastard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 11:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But don't you get to eat all the ice cream you could ever want? And no one will ever tell you off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 10:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than insurance for my phone I don't... I'll look into it. Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 10:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hooray for your own space! I am so sick of flatmates. Where you moving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doing grown up things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 01:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Thursday I move into a new flat where it will be just myself for the first time ever! Well until my girlfriend moves in at the end of July. I'm having a minor panic about doing all the grown up stuff like buying crockery and setting up my electricity provider and such. I'm really more worried that I'll forget something absolutely crucial and pay a horrendous price to get whatever said fuck-up is. Any advice on how to be a grown up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Designed by the sharpest tools in the shed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 19:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We make a peach version at work.

1 scoop each, chamomile tea, breakfast tea, peach tea and a spoon of citric acid brewed in about a litre of hot water turn into a 1:1 syrup.

The syrup gets topped with soda in individual bottles with 10ml of rinquinquin peach vermouth per bottle. Then served with a measure of makers in a highball on ice.

Super tasty and refreshing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 12:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is going on in that?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 01:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not bad pubs as such, but the dome is all about turnover rather than customer experience thus the fancy wetherspoons comparison.

Aye - quite odd but interesting concept food and drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 01:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye, it's owned by Caledonian heritable. As soulless as pubco's get - they even dabbled in the arms trade at one point I think... Timberyard is a much better shout. The food can be a little out there but it's really cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 23:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fairly heavy handed with it but I wouldn't want the whole sauce to taste like that so it's an as you go adding of the mustard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody's seen the Tennants ad.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! June 15th 2015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 14:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Bartender/Waiter in a fancy cocktail place. Thinking of changing that, though I don't know what too.

Fry off some streaky smoky bacon then put aside.
Cook some flour in butter then add milk slowly to make a smooth white sauce and chuck in Mature Cheddar to make it a cheese sauce (don't forget to salt n' pepper). Combine with your cooked macaroni. Add bacon. Place half the pasta into a baking dish and liberally apply chunks of Brie and Gruyere. Cover with the rest of the pasta then sprinkle a whole bunch of mozzarella over the top. Bake until crispy on top. Taste sensations ensue. 

It's all about Kim Philby, essentially the biggest fuck up of Britain during the Cold War was allowing Mr Philby to rise to prominence as he was a soviet double agent. It's a great little look at his life and the secret service at that time in general.

Aye - Spain. She's moving to Scotland in July though, cannae wait!

Nae vodka for me, I'm more of a whisky kinda guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 14:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working all weekend unfortunately...

Nothing hilarious this week so far at work, just the usual.

I made a 4 cheese macaroni with bacon a few days ago that was hella good. All the cheese.

Been listening to a lot of old style English folk. Peter Bellamy, The Waterstons etc

Just finished a book on Kim Philby called "A Spy Among Friends" by Ben Macintyre. Pretty good if you like all the cloak and dagger history.

First thing would be a plane ticket to Spain to see my girlfriend. Then multiple shiny trinkets probably, I'm terrible with money...

Just been on holiday so it's a diet of bread and water for me now. Ah well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 12:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd agree with you on everything except the dome, whilst it looks great it's really just a glorified Wetherspoons. If you are looking for somewhere "a bit special" then Timberyard is a much better bet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 12:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edinburgh,Scotland - Bramble, The Last Word, Panda   Sons, The Devils Advocate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 12:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civerinos at hunters square does a mean pizza. Well worth checking out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 23:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies in advance if the formatting on this is terrible, on my phone and lazy.

- [Al dente means with a bit of bite left, commonly used to refer to pasta. Literally " too the tooth".](/spoiler)

-[Au jus means served with its own juices.](/spoiler)

- [kebabs. Or skewers with stuff on em as they are known in my house.](/spoiler)

- [to deglaze a pan is to dissolve all the crispy bits left over from cooking meat in a pan with a liquid to make a sauce. It's sexy.](/spoiler)

- [mise en place literally everything in place, it's one of the principal tenets of both good chefs and bar tenders.](/spoiler)

- [searing.](/spoiler) 

- [fuck all. they're both an application of direct heat. Just the yanks getting it wrong again. (Unless you are meaning grilling like BBQing but that's a different matter)](/spoiler)

- [does a Bain-Marie count? If not probably stewing.](/spoiler)

- [blanching or flash frying depending if it's water or oil you are using.](/spoiler)

-[dry heat because oil don't like water.](/spoiler)

- [mirepoix is onion carrots and celery at a 2:1:1 ratio](/spoiler)

- [Bechamel, Espagnole, Hollandaise, tomato, Velout](/spoiler)

- [Jus is reduced and gravy isn't? Not sure. Jus is saltier? Although I think that's just the chef I work with being a bit shit.](/spoiler)

- [Chicken, Vegetable, Fish, beef](/spoiler)

- [Rare. Bloody. Still mooing.](/spoiler)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 11:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a good balance though. Made any cool discovery's recently? Or toasted any undergrads over a Bunsen Burner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 11:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shift work is different but honestly I would kill to go back to a 9 to 5. My shifts change every week, long long day's with little break (that's just hospitality though), never 2 days off in a row... Interesting? Sure, if you're a masochist. What's it like working in London? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 01:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ that's a bastard man... Holiday should be good though, clear your head and all that. What is it you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back to work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 23:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started back to work today after a stupid amount of time on holiday. Was struck by all the things I'd forgotten I loved about my job and all the things I really hate about my job. I mean really hate. Blurgh. Well at least the 12 hour shift was only 10 I suppose... Anybody else love/hate their job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edinburgh by Numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 23:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Madrid Airport smokers know what's up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 13:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 20:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. Am fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the hipstery apartment is awesome. Found it on wimdu from a company called the blue house. Lunch at Mercado de ribiera (a foodie market), a trip to the archeological museum in an old ruined church, pastela de nata at the first place to make them (the queue is worth it). Drinks watching the sun go down at Park (a rooftop bar on top of a car park) and dinner with live Fado music at Mascote de Atalaia. All of that was awesome and that was just yesterday. So yes, go. So much to do and see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The exploding olives were amazingly mental - definitely not do it at home cookery. We're staying in this dead hipstery self catering apartment right next to the funicular railway in the old town. Beautiful area and cheap as chips. 10/10 would holiday again 11/10 with rice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those devilish tarts will be the death of me... I've eaten so many all ready it's actually grotesque. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankfully I've been able to save up a chunk of cash by not spending my tips from work, which over the past few months turns out to have been a fair bit. Full belly and light pockets suits me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 20:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No such thing - I'm basking like a fat lizard in this heat, bloody marvellous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lisbon is beautiful... Just so you know... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 12:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much the title. On holiday with the lady. Went to a a restaurant last night and had cod with "exploding olives". Olives that had been turned into a liquid then sphereified, so when you bit them they exploded in an olivey goodness. Going to a 2 Michelin star place tomorrow for the lady's birthday too. I am going to be a fat fuck by the time I'm done here. How's everyone else's week so far? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 10:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call your councillor! They have more sway than petitions and can actually get shit done. It's a 5 minute call max. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 01:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article states "absolutely not fit to print" and I would agree. The author claims that in 2008 bartenders started muddling fruit into their old fashioneds. False. This Is a drink called a Wisconsin old fashioned that has been around since at least the 1980's. He also claims that water should be added to your old fashioned. False. No soda nor water need be added, the dilution from stirring with ice is more than enough. Shit article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 01:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also - cheers for formatting it properly, it looks fine on mobile haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 01:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you liked - check out "One Cigarette" by him as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 17:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were never strawberries
like the ones we had
that sultry afternoon
sitting on the step
of the open french window
facing each other
your knees held in mine
the blue plates in our laps
the strawberries glistening
in the hot sunlight
we dipped them in sugar
looking at each other
not hurrying the feast
for one to come
the empty plates
laid on the stone together
with the two forks crossed
and I bent towards you
sweet in that air
in my arms
abandoned like a child
from your eager mouth
the taste of strawberries
in my memory
lean back again
let me love you

let the sun beat
on our forgetfulness
one hour of all
the heat intense
and summer lightning
on the Kilpatrick hills

let the storm wash the plates


Strawberries by Edwin Morgan

I love poetry - slam, rhyme, sonnet, anything and everything. Really into Edwin Morgan and Norman Mccaig at the moment brilliant scots poets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 15:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weesht! Or I'll set "The Sturgeon" on ya! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 15:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NPR is American but is very well produced and just all round fantastic radio. Not one of the colonials maybe it's because as a Scot I feel empathy with my repressed colonial brethren haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 13:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically they have a mobile recording booth they drive around the US. They record people sharing things that have happened to them, 2 family members interviewing each other etc. Oral History in the vein of Studs Terkel (interesting man). This is my favourite " Danny and Annie"  https://youtu.be/WNfvuJr9164 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 13:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Radiolab from NPR, Serial (worth a listen even if no more episodes are available), StoryCorp, Philosophy Bites, Infinite Monkey Cage, Mark Kermode   Simon Mayo's film review, The Listening Project, and pretty much all the comedy from Radio 4. I highly recommend checking out StoryCorps video series on YouTube as well, although I will warn you to expect all the feels with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 13:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree with you on the asking people to leave thing. Where I work at the moment has an incredible tolerance for people's bullshit just because it's "fancy". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 18:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commenting for flair... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 16:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually any spoiled ballots have to be shown to all those standing for election in the constituency, so they Can agree that it is a spoiled ballot, not just an error. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 01:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try blind taste testing a few different brands (a mix of small brands and bigger) and see if you can tell the difference. I honestly thought it wouldn't be much until recently. Vodka tasting? Nah bet that'll be shite. It was awesome actually, vodkas that have apple notes, caramels, spice, butterscotch, lemons, pepper etc without being flavoured. Really cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 13:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent - that's super interesting, thanks! Do you have any more info on this? I'd love to learn more about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 12:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Furthermore, the Union appeared  particularly later in the war, and particularly among European revolutionaries  to be fighting to end slavery, even if American diplomats and most Americans would not admit that until the last two years of the war. "
Ok this is all news to me - I was under the impression that the narrative of the civil war was entirely about slavery? Are you saying that initially other reasons were used to justify the civil war? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 17:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Look, I've never had a dream in my life / Because a dream is what you wanna do, but still haven't pursued / I knew what I wanted and did it till it was done / So I've been the dream that I wanted to be since day one!"

No Regrets - Aesop Rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 11:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Test Icicles were fairly popular in the UK for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 22:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bar I work in (Devils Advocate) is that end and is a popular after work drinking place on Friday. Maybe not the best if you like a) having a seat or b) paying less than 4.40 for a pint... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed - it's just that wee bit far from the centre is all. Absolutely love 3 birds though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 14:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Apiary in Newington is excellent, friendly staff, great food. Or the Bon Vivant on thistle street, it won the best bar/restaurant award at the spirited awards last year which are basically the hospitality industry Oscars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 20:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommend asking this question in /r/askhistorians as well, I'm sure someone there will be able to give a detailed answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 22:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The city art centre and the all of the council museums run free activities for kids - might be worth checking out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
