<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But at least that 14 year old can grow up knowing how cyber-tough he really is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wholly agree with you.  But, I can understand how/why people want to be lazy and take shortcuts.  I don't agree with it, and I sure as hell won't accept it.  But I do understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that... And I know how tedious it can be to actually, you know, do your job.  But that's why we get this new thing called a pay check.  I understand people taking shortcuts.  Don't necessarily agree with it.  But I understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who read it, "in-fur-iate" instead of "in-fyur-iate?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The patient was involved in a bad car accident after being shot in the past.  He's really paralyzed from the waist down, legitimately, and unable to walk.

I brought this up to my coworker's attention.  They tried to justify it by saying they had the observation logs labeled incorrectly, and were looking at the wrong log/person.

I reviewed all of the logs, and every log stated someone was walking at some point.  They were unable to show me which log they thought belonged to the paralyzed patient...

So... we'll see how this goes when the supervisors and ethics board find out.  I hate being the one known for snitching on coworkers, but damn.  I ain't about to get sued or fired for knowing some shit and not reporting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have called before.  I was able to get the local agency to start a "Silent Sentry" program in which they randomly park unoccupied vehicles in various locations around residential neighborhoods.  They're usually parked near stop signs where people frequently fail to stop, and collisions occur.

Sometimes they park them mid-block to help with speed control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As part of our mental health treatment, we have to keep logs of patient activities. This was surprising. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, Macron won the election with less than 30% of public support... But, he still won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bet that guy didn't speed through that area again, did he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But... But... But the public is harmed... Because naturally the telecom monopolies will have to increase their prices to compensate for little Johnny downloading a TV show that's available on demand with the same monthly subscription through which he receives his internet connection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  It's part of the study, and is listed in the conclusion:

"The contributing factors identified were (1) the singular narrative that portrays the officer involved as guilty in traditional and social media and the subject as the victim"

There were other contributing factor, but the most common (and listed at the top of the list), was this ^

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scraping by.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact you're biased against cops you've never met makes about as much sense as anyone for being racist or biased against someone due to the color of their skin.

Fortunately,law enforcement officers being intentionally targeted, murdered, or feloniously killed in the line of duty at a very low/rare rate.  Therefore, there is not a very large sample of incidents on which to do a case study.  And considering this was done for only one year makes the sample even smaller.

The fact command staff was interviewed does not take away from "study" aspect of this, as this study does include data/facts as well as suspect statements as to why they did whatever they did.  This is in addition to any anecdotal information provided by command staff or officers who were interviewed.

But thanks for resorting to personal insults and showing me how smart you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is me, because I live in the S.F. Bay Area. And $80,000 for a family of 4 is low income. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't read the conclusion, did you?

"The contributing factors identified were (1) the singular narrative that portrays the officer involved as guilty in traditional and social media and the subject as the victim"

There were other contributing factor, but the most common (and listed at the top of the list), was this ^^^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's hard enough to get a sleeping kid out of the car without the neighbor's "help." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally understand being skeptical.  And I'm, unfortunately, aware of the FBI's disgraceful history with regards to the civil rights movement.  I'm still amazed the FBI was able to get wiretap authorization based on no probable cause, and barely a paragraph.

I also know many people are biased against law enforcement with little to no regard for the law enforcement officer as an individual.  You, obviously, are biased against me without knowing anything about me, except that I portrayed myself to be a police officer (which may or may not actually be true), and may not even be current information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, how does that make me biased in this situation?  Posting a report of an FBI study with no editorial comments is somehow biased?

Everyone in the history of ever has some bias regarding something.  Many can put those biases to the side while they evaluate facts, listen to opinions, and come up with their own decision.  Some people, unfortunately, cannot be open minded, and refuse to reevaluate their own positions despite being presented with new facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them.  Not all of them cited Black Lives matter specifically, although some did.  All of the cases in this study showed, at the very least, the suspects "believed attacking police officers was their way to get justice..."

Despite the fact the officers who were targeted were, obviously, not the ones who had committed any injustices or transgressions against the suspects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI study was published, this is just one place that reported on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /Overall, 60% (30/50) of the assailants had a history of drug use, with 32% (16/50) confirmed to have been under the influence at the time of the incident.  Forty-six percent (23/50) of the assailants toxicology was unknown at the time of the study.

Not to say criminal drug laws don't need to be looked at, and possibly reformed... But, people tend to do more stupid shit when they're under the influence of legal and/or illegal drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

The assailants inspired by social and/or political reasons believed that attacking police officers was their way to get justice for those who had been, in their view, unjustly killed by law enforcement.  These assailants expressed that they were distrustful of the police due to previous personal interactions with law enforcement *and what they heard and read in the media about other incidents involving law enforcement shootings.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Assailant Study  Mindsets and Behaviors - FBI Study Concludes Black Lives Matter and Mainstream Media are major motivating factor behind assaults on law enforcement officers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And I save tons of money in the process... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
