<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7982</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god how did I forget IASIP. I'll be honest, I don't know who I would choose out of those two couples. I guess from what I seen Charlie is so nice he might actually be up to do something like that. That would be awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet! I wonder, if Geoff and Griffon had a choice of absolutely any living couple for their show, who would they choose? Iconic, Like Barack and Michelle? Famous, like Jay-Z and Beyonce? Funny, like Chris Pratt and Anna Faris? Or maybe a couple that is more important to them personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet her brother is ugly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So maybe GOD is just the initials at the top of the leaderboard?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to do this for my dad recently. he doesn't have the money for a Xbox One, but he plays Destiny on the 360 daily. I hadn't cleaned it for him for a few years, and it was running really really badly. I mean, it's ten years old, so it's not the fastest anyways, but the dust build up on the inside was ridiculous. Once I cleaned it it was (relatively) a lot faster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. The casualties issue is a tough subject, and I'm not sure how we could mitigate that. Maybe lower speed limits through Spokane County? I'm really not sure.

For the Oil Spill, I think this should go hand-in-hand with the BNSF/UP firefighting team. They should absolutely have a local oil spill mitigation team, and should also work with the county on plans for a potential spill in the future. 

See the issue I see with some of these proposals (like the one in the article) is that they hurt BNSF's bottom line without giving them any benefit. That means that BNSF is going to challenge it in court no matter what, and you're not gonna find many lawyers better than those working for Berkshire Hathaway. 

Alternatively, if the city works on a mutually beneficial plan, we could work with BNSF without involving lawyers and court time. I just think that would be better for the city as a whole. I think if we make BNSF the "enemy", then we will never get anything done. 

Then again, this is all just guess work and conjecture, and maybe making them the enemy is the best way to go. It's really hard to say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I posted this in the survey, but I was thinking of ways to meet-in-the-middle for this subject. Maybe the mods could make a daily sticky for all First videos, and in that sticky have top-level comments for each video released that day. So people can have their discussions, but it won't clutter the sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it seems to me that BNSF/UP would gladly spend thousands of dollars fighting this, especially since a plant to reduce the flammability would most likely be incredibly expensive (although that is just a guess). We might be able to convince them to cover Coal however.

I wonder if there are alternatives that BNSF and UP would consider that wouldn't be as expensive as this other solution. Maybe setup a simple foam firefighting system above the tracks downtown? BNSF also has a foam firefighting train car at their yard in the valley, so it would probably be beneficial if the local fire departments developed plans with them to fight any potential oil fires.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil, coal train measure aims for ballot - Spokane Journal of Business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, Kitsap stores a huge amount of Nukes. San Diego doesn't (As far as we know) . Furthermore, it has the only dry dock capable of holding our largest Aircraft Carriers on the West Coast, and is closer to North Korea than San Diego. It's also has a massive fuel depot, the Navy's largest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize NK can dig small caves for their artillery, and their artillery is mobile? There is no way we could find all of their artillery until it is firing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think only like four out of thirty routes are actually profitable for Amtrak. They absolutely hemorrhage money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They've become endangered because of the shit humans have done.

Did you read the article at all? California Sea Lions aren't endangered, they are increasing in numbers! What has actually happened is that we've essentially set up a buffet for them at the base of dams. These Sea Lions have learned that it's a lot easier to go catch fish at the base of a dam instead of trying to catch fish in the open ocean while avoiding predators like Killer Whales. 

If anything, the animal we are really hurting are the fish themselves. Not only do they have to deal with a large dam/fish ladder they have to traverse, they now have new predators that were never there before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The groups that look for drug-running submarines are not the US Navy. The US Navy has *many* more resources at their disposal due to the USSR submarine threat during the Cold War.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for tivonews500 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you can use one of those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean really other teams don't even seem close to the Vikings and Hawks. George Fant first started for the Hawks on October 30th as our LT. That was his first ever start in real football. He had never played O-Line before, and the last time he actually "started" in a game was in pee-wee football. I mean, he has potential, but that's just pathetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well really I don't think Sherman will be with the Hawks at all by 2018. But yeah I could see one doing Nickel this season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest Hawks prediction for me: Pete Carroll gets two corners in this draft that end up being our two starters by 2018. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of right now, NKs largest missile is only about 50% successful. So let's say they fire four missile at us. We would expect only two of those to really get up to space. 

At that point, it first comes down to the US Navy. Depending on how many destroyers we have sitting in the Northern Pacific, they  would need to somehow make it past all of these ships with their AEGIS systems. Furthermore, they would also need to make it past the Japanese Navy, which also has ships equipped with AEGIS.

So if they get past all of these ships, they will then probably be flying over Alaska (assuming they fired at West Coast). In Alaska, we have thirty ground-based interceptors, so it would then need to get past these as well. 

So if they get past all of these ships, and the ground-based missile defense, they would finally have a shot at the USA. At this point they would need to actually hit where they are aiming, which they haven't shown yet. They could be aiming for LA and hit the Nevada desert (or something like that).

While our missile defense is by no means perfect, it's currently best-suited for states like NK that go "rogue" without too many missiles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, this is great. You got me on a Wikipedia spree now looking up stuff like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it's not easy but I think I would have to say when the group found out Geoff was an arsonist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the range needed for the Ohio-Class missiles, I'm sure they're actually somewhere in the middle of the Pacific. But yeah you're completely right. Our Nuclear Subs can hit basically anywhere,  anytime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's options for North Korea include placing nukes in South Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah! You fucking sheep! I won't believe it until I chop off the head of Radioactive Zombie Putin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean they should definitely live in fear of getting a parking ticket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crap! I didn't know that! Thanks though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh damn, this sounds like a fun write. If you don't want to read a somewhat long post I would recommend you shrink mine. These uppity bastards better be ready for an awesome 24 hours. 

*Side note, I really love Spokane, but I have to poke fun at it too*

---

8:00 AM: The committee steps off the plane, four members wearing nice clothes, so obviously out of place on a plane landing in Spokane. They introduce themselves, Bob (1), Bob (2), James, and Pam. 

8:15 AM They've collected their bags. We make small talk on the way to the curb. I think Bob 1 has thing for Pam. They let us know that they judge cities on a lot of criteria, but it really boils down to how lively a city is, and how beautiful it is. They apparently last visited Gary, Indiana, so I think Spokane gets a big boost right off the bat. We enter the Davenport Van. I mean, where else would they stay?

8:25 AM: I offer them brownies we picked up on the way to the airport. They all have one. Bob 2 says he's hungry, and has 3. Oops. 

8:30: I begin the "tour", pointing out some great sights on the way from the airport to Downtown. The business park near the airport is showing a lot of promise. Finch Arboretuem is a small piece of heaven next to a busy freeway. Sacred Heart is well known for it's Children's Hospital and Cardiac work. 

9:00 AM: We arrive at the Davenport. They get checked in as we go over the history of The Davenport and surrounding areas. Crab Louie Salad was invented here you know?

9:30 AM: We make it to our first real stop. The Museum of Arts and Culture in Browne's Addition. I notice that they all have red eyes. Bob 2 was singing to himself during the van ride.

10:00 AM: The Museum is going great! Bob 1 and Pam are watching a documentary, James is looking for a vending machine, and Bob 2 is having a staring contest with a large stuffed Mammoth.

10:30 AM: The committee requests/demands food. We take a walk over to Frank's Diner. I make Bob 2 walk on the inside of the sidewalk.

11:30 AM: Our total came to $107.54 for the five of us. I make sure to give the waitress a large tip, as James and Bob 1 got into a very loud argument about McNuggets. Pam also requested 7 water refills throughout the meal. Bob 2 is surprisingly coherent. We had a discussion about Spokane's Medical and Educational investments. 

11:35 AM: The van comes to pick us up and take us to Riverfront Park. I offer all of them all another brownie. They all accept. 

11:50 AM: We arrive at Riverfront Park. I note that the construction is a sign of improvement and investment. They pose with the runner statues. 

1:00 PM: After showing off the Riverfront and Huntington Park (They were memorized by the Falls), we load back up in the van. We now head to the Perry District. They like the Windmill.

1:45 PM: We load up in the van, and head up the hill. We stop at the Rockwood Bakery. They really enjoy the treats here, and the coffee really helped them wake up. Bob 2 nearly went comatose. 

2:15 PM: We arrive at Manito Park. It's beautiful. They like to feed the ducks.

3:00 PM: We now head North, we stop near the Monroe Street Bridge to look at the falls and grab some more coffee at Indaba Coffee. I mention that Kendall Yards is turning a former rail yard into a brand new nice neighborhood.

3:40 PM: We pass Garland Theater while heading North. James notices that they are playing Star Wars. He demands to stop. I thank my lucky stars they have bottomless popcorn. 

6:00 PM: We get out of the movie. I had to wake up Bob 2 and Pam. The other two enjoyed the movie. The van picks us up. I offer them all a brownie. They all accept. We head downtown. 

6:15 PM: I think about what to do for dinner. I had planned on doing something fancy, but in their current condition I decide on something more appropriate. We head to Dick's.

6:45 PM: The Van driver lets me know there is an extra charge for cleaning up a Whammy off the floor. Bob 1 takes offense to this. The van driver leaves. I guess we're walking everywhere tonight. 

7:10 PM: We stop at 7-11. James buys some cheetos. Pam asks me for another brownie. The Bobs are talking about the city with a citizen, who looks homeless. The man mentions Otto Zehm. I intervene.

7:45 PM: After giving them a choice of locations, the group decides that they want to bar crawl. We make it to the Hogwash Whiskey Den.

8:20 PM: The group apparently likes to drink. *A lot*. They are extolling the virtues of Spokane, so I'm not one to complain. 

8:35 PM: As we head north through the tunnel on Washington St., a bum whistles at Pam. Bob 1 takes offense to this. I try to diffuse the situation, and mention that the group is judging the city. The Bum starts yelling about about the City Council. We head North.

8:45 PM: We reach Sprague St. James notices the Barcade down the street, and runs off to that. We head the opposite direction to the Satellite for some more drinks. 

9:10 PM: Pam really likes Long Island Iced Teas. I put it on Fagan's tab. He'll never notice. 

9:30 PM: James comes back. He asks for quarters. I make him stay with us. I stop Bob 1 from fighting a bouncer. Bob 2 has slammed 6 shots of Whiskey in the last hour and a half, but is still surprisingly coherent. He wants to discuss the socio-economics factors of our new Pedestrian Bridge being built. 

10:00 PM: I'm exhausted. The committee is full of energy. I call us a taxi, and have them take us to Cliff Drive, overlooking downtown.

10:30 PM: We're at Cliff Drive. Downtown is beautiful. James is looking at the stars. Bob 2 is no longer coherent, and is now puking over the guard rail. Bob 1 and Pam hold hands.

11:00 PM: They still aren't ready to go to the Hotel yet. I tell them one more bar. We head to Jack and Dan's. 

11:30 PM: Bob 2 just slammed more whiskey. James went to grab Star Wars from a Red Box across the street

1:00 AM: Bob 1 just got 86'd. We're going back to the hotel. Bob 2 is coherent again. 

1:45 AM: They're finally all in their rooms. Well, Pam isn't in *her* room. I think today turned out well.

8:00 AM: I meet them in the hotel lobby, ready to take them to the airport. They decide to stay another day. They like Spokane. I offer them all another brownie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exploding a giant crate of bulk-bought bikinis, 900 gallons of tanning oil, remnant cases of meat cologne, and other former props

Oh my God this sounds like a Cow Chop video. They should bring them in!

demolishment techniques, with options including a rocket launcher, baseball bat, and forklift truck.

On second thought, maybe bringing in Cow Chop might be a bad idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a bit random, but here is some simple stuff I would love to see Gavin film in slow motion. It wouldn't need to be on main channel, I would definitely be okay with him using SMG 2.0 as a channel for less edited slow-mo. 

 - Milk + Food Coloring + Soap, I bet this one would look great visually

 - The next time there is a big storm in Austin he should set up his camera in the window and wait for lightning

 - A bee landing on a flower

 - Pop-its/ Fire-crackers

 - Hitting a (exploding?) golf ball

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely start at the beginning. It makes their achievements later seem that more important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ships of the US Navy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope this succeeds. That whole area is really a big blemish for Spokane's downtown area. 

I think one of the biggest issues for this area is access. Take a look at Division on the Northside, or 29th on the South. They constantly intersect with major arterials that give people easy access. Sprague, alternatively, meets up with Division near downtown. But then there are no major intersections (meaning major North-South roads) until you hit Freya 2.5 miles down the road.

I think one of the best things they could theoretically do would somehow connect Hamilton to Sprague. [Looking at the map of the area](https://www.google.com/maps/@47.6575941,-117.3961445,17.04z), I think the only viable solution would be something using Sprague Way. You could design it in a way to emphasize 2nd St as the faster way downtown, while Sprague would be for more local access. 

Would this be expensive? Probably, but I definitely think it's a hurdle in this whole situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Tired of dealing with the constant threats and violence coming from Hell, God decides to send his best new Angel to help straighten them out: Mr. Rogers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just found something else for the OP:

Uncheck Use hardware acceleration (Menu Settings Show Advanced Settings  System menu). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about video streaming backend, but maybe I can help troubleshoot until somebody smarter in the subject shows up.

Is it always 7 seconds that it crashes at? M3U8 (the stream) uses a streaming system where it constantly grabs from a playlist and plays them in sequential order. Just throwing the dice, but maybe it's crashing when you try to grab the next file in the playlist? I'm not sure how long each streaming section is, but 7 seconds sounds about right. 

Also, when you say crash, is it a tab crash or a browser crash? Also, I'm assuming Chrome browser?

A couple of things I would try:

 - Check for extensions that could be causing issues. Disable each one-by-one and test

 - Reinstall browser and plugins

 - Temporarily disable firewall/anti-virus and see if that helps

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Xbox One app is buggy, to say the least. While I haven't had your exact problem, I have had similar. At this point, I would try re-installing the app, but most likely it's just gonna be a waiting game until the next update.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can take the boy out Jersey, but you can't take Jersey out of the boy.

But I'm aware Rage Quit is overplayed, but even the nicest people can turn into maniacs while driving. And besides, it was a joke more than anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. My guess is they are testing two system. One would be a system to disrupt GPS to a certain area. The second, in conjunction with the first, would be a system to avoid this in our planes and vehicles. 

It says some of the tests are centered at McChord, and some at Bangor, throughout the month of April. So it involves the three main branches most likely, which means it's a good sized test. I wouldn't be surprised if part of this would be jamming to stop drones, since they are quickly becoming a dangerous weapon to US bases and soldiers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me I talked for about ten minutes to this guy and the logic in his mind doesn't really make sense. I think to him the government doesn't lie for money, they lie because they are the government and they want to control people (I guess?). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a guy that gets seatbelt tickets regularly (he has the money to pay them). We asked why and he told us that if we could prove seatbelts are safer then he would wear one. When we brought up the statistics on reduced injuries and deaths, he just brushed off those stats as government lies.

So yeah, that's the type of person that doesn't wear one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, March Madness just got over, NBA playoffs haven't started yet, and the Romo story is now a non-story. They needed something for NFL ratings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh good god could you imagine being the recipient of an actual Michael Jones rage tirade? It would be outstanding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy they're all okay, and I hope this doesn't stress out Lindsay too much because an expectant mother does not need that shit!

Also, I wonder if Michael is a calm or angry driver. Like not related to this accident, but overall. Would "Rage Quit: Austin Traffic Jam" be entertaining? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think I'll use my dremel and try to bring it in line with the wood. That's a dumb decision </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think for noodles? I'm not sure either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know I've never thought about that before, but ain't that the truth. I can never get a slice of pie out correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so too! Refurbishing older knives seems like a fun hobby anyways, and I really can't beat $7 for all of these </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I'm okay with that description as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh absolutely, but for the price I'm okay with refurbishing some and getting rid of some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I'm excited to get it and see how it performs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that would make sense, it just seems like an inefficient design for that task. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the purpose of "trapezoidal" knives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a collection of kitchen knives from Goodwill, and it included what I can only describe as a trapezoid knife. See picture below:

https://i.imgur.com/M3rTmK7.jpg

What is the purpose of this knife? Is the shape just a gimmick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors diagnosed with serious diseases, what symptoms made you go to the doctor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] In the future, health clinics are pretty convenient. You walk in, prick your finger, and out pops a pill that fixes every problem you have. Unfortunately, you've yet to find a clinic that can actually analyze you, they all give errors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He literally was the first player from his high school to make it to Stanford in over 20 years because of his grades and football skills.](http://articles.latimes.com/2005/nov/04/sports/sp-hssondcol4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props to whoever came up with the title on this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, I was really just trying to make a trebuchet joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also misses that recent NK tests shows us that if they sent 20 missiles in the near future, probably only 25-50% would actually succeed in actual flight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once miniaturized, nuclear weapons can be [as small as 90kg](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/W79). So if they can get with 300m of South Korea I think I know a weapon delivery system they could use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that's in Washington! The best state in the US!

^(unless you're from Cali in which case Washington sucks) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My local place has CBD tinctures for sell. A drop under the tongue and you're good to do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I PM you mine as well and have it fixed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making a Movie: The Movie

It will be a movie about making Lazer Team.

And if you think that will be good, just wait until it's sequel: Movie-Ception. The Movie about a movie about making a movie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! You too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for NubiaRivera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody else think we should make an alliance with /r/sweden and build it on their flag? Lots of blue space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay this all makes sense now. That's pretty damn cool how it happened! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The description on image 8 is crazy! That's some crazy growth. 

Also, just to clarify, what led up to the April 1st launch? How was it different than the 15th launch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry friend. Maybe we can make a heart next to our cow. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if we could make an alliance with /r/Funhaus we could forcefully take the entire area for RT.  Operation Cockbite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just spell RIP under Funhuas? It's gonna look weird now anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noo! Leave Cow Chop alone!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels appropriate that /r/CowChop is going to ruin a bunch of stuff while working towards a common goal. It's just like a Cow Chop video! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I mean, let's be honest. I was going to do this anyways, but I added a party hat to make it more celebratory.](http://i.imgur.com/uTaTpl1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh absolutely. Keep on rocking with whatever you're doing though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering applying for RT? You have talent, and clearly a portfolio.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! That video deserves to be 5 hours long, just to fit all the cool shit they have done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, this is really damn cool. RT should use it as a pre-roll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so basically video cameras work by taking a bunch of pictures and putting them together really quickly. When somebody says frame, you can basically pretend they said picture. So 24 pictures per second.

If you only see less than 10 pictures a second, your mind can still perceive them individually as pictures. But once you start going over this number humans start to see motion. 24 FPS was chosen because people seen it as motion, and back a while ago people would range from 22-26, so they chose 24 in the middle.

Higher can be better for multiple reasons. The first is smoothness. 60fps is good for video games as it makes the game smoother. Higher fps is better for slow motion too. If you record at 60fps, and playback at 30fps, everything you film will last twice as long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Cow Chop doing anything for their B-Day tomorrow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats to Gavin and Dan! To celebrate, they should get some champagne and cut the top off using a sword while filming in slow-mo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. I should head up there soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treasury secretary: It was wrong to plug Lego Batman movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is dumb. I'm no fan of Trump but NK has shown that they would continue with their own status quo regardless of who is President. Had Hillary won she would also be dealing with this same situation, and almost certainly her military advisers would be saying nearly the same thing. No military adviser is going to come out and say "Oh I guess it's okay NK is getting Nukes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If they ever got the capability it'd be destroyed in an instant

I mean how do we know this isn't already happening? The last two missiles they tried failed quickly, maybe we had a ship waiting off-shore to shoot them down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I really wish North Spokane had an equivalent to Manito </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manito is great, but I really wish North Spokane had a park or something that was similar. God only knows Harlan Douglass has enough vacant land up here to find somewhere to put it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! And my recommendation is to just try it out. A few months ago I responded to a prompt in /r/writingprompts, and it was the first time I really wrote creatively since middle school, probably 10+ years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Every time I see a post like I will definitely respond with a story or something if I have time. I may not be a good writer, but I sure have fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know for a lot of people it's difficult but if you can you could buy merch. That probably helps more than anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Elon Musk comes up with a lot of ideas. His advisers have to make sure each one is good, and get rid of the evil ones. Today Elon really wants to move headquarters into an active volcano. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making the Cubano's from Chef this weekend, I was inspired by [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/61z6dz/binging_with_babish_cubanos_from_chef/). Anybody else making anything good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you fired a shotgun shell with a uranium slug at another chunk of uranium would it form a bomb? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bit better. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Just listen through my speakers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Small request to Xbox for the new Guide update... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth, I did not get the system update yesterday on the Xbox One yet and I am still experiencing crashing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] When the US begins testing nuclear weapons at Bikini Atoll again, Spongebob must learn how to deal with the radioactive zombie sea-creatures that now roam Bikini Bottom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well deserved, on both awards. The good news for Gonzaga is that the increased freshmen applications this year will help pay for the inevitable raise Few will be getting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could focus on bringing in a Psychic too. That way it would be a Medium Long Short </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh absolutely, and that's a whole other debate. I almost think we should just let it die out with the current set of ranchers (a lot of them are older). To be honest I just felt bad for the rancher in this case, that false story led to him getting death threats and nasty messages, when really he was trying his best under current laws.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A large part of this is false. I wrote a couple of comments a few days ago addressing this:

https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/61ve2m/wolf_spotted_in_nevada_is_first_in_nearly_a/dfj1mzg/?context=3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I would love a show like that

---

*Thursday - 2PM: Matt Hullum is in his office, doing a 1-on-1 with the camera* 

**Matt:** Yeah you know I think we really run a tight ship around here at Rooster Teeth. We have our issues, but overall I think everybody really works out.

*As Matt finishes his sentence, a quick loud knocking is heard at the office door. Chris's voice can be heard*

**Chris:** Matttttttt! Maaaaaaattttttttt! Matt! Matt! Matt!

*Matt gives an annoyed/exasperated look to the camera.*

**Matt:** Alright alright! Come in Chris.

*As soon as Matt finishes speaking, Chris slams open the door. The door knob hits a makeshift stopper taped to Matt's wall. Chris then slams the door shut, which leads to a Master Chief action figure falling off a shelf on the wall*

**Chris:** Maaaattttt, Blaine won't stop stealing my juice!

*Behind Chris's back, Blaine can be seen peaking through the window to the office. Matt notices him, Chris does not.*

**Matt:** Well Chris, that's a serious accusation. Rooster Teeth does not condone thievery!

*Matt gives a quick smile to the camera*

**Matt:** In fact Chris, why don't you tell us how he stole it?

*Chris gets a big smile on his face, and sits down in the chair opposite Matt's desk*

**Chris:** Okay well I guess it all started back on Tuesday. So I came in to work that day and I was really tired, right?

*Matt gives a small nod and a slight smile. Chris begins to speak faster*

**Chris:** And well I knew I needed something to drink, so I started to search and I found a drink, and I went around asking people if it was theirs and everybody I found said no but I didn't want to take it yet because I didn't want to be a thief like Blaine but then I looked at the label and it said free so I took it and then I drank a little and it didn't taste as good as I thought so I went back to my office and I put it in the fridge to make it colder and I forgot about it until today so I went to go get it and it was gone! And Blaine stole it!

*Once again the door slams open, hitting the ragged taped up stopper on the wall. Blaine rushes in and also slams the door, leading to another figure falling off the wall shelf. Matt facepalms, and gives Blaine a tired look.*

**Blaine:** BULLSHIT! Bullshit! Bullshit bullshit bullshit! That was my FUCKING drink!

**Chris:** No it wasn't! It said free on it! I asked everybody!

**Blaine:** You didn't ask me asshole! I was in the bathroom!

**Chris:** Yeah... But it said free on it.

*Blaine pulls a bottle out of his bag and points at the label*

**Blaine:** You stupid ass! Does that look like it says free to you?!

**Chris:** Well yeah, it says it's filled with sugar, and it's free!

*Chris smiles at Matt, obviously hoping he will take his side.*

**Matt:** Chris, that says sugar free, as in, it has no sugar.

*Chris get a surprised look on his face.*

**Chris:** Ohhh... So that's why it tasted like shit!

---
End Scene

---

*Friday - 9:15AM: Achievement Hunter office. Michael and Lindsay are the only two in the room. Lindsay is sitting on the couch on her phone. Michael sits at his desk, the camera focused on his face. Behind him, in-frame, the door opens. Gavin walks in. Michael glances back*

**Michael:** Oh hey Gavin, sup?

*Gavin grunts back, it's easy to see he's still tired.*

*Cut in scene to Michael in a room talking 1-on-1 with camera*

**Michael:** Gavin and I have a great relationship. I fuck with him, fart on his shit, prank him, just generally be an asshole. And he always responds by sputtering and saying some British shit. It's pretty great overall.

*Cut back to AH office. Gavin sits down to his desk and turns on his computer. Michael gives a sly smile to Lindsay*

**Gavin:** Oi! This isn't my keyboard. It looks like it's in Latin! And my computer! Bollocks! All the words are in Latin too!

*Michael starts laughing*

**Michael:** That's Spanish you idiot!

*Gavin's voice raises, he's yelling at this point.*

**Gavin:** Michael where is my keyboard?!

*Gavin starts to stomp and bang his desk. As he stomps, a squish sound is heard. He looks under his desk*

**Gavin** MICHAEL!! You put dog shit under my desk too?!

*Michael's face looks confused. At this point the door slams open and Geoff runs in*

**Geoff:** Ahahaha you smarmy British Fuck! I did that to piss you off!

*Gavin begins to gag, and grabs a garbage can nearby*

**Gavin:** Geoff! *dry-heave* Clean up this dogshit! *dry-heaves again, head in can*

*Scene cuts, now it's Geoff doing 1-on-1 with camera*

**Geoff:** Yeah I love fucking with Gavin. Keeps him from getting too cocky, you know? Also, that was totally my shit. 

*Geoff winks at camera*

---
End scene

--- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done, and deleted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [One of the first improvements I think is needed in the new space](http://i.imgur.com/v0EGRq5.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at one point I know Geoff looked into investment opportunities during his Sabbatical. He wasn't too impressed with Kitten Mittens.

http://i.imgur.com/CudHeLD.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you hit the nail on the head with the problem they have. The main issue with the Let's Play Youtube channel is that they basically made it Achievement Hunter 2.0 from the start. To me, they actually shouldn't have put GTA and Minecraft on there. Instead, I personally think AH should have put one Let's Play a week on the Let's Play channel. The other four days should have been a mashup of Let's Play's from the other groups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to say Futurama, but at the same time I would never want it to pull a Simpsons. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does /r/worldnews have over 80 moderators? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, that's a lot. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/about/moderators </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh true. And I bet the flight from Seattle for that old lady is a bit cheaper in LA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. I would love to see Matt do a Let's Build in Minecraft, but entirely in his Bob Ross-ish voice. 

"And now we're gonna build some happy little trees."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's so much room for activities!

But seriously this looks like a great filming location guys. And if it ends up that Cow Chop isn't making enough you could always rent out the couch for somebody to film a porno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of those questions that can get tons of varied answers. Here are some of the questions that can help you determine though:

1. What airline do you use the most?
2. What hotel do you use the most?
3. What would you value in your card? Cashback, perks for other travelers, free checked bag, etc.

But here is the big question:

**What deals are currently going on?**

In my case, I recently got a Delta FF credit card, and I got 50,000 bonus miles for spending over $1000. However a week or two later the deal had changed and it was only 10,000 miles for 1000 spent. So it really depends what deals are going on when you buy.

In terms of subs that can help, I would also check out /r/churning, since they know what cards pay out well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common misconception, but no. The Dick's in Spokane is completely separate from the Dick's in Seattle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 on this. One really nice thing is it lets you Download a backup of what episodes you have viewed, and any progress you have saved, so if you move phones you don't lose all your info.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As other have said, most likely the Greenwood Reservoir. Looks like they started building it way back in 1901, from what I could find. 

They most likely have two because one was for the upper cemetery, and the other for the lower part. 

Also, for anybody exploring in this area, I would really recommend they check out Indian Canyon Mystic Falls. It's relatively close, and I bet it's running amazing right now. Here is a map of where it's at:

https://www.google.com/maps/place/Indian+Canyon+Mystic+Falls/@47.6488178,-117.4817766,132m </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If attached to an artificial blood system, could a head be kept alive like in Futurama? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! To be fair, that guy really misled a lot of people. It ended up that both the Professor and the Rancher started getting death threats, so it really was messy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the history of the rancher being opposed to wolf reintroductions and advocating for their extermination

Well I absolutely believe that could be the case. Tons of ranchers up here believe that. But yeah in this case the ranchers themselves seemed to be somewhat okay with wolves. This is from a local newspaper:

That rancher and another producer with cattle near the Profanity Peak pack had been taking steps recommended by the department to avoid conflict with wolves, Martorello has said, from deploying range riders to picking up carcasses to avoid attracting wolves, and turning out calves when they were bigger and more mature. He praised the ranchers cooperation.

As I was researching this, I think I found the person you were talking about with the scientific credentials, and it sounds like he wrote an article that had many inaccuracies. The University he worked for published some retractions:

https://news.wsu.edu/2016/08/31/wsu-issues-statement-clarifying-comments-profanity-peak-wolf-pack/

However I do agree with that same writer under some circumstances. He thinks Ranchers should have to sign [this agreement](http://wdfw.wa.gov/conservation/gray_wolf/livestock/agreements.html) with the state in order to receive protection, and I think that's a great idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I know what you are talking about, and that's one hell of stretch to make the rancher sound that bad. In fact, the rancher basically exhausted his options for dealing with the wolves:

*Producer 1 is the rancher I believe this comment is talking about*

 In this case, Producer 1  who experienced
all but one of the depredations by the Profanity Peak
pack  turned out cattle from June 8-10. The turnout
location, predetermined by the producers allotment
plan with the Colville National Forest,

So his location to turn out his cows was determined in part by the National Forest Service, not "he knew the local wolf pack was raising a litter".

However, by the end of June, an analysis of three
weeks of collar data from the two newly collared
wolves confirmed that the location of the packs den
site had changed since the previous year

They found out the wolves had moved their den in late June, but the Rancher turned out his cows June 1st. 

The proactive deterrence measures Producer 1 had in
place included calving outside of the known occupied
wolf habitat... The
local Wildlife Conflict Specialist concurred that these
proactive deterrence measures were suitable for this
particular grazing situation and were in place long
enough to meet the expectations in the protocol.

So he used proactive deterrence measures, he didn't "send them right through where they slept"

the local
Wildlife Conflict Specialist recommended adding a
range rider as a reactive deterrence measure, which
the producer did soon afterward.

So even spent more money to try and protect his cattle. Unfortunately, as the wolves killed more and more cows throughout the summer, the majority of the pack was removed. But there is no way you can completely blame it on the Rancher, it looks like he tried his best. 

Source: http://wdfw.wa.gov/conservation/gray_wolf/packs/files/ProfanityPeakPostAction_2016.pdf
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I speak for a lot of people when I say it would be awesome for you to join AH for a week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If (God-forbid) Rooster Teeth unexpectedly had to shut down, and you had to go get a mundane "regular-person" job, what would you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Dan,

It looks like it's a bit finicky. If you have an Android phone, you can cast your screen to the Fire Stick and try it that way. With the computer, however, you have to go a bit outside the box. 

http://www.alphr.com/microsoft/microsoft-windows-10-1/1002529/how-to-mirror-windows-10-to-an-amazon-fire-tv-stick

Here are some instructions. I hope they work for you!

As a side note, there are other options if you are willing to spend a bit more, or if the above doesn't work. If you have an Xbox One or (I believe) a PS4, they both include RT apps. Alternatively, you could buy an HDMI splitter, and place it between your CPU and monitor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MRGA sounds like the noise I make when I stub my toe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! Good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it Yik Yak? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a singular person behind the account now? Or is it just the Social Media team?

Also mods are you going to look into a perma-link to the RT account when doing the CSS re-design? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gonzaga basketball player accidentally scores on own hoop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A local newspaper runs an "I Saw You" section weekly. This was in this week's column </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mod Request: Carbon Monoxide poisoning active effect in the basement of Lakeview Manor. Needs negative HP and wavy vision </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sadly not a subscriber

If you want any recommendations for other RT shows just let us know! There's tons to choose from! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were some Cow Chop videos I could only find on Youtube, not the RT Xbox app, but they were sponsored. I'm not if the app was messed up or if they only post some ads to Youtube though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no opinion on the topic at hand right now, but I just want to point out how it sucks that the first two main comments are both so dismissive. There are people on this Sub that stifle so much conversation, and it's really dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have anti-virus? Try disabling it temporarily and see if that works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to using the proper email channels, if that fails you can also contact /u/chattykinson. She is part of RT support and responds really well on Reddit it seems like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, If you don't want your shirts to shrink as much after a wash, don't dry them in a clothes dryer. Instead, grab them by the shoulders, shake out any excess water, and hang up to dry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UberHaxorNova - MOVING </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call, I totally did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
