<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5591</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. My diet now consists mostly of whole foods, I really try to limit processed foods(minus protein shakes and bars), but its nearly impossible to avoid all together. I eat a lot of chicken and turkey, broccoli, spinach salads and potatoes. Sounds pretty boring but changing up how you cook everything helps! Also season EVERYTHING it makes eating much more enjoyable. I drink a protein shake every morning, usually with half an english muffin. It has definitely taken some getting used to, I would recommend baby steps! Eat like usual, but put more veggies on your plate. Drink water instead of pop. Crystal light and Mio really helped me start drinking water. Herbal tea and water are all I drink. I aim to get 3-5L of water per day. It gets easier as you continue, and making tiny changes is sooooooo much easier than completely changing overnight.

2.  I didn't exercise for the first year and I dropped 100lbs. This summer I started doing yoga and HIIT cardio on the elliptical (increasing the resistance for short periods of time). I started doing yoga, body weight exercises and lifting free weights as well. I work out at home, no gym membership! Youtube is AWESOME for workout ideas. Christina Carlyle, Blogilates, Yoga with Adrienne are all great channels to check out! I've recently started running and I'm training for my first 5K coming up! I like keeping my workouts varied, I get bored easily. I aim to workout for at least 30mins 4-6 times a week. I find things I enjoy and do those! I never stick with exercise that I hate. 

3. Yeah. Excess skin is a thing. Its not fun, but it's definitely better than having the fat! My whole body is a mess tbh. But I would take this saggy body over my old body ANY DAY. I'm looking to have surgery in the next year hopefully, and I'll probably need several. But I think everyone deserves to be happy with their body and if surgery is the only way, I'm game.  

4. I started losing gradually around April of 2015. January 2016 I was around 290. That's about when I started getting serious. By April 2016 I was 250 and have lost the last 60 since then. So just under two years I suppose! 


Sorry this is so long. I hope it helps! Please PM if you want more info! Always happy to help! Good luck, I believe in you!!! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha that sounds awesome! Thank you :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
