<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2521</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did I can tell you! Probably the best fried chicken I've made. The crunchy crisp of the batter and panko bread was great (:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's eaten at a place called Koi in Malmo Sweden (:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Panko fried scampi japanese style </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I Ate] Ebi Fry With Spicy Sauce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in Sweden for example we call this a burger. For international standards this is a basic replica of burger kings crispy chicken (in Sweden). 

But i do agree with you though, with the toppings and dressing it's more a sandwich but the buns are still "burger buns" (:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will try to post a more through breakdown but the short version is

Wet batter:
1 dl all purpose flour
1 tsp baking soda
0,5 dl beer
2 spoons of corn starch or potatoe starch
Salt
Pepper
Cayenne pepper
Garlic powder 
Paprika powder

Try maybe less and more of the wet and flour ingredients. I want my wet better to be wet but still so solid so when I dip the chicken down and bring it up it doesn't drip until maybe 1,5-2 seconds.

Dry batter:
Panko bread
Salt
Pepper
Cayenne
Paprika powder

Get it really dry on the outside, so after the wet better lift it up directly on to the plate with the dry batter and roll it really good so the whole surface is completely filled of the panko and dry!

Hope this gave you a little insight! And adjust the ration depending on how many burgers or fried chicken your making!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds great! Definitely gonna try it out (; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe countless tries indeed! All about the batter :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Crispy Fried Chicken Burger with Fries and Blue cheese dip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst part is that i have one size larger, but learning gradually. I have a couple of "planks" as well i use for plating. Will try to fit i better next time ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
