<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8902</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just go with other stones. I got my fiance a nice blue topaz stone as an engagement ring. It was less expensive and more beautiful than a diamond.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always hated that because it seems like they're saying "move on and don't worry, it's just a few bad apples", but everyone is familiar with the phrase about bad apples spoiling the bushel, and the phrase is grounded in reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cohost and I recorded an episode of our podcast talking about what makes the John Wick films so great. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Partner and I recorded an episode of our podcast talking about what makes the John Wick films so great. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the accusations, it doesn't seem like the company can sweep it away as a few bad managers, it really seems like a culture of sexual harassment and intimidation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arbitration is such a bullshit thing, and it's everywhere. Employee contracts, car sale contracts, and hidden in many other Terms of Services. 

Arbitration really puts the consumer or employee on unequal footing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A part of me has always wanted to buy one online and return it to the store though. Not that I ever would, I just think it would be funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My GM support manager was sleeping with a cap 2 associate who was married to the toy department manager. It never came out of the and the support manager is still there. The cap 2 associate left though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it includes Google Play Music too I would definitely go for it. The service would only be $20 more than my fiance and I currently pay for some streaming television.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the posted at arrest or conviction? I think it's terrible either way, but posting at arrest would be insane. Innocent people are sometimes arrested for crimes and they deserve a trial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a terrible idea, but is it only posted after convicting? Because if it's just posted after arrest, that makes it even worse. Since innocent people are arrested all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize The Onion is not a real news source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't even fathom the negative effect this could have on our tourism industry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could probably fill a few pages with great quotes by Larry Bird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Mr Plumber does good work, but they will charge more than other plumbers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an issue just last week, not anything related to gas, but I called Miller Legacy Plumbing and they were great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, how is that a comparison that could be made in anyone's mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would I watch it when I can just look at all the winners the next day, and watch all the best parts and speeches on Youtube.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually didn't know that. Wouldn't have expected an English lesson here, but I do appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck. It's only been 5 weeks. I think to some degree the conservatives in control are relying on the fact that we will eventually get exhausted and stop criticizing as strongly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have incredibly short memories. It's like some people are thinking "he's critical of Trump, he can't be that bad" and ignoring the character of GWB.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's a cop. Literally no other reason. Anyone else that did that would have undoubtedly been charged.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand jurisdictions in this universe. We've established there are human police officers and robot police officers. Are humans only able to police humans and robots only able to police robots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love her expression change in the last two panels. Goes from "eager to assist to I'm not going to tell you anything" almost instantaneously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anything You Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine that's some form of sarcasm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course. Religious freedom only applies to Christians </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my hometown. Never would have expected anything like that there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you're married doesn't make the other's body your property. Sometimes people may not be in the mood and taking it anyway is not acceptable in any way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When in May? During Memorial Day Weekend, Momocon is at the convention center downtown with many cosplayers, and that's prime people watching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While reading the article, I learned their are apparently 8 other states that have the same exemption. What in the actual fuck? I don't see how the exemption is defensible in any way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If being born and raised in America doesn't make a person American, then what does?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bannon has said he's against all immigration, and he's one of Trump's trusted advisors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't inherently disagree. I don't know that I agree with the sentencing in this case, but I think more people should get lighter sentences so as to not rot in a prison cell and become lifetime criminals. 

I just wish everyone would remember that when it came to minorities. No one should be rotting in a prison cell for possession of a drug or other minor offenses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't really cook, but my fiance is a great cook. I can clean though. She cooks. I clean. It works for us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But of course Brietbart is still given a front row seat and Alex Jones is someone Trump frequently calls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to try to paint everyone with the same brush. I'm not pro life, but I know many pro life people and most still understand the need for exceptions. Few people I've met are calloused enough to believe abortion shouldn't be an option in 100% of circumstances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. I suppose I meant dead in the fact that it has no chance at life. It will inevitably die soon after birth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, everyone should be forced to carry their dead babies to term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a tremendous act of selflessness on this woman's part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many Muslims and people of Indian descent were born here and as American as you. Where should they go?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would watch it just for the eventual payoff at the end of season 1 when he eventually pulls the sword from his ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand what you mean and could definitely understand why you feel that way. At least you have other options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest question: why, since the tip is optional?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not religious, but I really respect the new Pope. He's basically made quite a few statements telling so called Christians to put up or shut up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always liked Lyft more, just because they allow you to tip the driver using the app.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no question it will get vetoed again. Such an obvious waste of time and energy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy cow. That's amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My partner and I recorded an episode of our podcast reviewing The Lego Batman Movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My partner and I actually recorded an episode of our podcast, The C C Geekcast, about The Lego Batman Movie. It's available at www.candcgeekcast.com and on all podcast clients if you would like to check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My partner and I recorded an episode of our podcast reviewing The Lego Batman Movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My partner and I recorded an episode of our podcast reviewing The Lego Batman Movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're joking, but it does seem a few members of the community feel that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Know it's not Atlanta proper, but there's a road closing in Kennesaw that could affect some of your commutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kind of jokes. Though I'm not very good at puns myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Movies] [C C Geekcast](www.candcgeekcast.podbean.com)

SFW

Hey guys. My friend and I started a movie podcast about 6 months ago. We bill ourselves as the only podcast where two guys with speech impediments talk about movies. We like to take one movie and review it in depth. Our episodes generally last around 20-30 minutes. Our most recent episode was on The Lego Movie, the surprise animated hit of 2014. We discuss what made the literal giant Lego commercial such a good film and so enjoyable. We also discuss our thoughts on all the coming spin-off films. It'd be awesome if you took the time to listen and subscribe.

[iTunes Link](https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/c-c-geekcast/id1168343985?mt=2)

[Website](www.candcgeekcast.podbean.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Movies] [C C Geekcast](www.candcgeekcast.podbean.com)

SFW

Hey guys. My friend and I started a movie podcast about 6 months ago. We bill ourselves as the only podcast where two guys with speech impediments talk about movies. We like to take one movie and review it in depth. Our episodes generally last around 20-30 minutes. Our most recent episode was on The Lego Movie, the surprise animated hit of 2014. We discuss what made the literal giant Lego commercial such a good film and so enjoyable. We also discuss our thoughts on all the coming spin-off films. It'd be awesome if you took the time to listen and subscribe.

[iTunes Link](https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/c-c-geekcast/id1168343985?mt=2)

[Website](www.candcgeekcast.podbean.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had it been constitutional, the Supreme Court wouldn't have ruled the way they did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there was no good reason the former law was still in place. There is literally no reason to oppose same sex marriage that's not religious in nature, and I don't talk laws should be in place just to appease religions. If one wants to live in a theocracy, there are many other choices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 17:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "See the turtle of enormous girth, on his shell, he holds the Earth" 

I assume you were referencing The Dark Tower. If so, Internet high five.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to do something about these guys. They're rapists, they're murderers, and some, I imagine, are good people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blood on her Hands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems Jeph's butt disease has returned. Not that I'm complaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I'm half of the C C Geekcast. We bill ourselves as the only podcast where two guys with speech impediments talk about movies. We take one movie at a time and do a relatively in depth review each episode. Our episodes usually run around 20-30 minutes, and we have 19 episodes so far with movies of every genre having been discussed. 

It'd be awesome if you took the time to listen and subscribe or gave us feedback. We're available at candcgeekcast.podbean.com and every other podcast client. Thanks guys and happy listening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My film podcast, the C C Geekcast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, my partner and I recorded an episode about our thoughts on 2014's breakout animated hit, The Lego Movie. We talk about what made the movie, which was a literal Lego commercial, so good and so memorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C C Geekcast: The Lego Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, my partner and I recorded an episode about our thoughts on 2014's breakout animated hit, The Lego Movie. We talk about what made the movie, which was a literal Lego commercial, so good and so memorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C C Geekcast: The Lego Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, my partner and I recorded an episode about our thoughts on 2014's breakout animated hit, The Lego Movie. We talk about what made the movie, which was a literal Lego commercial, so good and so memorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C C Geekcast: The Lego Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are their games going to be televised on Fox Sports South like the Hawks games? Or is there a TV deal with the MLS at all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [movies] C C Geekcast | Episode 10: Guardians of the Galaxy (SFW)

On this episode we're going to be discussing one of our favorite films within the Marvel Cinematic Universe, Guardians of the Galaxy, which also happens to be one of the best space operas of recent memory. We're going to be discussing our thoughts on Marvel expanding into the intergalactic realm. We're also going to be discussing our thoughts on all the characters introduced, as well as the villain and of course Thanos. We're also going to be discussing how we think it compares to other great science fiction films.

[Podbean Link](http://candcgeekcast.podbean.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [movies] C C Geekcast | Episode 10: Guardians of the Galaxy (SFW)

On this episode we're going to be discussing one of our favorite films within the Marvel Cinematic Universe, Guardians of the Galaxy, which also happens to be one of the best space operas of recent memory. We're going to be discussing our thoughts on Marvel expanding into the intergalactic realm. We're also going to be discussing our thoughts on all the characters introduced, as well as the villain and of course Thanos. We're also going to be discussing how we think it compares to other great science fiction films.

[Podbean Link](http://candcgeekcast.podbean.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, my friend and I started a podcast about 6 months ago. We just take one movie and review it in depth. They're generally geek films, as is obvious from the name, and we're up to episode 18. It would be awesome if any of you were able to take the time to check it out, and just so you know, we're available on iTunes, Stitcher, Google Play Music, and every other podcast client. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C C Geekcast: The only podcast where 2 guys with speech impediments talk about movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, doesn't matter the crime or circumstances, just throw these teens in prison for the rest of their lives   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've enjoyed the robot storyline, but it's been a while since I we've seen a human centric one, so I think it would be nice to see again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kubo is one of my favorite films and one of the best animated films of recent memory. My friend and I recorded an episode of our podcast talking about why we love the film so much. It would be awesome if you could take the time to listen.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Episode 18: Kubo and the Two Strings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The panel with Punchbot as a CPA legitimately made me laugh out loud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea of Spookybot as a villain is legitimately terrifying since their ridiculous power has already been clearly illustrated. 

So much great story telling potential.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone recently said that Lebron has no good quotes. I think that narrative is being changed now. He is getting sassy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am afraid of some random dude getting angry and shooting me. Is that better?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And extremely anti gay, and also a member of the Army of God.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the suburbs. I don't anticipate a terrorist attack happening in my town, but I am surrounded by a town where everyone owns a gun. Just last week a dude went crazy and murdered his wife here a few miles from my house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the suburbs of Atlanta. I just seriously doubt any Islamic radicals are going to care about doing damage here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both of whom were US citizens and any ban would have done jack shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm legitimately more afraid of being somewhere a white dude is going to shoot up, a church, a movie theater, or a school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kubo is one of my favorite films and one of the best animated films of recent memory. My friend and I recorded an episode of our podcast talking about why we love the film so much. It would be awesome if you could take the time to listen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C C Geekcast, Episode 18: Kubo and the Two Strings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kubo is one of my favorite movies and one of the best animated films of recent memory. I would absolutely love it if someone took the time to listen to me and my friend discuss it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the smile in the last panel, I think it's obvious which option Spookybot would prefer. 

I should enjoy watching CW get her comeuppance, but I definitely don't. She's being tortured by a being so powerful, she has absolutely no chance of fighting back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C C Geekcast, Episode 18: Kubo and the Two Strings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My congressman is co-sponsoring this bill. Definitely going to call his office and make my voice heard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my district. Thanks for the heads up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My check is beautiful. 124 hours of pto and I'm a sporting goods Dept manager  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but the original poster does. He added that sarcastic remark at the end of the title  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm incredibly critical of Trump, but I definitely support the Right to Try law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't imagine why anyone would want to travel there, and that's okay, but this guy has trained for a while for this competition and it's a big deal to him. Especially considering it's nothing he's done, just politics getting in the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 18:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always found it cool that he is loyal to Atlanta. He's a relatively big name in the cooking world and could probably be successful anywhere, but he chooses to do things like this here.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta coffee: Alton Brown to open coffee shop in Marietta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how sharing debunked lies regarding immigrants and their propensity for crime is anything but racist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I see that now. Whoops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not wrong though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's referring to you since you have Pelicans flair and Pelicans and Saints share a city? Maybe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Falcons are still an Atlanta sports team, so I wouldn't be shocked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawks to honor Super Bowl-bound Falcons before tonight's game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawks to honor Super Bowl-bound Falcons before game tonight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 00:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atlanta is undoubtedly one of the best cities for nerds. Never change Atlanta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Borden has the best chocolate milk and you can get a quart at any Wal mart for like $2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, wow. I didn't even think of that. The possibility that the memories never existed in the first place and Corpse Witch just made Bubbles think they were there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was legitimately unexpected and a potentially very interesting development. This could mean instead of having repressed memories encrypted and inaccessible because of Corpse Witch, Corpse Witch just wiped them while making Bubbles think they were still there and just locked away. Not sure what's going to come of this development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. I'm dumb. I suppose monster was a representation of the measures Corpse Witch had put in place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't take the monster as a representation of ptsd. I took it as a representation of the encryption. Something terrifying and unbeatable for most, able to be defeated without even trying by the spooky suit guy and their technology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was 4, so it's pretty interesting to me knowing things like this aren't even older than I am.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually didn't know about the campaign. I think it's incredibly interesting, and I don't think it's necessarily demonization, it just reminds us how recent a lot of awful shit is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
