<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3180</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean they're definitely sweet but not overly so, in my opinion - it's just a light coating on the rice cake so it's pretty well balanced. I always felt like the chocolate ones just made me want real chocolate, but these are actually satisfying to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caramel corn rice cakes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha! Those are my salt and pepper shakers... but their positioning in this photo is pretty suspect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually really great advice! I definitely put too much in the bag... probably how I managed to explode it all over the place. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sorry, my shells are just regular plain shells (dyed yellow) - the only lemon bit is the lemon curd in the middle! I have heard of folks adding lemon to shells (although I think usually just the zest to avoid adding moisture?) but I've never tried. Maybe try just sprinkling zest on top after you pipe them?

Edit: I've also made vegan macarons for a friend before that used vegan ganache and raspberry jam in the center - those might be nice dairy free fillings to try as well! The shells themselves don't contain dairy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whaaaat... that's crazy! Tempted to do this if my hands start to hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it! It's like a Willy Wonka cake! Is it also rainbow on the inside? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT. These look incredible. I never would have thought to do this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you Stephen or "Go Pats"? :P

In case it's not obvious, I did this test run on Super Bowl Sunday... The one that says "Stephen" (illegibly) is the one my piping bag just exploded onto. It was so ugly that my friend decide to write on it and give it away as a purposely hideous gift.

Bonus edit: Another friend later decorated [this cookie](http://imgur.com/a/q6jSZ) to accurately describe the state of these cookies. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know some people hate coconut, but I LOVE lime and coconut! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO cute! Were they actually watermelon flavored somehow, or just watermelon themed? I feel like it's such a delicate flavor it would be hard to make that work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup I've read a few things here and there, I think it will mostly take some practice to see what the right consistency actually looks and feels like vs just reading about it. 

I'll probably also look for some youtube videos - sometimes watching someone else make it is even more helpful. Recommendations welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it helps, my friend recommended this cookie recipe to me:

http://www.marthastewart.com/966161/ideal-sugar-cookies

I never ever make sugar cookies, but honestly it was super easy and they turned out well on my first try (which almost never happens)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that's really helpful!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my upcoming party, I'm going to try pink heart-shaped macarons, heart-shaped frosted sugar cookies, and pretzel rods dipped in chocolate with v-day sprinkles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What flavors?? They look delicious, even the less-than-perfect ones! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I actually had read that and bought a couple, but the openings on them are TINY. I tried using them but it was so hard to get the icing out that it hurt my hand more than using a bag... I think I might try cutting one of them to widen the opening and see if that works. Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had no idea that existed, thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'll be trying again today and hopefully it goes better... I think part of my challenge was that I was experimenting with icing thickness and the size of the piping tip at the same time. Accidentally went too runny and too large which made for a big mess.

What size do you usually use (if you know)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lemon curd usually doesn't make a great macaron filling on its own because it's a bit too soft and runny, I think, but for some reason I was *craving* these and had to try them.

Like I expected, pretty slippery off the bat, but after refrigerating for a day, enough of the liquid soaked into the shells that the macarons were plenty stable and they absolutely melted in your mouth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lemon curd macarons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm throwing my second annual (very cheesy) Galentine's Day party this weekend. This year's craft is cookie decorating, so I'm planning to bake and "flood" a bunch of cookies ahead of time so that everyone can decorate on top of that. 

This was test run #1... The icing was a bit too runny, and then I accidentally exploded some icing out the top of the piping bag, at which point I gave up! Going to need lots more practice this week...

Edit: really entertained that this has this many upvotes even though it's so ugly. That's why I love /r/Baking! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to teach myself royal icing... ugh. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also look for "merengue powder" - different name but it's just dried egg whites + a bit of cornstarch to prevent clumping. I've never used it in macarons but it's commonly used to make royal icing. I know you can buy it at Michael's.

Edit: PS These are BEAUTIFUL. I'm going to try heart macarons this weekend for a Galentines Day party... fingers crossed they turn out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true! On a smaller scale oven temp can determine whether your "feet" explode out sideways or rise straight up. It can take a lot of testing to pick the right temp for your specific finnicky oven (and/or just get an oven thermometer I suppose...).

I also only ever bake one tray at a time just in case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even Sarah Palin went on the show to do a bit with Tina Fey, and SNL was not flattering to Sarah Palin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually do a greek yogurt cup (lately usually Oikos triple zero ones) + half a scoop of protein powder. This morning's was 185 calories and 27g of protein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to throw in my 2 cents, I'm not sure the hotel advice rings true during busy season. Hotels/hostels tend to book up way in advance and you run the risk of being left with nowhere to stay. It's quite different during winter months.

Also, I took a one day tour on a minibus before renting a car and doing my own travel, and I actually loved it and would highly recommend it. I did a Golden Circle tour with Iceland Horizon. The driver was an older Iceland native and gave tons and tons of interesting information and great stories during the tour. It was nice to learn a bit more before heading out on my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they're lumpy they're probably a bit undermixed. They should ideally smooth out after you pipe them if the batter is the right consistency. Try adding a few extra stirs before you pipe them and see if that helps!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo I've never been a baker at all, and one day I decided out of the blue that I wanted to bake macarons as holiday gifts and just went with it. They turned out fine. Now I can't stop baking them. They're not really as bad as they seem, and even if they turn out less visually appealing than you want they still taste good. Go for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the cutest pie crust! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorites so far have been raspberry chocolate (a little smear of raspberry jam on one shell, and then pipe chocolate ganache onto the other), red velvet with cream cheese frosting, and lemon curd!

I keep seeing Smores and desperately need to try making them... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a tendency to do the exact same thing so I always go a bit longer than I think I need to! But I totally agree, the mixing is way more important than sifting. I actually made my last batch without sifting at all, just to experiment, and it was not at all noticeable. Undermixing prevents them from getting nice and smooth, and adding a few strokes takes WAY less time than sifting flour, so I'd go with that. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cute, I'm loving the little rainbow sprinkles on the white macarons!! I may need to steal that idea. Did you sprinkle them on before baking, or somehow adhere them later?

And I agree, it looks like they may be just a bit undermixed (maybe just the chocolate, I can't tell) which can prevent them from smoothing out as much and make them look a bit lumpier - I have a tendency to undermix too so I always try to go a bit longer than I think I need to. But they look fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 13:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the shells themselves, I use the Italian method - there are a ton of recipes that all slightly differ of course. The one I use is probably closest to [this one](http://loveandmacarons.blogspot.com/2013/01/macaron-recipe-italian-meringue-method.html). 

I didn't follow any particular recipe for the color and filling, I've just been experimenting, but getting a swirl like this is actually really easy. I just took a paintbrush and painted a few lines of food coloring gel down the insides of the piping bag before filling it up with the macaron batter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 16:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So adorable!! I really want to try macarons in other shapes like this... Did you just pipe circles first and then add the ears afterward with a smaller tip? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're very Barbie, but they're raspberry chocolate so I felt the need to go with some sort of pink/purple color scheme... Things to try next: rainbow swirl and maybe the "galaxy macarons" that I've seen here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Decided to try macarons with a color swirl - I love them! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 15:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My neighborhood is almost all cones, but my favorite is a children's lawn mower toy that my neighbor puts out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 19:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I used [this recipe](http://theblenderist.com/vegan-macarons-aquafaba-recipe/)! It uses aquafaba, which is just the liquid from cans of chickpeas. I guess you can also make your own by soaking beans in water if you wanted to. It's pretty amazing how well it whips up like egg whites! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cute! I clearly need more exciting cake pans in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorites! These look divine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually audibly gasped because these are so beautiful!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not vegan and have no experience doing any kind of vegan baking, but I have a vegan friend visiting and wanted to give this a shot.

It didn't go amazingly well - I think the temperature is partially to blame. Most recipes recommend cooking at a much lower temp than regular macarons, and for longer. I experimented a bit between two pans and not sure either way worked super well. Most of the batch looked [more like this](http://imgur.com/a/F2x3h), and a few of them cracked/were hollow inside. :)

However, I'm still impressed with how well aquafaba (the liquid in chickpea cans) whips up like egg whites!

They're filled with a thin layer of raspberry preserves, plus a vegan chocolate ganache. My ganache ratios were also a bit off (maybe just because almond milk is so thin) so that turned out a bit runny... Not my best work, but they taste fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vegan chocolate raspberry macarons - most of the batch was a failure, but I got a few good ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 14:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I was thinking more like this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mTTwcCVajAc t=2s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
