<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5460</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The suicide party episode in Welcome to NHk and the backstory of Tsubaki in Mirai Nikki </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Intermittent fasting](https://www.reddit.com/r/intermittentfasting/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This! Di ko mapigilang umindak kapag naririnig to. Speaking of this anime. Ilalabas na daw yung 4th installment ng End of Evangelion. Can't wait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 07:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  School Days Ending
  
May ghawd! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im planning to continue reading Ready Player One. I put this on hold last year as I was got busy with work..and life :D. What I remember from this book is, this has a lot of 80's reference, which Im not familiar with LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember I was having a hard time putting this down too. I almost re-read the series 3 times until I got them all out in my system hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sabi nung college friend madali lang i-drawing ang mukha ko. Drawing lang daw sya ng plato na may 2 tuldok, tapos na! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eto ba yong [Hario V60](http://www.lazada.com.ph/hario-vd-02w-coffee-dripper-v60-02-white-7664870.html?rb=7003) and [AeroPress](http://www.lazada.com.ph/aeropress-coffee-maker-basic-set-80r11-236838.html) ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> automatic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magkano at saan makakabili? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any recommended coffee maker? kahit 5c lang. TIA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any recommended podcast? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feeling ko meditiation na lang ang kulang sa daily habit ko..pero di ko alam kung saan mag-uumpisa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feeling ko meditiation na lang ang kulang sa daily habit ko..pero di ko alam kung mag-uumpisa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asian here! My typical meal(lunch) is fish or chicken with steamed/cooked vegetables.  I completely remove rice from my diet. It was hard at first but I got used to it eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **01** Reached 50 kg by the end of the March. Currently at 53 kg  
**02** 5 days of 18/6 IF with 2 days of 24H a week  
**03** I'll report only what are noticeable changes ie. weight, feeling during the fast etc. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was your menstruation? I remember when I tried IF in 2014, my period became regular (I have a irregular period which is one of the symptoms of PCOS) I was only diagnosed with PCOS later last year. That time I already stopped IF and my menstruation back to irregular. Now, Im doing 18/6 IF again for almost 3 months now to see if my menstruation will be back to normal again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rehydration tablet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone here take a rehydration/electrolyte tablet when fasting for longer days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saan sya nabibili? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merong coffee maker sa office na di nagagamit. And since napapagastos ako ng 40-60 pesos para lang sa kape ng 7/11 araw-araw, naisip ko na bakit di na lang ako bumili ng pang 'brew'. Ngayon ang tanong ko anong best coffee ang magandang bilhin na mura lang? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed reading these 2 and gave me the same "vibes"  
1.[Oregairu](https://www.baka-tsuki.org/project/?title=My_Youth_Romantic_Comedy_Is_Wrong_As_I_Expected) (A light novel. It has an anime version too)  
2. [More Than This by Patrick Ness](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/21969786-more-than-this) (Its a dystopia though) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was what the protagonist said about being alert; not prejudging things, listening to what's going on, keeping your ears, heart and mind open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I like most of japanese novels. They describe loneliness and isolation like it's a wonderful thing that can happen to anyone. They romanticize it, just like falling in love.  
  
The truth is, my book kryptonites are the books with lonely main protagonist. In fact one of my favorite books is Perks of Being a Wallflower by Stephen Chbosky 
  
You really lucky to have a teacher who guided you to the art of writing. I regret now that I didn't stay in journalism when I was in highschool( poverty and family problem got in the way) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Di yata nakakain ng maayos dahil sa paglandi ko hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but it turns out he ate again after our dinner hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not completely related to dating but I still want to share..  
  
This just happened last week. As I was about to go and grab a dinner, I saw my officemate. We decided to eat together since we were both alone. We talked a lot of things from work to hobbies and I just kind of flirted with him and show that I am interested on him (Im sure he's single and not currently dating)  
  
Then after an hour or so, after our dinner, I saw his facebook post about food, tagging another girl :(  
  
That's the most pathetic thing that Ive ever felt in my entire existence since that was the first time I really flirt with a guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ako naman nakahanap ng 20 pesos sa jacket ko. Pinambili ko ng mochaccino ng 7/11 hehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im currently reading Sputnik Sweetheart by Haruki Murakami. Its a story of a guy who is in love with his lesbian best friend. Im trying to read it slowly and intensively as I really want to understand it thoroughly. What I like about this book is,  I feel like I am eating a bread for the first time after being hungry for so long. That's how I describe it.

This is the first book I read after being on hiatus for almost a year. And Im reading this book for almost a month now despite this being a short novel. I hope I can finish this week.

On unrelated note, i like your writing, OP. Its really good. What did you do to be able to write like that? Sorry for my poor english writing. Im still improving though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ako yung pang-ritemed version lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you already have a planned routine to achieve number 2? I really lije to have a flawless skin too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it safe to do this if you're totally a beginner? (No experience in meditation) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a time when I sneezed 10x consecutively. [Like this](https://youtu.be/9NwFwM6R8jI)  
  
On average, I sneeze 5x consecutively
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 05:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oi galing sakin yan ah..hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Financially stabled ka na ba? Wag kung hindi pa.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Wag nyong pagtawanan ang isang taong nagsisikap na i-improve ang sarili nya" - me to my mother. 

Hayss..nakaka-toxic sa bahay..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
