<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject723</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't the first line say this is not intended to be made public? At that point I stopped reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumpnut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russell Moore: Why Sola Scriptura Matters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We always think of the "culture " being pornography, drug abuse, nihilism, etc, but a large swath of the "culture" is just shallow, self-righteous conservatism.  In a way, that is very similar to the culture Christ had to deal with in his time.  This recent election has really opened my eyes to this, as I'm sure it has yours.  
This self-centered conservative culture is as corrosive as the other-maybe even more so because it has the sheen of morality while rejecting the Christ-taught ethos of "love your neighbor".
The only way to change these views in your young friend is to SHOW him another way.  Service is the body when faith is the spirit.  You aren't going to argue or proof him out of it.  Also, point him to an immersive scriptural experience-in the Word every day-the Word on the morning-the Word in the mid-day- the Word in the evening.  This is where transformation starts.
I would point him specifically to the parable of the Sower and point out that these theories he's preoccupied with ARE the thorns sucking the nutrients from the good soil-occupying the space that passion for Christ should </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cows ARE delicious... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like a TMZ writer wrote an article on a book his roommate read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name of the Wind by Patrick Rothfuss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "All for naught" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were cute!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just shoot the dog.  Go buy another one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All out at the buffet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha!  Watching biketards wreck is the only way to spend a Sunday afternoon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think you were being hateful.  The sign just said you shouldn't be-and it's right.  If you want to understand how to reach the homosexual community for Christ you should check out Rosario Butterfield's testimony.  She's been up on The Gospel Coalition podcasts quite a lot recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donorcycle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to worship a painting or a statue, go for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be hateful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are trained to intubate, so if the need arose I would certainly do it and ask forgiveness later.  Our hospital has a lot of resources and we have an airway team that can be there in a flash-staffed by 2 anesthesia residents-so generally we are covered.  
I do TEEs ( IMACOR), arterial lines, PIV, chest  tube and other drain removal, wound debridements, sew lacerations, apply and change wound vacs, change out tracheostomies, place trans pyloric dobhoff tubes.  I don't do all of those every day, but wouldn't be surprised to do some of those most days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intubations and chest tubes, Bronchoscopies-I'd like to do all these.  Each state has its own limitations and each hospital will allow midlevels to do various things.  PAs in my state can do CVLS (IJs, not femoral or subclavian)-but the residents are desperate do them because they need a certain number-so generally you are just helping do those procedures.  Still-it is awesome and I still love it after 7 years.  I sleep like a rock when I get home.  I learn something new every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I arrive before 5am-the other PAs and I are in charge of assigning the 28 patients.  Depending on how many residents we have we may see anywhere from 4-8 patients each.  
Usually I'll go do a physical exam, lab/micro/rad review, and type in the progress note with the plan for the day.  Then we will all (attending, fellow,resident, students, sometimes RT, sometimes Charge RN) do bedside rounds on half the unit.  There are 2 PAs there during the day and our 28 beds are divided into 2 loops.  While the "low side is rounding, the same thing is happening with another attending on the other side.  The attending surgeons sign off on our plan for the day or alter it.  It's very collaborative-everyone has input and no one is discouraged from challenging a plan or whatever.  Full-contact rounds.
This takes us to about 10am.  Then we really get to work doing procedures, calling consults, doing tertiary injury surveys, weaning vents, extubating or intubating people, talking to families, moving people in or out of the unit and responding to emergencies, changes in condition-all the bad stuff that happens to these people.  We usually get off after 5pm, just depending what's going on.
Last night I got off at 630pm because a patient became acutely hypotensive and I was at the bedside managing the vent, getting him on pressors, performing a bedside TEE to establish preload status, ordering stat labs, and generally trying to keep the guy from coding.  Fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KILL IT WITH FIRE!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just upvoted you for being so tolerant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no upvote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decreased property values?  Increased insurance costs?  Increased road and infrastructure costs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a PA.  I work in a 28 bed level 1 Trauma ICU.  I do direct patient care, vent management, bedside procedures, etc.  We are the continuity in the ICU as our fellows, residents, students, and military guys rotate through.  It's a ton of fun, always busy, great schedule (we make our own, 20 12-hour shifts every 6 weeks).  We are just above median for salary, but the schedule is the best. I have 4 kids, so I want to see them.
As a PA you have a lot of choice in what you do and where you work.  Just remember it's now a complete meritocracy-if you suck you won't do well; if you're good you'll be fine.  Also, you will never work for an MD or group that is NOT swamped.   Otherwise, they wouldn't need you, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John the Apostle's works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happens a lot.  A gunshot is not a terribly reliable way to kill someone.  I work in a level 1 trauma center.

Good for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know the White House had short bus parking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's FAUX News when you need them, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's part of the atmosphere now.  You might as well complain that cartoons aren't real people.  Satire lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just laughed out loud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you aren't naked with a sharp rock ONLY, it's not TRUE camping.  I disdain your "tent" camping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine to all of that-just don't lose sight that this is a relationship, not a mechanism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it has to be followed by "eh". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that he doesn't love America, it's just that he loves himself SO much more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KILL IT WITH FIRE!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NDGT is as overexposed as Bill Nye and Miley Cyrus.  Sick of their faces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy fresh veggies in very small amounts.  Plan to eat what you buy that same day or the next.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just put in the #4guard and shave away.  Haven't paid for a haircut in 7 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And-he's dead, Jim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously-the guy is more exposed than Miley Cyrus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is such a piece of trash.  Here's hoping for a stroke-for the good of the nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are not five sparrows sold for two pennies? And not one of them is forgotten before God. Why, even the hairs of your head are all numbered. Fear not; you are of more value than many sparrows.
Luke 12:6-7  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, they're wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone else sick of seeing Bill Nye's face?  It like seeing Trump's smarmy mug, but nerdier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smash it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumphat makes an 8 a 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our favorite section is from there to Hwy 19!  Shhhhh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go ahead and quarter him before he gets too dehydrated .  Delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I could move to ANY town in CO to be near good hiking/camping and skiing, wanted to not break the bank or be around a bunch of rich people-where should I go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I see Darth Vader's body... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pinhote trail near Talladega in Alabama-Mount Cheeha.  This is just east of Anniston/Oxford on I20.  The absolute best views in Alabama and LOTS of overlooks.  

The Dismals in northwest Alabama-I've heard are good.  Not been there myself, but been to Sipsey Wilderness right around there and had a ton of fun.

In Northwestern GA we like Amicalola Falls-hike to the Hike Inn, then do a section of the AT.

In TN and NC, our favorite section of the AT is Carver's Gap to Hwy 18 in NC.  It's about a 23 mile stretch.  You should take about 2 days to do that.  Any AT section is worth the walk, but that section with the "Balds" is really something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hire a house cleaner to come once a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one would even care if he hadn't made such a big deal about Obama's golfing.  He just can't keep his fat orange face shut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 10:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 human life is worth more than all the animal lives on the planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get your yearly colonoscopy too?  You only have one colon... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still have to fax or send a copy or they call the prescribing optometrist to confirm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike your mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to have an active prescription to buy contact lenses and hose expire yearly.  This-the yearly exam.  Hence the frugal tip to buy overseas.  There.  Linear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no idea what you are talking about in regards to "screening".  I'm using it as a medical term.  If you get your screening colonoscopy at the county fair you might want to call the police and do a quick internet image search with your name and "gape" in the search field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you tell people not to sleep in their contacts?  That's got to be malpractice to allow people to sleep in them.  Then you have them come back twice a year?  You're like a fungal infection/corneal
Ulcer epidemic on your own!
How much per visit on your market?  It's $100 in mine.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I linked to an extensive document titled Comprehensive Adult Eye Visual Examination, Evidence Based Clinical Practice Guidelines. Here's the link again:

http://aoa.uberflip.com/i/578152-aoa-clinical-practice-guidelines-adult-eye-exam/24?

If that doesn't work just Google it.

I don't care what your recondition is.  I assume you are an optometrist?  How much do you charge for your yearly screening exams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great!  Save 50%.  Go every 2.
Enjoy your yearly full-body MRI with the savings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sure, have no need to beg!  You are getting the screening exam at the EXACT interval recommended as the standard of care!  It's not yearly-so you are saving 50% more than the other retarded posters having an emotional breakdown that I would dare suggest you not go yearly.
I am not recommending never getting eye exams, simply getting them at a reasonable frequency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AOA recommends an exam every 2 years for most people.  You won't see that posted in the optometrist office-so I linked it for you on my last comment.  I bet if you got a yearly colonoscopy and full body MRI they'd find some stuff too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AOA recommends eye exams every 2 years-not every year.  I helpfully linked it for you.  Enjoy your yearly full-body MRI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you.  See my last comment for the APA recommendation on exam frequency.  It's every 2 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my last comment.  Why not get a mammogram, PAP smear, and colonoscopy every year too?  Because they are screening exams, that's why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's TIA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To all the redditors currently having an emotional breakdown over my suggestion- the AOA only recommends screening EVERY 2 YEARS for most people.

http://aoa.uberflip.com/i/578152-aoa-clinical-practice-guidelines-adult-eye-exam/24?

See page 25

By the way, I do vaccinate my kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  Every single person lives in a city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have legitimate problems that need me monitoring.  Not every member of the population from age 16 up needs to be screened for glaucoma, detached retina, optic neuritis, etc.  That's my point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From your histrionics I'd guess you were female, right?  How bout if the "standard of care" just happened to be a yearly breast exam and mammogram at $100 a pop starting at age 35?  You'd defer your internist "feeling you up" every year I'd wager-mate.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever heard of overscreening?

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/m/pubmed/25591194/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snarky.  It's fine if you disagree.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your eyes will liquefy like that Nazi who looked on the Ark in Raiders of the Lost Ark.   Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my 20 years of wearing contacts I've never had a corneal ulcer.  I have so been skipping the yearly exam for about 5 of those.  
Just use common sense is what I am advocating.  Corneal ulcers come with symptoms-if you detect any, go to the doctor.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.com/amp/mobile.reuters.com/article/amp/idUSKBN1684GI

Mine's most recent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha!  This post, like your pic, is probably not for everyone.  If you notice a mushroom starting to grow out of you eye, go to the doctor.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't pay for a yearly eye exam just so you can buy the same script 10 years in a row. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off-if you need an eye exam, go get one.  I trust that, as adults, we can detect when one of our own senses has degraded to the point that an intervention is required.  At the very least our wives will let us know, right?
So it galls me that you can't buy disposable contact lenses in the US without an active script.  The Optometrists have decided that you need to be reexamine at least once a year.  Why this often?  $.  
So I say screw them.  I'm not dropping $100a year just for the privilege of buying the exact same lenses for 10 years in a row.
So, my frugal friends, simply buy from Europe.  I use VisionDirect, but I'm sure there are plenty of other companies that sell the exact product that you'd get here without paying the Optometrist's second mortgage with an unnecessary yearly eye exam.  If things get blurry, make an appointment. Duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You pay taxes, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my personal experience this heresy is so pernicious because the RCC refuses to submit to common uses of common words.  They DO pray to and worship Mary, by any definition that any thinking person but a Church Lawyer would admit to.  JP 2 called her "co-redemptrix" compulsively-essentially redefining the RCC dogma on salvation after Vatican 2.  
The RCC is a twisted nest of heresy-they've not changed for 1500 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be polite.  You don't have to make an issue of it with someone your DON'T EVEN KNOW at a friggin barbecue!  Just say, '"oh excuse me!  Sorry about that." And then move on.  I mean, really, what else are you going to say to this person?
Is this an issue of "TGIE" or just common sense and decency?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless he's saying all the Pedophile Priests will be chemically neutered or excommunicated I don't care to hear anything from his mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No-that's where all the people are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one knows what their lifetime is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the divorce rates among Christians, I'd say this is hardly a huge problem.  In specific instances, law enforcement needs to be involved and after that Church discipline enforced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That can't have been very hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That kid fell out of the ugly tree... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sucks.  Rich \=good taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah.

They are being destroyed forever-not they have been destroyed and will never be undestroyed.  You are simply taking an idea you want to be true, twisting some verses in that direction and hoping it sticks.  Annihilationism has been refuted effectively for millennia.  It keeps popping up because people just can't believe a loving God would punish someone FOREVER!  That can't ACTUALLY mean forever-it must have been misinterpreted or Jesus must have been mistaken.
And these will go away into eternal punishment, but the righteous into eternal life.
Matthew 25:46  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The quote I used was from a RC Theology website.  It wasn't saying that JP coined the term, just that he used it early and often, enshrining it in the practice of the RC Church.  The Vicar of Christ said it!  God's DIRECT representative on earth, no less...

1).  So, what you are saying is everyone, regardless of their heart, who has attended a mass AT ANY POINT has prayed to God.  Well, that just makes no sense.  I'm not even going to break that argument down because it is already broken.

2).  The whole praying to God through the saints is not correct either.  Supposedly you are asking the Saints to intercede for you in some regard-not praying directly to God.  Beyond the question of whether they can even hear you (no scriptural indication that they can, but I understand the RC Church holds Scripture as on equal authority as tradition-that is to say, degrades Scripture), you still aren't praying TO God.  Christ said He is the ONLY mediator-the ONLY mediator-the ONLY mediator.  Did I say the ONLY mediator?  Yes, the ONLY one.
For there is one God, and there is one mediator between God and men, the man Christ Jesus,
1 Timothy 2:5  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fucking horrifying!  How long did they spend in the ICU?  Does their face scare children now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I buy my contacts from Europe-same brand and I don't need to get a damn eye exam every year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KILL IT WITH FIRE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no new heresies, just the same tired old  ones trotted out every generation or so to befuddle fools who don't have time to actually read the Bible.
Annihilationism.  Look it up.

And the smoke of their torment goes up forever and ever, and they have no rest, day or night, these worshipers of the beast and its image, and whoever receives the mark of its name.
Revelation 14:11 

Fairly good overview of why Fudge is wrong.
https://www.thegospelcoalition.org/article/j.i.-packer-on-why-annihilationism-is-wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
