<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3861</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Several thousand Poles protest against right-wing ruling party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal grant that Trump wanted to abolish is a lifeline for poor families </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ivanka is the true champion of women! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration proposes massive cuts to Drug Czar office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, most people generally do. Having experienced him face to face must be a terrible experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump lashes out at 'fake media' over coverage of healthcare act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, but women are always equal under the law in modern society, so women don't need feminism. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk, can someone quantify the exact number of fuck yous to women are in this bill?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House-passed GOP health care plan is 'unconstitutional,' NY attorney general says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not quite.

Le Pen is different from Trump. For one, the Le Pen name has loomed over French politics for what seems like forever. She is an established politician. Not only that, but Le Pen's economic policies are alien to the ideas thought up by the GOP. Le Pen can at least pay lip service to the welfare state.

Macron also has difference from Clinton. For one, he is much younger with much less experience. And he isn't running as part of an establishment party, his is brand new.

And Melenchon- he isn't even close to Bernie. Bernie in France would be considered establishment left. Melenchon is far to the left, a staunch anti-capitalist. 

Also, Le Pen doesn't really have a chance. I know people like to talk about how the polls are all wrong, but she's like 20 points behind. To be that far off would be unprecedented, a whole different league from Brexit or Trump. And Macron doesn't have to worry about having the election stolen from him by an undemocratic electoral system.

Honestly, it seems to me like Americans like to see every global event as an extension of their own country. Not everything is a parallel to America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate how everything requires a constitutional amendment to change, but constitutional amendments are borderline impossible to push through. Seriously, I honestly wish we could get a new constitution because our system is in serious need of reform in all areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, should have caught that, I read hamlet a couple of years ago. I was confused for a second there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you mean to write "Denmark"?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Memorialized Civil War Battle That Never Happened On His Va. Golf Course </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Czech PM reverses planned resignation as political crisis deepens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US negotiator of Paris climate deal: Exit would do 'enormous damage' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vulnerable House Republicans fear political consequences after healthcare vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is not the health-care bill that Trump promised </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a criticism of socialism, it was a criticism of Joseph Stalin (aka Napoleon) and how he violated so many fundamental leftist principles and established a police state and a cult of personality and put the USSR in a situation just as bad as it was in before under the repression of the farmer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Next Step for the Republican Health Care Bill: A Skeptical Senate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamacare repeal likely to factor into Indiana's Senate race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India set to launch satellite for South Asian countries, Pakistan says no thanks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malcolm Turnbull still isn't very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the GOP's Health-Care Gamble Means for 2018 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump Praised Australias Universal Health Care Right After The House Repealed Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *SPACE* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the skittles colourless too, or just the packaging? Because if it's the skittles too then I wouldn't buy this because I like knowing what colour skittle I'm eating. 

Either way, obviously a scheme to save them money because now they don't even have to pay to add the colours to the packaging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, what aren't they ruining? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the heck is there an apostrophe in "white's" when they're not using it as a possessive? Damn it you white supremacists who don't use proper grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semi-related

The number of people I know who understand nothing from Orwell and just think it means socialism=bad is just astounding. People fail to realise George Orwell was an anti-capitalist, and never intended to have his works interpreted as support for capitalism. The reason for that is they teach it that way in schools, I've had to sit through a teacher lecturing about how Animal Farm supports capitalism, even though that misses the whole point. Anyway, people forget that the main target of his criticism was authoritarianism in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands protest at Yemen president's sacking of southern leaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria: Russia, Turkey, Iran agree on safe zones at ceasefire talks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MLK is rolling in his grave. I've been seeing more and more of this in the news. I think it was SC that had an incident recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to capitalism, where your bright ideas will do nothing for you while other people get richer by doing nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deported mother and son at risk of getting killed, US senator says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is US steering clear of South China Sea under Trump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, good, for a second there I thought it would just be a white flag or something dumb like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...This makes no sense. Texas leaves=America becomes ISIS? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that's one of the harder ones. 

I'm just glad I still have like a week left to study for AP Euro, because that's going to be not fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sean Spicer clashes with press over definition of a wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans are trying to decrease overtime pay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the United States get colonised by the European Union and I just didn't notice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those people with cancer should have just worked harder, then they wouldn't need the government to get them free stuff like health insurance. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do-or-die: EU pushes Trump to stick to Paris climate deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, sorry, I see how that slipped now. I used the key words "Libya" and "France" in the search function, and that post had them hyphenated as one word, so I guess they didn't show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
