<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8379</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, you'll keep digging and avoiding your claim. Got it. 

There are lots of discussions about herbicide use--which, if you understood the field better, you would find are not unique to GMOs. I've seen some calls for more herbicide use as a way to ensure resistance doesn't develop as quickly. 

But your claim continues to be wrong, no matter how much smoke on other issues you want to raise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, here's how claims work. You made a claim (which was incorrect). I showed you the evidence from a national academy report, and from a weed researcher. 

You need to support your claim. And here's a pro-tip: the academy specifically said that the pounds-on-the-ground metric is not the right one to use. In your own quote of it, they say why: "because such data can mislead readers."

You've been misled by whatever your sources are. You could stop digging (which would be wise), or you can show the evidence you have (which better not be pounds on the ground).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to grab a copy of the lyrics, all credit to this team for the work:

Join us on 22nd of April 11am @HMS Quad in Boston for a rally 'Science is good for your health'. Keynote speaker: HMS dean prof. George Daley!

www.marchforscienceharvard.com

Donate to Boston March for Science chapter: https://www.marchforscienceboston.com...

Lyrics:
STAND UP FOR SCIENCE
(sung to the tune of "This Land is Your Land" by Woody Guthrie)

Stand up for science-
No time for silence!
The cure for cancer-
We need an answer.
Hear our entreaties-
Cure diabetes.
Science is good for you and me!

For global warming,
The facts come swarming.
Climate denial-
It's suicidal!
You might deny it-
We just don't buy it.
Science is good for you and me.

Don't de-fund science-
Join our alliance!
New forms of energy-
It's time for synergy.
To protect our planet,
Science- don't ban it!!!
Science is good for you and me!

You huddled masses-
Come take our classes.
If you are yearning-
Come here for learning.
And after college-
Please share your knowledge.
Science is good for you and me!

Our Muslim brothers,
Sisters and others:
We stand beside you
And won't deride you
Banned immigration-
Bad for our nation
Science is good for you and me!

Healthcare is our right,
For which we must fight.
Our vision's global
Our cause is noble.
It's our insistence-
Join the resistance!
Science is good for you and me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March for Science unofficial anthem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't access the article, there's a handy tweetstorm from one of the authors: https://twitter.com/skathire/status/852204881616261120 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human knockouts and phenotypic analysis in a cohort with a high rate of consanguinity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indigenous-owned company brings renewable energy to First Nations - CBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can keep trying to weasel out of your claim, but that does also not say 
My issue is round up ready crops are using more pesticides than non-GMO crops ever did.

I am not misunderstanding this report that you just discovered, that I followed the whole time during the webinars, the release, the subsequent discussions.

One more time--this is not true:
My issue is round up ready crops are using more pesticides than non-GMO crops ever did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently it wasn't indexed when I searched for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yah, but what do you do when those are public, but they aren't anywhere else? 

The Facebook one I posted yesterday was open--I have never had a facebook account and I could see it. And this is twitter--which is also banned as a source on this sub. I searched YouTube for this and it wasn't available.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's something that I need to understand better as some of my hopes for other routes are disappearing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's not what you are saying, so you can be an ass and stop lying. 

What you said:
My issue is round up ready crops are using more pesticides than non-GMO crops ever did.

And when confronted with the science that does not show that that GMOs are using more pesticides than non-GMOs did, you resort to namecalling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is world-class nutty. Thanks for shining the light on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upcoming talk: Solar Geoengineering -- w/Taylor Milsal - Long Now Boston (Cambridge, MA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of the prohibition on Facebook and twitter, for the second day in a row I can't post a great skeptic-relevant video. Can we discuss that?

Here's the only copy I can find of this. It's really funny. https://twitter.com/theweeklytv/status/852121917960011776 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learn about herd immunity and the stink bus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People upvoted the refutation I posted with pretty good numbers. Most of aren't humorless and understand the symbolism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On eve of science march, planners look ahead | Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Lynas on why scientists suck as activists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not clear on why I can't link to facebook from here, but there's a great video that addresses the tension between science and activism. It's a clip from a GMO film that I don't think exists anywhere else. The film producers came out in support of Science March today and released this to go with their announcement. They asked people to share it around. It's a public page--I'm not even on facebook and I can see it. 

You can find it at the facebook dot com and then /FoodEvoMovie/videos/279149632528806/

I think it's hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a thought: my community was gifted with some chargers. They couldn't find enough places to put them (yah, I know, I wasn't involved at the time). 

Give your city's enviro office a call and see if anyone has heard of this kind of thing. Someone could be sitting on one that needs a home. Worth a shot before you spend money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is the closest to right that I've seen on opinion/editorial pieces.

But large numbers and strong opinions are what give protests their power. Despite internal wrinkles, the positive message that crowds of pro-science people on the streets present to the broader world will surely show through.

Despite the inside baseball that we've played on this, our neighbors want to support us. They need us to lead on this, because it's our responsibility. To the wider public, the internal squabbles are not going to be what they remember about this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opinion: Lets march to stress the value of science for the public good, not to engage in partisan politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh. I saw a really good post on that today. https://sustainableschoolteacher.blogspot.com/2017/04/an-open-letter-to-teachers.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Lynas on the inherent conflicts in science activism (video clip) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump wants to cut billions from the NIH. This is what well miss out on if he does. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it will get coverage. Some of it will joyously say that turnout was lower than people hoped.

That said, I think it matters more that you bring friends, you take photos and post them to your facebook page, post them to twitter. 

I think that to some extent the media is on our side on this. And general public folks I saw in Boston want to support us. 

But we have to show up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Church gives a sneak peek of his March for Science speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sessions orders Justice Dept. to end forensic science commission, suspend review policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm Marching for Science! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you been watching as the Assembly developers try to get out of that? The more ways we have to hold developers to their promises, the better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pretty good list. But I know they are open to more partners.

 Union Square residents

 Union Square business owners

 CAAS

 Concord Ave Community Space

 Groundwork Somerville

 The Haitian Coalition

 Immigrant Service Providers Group/Health

 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 103

 SEIU Local 888

 Fr. Ademir Guerini, pastor of St. Anthonys parish

 Fr. Richard Curran, pastor of St. Josephs, St. Catherines, and St. Anns parishes

 Pra. Leide Miculic, pastor of Last Hour Ministry Casa de Orao

 SCATV

 Somerville Community Corporation

 Somerville Homeless Coalition 

 Somerville Labor Coalition

 Teen Empowerment

 The Welcome Project

 UNITE HERE Local 26

 Ruby Rogers Center

Tell me about the other groups, and the size of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, they were fucking patenting seeds back then.

And every crop today is still *regional*. There's a different variety for different regions because of weather, maturity date, and a number of other features. You don't actually understand the seed market at all, do you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The National Academy was a major report. Sorry you missed it. It was kind of big last year. It is hard to keep up, though.

https://www.nap.edu/catalog/23395/genetically-engineered-crops-experiences-and-prospects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bring local science-related links and citizen science opportunities to your march </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone today was asking me about the march, and whether it's really a good idea to get into the streets. I firmly believe that visibility matters very much, and that our facebook and twitter photos will make people realize that their community does value science.

I was also thinking back to the Boston rally, during the AAASmeeting. Now, I'm from Boston and I was at the AAAS rally. But even I didn't know most of these people. The ones I talked to were largely non-scientist neighbors who are looking for a way to support us.

I had several conversations with people who wanted to do more. One woman asked me if there was some kind of science-led petition to sign. Another guy asked me for local events to connect with science. I gave him a couple of pub science sorts of things. 

But I was wishing I'd had some small flyers with links. So I'd like to recommend to you to bring some quarter-sheets perhaps. Put the links to local science and technology meetup groups, or facebook pages, or local science-based projects that you know about.

Some of this may come from the organizers. But if you have something, bring it. It would be great to get these people to future engagement activities. 

For example, in Boston I recommended:
**Science By the Pint**, http://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/science-by-the-pint/

**Boston Skeptics** https://www.meetup.com/BostonSkeptics/

**Long Now Boston** https://www.meetup.com/Long-Now-Boston/

**DIY Biohacker group in my town** https://www.meetup.com/BosLab/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your logo. I'm really enjoying seeing all the local version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ford Fusion hybrid police sedan rated at 38 mpg combined city, highway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a retrograde idea. It is very hard in cities to ensure that EV owners can charge at their homes, as high-density housing means that many people may rent or share facilities--and some may have no access at all. Making this harder is a way to ensure people won't have the confidence to switch.

But I'm glad to know about this, thanks for bringing it. We have a net-zero city meeting coming up, and I'm going to raise the issue of parking regs for EVs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hasn't gone well for Specter. Which is really strange, he's usually good on science issues. And someone who has closely watched the AIDS situation play out should know exactly how much street action and visibility made a difference in policy and research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Vaccines Cause Autism in Dogs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterinarians doubt validity of ImmuneIQ allergy test | Vets do a great sting on crank diagnostic test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, these folks have worked really hard to develop a large network and to include so many different groups, it was really great to see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really don't seem to have a grasp of this at all. The CBA agreements include affordable housing.

I'm so glad I brought this over. There's so much misinformation about there on this topic, and I really appreciate how much of that you demonstrated. Thanks so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what the National Academy study found. https://twitter.com/subject8379/status/732592637690142721

My other favorite image on that is here: https://twitter.com/WyoWeeds/status/713084964846182401 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever happened to the heroes? | Sweary take on food + plant science and Borlaug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On twitter I got the SkeptVet's attention with this, and he contacted the researcher whose data is being misused by these cranks. The researcher completely disavows his work supports these claims. 

He's gonna write it up. I'll bring that over when it goes live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let science be science again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March for science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autism Symptoms in Pets Rise as Pet Vaccination Rates Rise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monocultures existed before GMOs, and if GMOs went away tomorrow there would still be monocultures.

It's really important to get to the right target if you want to really look at an issue and make changes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March For Science - Amsterdam - 22 April 2017 | Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to hear people celebrate that science give us great things--it drives prosperity, it benefits our health, and it gives us tools to ask and answer the right questions.

But I also think we have to illustrate what the threats are. Do you like clean water? Do you like tornado warnings? Do you like the idea of a Zika vaccine? 

If you have specific local examples, I would also tie it to those. And give people ways to get involved. Volunteer with the watershed group. Join the Medical Reserve Corps. Give science talks in pubs. And, of course, stay connected and call your representatives when a science issue is looming. 

I think it should be part inspiration, part rallying the base, and part call to action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Further progress for Florida antiscience bills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for making the case that crappy structures can have impact for a century. And your self-centered interest in your property value also makes the case for why neighbors want to influence how their neighborhoods work in ways besides profit. 

Couldn't have made a better case for CBAs. Thanks for coming by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you understand that if roughshod development of crappy and careless structures disrupts the neighborhoods--the Somerville you love ceases to exist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Googles fact check feature goes global and comes to Google Search </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the label drama is currently on hold, they are not quite sure where to aim. They have shifted a lot of effort to glypho-hate. 

I also think the gene editing thing is about to stump them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, that's not it at all. Sounds like you have a lot to learn about them. 

Or, maybe you are a developer, and prefer to just extract profits from a community and leave it with a giant ugly structure and nothing that benefits the community at all. Donnie, is that you? 

But many of us care about the quality of life in our existing neighborhoods, and we want to ensure that affordable housing options are part of any project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wondered that too, but I can't be arsed to look into what they think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CKNW Energy Series: Electric cars | News Talk 980 CKNW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I watched Alex Jones give his viewers health advice. Heres what I learned. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Climate Change Deniers in Charge, Time for Scientists to Step Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> William Shatners Twitter Meltdown Is a Classic Case of Misinformation Spread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its a strange world, after all: Orac vs. The Shat and fake news overAutism Speaks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Solar Massachusetts Renewable Target (SMART) Program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am posting this because last night the Winter Hill neighborhood group had a meeting, and we want to learn from other neighborhoods about best practices for having some influence over development in our area. 

Union United folks came to tell us about their experiences. It was great. http://unionunitedsomerville.com/

CBAs are a way for the neighbors to try to hold developers to some commitments for the way changes to the neighborhood to roll out. 

Union United is piloting one in Somerville, but our group and other neighborhood groups should be planning for this and thinking about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learn about CBAs, Community Benefits Agreements | Union Square </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress's one PhD-trained scientist will join march on Washington </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna say you could package them and sell on Etsy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just put one of these types of things on a city-owned EV that does not understand EV etiquette. It's always parked in one of the 2 charger spaces.

The ones I have include a broader type of issues. I will go back to the city site periodically and see if it changed the behavior. 

Someone recently pointed to these on etsy: https://www.etsy.com/listing/496637243/ev-etiquette-survival-pack-gift-pack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. I haven't seen vaccines used as an argument on gut flora before. Man, these guys adapt quickly to inciting fears that are trendy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I wish I had known this before I made my flight plans. But maybe I can make the later stuff.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before You Join that Science March: An Undark Essay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I called mine Leafy McLeafface. I need to do better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things that cause cancer: alcohol.
Things that don't cause cancer: GMO.

Which one did you ban from your product? Yah. That makes sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Greenhog day. Again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Concerned About "Alternative Facts?" Get Out The Science! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Egads, yeah--even just looking at crank books gets me more "recommendations" about them. But I do sometimes read them for oppo research. And for reviews. https://www.biofortified.org/2014/11/the-gmo-deception-is-in-fact-deceptive/

Typically, though, I do not want to give cranks any purchases so those I get the ISBN and check them out of the library.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, some people are offering poster signs too. You can just print them up. http://allianceforscience.cornell.edu/medium-march-science-print-posters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My housemate took a lot of photos at the Boston rally, I gathered people's tweets, and I collected a lot of press stories that have photos you could look through too.

https://storify.com/subject8379/no-science-no-beer-no-science-no-coffee

EDIT to add one more thought: **please consider doing something on both the front and the back of your poster. When people are behind you and taking photos, you want to appear in their images too.**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds OK Green Line extension costs, securing projects future - The Boston Globe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good idea. People have to change cars so it's possible there's low-use stuff out there. Thanks for that tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. I read it earlier, but I see the same thing you do now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Co-purchasing seems like an odd way to assess things like this. Maybe other people buy multiple books at a time, but I usually don't. And I get a lot of stuff from the library. 

They could also be work-related purchases, gifts, lots of confounding here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I didn't see that coming: it ended up being a defense of skeptical thought and rational thinking, via mockery.

Hmm. Must up my game in comment sections. MOAR SATIRE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh. Yeah, every time I mention that around someone asks that. 

But this group has awesome institutional memory, great connections and deep city info, and is so rarely trolled. 

There was a profile on it a while back: http://scoutsomerville.com/davis-square-livejournal/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks--I was worried it was an autocorrect. I was just on Evergreen a couple of hours ago and didn't see any signs. Maybe I'll swing by Howe later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am in the market for a kayak rack. Anybody got advice on this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been in the market for this for a long time. I dumped the ICE vehicle with a rack that was 14 years old, so I haven't had to explore this at all for a while.

Good or bad experiences are welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Join us for the first ever SustainaVille Week! April 22nd - 28th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is Homer Street? I can't find it. I'd be willing to walk over there and see if there are flyers around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dog found on Broadway near Winter Hill Bank | White Bichon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently re-watched *How to Survive a Plague* because they were such an effective and recent science and social protest movement, and I was struck by the power and simplicity of the "Silence = Death" message on their protest signs. So that's the context for what I'm gonna ask for.

I would like to convey that Science = Life Prosperity Health. I learned about the phrase "Life Prosperity Health" when I studied hieroglyphics in college. After the pharoah's name, they would always write L/P/H. It's called Ankh wedja seneb. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ankh_wedja_seneb

People won't know the translation, so I think it needs to include the English. But I like the message, through the ages, you know?

If you could play around with that, I'd love it. Thanks for the offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy who makes most of that bizarre anti-GMO art that they use is an anti-Semitic anti-vaxxer chemtrailz NWO illuminati nutter, named David Dees. I'm not gonna link it, but search for his art site. It's pure fever swamp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, what is your field? I'm curious about your background because you aren't very good at cherry picking studies. What is your training?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your cherry picked literature and claims of people being paid off aren't any better when you repeat them. 

What is your field?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decisions made on cherry picking data and conspiracy theories are always going to be unwise. I know it's fashionable in Congress right now, but that doesn't make it right either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they did not try to do it. That's what unsubstantiated means.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am familiar with herbicides. You are not. Maybe this will help you: Before GMOs, 96% of acres were sprayed with herbicides. Guess how much was sprayed after? 

https://twitter.com/WyoWeeds/status/713084964846182401/photo/1


And Roundup does not cause cancer or other health maladies. You need to find better sources of information, because the ones you have been reading are not correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wearing my Park Ranger gear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, if you are just going to assert there's a conspiracy and everyone is paid to disagree with you, that's even less helpful than the cherry picking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now you are saying you do want to remove choices from farmers and consumers? I'm sorry to hear that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How scientists should communicate their work in a post-truth era </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But GMOs aren't using more pesticides. Some reduced, some swapped, but if GMOs were gone tomorrow we'd use the same more more pesticides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it does. It includes some genes or gene variants, it eliminates other genes or gene variants. That's how it works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm glad you support the use of GMOs then. Many farmers find that they are the best solution for their situation. And many of us want to have access to the sustainable and healthy products that are being grown. 

And since you have the option to avoid them by choosing organic, and supporting the many organic companies that are marketing them to you to make money, there's really no reason for your hostility, is there? We both have what we want. 

The organic industry is very profitable, I'm told. And they get a lot of support on social media because they pay people to do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selection modifies the genome of the plants. It just does, it's a fact. You are choosing which genes you want to carry forward, even if it's messier than inserting just a gene or two. I love the table that Kevin Folta shows for how much of the genome is affected by selection. Look at the table in this piece: https://grist.org/food/genetic-engineering-vs-natural-breeding-whats-the-difference/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked at the number of "other discussions" for this, and found it was generating a lot of good chatter. And it's becoming clearer that a lot of people are on to the lies about terminator, and are beginning to grasp the IP stuff is not unique to GMOs. 

The discussion over at AskScience was quite reasonable, I thought. 

But mostly I was worried about my science amigos. And none of them have chewed me out for this. So I slept better last night :).

On the "modification" thing: yeah, I know this bugs people. But one of my first edits was to make them change that--they said engineering at first. I talked them down to modification at that spot. And I am firmly in the camp that we have been modifying genomes for millennia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even your choices are not consistent--it's not worth the time to point out that they say different things. Nor is it worth the time to ask why you didn't include the [same group's paper that said this](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23097397):
These results indicate that transgenerational consumption of Bt maize diets is not detrimental to pig growth and health.

You are cherry picking. You can probably fool some people with that strategy. If that's who you want to be, you go girl. 

But here's the problem with that: the people who do the evaluations of these things--like the National Academy of Sciences--don't fall for that. They are professionals in the field who understand the scope and the issues with individual papers. You can't fool them. And that's why all of the researchers around the world who have looked at this have concluded that there are no safety issues.

I think an important part of public education is to illustrate to others when they are being misled. And you are misleading people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breeders are really aware of this issue, and there's quite a lot of diversity out there now that people don't realize. People think there's 1 kind of corn, but there are actually so many different traits, varieties for different locations, and it's not just one kind. 

But that's also not an issue unique to GMOs. There's a new rust threat for wheat: [New, aggressive rust threatens wheat crops in Europe, Africa, Asia](https://southernafrican.news/2017/02/21/human-activities-destroying-pollinators/)

And they are always looking to bring more in for many characteristics. There are huge stores of plant varieties that are great resources for this, in gene banks. Breeders have to keep changing their tactics all the time because, as they say, rust never sleeps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there was a great article on that once: http://www.vqronline.org/reporting-articles/2014/05/linux-lettuce I think a lot of people don't realize that there are all sorts of intellectual property issues on all crops--they want to fixate on GMOs but it's not unique to them.

But there's another twist to that: farmers in South America want to have the IP on the quinoa that they grow. Should they be allowed to control that? Some people want to abolish all IP, but I think those farmers have a right to control theirs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not entirely. Any breeding event could cause new changes. And there have been cases where traditional breeding had consequences that were harmful. https://boingboing.net/2013/03/25/the-case-of-the-poison-potato.html

And over the millennia, farmers have sometimes specifically selected for toxic products. https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/?term=9431670 These can help farmers to maintain yields. 

Selective breeding isn't necessarily safer. It's just a different strategy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are strategies to explore the whole genomes pretty quickly now, and we are developing a lot of other tools to look at the other characteristics as well. 

But this would be a concern for anything you do--traditional breeding from 2 parent plants could cause unintentional things. 

So we look at many aspects of the plants and their environment. But each crop is different so you have to look at each one and what it's doing differently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the case of farming, you have to compare it to other strategies that farmers would use. So let's say we talk about the Bt eggplants. If farmers didn't use those, they'd use a lot more pesticide. 

And most of the pesticides that they would spray would have broad effects--not just on the catepillar that's snacking on that eggplant. It would spray all over the field, and take out a lot of other insects potentially as well. It also can affect the farmers who have very little protective equipment, in the case of Bangladesh. 

Farmers will have to control pests. Doing it with less impact is better. But we also want to maintain yields so that we don't have to take more land for farming.

So you have to consider the whole picture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patents and intellectual property issues exist, but they exist on all kinds of crops--not just GMOs. So it's not an issue unique to GMOs, but a lot of people don't realize that.

There have been no suits for unintentional contamination of a farmer's crops. In fact, when organic farmers when to court to try to claim this, the suit was dismissed: http://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2012/02/27/147506542/judge-dismisses-organic-farmers-case-against-monsanto
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Restrictions depend on the regulations for each country. But most of those have to do with safety, invasiveness, growing conditions, stuff like that.

As far as I know there are no restrictions on tomato addiction. But there are food science folks at most of the companies that are always working on things like texture, mouth feel, flavors, etc. And you don't need to be doing genetic engineering for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The taste of things is affected by a lot of factors--including the genetics. I know there are researchers working on taste now, though. 

https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/27/science/better-tasting-tomatoes-genes.html

A lot of work has focused on better production. But now a lot of other efforts are turning to other features. GMO might be the right choice sometimes, traditional breeding in other cases. The tools are better now, though, if we want to use GMO to add back just the flavor things without harming the other hardy features.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked about the GMO chestnut once, and my impression was that they expect the new ones to be suitable for the range they used to be in. https://www.acf.org/the-american-chestnut/native-range-map/

They used to go to Maine. But there may be other reasons they weren't in Minnesota. 

You should check with your local University extension service for appropriate plantings for your area. They love to help people with stuff like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we need to keep evaluating things as we go along. We don't know what we are going to face next. Pre-emptively withholding tools doesn't seem like a good strategy to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My theory on this is because cancer has touched so many people, and it's so scary, that people want to place the blame. 

But a lot of what we are seeing is because now we live long enough to get cancer. There's a great graphic of what used to kill people 200 years ago, vs now. https://io9.gizmodo.com/5920871/how-we-died-200-years-ago-compared-to-how-we-die-today

Just the other day I was looking at this stomach cancer graph too: https://twitter.com/humanprogress/status/847251282192506881

You can show people data all day long, but cancer is still scary and disconnects you from thinking rationally. And you want to blame it on something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found this Amish farmer's discussion of why he chooses GMOs to be striking: https://www.biofortified.org/2013/10/amish-gmos/

He cares about his farm, and passing it on to his kids. Farmers don't want to trash the land.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how consensus works. I would encourage you to read up on recent information, like the National Academies of Science report: https://nas-sites.org/ge-crops/ 

But that's certainly not the only consensus document. Scientific societies around the world have reviewed the data and come to the same conclusion. This post has a good list of them: http://www.skepticalraptor.com/skepticalraptorblog.php/gmo-scientific-consensus-broad-unequivocal-safe/

Cherry picking some papers is unhelpful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the ag companies trying to prevent anyone else from farming they way that they want to.

The only folks trying to stop farmers from having choices are the anti-GMO folks. That's why it's adversarial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we have begun to turn the tide on the rhetoric. For a long time scientists stayed out of the fray, but more and more are contributing to the discussions now. I think the good examples of public projects--like the Bt eggplant--make it harder to dismiss all of the GMO stuff.

Some of the more organized ways--like the Cornell Alliance for Science work--really helps too.

I feel like the discussion really began to turn when we started pointing to the scientific consensus on GMOs. In the earliest days we didn't have that, because we wait for data. But now that we have seen so many scientific societies and consensus reports, we can point to those things.

And for folks who want us to adhere to consensus on climate science, it's getting harder for them to abandon it on other topics. 

I am personally a fan of new efforts to reach untapped sources--like the SciBabe's stuff at Cosmopolitan, for example: http://www.cosmopolitan.com/author/15789/yvette-dentremont/ I think that a lot of the "official" science communication has been stodgy and 3rd person snoozes--you know? But that's not everyone's style.

Multiple fronts--standing on the solid science and consensus--with many strategies. Courses, lectures, videos, comment sections, womens' mags, all of it can help. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked them if they wanted to cover animals, but they wanted to only do the plants right now. 

I think the GMO salmon is great, I'd love to see it in the grocery store. But it is only approved for contained tank systems. Here's a bit more on that: http://www.factcheck.org/2016/03/false-claims-about-frankenfish/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe tell them about all the academic projects that are out there. Here's a good quick look at some of those. https://twitter.com/DanielNorero/status/596639109025792000/photo/1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The eggplants were a big part of this video. 

What part was about the antioxidants? Can you point to that part of the video with the time?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Others have addressed some of those references, but this piece explains what happened with your item 1. They were using the wrong test, and inadequate controls. 

https://www.biofortified.org/2012/10/bt-in-blood/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they didn't. It is genetic modification to select for traits you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both cases were farmers choosing to grow a crop that they knew were likely to have the traits of interest. Neither was accidental contamination, which is typically what people claim about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are repeating misinformation about the lawsuits. No "unlucky" farmers get sued. In fact, the case was thrown out of court because despite their claims that this was an issue--not a single farmer in the supposedly huge OSGATA suit could be found that this happened to. 

http://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2012/02/27/147506542/judge-dismisses-organic-farmers-case-against-monsanto
Instead, the judge found that plaintiffs' allegations were "unsubstantiated ... given that not one single plaintiff claims to have been so threatened." The ruling also found that the plaintiffs had "overstate[d] the magnitude of [Monsanto's] patent enforcement." 

You aren't screwed. Glad to put your mind at ease there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vaccine skeptics gather in D.C. to protest -- and lobby | They take to the streets. This is why we need to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you for accepting the correct information. I hope you can continue to do so.

I would encourage you to find better sources than YouTube documentaries for additional information. Maybe something like the the consensus of scientists around the world, from all the scientific agencies, on the GMO issues. http://www.skepticalraptor.com/skepticalraptorblog.php/gmo-scientific-consensus-broad-unequivocal-safe/

A great recent source is the National Academy of Sciences report here: https://www.nap.edu/catalog/23395/genetically-engineered-crops-experiences-and-prospects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because that's not unique to GMOs. If you buy non-GMO herbicide tolerant stuff, same thing.

If you grow these organic tomatoes, same thing. https://twitter.com/songberryfarm/status/457285494318317568

If you want to be effective with your arguments, you have to aim better. If you hate plant breeder's rights, fine--hate them. But don't pretend it's a GMO issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can (but not always). If you are growing hybrids, they could be a mess the following year because of the way genes get segregated among different offspring in each seed of corn, for example. Also, just being hybrid offers this feature called heterosis, which juices up the plants. See this page at NSF, and look over at the photos of the parents vs hybrid on the right: https://www.nsf.gov/news/news_summ.jsp?cntn_id=115920

Also, plant breeders are always trying to stay ahead of pests, or introduce new flavors, or changing maturity dates, or a range of things. So to keep up, or get a foot up, some farmers might want new varieties. 

And yes, down the line, you could see reduced effectiveness, yield, or other things. But like most things--it depends on the crop. For your backyard tomato, maybe it's fine. But if you are a subsistence farmer somewhere, it could be a real impact.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you actually think non-GMOs don't use pesticides and herbicides? Really? 

In the video links I provided for the herbicide section, I think this one would benefit you the most: http://weedcontrolfreaks.com/2016/02/herbicide-diversity-trends-in-us-crops-1990-2014/

In case you don't know, the wheats and rice are not GMO. But that's just one example. Have a look at what non-GMO sugar cane can use: https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3075403/table/Tab6/

You may need to expand your grasp of agriculture. You are conflating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woot! Bookmarked. 

See--I learned something here. I'm gonna be using that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, many crops are worth developing. And many are underway. But the fog of misinformation keeps people from knowing about these great projects, and from getting them through regulatory barriers. 

The eggplant project is a great example of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no strategy anywhere that escapes everything--organic, conventional, GMO--it's always a race ahead of pests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best source of the modifications that are out in the world is probably this list: http://www.isaaa.org/gmapprovaldatabase/default.asp

So these made it out of the lab, past all the regulatory hurdles, and have been out somehow, somewhere. 

But in the field, we all know of a lot of other projects that haven't made it this far. There's no really good list of that. It doesn't mean they didn't work, but that they didn't get commercialized.

Is that what you mean?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for being open to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it is unfortunate that activists have made it so hard for good academic projects to get out to where they are needed. Here's a good quick look at a wide range of projects around the world, but nobody knows about them because of the fog of misinformation. 

https://twitter.com/DanielNorero/status/596639109025792000/photo/1

We all know of a lot of good projects that won't go anywhere because the legal issues are unaffordable for anyone but the big players.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you won't like this, but it's the horse's mouth: http://www.monsanto.com/newsviews/pages/terminator-seeds.aspx

http://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2012/10/18/163034053/top-five-myths-of-genetically-modified-seeds-busted

https://theconversation.com/terminator-seeds-will-not-usher-in-an-agricultural-judgement-day-21686

https://skepteco.wordpress.com/2012/09/02/the-truth-about-the-terminator/

Stewart Brand's book: https://books.google.com/books?id=RCPpx-cn7A0C lpg=PT128 vq=suicide%20gene dq=whole%20earth%20discipline pg=PT125#v=onepage q f=false

Anyone who tells you there are terminator seeds in farmer's hands is lying to you. Demand their sources.

***had to repost this comment because the bot removed a shortened link I used for Stewart Brand's book. I don't know if the long one will work, but you can try it. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because farmers want quality controlled seeds. They rely on the right maturity, characteristics, and traits being in the seeds they plant. There are new features coming out all the time--disease resistance for pressures they face, maybe a different herbicide to use, maybe they don't need a trait they used before.

The seed world is crazy complex, not like the people who keep shouting that there's no diversity in the crops. Check out a seed catalog like this: https://www.pioneer.com/home/site/ca/products/corn/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you won't like this, but it's the horse's mouth: http://www.monsanto.com/newsviews/pages/terminator-seeds.aspx

http://www.npr.org/sections/thesalt/2012/10/18/163034053/top-five-myths-of-genetically-modified-seeds-busted

https://theconversation.com/terminator-seeds-will-not-usher-in-an-agricultural-judgement-day-21686

https://skepteco.wordpress.com/2012/09/02/the-truth-about-the-terminator/

Stewart Brand's book: http://bit.ly/1dSEbuJ

Anyone who tells you there are terminator seeds in farmer's hands is lying to you. Demand their sources.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right--but people are asking about sterile seeds--meaning they can't be used the following season. It's commonly conflated in people's minds that "no re-use" and "sterile" are the same thing. They aren't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check this out: https://twitter.com/rsaik/status/847516448050233344 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just finished a fundraiser: https://fundly.com/chestnutchallenge

I bet if you contact them, they'll be able to help you out :) . I'm not associated with that project at all, so I don't know what the right route is. You can also try to reach out to @ChestnutPowell on twitter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really pleased with the reception this has had. There are many discussions, all of which have a lot of smart people invovled. 

BTW: I was a volunteer editor on the script. I didn't have final edit control, but I was overall ok with how this ended up. 

We had a discussion in AskScience if you want to see that: https://redd.it/62e54o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Seralini's team was restricting journos from talking to anyone. That's not normal. http://blogs.discovermagazine.com/loom/2012/09/21/from-darwinius-to-gmos-journalists-should-not-let-themselves-be-played/
But those outside experts were slow to comment in part because reporters who got to see the paper in advance of the embargo had to sign a confidentiality agreement to get their hands on it. They werent allowed to show it to other experts.

[I spent over a year](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/26133768) asking for Seralini's team for raw data on another publication. They refused to provide it.

We've been asking for the raw data for a current publication for months. They have refused to deposit it anywhere. 

This is not normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there's a lot of misinformation among food discussions and womens magazines. GMO is one of the fads among many of the folks who frequent those.

There is a lot of testing of the products to ensure that it's not different from existing products in substantial ways (like different strains of corn), and if it's something completely new there might be extra tests requested. In the US the government process involves several agencies. Here's kind of an overview: https://www.usda.gov/topics/biotechnology/how-federal-government-regulates-biotech-plants

But a nice ice-breaker might be a piece like this--one of my favorites. [The "Food Babe" Blogger Is Full of Shit](http://gawker.com/the-food-babe-blogger-is-full-of-shit-1694902226). I think it was particularly effective because it came from a woman scientist (the SciBabe!), and it talked about the things women are reading and hearing about among food conversations. 

The SciBabe has other fun stuff over at places like Cosmopolitan lately. So I think some of those sources are catching on to the nonsense that they had been spreading. http://www.cosmopolitan.com/health-fitness/a8111873/gmo-myths-misconceptions/ or maybe http://www.cosmopolitan.com/lifestyle/a7026682/environmentalist-myths-signs/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna mention the Bt potatoes for the potato beetles. But since those haven't been around for a while I thought maybe I should look that up first. https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/17461085 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's another burger on the way that isn't a muscle-type cell, but a GMO heme protein gives it a more muscley (?) flavor. I haven't had it yet, but I know people who have: http://www.sfchronicle.com/bayarea/article/Veggie-burger-that-bleeds-set-to-take-on-11020144.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many studies out there, and many have been done by non-industry folks. 

It's also not true that there's some kind of law that disallows studies or publications. 

You may want to reconsider the sources you use. Maybe you should look over this great recent assessment of GMO crops for better and more solid information: https://nas-sites.org/ge-crops/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine to try, but I haven't seen the studies. Please show me the evidence that it works in farmers' hands, and is increasing their yield and safety.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of projects that people don't know about, because of all of the drama around the corporations. It's too bad, the work on GMO cassava could have major benefits for the developing world. 

And the GMO banana wilt solution may save a key cultural food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the funny things about the terminator idea is that we don't know if it works. There was so much drama around it that work stopped. I was not really convinced it would work. But I'm always open to new data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't rot very fast. In fact, chestnut was prized for woodworking because it was so good and decay resistant. But some of it might also be made into structural stuff that lasts a long time (once we get that far).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I think it's fair. What is your solution to fruit and shoot borer for Bangladeshi farmers that has demonstrated improved yield, improved income, and improved safety?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How things are tested depends on the crop. Things you need to assess for corn would be very different from apples. So different federal agencies review the applications, and evaluate if the testing was appropriate and effective.

The GMO non-browning apple was in field trials for 10 years. Have a look at what they went through: https://www.aphis.usda.gov/brs/aphisdocs/10_16101p.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A gene that causes herbicide resistance in one species could have a very different effect in another species.

I was re-using your example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nitrogen use is a tougher nut to crack. There are 2 different strategies underway (that I know about, others may know more). You can get other plants to make nodules like legumes do and use the same bacterial mechanism to access the nitrogen in plants that don't naturally do that.

Or you can look at NUE, nitrogen use efficiency, and try to improve that. 

Here's a recent example: [Soybean nitrogen breakthrough could help feed the world](https://news.wsu.edu/2016/10/10/soybean-nitrogen-breakthrough-help-feed-world/)

This article has a nice description [paywalled, but search Google scholar with the doi]: [The nitrogen fix](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/353/6305/1225.long).

Most of the work I've seen uses existing genes from one place doing one job and moving it to a new species. But, increasingly we may find that synthetic biologists can design some new strategies from scratch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One system that's used to introduce genes--Agrobacterium--has been called ["The Natural Genetic Engineer 100 Years Later"](http://www.apsnet.org/publications/apsnetfeatures/Pages/Agrobacterium.aspx). They found recently that all sweet potatoes carry inserted genes from this! [Natural GMO? Sweet Potato Genetically Modified 8,000 Years Ago](http://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2015/05/05/404198552/natural-gmo-sweet-potato-genetically-modified-8-000-years-ago).

Biologists have taken a number of tricks from nature to use for other purposes. Restriction enzymes that cut DNA in precise locations are like that too. And the new CRISPR editing tools are "natural" and we're harnessing them now for other purposes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have never been terminator seeds. 

The issue was revived recently, though, and in the video links there's this piece: [Terminator seeds will not usher in an agricultural judgement day](https://theconversation.com/terminator-seeds-will-not-usher-in-an-agricultural-judgement-day-21686). It discusses a way to keep plants that produce pharmaceutical products from spreading. So there might be reasons to consider the technology. But it has still never been released.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have never been terminator seeds in farmers fields, anywhere. If people tell you that, they don't understand the biology. 

Sometimes people imply this, though, when they are really referring to the legal agreement not to save seeds for the following year. But buying new and improved seeds each year has been common in production systems for a long time, long before GMOs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's helpful to disentangle the issues. Monocultures existed before GMOs, and if GMOs went away tomorrow you'd still have monocultures. But that said, there's a lot of misunderstanding about monocultures too. Here's a piece that looks at that: https://appliedmythology.blogspot.ca/2014/08/do-gmo-crops-foster-monoculture.html

When GMOs are being studied, they examine the issue with wild relatives. Frequently it's not an issue, as there aren't wild relatives to crops. But when there are, they evalute the risk. But again, if you are worried about herbicide tolerance spreading, that's not a GMO issue. https://www.biofortified.org/2012/02/herbicide-resistant-johnsongrass-coming-soon-to-a-farm-near-you/

Patents and intellectual property are also not unique to GMOs. 

Conflating these things sometimes lead to people misunderstanding the issues. And it would be unfortunate if people didn't realize how many public projects are out there that have nothing to do with monocultures, patents, or herbicides.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This GMO soybean is off patent: https://www.technologyreview.com/s/539746/as-patents-expire-farmers-plant-generic-gmos/

But as others have explained, patents are not unique to GMOs. This was a great piece about open source ag: http://www.vqronline.org/reporting-articles/2014/05/linux-lettuce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a paper that looked at this for the chestnuts: [Aboveground carbon biomass of plantation-grown American chestnut (Castanea dentata) in absence of blight](https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0378112709002837) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a common misunderstanding. Here's a good piece that described what's up with that (see item 2): Top Five Myths Of Genetically Modified Seeds, Busted https://n.pr/S1Zz4s

But as far as I can tell, Monsanto has never sued anybody over trace amounts of GMOs that were introduced into fields simply through cross-pollination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are various ways to reduce the chances of cross-pollination. There are farmers today who grow GMO corn and non-GMO corn on their same farm, and it's possible to manage this. You can do this with planting timing and buffer zones. 

But most of the crops that are GMO right now are not things that survive really well in the wild. A biotech plant researcher (Pam Ronald, married to an organic farmer) once described this as "frankenpoodles". Here's what she meant by that: http://scienceblogs.com/tomorrowstable/2010/11/14/faustian-frankenpoodles-sighte/

Something like herbicide tolerance is not necessarily a benefit in the wild, so it wouldn't necessarily be a stronger competitor. There was a fascinating study of virus-resistant squash that illustrated this too. Pam also wrote about that here: http://scienceblogs.com/tomorrowstable/2009/10/28/sex-and-its-unintended-consequ/

Although the plants were more resistant to viruses, they were tasty to beetles still. Those beetles brought a different pathogen. So what makes them great for farming doesn't mean it would be stronger in the wild.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, they wanted to focus on the GMO issues. But if you look at the links in the video description area, I offered links that explore the wider issues with herbicides, specifically noting that the issues are neither new, nor limited to GMOness. 

The issues are so often conflated.

I do wish that people who want to reduce synthetic pesticides would understand how GMOs could benefit that kind of production system, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a project underway now that makes the chestnut resistant to the blight infection. It uses a gene from wheat to reduce the blight's damage to the tree. And then this huge tree just pulls the carbon out of the air for it's own growth. 

Here are some details about that project. https://phys.org/news/2016-01-genetically-american-chestnut-decimated-iconic.html 

They are testing the GMO chestnuts in a "century" experiment right now. You can see more about that here: http://allianceforscience.cornell.edu/blog/chestnutrestorationforest

As the video noted, there are no terminator seeds. Chestnuts used to provide huge amounts of nutrition for animals and humans. You can also make beer with them :) . Restoring them to their ecosystem will have many benefits besides being carbon sinks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are various genes that helps plants deal with stressful situations. For example, if you can keep the stomata closed so that plants lose less water, that could be one way to use the water more efficiently. http://www.nature.com/articles/srep12449

But here's a table with a variety of different strategies that are being explored: http://www.nature.com/nbt/journal/v32/n7/fig_tab/nbt.2948_T1.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the video: https://redd.it/62e54o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyway, here's a fairly recent trial of flu vaccine. They check the antibody titers, and they check on illness over 2 flu seasons. 

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/26762363

They are just flat-out wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is their explanation for the elimination of smallpox? It just went away? That's nuts.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert F. Kennedy Jr.: Your anti-vaccine crusade is a disgrace to science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know about the Candlewick Press? They may have local sources for that. 

Edit to add URL, forgot, sorry: http://www.candlewick.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have to watch Mike Capuano talk about his underwear in Congress. Also, internet privacy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, that's number 666.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heads up on a thing Thursday Mar 30 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi folks--

I'm writing to give a heads-up on something that will happen tomorrow. These folks, Kurzgesagt, will have a new GMO video. And they've arranged a discussion at r/AskScience.

https://www.youtube.com/user/Kurzgesagt [autostarts, warning]

The goal is entertaining, engaging, but not super wonky detailed science issues discussions. 

I helped them with some background, but I have not seen the final video and did not have final editing oversight. I just offered what I knew and what sources I thought would help. However the final video looks, it will surely generate discussion that would benefit from farmer and science perspectives. I was not paid by anyone for this, just volunteered to help get it right. 

The video will release tomorrow afternoon in Europe. Soon after, I'll be up and caffeinated. But there's no specific time like there is with other discussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somerville mayor calls Bristol sheriff jack-booted thug in sanctuary city spat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love my RingTheory pass. http://www.ringtheory.com/

Mine was from their kickstarter, and it's still working great several years later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I didn't even understand that part. He claims the letter in 2002 went to Elsevier. So it's not like a law office just started their own journal.

Also, the journal's thrust is "Regulatory". Regulatory is a very specific branch of issues--which are, wait for it--legal issues. It's not really something your average biology department or chemistry department does. 

From their description page:
The journal is devoted to reports of significant developments, public opinion, scientific data, and ideas that bridge the gap between scientific information and the *legal* aspects of *toxicological* and *pharmacological regulations*.

Emphasis theirs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He asserts that there are peer review failures, while completely failing to demonstrate it.

Hilariously, he leads with the latest Monsanto drama, while twice admitting there was nothing to it in the body of the piece.

Thacker is a piece of work. And refuses to say who pays him, ironically enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's climate policies put China in charge of our future | "we must all March for Science on April 22" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You keep posting similar assertions, and demanding debunking while asserting how hard to debunk your claims are. Can you find a new hobby, please?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, don't do that as a novice. It was a separate thought about water-based activity. 

Although there was that guy who was doing it. I don't know if anyone does it as a company. https://mattgphoto.wordpress.com/2010/09/02/kayaking-to-the-boston-harbor-islands/

http://www.bostonharborislands.org/general-faqs

This guy did a canoe: http://www.nydailynews.com/news/national/man-lives-14-foot-canoe-boston-harbor-article-1.1213861 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, as they continue to look they are finding other consequences. There may be vision problems, Guillain-Barr syndrome, and other stuff that hasn't all played out yet at scale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it came out, I remember being struck by the effectiveness of the AIDS activists covered in the film "How to Survive a Plague". I re-watched it on Netflix this weekend to take more notes on a fairly contemporary movement that had science and political aspects to it, as well as important social dynamics. 

I didn't realize that there was a book out now as well, I think it might be worth reading. We're gonna need some strategies for the next few years. http://surviveaplague.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw the list. Plant science reprazent! Woot!

https://marchforsciencesf.com/blog/index.php/2017/03/25/announcing-our-rally-speakers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
