<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject721</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it'd be difficult at all to adapt any given existing pen   paper system for a FO campaign.

Guns are mostly pretty shitty, in terms of build quality and such, do it wouldn't be hard to reskin crossbows and the like as a gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see it more as a, "I've been playing for a long ass time" sort of thing rather than, "Look how much disposable income I have!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either I didn't know that, or I forgot.

In any case that's hilarious. Seems like such a Bethesda thing to do, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there are many factors at play, but I thin there's a certain distinction between "DLC" and "micro-transactions".

I suppose it depends on exactly what you classify as "content" in the phrase "Downloadable Content" but to me DLC is akin to an "expansion pack". You're buying for something that adds a not insignificant amount of content to the video game. Perhaps a new class or character. New zone(s). Things like that.

MTX on the other hand, I see as insignificant things such as skins or things that don't make any *real* difference to the game.

I can't believe the whole Horse Armor thing was over a decade ago. I can't even remember what I was playing then, never mind what the "gaming landscape" was like in terms of DLC/MTX. But as you / others have said, I think ultimately nowadays gamers are simply sick and tired of feeling like they need to buy DLC to play with their friends, or get fatigued playing these massive open world games and as such have started to favor cosmetic-only models.

Also, I don't think it's *entirely* fair to compare Steam Market prices for items. It's not reflective of what content creators charge for goods. It's totally open to let people pay whatever they are willing to pay.

That said, I think multiplayer vs singleplayer plays a huge role in how it's perceived. Why would I pay for some mediocre looking armor that literally no one but me will ever see in a single player game? People don't even like pre-order cosmetic exclusives, let alone paying extra for it today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know very little about this sort of thing, but from my understanding a major reason Ford isn't developing an RS is because the Fiesta is just too small.

I'm not saying swapping a Golf R drivetrain WOULDN'T work, but:

* Golf R wheelbase is 103.5", Fiesta is 98"
* Golf is 168" long, Fiesta is 160"
* Golf is 70" wide, Fiesta is 67"

Again I'm far from an expert, and obviously the drivetrain doesn't take up the full length/width of the vehicle, but it sounds like you'd have to do a lot of adjustment to make it fit.


The said, there's a way to make it work because [this monstrosity](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ford_Fiesta_RS_WRC) exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finish school first.

You don't want to finance a car and then not be able to get a job in a year or two when you graduate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say tomato, I say tornado </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. I wouldn't necessarily consider those *content* though.

But you're right, they could certain make the client better / add features. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can release heroes and maps with the frequency they please.

Hearthstone has to concern itself with card expansions and such since only certain sets are valid for competitive, right? So no one's going to buy cards if there's a new set every month or every other month. That's not long enough to get much value out of the cards before they're "out of season". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're taking it too seriously.

The way I interpreted it, is that no one goes to C C to see a completely run off the mill car try and do a sick burnout, bro.

Show up in whatever you want, check out people's cars, have fun. Just don't act like a fucking wanker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom's had 2 kids and 5 stones. Says she'd chose labor again every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish my kidney stone was that "easy".

I just turned 18. On the morning of my last day at my summer job before starting college the following week, I woke up due to the most intense pain I ever experienced. Laying down hurt. Walking hurt. Sitting hurt. I could do nothing to relieve the pain.

My mom took me to the hospital and they loaded me to with pain killers and it was much better. They did some scans and quickly found the rock in my kidney. They said it was **too big** to break up via ultrasound; it would simply break apart into smaller stones.

The doctors kept me there for 24 hours to pump me full of fluids, in an attempt to get me to pass the stone. No such luck.

I had surgery scheduled 2 weeks later to have it removed.

For two weeks, I lived with this big ass rock that could move without notice and throw me into a crippling pain. And as I mentioned above, I was just about to start college... Commuting 50 miles each way. I was super scared of it happening while driving.

Fortunately, it only moved on the weekends when I was around the house. One day it was so bad, if I ate or drank or tried to go to the bathroom I would puke from the pain. Got sent to the ER that night because there was a risk of serious dehydration.

Eventually got it removed. They had to play a Crane Grab game. Shove a camera and a little claw up my dick, pull the fucker out, and stick a catheter in.

Having that in me was extremely unpleasant. Pissing blood is disgusting. Having the nurse try and start a lawnmower with my ripcord was very close to the worst part of the whole ordeal, but not as bad as the long-lasting pain of the stone movements. Or the fear of a movement.


Fuck kidney stones, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> '14 Fiesta ST.

Bone stock, but I've been meaning to replace the rear motor mount. And some day I want to buy Cobb's "Stage 3" package. Tune, intercooler, intake + exhaust. $3K gives "+20%HP and +40% torque" according to Cobb.

I'm completely OK with 220HP and 280 lb-ft of torque in a car that only weighs 2700 lbs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But no part of the definition is dependent upon knowing the other users "in real life".

It might change how you act and what you post, but it's still social. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss my Z :(

Had to sell once I got a new job -- a job which didn't let me work remotely 5 days per week and I'd actually have to deal with winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As others said, just stop using it all together if you can, or drastically reduce how much you do use it.

Resist the urge to post whatever menial thing happened to you on a given day. Resist the urge to post another selfie; no one forgot what you look like. Unfollow people.

At this point, I basically use Facebook for:

* Keeping track of Events happening at a variety of local places: concert venues, motorsports, and local gaming shops
* Following bands I listen to. I dislike subscribing to record labels' mailing lists because it's easy to overlook news about bands I actually like as they send you stuff about all the bands they've signed. So FB is, IMO, a good way to get updates from the bands I care about in regards to new albums, tours, and other news.
* Communicate with my D D groups. Honestly I'd rather just have a group text going, but whatever. There are arguments for using something other than texting; easier to share PDFs, separate discussions etc.

I very very rarely ever actually post status updates, photos, share stuff, or comment on people's statuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit absolutely is.

Wikipedia defines social media as:

 Social media are **computer-mediated technologies** that facilitate the creation and **sharing of information, ideas, career interests** and other forms of expression **via virtual communities and networks**. 

Emphasis mine, obviously.

Just because I don't actually know any of you fucks doesn't make Reddit *not* social media. It's 100% community driven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it odd/interesting how delicate the male ego can be, especially when it's something they have no control over.

I'd probably also react poorly to a girl laughing at it, but I still think it's just a weird behavior.

Would you, OP, be "shaken up" if a guy laughed at your vagina?

But yea as others have said, I think if you simply apologize then explain, "Well, it was contorted when I pulled it out, I never saw it like that before. You **know** I like it, I'm sorry I laughed" then you should be OK as long as he's a level dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a tattoo of Mr. Skeltal on your penis shoulders. Very spoopy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Progressive metal.

Ayreon's new album "The Source" leaked last week and I haven't stopped listening to it since.

Everything he writes is a concept album, and be plays most of the instruments then has a bunch of guest vocalists from other bands sing the lyrics for different characters on the album, it's really cool. This album has vocalists from Dream Theater, Blind Guardian, Epica, Nightwish, Kamelot and a bunch of other bands. \\m/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a 2016 with the 6MT. That thing did not feel quick in any sense of the word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can go and ask literally any car journalist of you don't want to take random redditor's opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why is it always the people with shitty cars that try and show out? No one gives a fuck about your 10-year-old V6 charger, I promise.


This guy gets it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that interior looks really 2005ey to me

I'm completely ok with this.

Nissan steering wheels are ugly though, no doubt about that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All fair points. I haven't looked at it very well. Though I do often see one on my commute to work, always catches my eye... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleted my comment, as I was able to select it on the desktop site.

Side note: lol, it comes standard with the CVT and the optional 6MT is the same price. Instead of charging you more for an auto, they just give you the auto and make it a manual "for free". Fuck Nissan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read any of the comments here? It's quite clear.

Overpriced, under powered, power comes on too high in the rev range etc. etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fully loaded with recaros, yea. Under $25K without 'em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure Toyota has done the math and determined which is more cost effective.

And drum brakes being not as effective doesn't matter much when you're talking about the rear brakes on an ecobox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bored waiting at the doctor's office. I checked autotrader.

[They're all well below MSRP lmao](http://m.autotrader.com/cars-for-sale/searchresults.xhtml? zip=67108 endYear=2018 interiorColorsSimple= pageLayout=list mpgRanges= mmt=%5BNISSAN%5BSENTRA%5BSENTRA%7CNISMO%5D%5D%5B%5D%5D transmissionGroup= doorCodes= vehicleStyleCodes= driveGroup= fuelTypeGroup= startYear=2017 listingFeatures= engineGroup= extColorsSimple= searchRadius=0). Just under $22K.

If you're in the market for a fun car under $25K and **have** to have used, it's probably not a bad buy for $22K.

But I suspect I'd take my Fiesta 10/10 times.

I will concede that I like the [dash](http://images.autotrader.com/scaler/920/640/hn/c/927219114ba849bfa5d50d44eaa6534b.jpg). Extremely simplistic climate controls, small screen flush with the dash. I hate my Fiesta's dash, it's fugly. Oh and a backup camera, which isn't even an *option* on the Fiesta despite being standard on the Titanium trim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the bright side, you've had 5 more people (initially) agree to go on a date with you than I've had in the past 3 years :|  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friday was a solid D D session.

Saturday was spent sleeping in late, doing errands, and going to bed early. Kind of a waste, but the sleep was much needed and the errands were in preparation for fun things so I didn't mind doing them.

Sunday was the first autocross event of the season. Came in 12^th out of 22 drivers in the Novice class, and it was only my second event so I'm very pleased with that. Beat a guy in a Porsche Cayman with my little Fiesta ST, too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USB port got damaged on my old Galaxy Nexus. Really liked the wireless charging with my Nexus 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, the ghost poop.

"I swear I felt something come out, but there's no trace..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask me again when I'm 50.

There's probably a bit of truth to it. Young and optimistic about how much better the world could be, if we'd all just stop being so greedy and selfish.

Then you get older, probably have a family to take care of, care more about how much gets taken out of your paycheck because you've got mouths to feed. Less energy for working and being responsible for things outside of work, so you're less pleased with what gets taken out for taxes.

Certainly not the case for everyone, but.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find lately games just don't hold my interest.

"Oh sweet, Planet Coaster is on sale"

 One week later, with 6 hours of playtime logged

"Well I'm probably never playing this again."


So yea. I spend more time waiting for games to go on sale and then hardly touch it in most cases. I suppose that's better than the alternative; Buying it at full price and barely playing it... But still. I should just stop buying games.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious, has anyone here been shopping for something in the Corvette price range, but crossed it off your list? If so, why?

I'm not especially into 'vettes, though I do like them. So I don't know what sort of things might make someone decide, "You know what, never mind."

They strike me as a car that someone's going to buy no matter what. Like either you want one and you can afford it so you get it, or you don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On top of that, the Nissan 1.6T is getting old and doesn't have the 2 big advantages of small turbo 4s from other brands: lots of low-end torque and good fuel economy. 

The article mentioned this, power is too high into the rev range. Which sounds pretty dumb for what they think this car is supposed to be.

I love that my Fiesta comes alive right around 3K. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had the money I'd buy a 370Z Nismo for a DD.

If this were to be a weekend / autocross only vehicle I'd probably look into something used from Germany though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I definitely agree that, if nothing else, it's no longer "a poor man's supercar."

I was more OK with it when it was "only" a $30K increase costing $100K, but the jump to 110 last year is a bit crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't even care about the R35 being a dinosaur if Nissan kept it at the original MSRP of $69,850

I agree that the GT-R's price is quite high nowadays, but you act as if today's GT-R is the same as what came out in 2007.

Originally, it was making 478HP and 434 lb-ft of torque.

This improved to 523HP and 451 lb-ft in 2010/2011.

After that, Nissan squeezed even more out of the VR38DETT and listed the GT-R's specs as 545HP and 463 lb-ft of torque.

And that's strictly just looking at the engine. They also improved the suspension, threw bigger rotors on it, lighter wheels, aerodynamic improvements with the "facelifts" it's received, and they've improved the interior.

Now, is all of that worth the $100K base price Nissan is asking today? I'll let you decide. But yea, the GT-R you buy today and the GT-R you bought in 2007 are **quite** different. 

Edit: It's actually $110K for a base GT-R, now. That is **quite** expensive indeed. But I still stand by the fact that Nissan *has* improved the GT-R quite a lot over it's life.  

Double Edit: Their site actually lists it as 565HP too, so even more than I said above.  I can't think of many cars that have gained a nearly 20% increase in HP for the same generation of the car without significant price changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diehard fanboy is pretty much the only thing I can think of, yeah. But... The Sentra?

I can see people buying a 370Z and saying, "I know it's not the best at X, Y, or Z, but I don't care I like this car." But I can't see the same thing happening for a Sentra.

Oh Nissan :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it's strictly Toyota, but I haven't followed the news particularly closely because I won't be buying one when it comes out.

Toyota started competing in the World Rally Championship again this year, debuting their [Yaris WRC](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toyota_Yaris_WRC). The Yaris Gazoo is just going to be a toned down version of that; like the Fiesta ST compared to the [Fiesta RS WRC](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ford_Fiesta_RS_WRC). I'd be kind of surprised if manufacturers did a "joint project" for motorsports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The SR was never supposed to "handle well".

When the Nismo was first announced people kept comparing the two but were overlooking the fact that the Nismo was supposed to have a more sporty suspension.

But yea, now that we've seen the full details for this thing... What a joke, Nissan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be hard to fuck up the Yaris Gazoo worse than this Sentra Nismo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $26K MSRP without Navigation on Nissan's US website.

$26K for 188hp, sport seats, and a stiffened suspension with a CVT that probably sucks.

What a joke. I tried to defend Nissan when a Nismo Sentra was announced because we didn't know the price or any real details beyond the exhaust, interior, and suspension mods. But goddamn. Classic Nissan: overcharge and under perform.

Who is this car marketed towards? People who want a Focus/Fiesta ST but can't drive stick?

Like I literally cannot come up with a single person who would pick this over any other car in the $20-30K range.

Edit: I can't seem to find an option for a 6MT on Nissan's website but the article says they had one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they will. The technology is only going to get better, and prices will come down as both competition and production increase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See reference "Comic book movies"

That bubble's gonna burst sooner or later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it sure as shit isn't that in *Rhode Island* of all states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think one of the biggest issues is that it came out about 3 months (2/7/12) after Skyrim (11/11/11).

How many people are going to spend $60 on a no-name single player fantasy RPG three months after TES? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 12:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Children born tomorrow might reach 16 years of age and have absolutely no clue what a manual transmission is or that such a thing ever existed. 


"Oh, you drive... One of... Those" - woman from work who I gave a ride home said that when she saw the gear shifter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5QI3PVO9Zn4 he has </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gross, what kind of sick freak do you think I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I draw the line when you're smearing anything that came out of your body on someone's face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like a regular desk, except splattered with blood after they blew their head off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that it should simply just be:

    class Dog
    {
        public bool IsAGoodDog { get { return true; } }

        //whatever else
    } </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you talk about the Corvette of all performance cars? No kidding it's going to be low volume, look at the price.


Ford sold 106K Mustangs last year. 122K the year before that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, compared to how often Doug and Matt's videos get posted here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $400 purchase. Say my bill averages $75/mo. After 3 years of ownership, that's $3100.

Wow, you're right, instead of an insanely powerful portable computer which I can use to learn anything I want and communicate with anyone in the world I should've just bought a beat ass Miata which would then need to be insured, fed gas, and maintained and other expenses.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... many people I know regard the "budget" class of 30-35k as unattainable when things like student loans and housing cost are higher priority.

True fact. 25% of my after-tax income goes to student loans.

Add on rent, insurance, and other expenses all I can afford is this Fiesta.


It was depressing showing up at the dealership to test drive it and see a Focus RS sitting in the lot. Just thinking, "I'd be driving home in that if it weren't for these ludicrous student loan payments."

Sigh. Only 5 more years :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be interpreted as a 110% increase rather than just a 10% increase though.

"11Ghz upgrade" rather than "upgrade to 11Ghz" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean, but TW just isn't "that style" of a game when it comes to crafting.

It kind of goes against everything most RPGs teach you of looting everything and getting every resource that pops up.

But if you try to do that in TW you will literally just spend hundreds of hours walking across the continent picking up herbs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To each their own, but you don't need to pick plants at all. And even if you do opt to make potions and oils you certainly don't need to pick every thing that pops up on your mini map. If you try to do that you'll never actually get anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't they confirm it'll be a while before their next project since it will be on a new engine?

Hopefully it'll be better.

I enjoyed FO 4, even with its shit dialogue but that's because I'm from MA so visiting the post apocalyptic Boston was cool. Although I am still bitter they left out the aquarium :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halo.

In my opinion it's just a completely average shooter. Seemed like the original gained a ton of popularity simply because it wasn't bad. Then it just snowballed.

Give me Unreal, Titanfall, BF, or COD over Halo any day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah man, he's getting along great with Russia and China! He / his daughter was even granted a whole bunch of ~~patents~~ trademarks in China :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the first time I've said, "who saw that coming?" and actually meant it this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  According to Tesla, a defective part in the parking brake could prevent the brake from releasing. We do not believe this issue could ever lead to a safety concern for customers and we have not seen a single accident or injury relating to it, Tesla said in an email

Nothing major, but that's a lot of vehicles to issue a recall for. Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume you "main" HOTS?

In League/DOTA, because you get gold from kills to buy items, *some people* can be very "omfg you kill stealer, I'm just going to troll/feed now" douchebags but it's not especially common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a shameful amount of hours logged in DOTA 2.

There are a lot of things I dislike about HotS, but I do have fun when I play it. More specifically, I generally have fun *no matter how the game goes*.

I think I have a pretty good understanding of "DOTA Theory", but my actual skills are on a much lower level. And for me, there are few things worse than a shitty, long game of DOTA. 30 minutes in, stomping the other team but no one on your team wants to push your advantage. No one will take high ground. It just drags on another 30 minutes of pussyfooting and you eventually lose. Or one of those games where you're just losing the entire time but, again, the enemy team is also not very good and instead of ending the game they back off, wait for Rosh, farm their next item, then win. Meanwhile all you can do is sit in your base and kill creeps because the other team has covered your entire jungle in vision. I fully admit I'm just as much to blame for a loss as anyone else on my team; that's not my issue. My issues is that I don't want to queue up for a game and have it potentially be an hour long trainwreck.

There's none of that in HOTS. Even when you're losing, because the objectives are so powerful, it's always worth contesting them. You're never stuck just turtling in your base forever. Games are over in 10-20 minutes.

I miss laning in DOTA, the comparatively insane power and long stuns. But I'm just not going to play a game where I can be stuck getting berated by teammates for an hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just listen to him and be with him, help him with whatever you can.

I lost my only brother unexpectedly, five months ago. Not necessarily the same as losing a parent, but certainly shitty in its own right.

My best friend sat up with me all night the day I got that phone call (live far from my family) and went to the store and bought some ingredients to cook me whatever I wanted, try to make me laugh when I wasn't crying, and asking what thoughts and emotions were going through my head when I was.

Everyone grieves in their own way, but I'm very grateful for how he dealt with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that Trump is president, clearly widespread misinformation works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish he'd stop with the binary verses :/

It was, in my opinion, downright bad in Age of Shadows. It didn't annoy me as much in this album, just cheesy... But in any case, I definitely wish he would stop.

But hey if that's my biggest complaint, then I'd say it's a pretty good album. Ended up purchasing it off Amazon after listening to the torrented version. I was just going to stream it, but it's a good album and I wanted the art/lyric book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article says "Mid 30" so I'd guess it will start at 33 and go up to 38 with options </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't feel like network television can do something like this justice. 

For the most part I agree, but given AMC brought us Breaking Bad, I would say it's not *impossible* for a regular TV network to do it.

But then, that was pretty realistic --- at least in the sense of Magic and Fantasy settings -- which makes it easier IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus the whole end fight *at* the Eye.

And even still, that's only one book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished the fourth book like a month ago before giving up on the series.

There's a lot of things I found really interesting, but there's just way more I was not interested in at all and I can't be bothered to read the next two thousand-page books for a combined total of 10 chapters that would be pertinent to what I like about the series.

I'll definitely check it the show when it airs though. Assuming it follows a Game of Thrones format, I could get through 10 hour long episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, instead of wasting $1,000 for a short shifter, eBay exhaust and cheap wheels, put that money aside for a Miata or some other cheap, fun car.

You can polish a turd but at the end of the day it's still a turd. I don't mean that a Matrix is a bad car across the board... But it certainly wasn't developed with *spirited driving* in mind, and trying to make it into something it's not will cost *at least* a couple hundred dollars bare minimum. And it won't be much more fun at all.

Just do the standard maintenance things you'd do for *any* car and bank what you can for a base vehicle worth dumping some money into, if you want better performance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm inclined to agree that they're a little static, especially at this point. But that's not to say I don't enjoy them.

A few things:

* I think Matt is simply a charismatic person and enjoy listening to him. If schmee tried to do these, I'd never watch them.
* I really like seeing some of the insane projects people work on, such as that widebody 2JZ BMW, the Coyote Cayman, and that SEMA-prepped Veloster
* Some of the guests can be very interesting. The recent Honda Insight video is a great example. I always thought the Insight was sort of cool, like it had lot of elements of an almost really cool car. Then you actually look at it and say, "nope" -- but the car owner knew a ton about the car, about the batteries, and even though it's not something I'd ever buy I still like learning / seeing people who are into their car
* Vehicles I'll never even *see* in person let alone drive or own, such as last week's DB11 video
* Also interesting to see Matt's opinion of any given car. I have a tremendously limited list of vehicles I've driven, and of those cars less than half of them are cars anyone is interested in.

I'm definitely much much less interested in his videos for new "average" cars, though. For example, I didn't watch this week's Camaro SS video. I've never been into Camaros so I simply don't care. It's a 2017 so I assume it's stock, or close to -- even further lessening my interest.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jokes on you, I don't want kids anyways! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More gesturing.

Let me know when they threaten a bigly-mighty attack and then maybe we'll take them seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably helps that you don't need to shave it face, though. I think that would be hard to do without a mirror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I shave I run a little water on the sink and spread it around, then put a paper towel or two in the sink.

Use the clippers to neaten up the beard. The slightly damp paper towels in the sink will catch and hold on to most of this. Then just pick up the towel and throw it in the trash.

I only 'actually' shave my neck, and at this point there's nothing left but the tiniest of stuble which is easy enough to just wet another paper towel or a few squares of TP and rub around in the sink to pick it all up. Or just wash it down, but that might be bad for the plumbing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unzip fly

Pull dingdong through opening in boxers

Pee


I don't even understand how, when, or why I'd get my balls out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you tell? Uniform? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting the original. The bandana looks terrible in the one OP posted here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew VT did not not the others.

I wish more states would. They're an eye sore and are dangerous. Drivers don't need even more distractions, especially not one designed with the purpose of making people go and buy things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both made it to F1.  And even if you don't, there are a lot of places to make money racing. 

That's the first time I've ever heard this.

"How do you make a small fortune in motor sports? Start with a large one." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Massachusetts you don't need to stop or slow down for toll booths anymore. Keep cruising along at whatever speed and it'll bill you automatically if you have a Fast Pass (EZ Pass? Whatever it's called), or they bill your license plate address if you don't have a pass.

I commute between NY and MA regularly, it's so annoying getting to NYS and having the 5 MPH booths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree the backlash will be problematic, but that doesn't mean we shouldn't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I didn't spend $2500 on LASIK so I could wear interactive glasses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So his argument for why you should be allowed to have a concealed firearm on campus is in case there are bombings?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the person hasn't gone to trial and been convicted of the crime.

There is exactly zero doubt in my mind this specific person is guilty, but there are plenty of cases where it's not immediately obvious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All those hours spent playing Grand Theft Auto.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oddly enough, I torrented it today and came home and purchased it immediately. I was like, "Eh I'll just listen to it on Spotify" but fuck it, I want the lyric/artbook after listening to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've sold that many? That's actually seriously impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... instead of take over the world. 

One thing at a time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeap, definitely think Poopmobile every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the improvisational tone to the One Take videos, I don't think I'd want something rehearsed -- even if it was only a quick run down ahead of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that depends on the partner/relationship.

Long story short I had a FWB thing with a girl who didn't like to give head, and told me she didn't much care for receiving it either. So we'd just make out, get handsy, then bone.

Her poorly kept hair downtown didn't bother me much because there wasn't the expectation I'd be up to my nose in it.

If the girl did like/want oral, then maintenance would be **far** more important.

My personal preference is for it being smooth down there, but that's not a deal breaker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Give that man the $10,000!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WUTVmuqviqE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The barbed wire looks like it's angled 'toward' us, so wouldn't that mean these cats are breaking in?

:O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....There is no other possible explanation for this photo other than the cat is actually saying that quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, I've never heard that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real. Sorry Mom and Dad, but I got out once I'm not sneaking in just to sneak out again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just try to avoid potholes as much as you normally would and you should be fine. 

Easier said than done in Buffalo NY :)

Thanks for the input though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately the 16x7's aren't outrageously expensive, but you're certainly right -- don't want then getting bent any how.

I'm just not in a position to get dedicated tires and wheels right now, unfortunately. No space to store them,  nor the money.

Have you bent yours? Or just heard of people doing it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone here have experience with OZ Ultraleggera wheels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want a set of Ultraleggeras for my Fiesta ST because they're insanely light weight. I started doing some preliminary research but I'm seeing lots of people saying they bend easily? However a lot of these posts are quite old.

I'd *like* to use them as my daily driver, but I live in the North East. Afraid potholes will ruin them.

Anyone here use them? Are they as prone to damage as it sounds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Science, cars, marijuana.

Got high and stayed up until 2AM reading about superfluids, last week. Shit's crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably ask if she can read lips. If not, I'd pull out my phone and type "I don't know how to sign".

If none of that is an issue then that wouldn't be a deal breaker for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't these government officials realize they are stunting the technological growth of the entire country in order to increase the profit margins of a few companies.


That's not true, they're getting rich too. So therefore it's OK, duh. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.

I really don't even know what the fuck to say. How did he actually become President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, he's just saying there's no reason to believe private accounts are more likely to own a certain game, therefore you shouldn't assume steamspy **under-represents** the actual figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it's off by 10%, I think that's still accurate enough to use as a reference -- especially given the fact that we have nothing else to really go by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're right... But let us dream :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do MS/Sony take for digital sales on their consoles? Anyone know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you compare any game in that list to COD?

That is one of the most successful series of games **of all time**, and according to Wikipedia is the single most successful FPS series.

With annual releases and a heavy MP-focused game it also has the benefit of "social sales". People buy it because their friends buy it and they want to play together.

You really couldn't have picked a more apples:oranges situation here while still picking 2 video games. Different genres, different expectations, different budgets for developing each etc. etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's absolutely no way it took them $2M, or even close to that, to port the game.

That has to be a very respectable ROI, even after Valve's cut.

Not to mention the fact that once a company gets one game out and sees success, they'll be more inclined to port over others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like the market for core japanese Action Games is quite strong on PC. 

I wish companies would quit it with Console Exclusives and release their shit on PC too. I want to play the newer Disgaea games but I'm not going to pay for a PS3/4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get a decent Japanese sedan for $3-5K easily on Craigslist. I assume laws vary by state so you'll have to do your own homework on buying used vehicles through a private sale. Chances have it, you (the buyer) will have very few 'protections'. I sold a car off CL though, it was tremendously easy. $3K for a Corolla with 135K miles, I was getting emails not 15 minutes after posting it. Agreed to sell it to one guy, he showed up with a wad of Hundreds, we both signed the Title, took the plates off and he drove home with the title.

---

Any old Corolla or Civic is fine really. Obviously lower miles is better, but ultimately those cars will run forever.

The most unfortunate part of this is that you absolutely should get it looked over by a mechanic. I want to say this is referred to as a "third party inspection" or TPI, but I could be mistaken. It's early and I'm not awake yet.

This will cost you $50-100, which is a lot, especially for someone in your position but it sounds like you cannot risk buying something and find out it's got some massive issues and die not long after.

But yea, you don't need a $10K+ car. Something half that price should be perfectly adequate.

I'm not sure what /u/PvtPyle05 is referring to by "driving services", were you looking to become an Uber/Lyft driver or something?       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people would say that the Fiesta ST gearbox is great. It has a good weight, throws easily.

*Sometimes* it doesn't like being shifted into first, I just throw it back into neutral real quick and try again but that doesn't happen often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Falling doesn't kill, it's the sudden stop at the end" is probably my favorite quip along those lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insurance companies and medical professionals have a say in driving policy, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why though? Once you report a phone stolen the IMEI is blacklisted and won't work.

The people you sell them to off Craigslist won't know it's stolen.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'know how Time Warner and Charter just merged into a single ISP? That's good for both.

The ISPs like it because it's less competition.

It's also good for Trump because once they repeal more Net Neutrality fundamentals then they have fewer ISPs to deal with to inject date into your web traffic. Trump / Russia could then theoretically just push fake news into your web traffic to support whatever assinine claim he wants to make. It's one fewer ISP to deal with in the courts to get user data.

I know that's full on 1984 shit, but the fact is it's a dangerously powerful tool that needs tremendous oversight.

The President who has flat out referred to "First Amendment people" as "foolish". Now they're ceasing to publish the White House visitors. He clearly thinks information and the internet is an enemy, and by giving ISPs whatever they want he puts himself in a better position when he needs a favor from them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do believe he's working under the influence of cable companies and doesn't actually think this is best for the internet... But what are you trying to show with that link?

He worked for Version for a few years I've a decade ago, and then a lobby group for a year at the beginning of this decade. Ok?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a '00 Pontiac Grand Am.

Not a bad car, except it had a massive oil leak which ended up killing it. Was putting a quart or two in per week. Didn't get paid from work one week, didn't want to ask my parents for money and it ended up seizing up on the highway one night :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50% that, 50% "peasantry" screenshots of YouTube comment trolls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's Freedom of Speech! Money talks, don't you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for being the only person to actually respond with why you like it instead of just downvoting lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd then ask you what is "1M Sales" good? The narrative, themes, and gameplay design are phenomenal. Sure it visually looks dated, but in part due to the visual design choice to support the theme and narrative. I wish more people would play this over swooning ME:A, BattleFront II, or other recent titles.  

Like I said man, I only watched him play for an hour. It looked like typical hack n slash gameplay.

I'll admit the giant robot orgy cutscene early on definitely made me say, "what the fuck is going on here?" but that's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll not trying to rag on this game, but why is it getting so much attention / reception?

I watched a friend play for about an hour. He was just starting out and it didn't look bad or anything but it certainly didn't seem "1M sales" good either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Honestly, I sometimes have a hard time figuring out what infuriates me more; The ignorant Trump supporters, or the Clinton supporters that throw around the Berniebro insult. 

That is a tough one. I almost think that at least Trump supporters can be given the benefit of the doubt that they're just a chump who fell for a con man. 

The hardcore 'feminists' who think Clinton only lost because she's a woman are just pure crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing that bugs me about IT is no overtime pay.

The last time the laws were updated, in the US, was in 1996 when they made it so that "salary employees earning at least $455wk or $27.63/hr are exempt from overtime laws."

If you're wondering how they came up with that $27.63, they tweaked the law from how it was introduced in 1990*. Back then it said you must earn at least [min. wage]  6.5. When they adjusted the law, they set it at [1996's min. wage]  6.5. As for the $455/wk figure, they tripled the old value of $150/wk which was some arbitrary value established in the 70's.

So it pisses me off that the wage laws are 21 years old.

\*: "Computer Employees" were added to the overtime exemption list in 1990, the laws governing these requirements were first introduced long before then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shaming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google: Free services which directly benefit from my information being sold. Google Maps with traffic updates? Awesome. Suggested Search Queries? Great.

Microsoft: OS you pay for unless you got the free 'upgrade'. OS does not become any better at running software or managing files by harvesting data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like what? Not that I don't believe you, but I'm curious what regulations they're supposed to comply with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm as cynical as the next Redditor and I strongly dislike FB, but do you **really** think they're honestly just like, "Eh. Dude gets murdered, but so long as we get paid then so what" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  too much away for retirement. 

There is no such thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty bogus that's what things have come to.

A coworker's husband was a teacher. Somehow one girl got it in her head that he was in love with her and she told a friend. By the end of the day he was asked to resign.

I understand schools need to protect themselves/kids, but damn. Someone can just make up a sentence and your life is through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movie makeup/prop, perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure the lense has a lot to do with it, but this gets my heart rate going just watching... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man punched the other man because he spat in his face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the dyno sheet? Looks / sounds amazing. /r/cars would like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys were supposed to open for/with Pain of Salvation at Progressive Nation '09.

Still sad I didn't get to see that show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit generator. Gives the same password no matter how many times I watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arbitrary Time Units </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something I've wanted for years.

There is this tool, [qTab Bar](http://qttabbar.sourceforge.net/), which does this. Haven't used it in a long time but I remember liking it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure they do have an unbeatable "mechanical" feedback but I like the look of the BRZ more. Plus I'm wholly opposed to reflective things in the cabin.

I just like the more compact switches, makes me feel like I'm in a fighter jet or something. Like exotics with the flip-top cover for the ignition switches :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no way to prove any sort of liability on the town's part. Not going to get a cent out of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say "more than most cities", but a good number of IT jobs for sure. Got laid off and was in a new job 2 weeks later. Admittedly, I was told I was being laid off so I was looking for work but I had no trouble finding interviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My preference is for anything that's not in the WNY region

So the rest of the world?

Boston, NYC, Silicon Valley are all great for IT but have fun with the cost of living in those areas. I moved here *from* the greater Boston area. Fuck that mess. The affordability of Buffalo is awesome.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I would say you figure out your price, first. It's a lot easier to narrow things down that way.


But I agree, Porsche naming conventions are terrible. If I pull up their website right now and click on "911 Models", you get this page:

911 Carrera has 8 options.

911 Targa has 2 options.

911 Turbo has 4 options.

911 GTS has 5.

Then there's also the 911 GT3 and 911 R listed, too.

That's **21** different 911 Somethings which all look quite similar. In addition to that, I think "Carrera", "Targa", and "GT*" are all extremely ambiguous. The only 911 sub-brand which which implies "additional performance" based off the name would be "Turbo", in my opinion.

I love Porsche and I'd love to own a 911 one day, but fuck trying to figure out which one.

And then once you do, you get to go through the dozens of individual options for your vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... impossible to move any raw material from one gravity well to another, and make money. 

What exactly is meant by this? That the energy required / difficulty of escaping the Moon's gravity along with the cargo would be too great to justify the cost?

Don't know what you mean by "gravity well". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ah, yes](https://xkcd.com/974/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disclaimer: I don't know a ton about physics.

I recently learned about superfluids and liquid helium -- specifically He-3. Seems like it would also be very valuable simply to study it too, no?

I know scientists have known about it for decades, but from what I understand we still know so very little about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't they be rare lunar metals at that point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [They started to do that!](http://jalopnik.com/the-nissan-idx-is-reportedly-really-really-dead-1706363899)

Yea... Nissan just hates fun now. Well, not 100%; this is a pretty cool project they did [last year](http://jalopnik.com/nissans-demonstrates-autonomous-technology-with-terrify-1759519992) :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  With lots of cars tipping the scales at or below 3,000 lbs., I don't think it's unheard of to ask for the same from Nissan

What can you buy with a V6 today that is close to or below 3,000 lbs?

Not counting things like Porsche, Lotus, Alfa Romeo etc. because those are in an significantly different price point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that'd really do much of anything for the Z.

American muscle cars have decades of culture in the US that Nissan simply can't match. Like yea, the Z has a pretty strong community but it's not even remotely close.

I know people who like Camaros and Mustangs because their dad had one growing up. They not really "into cars" very much but still like driving something fun. These aren't potential customers Nissan is losing out on by not offering a cheaper option; these are people who are going to buy that specific car regardless.

I just looked up the Mustang's price and the V6 is actually *cheaper* than the ecoboost -- so even if Nissan did go this route and offer an I4 turbo / NA V6 it's not going to be much cheaper, if at all. So yea... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  mercedes amg ev stuff

I think you mean [Project One](https://www.autocar.co.uk/car-news/mercedes-amg-hypercar). 

 The Project One will use the 1.6-litre turbocharged petrol engine found in the W08 Formula 1 race car (pictured below), tuned down for the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've spent very limited time in a BRZ, but I love the [switches](http://subarupmd.edgesuite.net/content/media/mp_hero_880/2017_BRZ_photos_int_04.jpg) on the center for climate controls.

Just something oldschool-ish and cool about them. I wish more cars used similar styling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it, but then again I drive a Molten Orange Fiesta with orange interior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I much prefer the size of my '73 240Z and would love to see them get back to that formula.

I don't think anyone would disagree but you have to realize that was over **40** years ago. Safety and emission standards require *a lot* of cars nowadays.

I wouldn't expect any mass-market car to be remotely close to the size or weight of a car from the 70's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think it could and should be lighter. It's bloated with a lot of "luxury" features which make me think it overlaps with the G35/37 too much.

But yea honestly I don't get why so many people cry about it being so heavy. It's 2-300 pounds lighter than the Mustang (I4 or V6) and Camaro. And like a million pounds lighter than the Challenger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think most of us would settle for simply, "A new Z car" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Honda even make anything RWD? Not counting Acura models </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly how I always thought of it! Looks like a stupid mouthguard for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention RWD vs computer-crazy AWD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was more fan speculation than anything.

They teased the "gripz" and said it was a throwback to their Rally days and then everyone was like, "Oh my God the Z is a crossover!!!"

It was a fugly design, but it was mostly over reaction to something that was obviously not going to come to fruition </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
