<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4116</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be quite honest, at this point such brazen disregard for the law no longer surprises me among politicians. I don't find that the least bit unbelievable considering the blatant and ridiculous crap that goes on every day.

That being said, u/ampersamp has provided fairly clear cut evidence of malicious tampering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lack of evidence against isn't evidence for. That the leaks are not verified doesn't give you license to leap to the conclusion that the documents have been tampered with.

That being said, u/ampersamp has provided fairly clear cut evidence of malicious tampering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much appreciated for the information. Though it makes me wonder, best I can figure either Roshka is pretty incompetent or this is some kind of red herring. And the former just seems too surreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, you know there were fake documents added to the hack, right?

I've heard speculation about this, but have yet to see anything concrete. What makes you so certain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you may have misunderstood my point. I'm not arguing that information gained from Wikipedia is necessarily inaccurate, or even that more often than not it will be inaccurate. What I'm arguing that that not allowing Wikipedia as a source in school, and in other parts of life, is a good thing because people should not be in the habit of just reading a wikipedia page when they're trying to really understand things. Sure a Wiki page is a great place to start, but you're much better off reading the sources for countless reasons. Defacement being one of the bigger ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People aren't putting false info on Wikipedia, it's only passionate professionals that put info on the site.

This is absurdly naive, but your reply also doesn't sound the slightest bit disingenuous so I have to wonder, is your wit just super dry or are you actually not aware that many people consider it a pass time to go around defacing Wikipedia articles?

I mean heck, I've personally made a couple of defacing edits, in good humor for a joke with friends and always reverting it myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Dunno why they would cut that out. Also, the link is a real nice touch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lung cancer has a 5-year survival rate of only 55% when detected on time (before it spreads to other body parts)

What's the survival rate if it's not caught before then? For instance, what if it spread to the lymph nodes first? 

Is the survival rate altered much if the patient has gone into remission, but then returned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're referring to the study I found through googling then that was 12 years ago. Wikipedia was much less popular. Hell, the internet was much less popular. 2005 was the first year that there was over a billion users. We have more than 3 times that now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wikipedia is a terrible *source* because most pages are editable by anyone, and even the ones that aren't are not necessarily maintained or in any way without error. But it's a great place to look up a reasonably detailed synopsis of most anything that strikes your fancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the big twist they cut out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yeah, they're the idiot.....](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/0d/18/40/0d18406cd16e3015fc5ff2c23ad261a4.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucken eh, those hips are wide enough to birth a celestial being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a mod and you don't know the rules?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if you promise to chaperon us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time and Relative Dimension in Space in case anyone might wonder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously. How could this not be referring to the holy trinity of the Norns? They control the fate of man and god, and autist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well.... No... They didn't. They turned from male frogs into female frogs. They even mated with male frogs, and produced viable eggs if I remember correctly. An interesting quality of this is that because both parents were genetically male the offspring resulting were always male.

But that's only the result on ~1/10, like 2/3rds were simply made infertile. 

And this, and many other probably worse effects are why the status of Atrazine is under review by many governing bodies, and is already banned in EU member states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, you're right. Instead what they do is completely ignore the possibility of valuable medical histories, because the only person who can check seat numbers also always happens to be the singular rescue worker dealing with the injured person. You are, of course, not being reductionist but rather extremely unbiased and logical in your examination.

Yup, that silly National Transportation Safety Board. They're wasting their time DEMANDING passenger manifests in the event of a crash because they're completely useless pieces of information.


I'm trying really hard right now not to be extremely rude, but your ridiculous assertions and vapid statements of how "[you're] sorry my argument is invalid" because you've come up with some overly simplified example, and because the information isn't 100% reliable, I feel like you're so ridiculously biased that there's no real avenue for logical discussion. You clearly have an opinion, I disagree with it vehemently, based on your comment I have serious doubts there was any possibility of this going anywhere near a reasonable disagreement. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree that a courts disagreement in this case would constitute bad judgment. The dad signed a contract, whether he likes the terms or not. And contracts are binding, all the terms therein to be upheld (within reason), not just the ones that suit you in the moment. 

Imagine if you contracted a builder to erect an addition onto your house, but when you finally see it finished you see that instead of the schematics you received planning permission based on, they've drawn up entirely different ones and have completed the build based off of them. When you tell them that this isn't what you've contracted them for, they tell you too bad you contracted them and they get to build what they want.

Obviously the two situations aren't identical, one is clearly more egregious than the other. Yet both constitute violations of contracts. The core of the issue is the same. You have laid out the rules, both parties have agreed, but then one party just says "lul fuck that shit" and does whatever they want anyways.

Do I agree with the stipulation in question? No, I think it's a devious money-grubbing tactic with a tiny bit of merit in that passenger lists are valuable pieces of date for many reasons.

For instance, in the event of a crash passenger lists are handed off to the NTSB so that they can identify bodies, live ones aswell if they exist. So they get handed a list that says that the passenger in seat D5 is Guy Boberson, whom they've just so happened to find alive, and he gets brought to the hospital under that pretense and is treated under that pretense. But it turns out who they actually have is Gary Smith, who it turns out is allergic to the antibiotics they're giving him and he goes into anaphylaxis and dies and none of that would have happened if Gary had just forked over the money and changed the name on the ticket.

I flat out don't agree with charges for changing the name on a ticket days in advance, but I also flat out don't agree with not changing the name on the ticket at all. Just take your lumps, pay the price you've agreed to pay in the eventuality, and then take the next week off work and picket the bloody airline.

But understand that passenger lists are valuable, not just monetarily, and that not upholding contractually obligations can cut both ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/shitredditsays

r/shitpoliticssays

I'm sure there are tons more, but those are the two [vote brigading](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vote_brigading) subs that I can think of off the top of my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A knight and his comic relief are off to save the princess from the big scary dragon, except the knight has just died and now it's all up to the comic relief. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A knight and his comic relief are off to save the princess from the big scary dragon, except the knight has just died and now it's all up to the comic relief. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think there's that much of a difference between the leaders on either side of the spectrum, for the most part? There are goods and bads on both sides, and coincidentally enough the people in the highest seats of power on both sides have a tendency towards shady and illicit behavior. It's almost like we have some sort of systemic issue or something. Naw, can't be, must be them damn dirty righties/lefties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homophobe massacred </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely and wholeheartedly disagree that you can understand Stalin the politician without understanding Stalin the man. After all, his actions and words as a politician didn't arise ex nihilo, his personal life and political life are inextricable if one wants to understand the why, and not just the how.

Stalin's first son, Yakov, shot himself. He missed his heart, and instead hit his lung. While his stepmother was tending to the wound, waiting for a doctor to arrive, Stalin is quoted as having said "He can't even shoot straight."

Later, his son being captured during WWII by the Germans, Stalin was offered an exchange. For Field Marshal Friedrich Paulus he would receive his son. Stalin refused the trade. His son later succeeded in his second suicide attempt by running into the electric fence surrounding the concentration camp in which he was held.

Do you find that immediate and personal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never played Arma, but from what I understand of it I doubt that you can do half the awesome PvP stuff there that you can do in DayZ. 

My best memories of playing DayZ are of either getting fucked with by bandits, fucking with bandits, or fucking with someone as a bandit.

God I miss handcuffing people then feeding them weird shit, stealing their blood, playing mind games with them. Tthat was such a good game before I just couldn't deal with the buggy platform anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is that not every leader who leaves behind a great legacy, leaves behind a legacy that includes some good. 

And I believe that's a fact that should be accepted, accounted for, but not treated as cause for renouncing the observation of things created by these leaders. 

If you find their legacy to be repugnant and don't want to even look near it that's your perogative. 

Personally, I think that it's all the more reason to look, because if a great person does terrible, disgusting things, it's important to examine what they did and how they did it in an effort to prevent someone similar from rising to that same greatness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stalin did absolutely nothing good, that I can think of, yet I'm quite sure he will be remembered for the foreseeable future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've bricked 6/7 of the presence of chayulas I've had this league, so yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  lets say that 10% of people are gay, and 50% of people are women. If all were equal, we'd expect that 45% of mass shootings would be committed by straight men.

Uhhhhh, no. We would expect that with a large enough sample size 45% would be committed by straight men. But when our sample size is maybe a bit more than 100 cases, and less than 4% of the population identify as gay, well it sounds to me like you're jumping the gun here.

So [~4%](https://williamsinstitute.law.ucla.edu/research/census-lgbt-demographics-studies/how-many-people-are-lesbian-gay-bisexual-and-transgender/) of the US population identify as homosexual. Now there were [90 mass shootings](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/26822013) between 1996 and 2012, so call that 90 individuals who committed mass shootings.

So since the population of the US is [~323,000,000](https://www.census.gov/popclock/) that would make mass shooters  
~0.00003% of the population. Assuming those numbers were to hold for the gay community, 0.00003% of 4% of 323,000,000 is ~4. So 4/12920000, and while I've always been pretty terrible at statistics that deviation from the expected result would seem to be reasonably accounted for by small sample size.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An interesting read, but [just so you know](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Christian_headcovering) for the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
