<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8593</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 21:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, what do you call your kitten?

I'm having trouble deciding on the character. Perhaps my little Catholic boy, because he's all sweetness and full of love, but has this ridiculously dark, psychopathic  undercurrent. He believes he's on a mission from God to rid the world of evil by, uh... killing people. I just love being able to let out my inner crazy now and again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 20:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, I do love your username. :) What kind of video games do you like?

Aww, bunnies are great pets. Mine have never tried to bite anything besides the furniture, they're really sweet little souls. They are just walking poop machines, though, haha. But thankfully they can be litter trained and mine only have the odd accident outside the box once in a blue moon. 

I have all of my work up in my [DeviantArt](http://tiny-tea-party.deviantart.com/gallery/) gallery. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 20:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you have a sewing machine so you're already well ahead of where I started out! I had to sew all my plushies by hand for the first year! 
Honestly, the best advice I can give is to just jump straight in. I'm completely self taught in regards to sewing, and this is how I started out. 

Buy a metre of cheap fleece fabric (fleece is great for learning to plush with, as it's forgiving of mistakes and easy to find in large quantities.), an old pillow you can rip open for stuffing and find yourself a simple plush pattern that you quite like. 

[This](http://gurliebot.deviantart.com/art/Darling-Plush-Pattern-127849093) sort of pattern is a good thing to start with. :)

I think the biggest secret though, is just determination. Your first few will look like crap. Expect it. But know that you'll get better by plush 4-5 when you've figured out how everything goes.

(If you ever need any help with anything when you get started feel free pm me!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 20:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh awesome, what kind of plushies do you collect? :) I have all the things I've made in my [DeviantArt](http://tiny-tea-party.deviantart.com/gallery/) gallery if you want to take a look! 

That nightmare sounds horrific! Especially the bullhorns! Christ! Did you eat lots of cheese before bed, or something?? D: Thankfully I'm not easily grossed out in the slightest, I'm quite desensitised. I tend to uh... gravitate.. towards the creepier, more disgusting stories. So thank you for sharing your dream with me. I find dreams, especially the weirder ones, super fascinating. 

I used to have tons of really horrible, violent dreams like yours a few years ago! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 20:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. That's a tough one. Not sure I have many geeky obsessions, weird and questionable ones maybe, ha. So, perhaps just my thing for manga. Male cast manga. With a bit of gay. ^And ^catboys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 13:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds a lot like the dreams I have when I'm anxious about something. I always end up back at highschool and can't find the class I'm supposed to be in, or I've forgotten my P.E kit. Horrible! 

Omg, I can never find the patience to crochet scarves. I've started a few but given up on them after a ten or so rows. Do you have any tips on how to stick with one and get it finished? I feel you on wanting more room to sew, I'm currently working out of a tiny 7x6 box room that also has my bed and wardrobe in, as I'm lodging with my grandparents. It gets really stressful sometimes. I know I'd be more productive if I had more space and didn't have to use my bed as a second desk, haha.

I think the hardest part was deciding to quit my day job and actually take on the plushing full time. I'd been working in a ridiculously unappreciated retail job for six years and from the way they treated me/their workers I was convinced I was pretty worthless and couldn't ever do anything else. At the beginning of this year I ended up at the doctors with a badly worn down rotator cuff in my shoulder from folding t-shirts on tables for five days a week for six years and either the job or the sewing had to go so I could rest. I chose to quit my job and try make a business out of the sewing. It took three weeks of laying in bed to make the decision and it was absolutely terrifying. Probably the scariest and hardest thing I've ever done in my life. Best decision I ever made though. 10/10 would go through weeks of paralysing pain to do it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 04:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I had beef curry with a baked potato! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 03:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) I wish I'd prepared better for Halloween and done more of those, they were so much fun. It was nice to step away from the florals and pretty girly stuff for a while! 

I can guarantee you my first few plushies looked incredibly handicapped. We do not speak of those abominations, haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 02:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow! That's a ton of crafts! Do you have any pictures of your work, I'd love to see them! :D

I have all my stuff up in my [DeviantArt](http://tiny-tea-party.deviantart.com/gallery/) gallery, if you'd like to take a peep! :) 

My god, I bet that plush was difficult to create, I can't even imagine the amount time he would take! In general it's not that difficult to get into plushing though. Especially if you already have sewing and crafting experience. I taught myself completely and before learning, the most I'd ever sewn was a button. It's really just a matter of jumping in head first and having the determination to try again every time you mess up - cos you will mess up a lot. 

Haha, I remember the old Disney Book Club one being one of the worst offenders. Some of the perspective and anatomy in that is so bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 02:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Let's do this! I love winter because big coats and knitwear are so cute, but gosh do I hate the rain. :( And the wind. And all the inside out broken umbrellas I end up with.

Aww, how old are your daughters? :) I sell on Etsy but my shop's closed at the moment, until the end of November due to a massive surge of Christmas orders I'm trying to wade my way through. I have all of my stuff up in my [DeviantArt](http://tiny-tea-party.deviantart.com/gallery/) gallery, though, if you fancy having a peek! 

Oh my god, that dream sounds terrifying! I bet it was a relief to wake up! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 02:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see how cross-stitch can be relaxing. I used to crochet a ton before I started sewing, and found it really therapeutic with all the repetitive motions. I can't sit down and crochet any more though, the almost instant results of sewing have spoiled me, hah. 

Yay! I'd love to see those beads. :D

And *high-five* for the mutual pokeponycup love! What's your favourite Pokemon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 01:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, it's only just occurred to me that I've never had a flying dream. Going to have to aim for one now, I feel like I'm missing out. 

I'd love to see pictures of your cross-stitch and those bead animals if you have any! :) The bead animals especially sound adorable. I've never managed to get into cross-stitch, I don't have the patience for it, so I admire those who do! 

I have my own range of 'Teacup Bunnies' which are little rabbits small enough to fit into teacups. They're all vintage inspired, so I use a lot of up-cycled and off-cut fabrics and accessories to make and decorate them. :) I also do other animals now and again, and make a lot of Pokemon and Pony inspired plushies. Most of my custom orders are Pokemon or ponies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 01:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 01:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always find it really odd when I meet people who don't remember their dreams. My S.O doesn't dream (or remember them) either. Whereas I remember all my dreams so clearly in the morning that I feel like I've been awake all night. 

Thank you for the welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 01:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! I craft! What do you craft? Let's talk about crafts! :D

I sew plushies, but have been known to dabble in crochet and also mess with clay like a little kid from time to time too. 

I love that you're a collector of The Lion King things, haha. It's my favourite Disney movie and when I was little I used to collect all the different versions of The Lion King story book so I could admire the artwork and draw from them. By the time I hit my teens I had about twenty. Some of the illustrations in the cheaper books was so bad, hah. I'm sure my mum still has all of them somewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Intro] Hello all you beauties! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 00:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so many Redditors after my own heart. *Swoon*. I've been lurking here periodically for a bit now and finally decided I should just jump into the fray. I love giving presents and with the holidays coming up it seemed like a perfect time for me to get giving. :)

Anyway! Hello, I'm Debbie. I'm 25 and I'm from the currently incredibly wet, grey and miserable North of England (though, to be fair that kind of describes it all year round). I'm a big book lover (transgressive fiction is my favourite) and wannabe novelist. Into manga and anime and video games. 

I'm currently self employed, running a little business from home sewing plushies and cute things for a livin'. Work is super busy at the moment, so I'm pretty stressed and weighed down with deadlines, but holy hell, I love my job. Getting a lovely message from someone once they've received their plush is, hands down, the best feeling in the world. I would do it for free if I didn't have three hungry pet rabbits who try to eat me out of house and home. 

Does anyone else craft at all? Anyone into sewing? Want to learn how to make plushies? I'm trying to have a crafty clear out and I have quite a bit of scrap fabric and other odds and ends such as buttons sitting around that I'm trying to find a new home for. So if anyone is interested in taking them off my hands - free of charge! - let me know!

So uh... ask me anything, if you like, I guess! But you must answer me this first: **What's the last dream you remember having?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 00:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just share the hell out of it on social media if possible, even if you're 5,000 miles away! 

I'm from Bradford and the story was in the local paper today, so it's definitely attracted a bit of media attention. I don't know if it was on the regional t.v news this evening or not, though. 

Fingers and toes all crossed that they catch the cunts who did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
