<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1073</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem operatives unveil new progressive tech incubator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Juan Williams: GOP health moves set to backfire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She Was Desperate. She Tried to End Her Own Pregnancy. She Was Thrown in Jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because while the vast majority of Democrats understand that Bernie did everything he could to help her, a few of the more vocal Hillary supporters need a yet another strawman to excuse her electoral college loss. No matter how many times to tell them that Bernie strongly supported Hillary in the GE, they refuse to listen.  They need to hate and that doesn't reflect well on Hillary or Democrats in general.

Notice you never hear Hillary blaming Bernie for the loss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'd better be the one to do that, comrade.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're spreading lies in the hopes of deceiving the less informed.  Work done.  Go home to Moscow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny how your "truth" is actually a complete lie.

Not funny "ha ha," of course, funny "man this ass is a complete lying bullshit artist trying to sell propaganda at the behest of a foreign nation" funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the Kremlin's official line now that the fascist LePen has lost?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Sanders: 'Xenophobia' lost in French election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Euro strengthens as Emmanuel Macron wins French presidential election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same could be said for assholes slavering to condemn people to death without a fair trial.  A practice also known as murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck do you want u/mackduck to do about it?  Pull a Rambo operation on Gitmo singlehandedly?  I haven't heard anything about some redditor called PurpleBanner doing that.

The poster said it was terrifying and a disgrace.  He obviously disagrees with the policy very strongly.  There's no reason or excuse to be a dick to him about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that Hilary would have been better than Trump, but if you're asking what she did wrong....

-Pushed for the Iraq War without proof of WMDs.
-Pushed for Libya attack without a plan for a peaceful solution.
-Pushed for escalated Syria involvement.
-Pushed for trade deals that harmed US workers.
-Cheated in the primaries.
-Pushed for Trump to win the Republican primaries.
-Supported the Keystone XL pipeline.
-Didn't support a living wage for all workers.
-Didn't support healthcare for ALL Americans.
-And yes, kept a personal, poorly protected, email server over which she sent classified materials.

There are many, many more things she did or didn't do that I believe were wrong and detrimental for the nation.  That doesn't mean she'd be as bad as Trump is now.  Of course she'd be better.  It means she was a lousy choice to put up in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say I was in a safe state so I had the luxury of voting for Bernie in good conscience.  Had I lived in a swing state, I would have held my nose and voted Hillary.

Is Maher so extreme that everything is black/white to him?  What an idiot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So "innocent until proved guilty" are just words people say in court that have no meaning to you.

I'm guessing you voted Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly Republicans but there were plenty of spineless Democrats who helped as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll knock Obama for a lot of things, but a refusal to close Gitmo isn't one of them.  He tried repeatedly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the catastrophe that is Donald Trump in the White House, it's easy to forget how horrible George W. Bush was.  

His policies led directly the the slaughter of hundreds of thousands of innocent civilians, the loss of many of our rights, fear of others, and to Guantanamo.  

We should never forget that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I Want Americans to Know That Guantnamo Happened Not to Monsters, but to Men" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is The Horrific Violence Trump Is Forcing Central American Refugees To Return To </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IOW:  "We don't have the votes to pass Obamacare repeal."

FIFR (Fixed it for Ryan) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Brock is back to his old games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, just laughing my ass off at the "anarchist."  What a childish belief! Hahahahaha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you'd prefer a source that has been flooded with Russian cash, but going to Brietbart makes me nauseated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or c) someone who still supports Trump and therefore by definition has the intelligence of a kid trolling on the internet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're asking whether I think that calling racists and greedy morons willing to destroy the planet for a few bucks garbage is acceptable, then the answer is yes.  Every day of the week.

If you fit into that category then consider yourself insulted, if that's possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
