<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8089</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're willing to take the Metro (or drive) up to College Park, [Wells Ice Rink](http://www.pgparks.com/Things_To_Do/Sports/Ice_Skating/Herbert_Wells_Ice_Rink.htm), which is a public rink *right* next to the College Park Metro Station, has an adult men's league.

My son figure skated competitively as a young child and played hockey there from middle through high school.  I knew a bunch of the guys on the men's team during that time and they seemed to really enjoy playing there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak with any authority in the case of AMEX, but I used to work for Visa International and that's definitely a violation of the merchant's agreement with the card issuer. It's not a grey area; such things are explicitly prohibited in the contract between the 2 parties.

However, with that said, so are the "$5 minimum purchase" policies that so many (especially small) retailers have and even enforce.  It's explicitly not allowed to impose a minimum purchase requirement, or *even to permit a split payment* (your total is $100 and you want to pay $60 on your Visa and $40 in cash), but obviously, merchants all over do it all day long, every day.

Cardholders who are aggrieved by these practices can complain to both the issuer and the credit card company (not the same thing:  the issuer would be Chase, for example, and the credit card company is Visa).  Unless they're receiving *a lot* of reports about the same merchant, though, neither entity is likely to take much action.

TL;DR:  Are they *allowed*?  Not technically, no.  But in practice, it happens all the time and there's very little in the way of meaningful enforcement.

EDIT: removed a single extraneous, confusing word.

EDIT 2:  Thanks to u/BrokenFireEscape for the correction about recent changes due to Dodd-Frank.  From [the FTC's website:](https://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/guidance/new-rules-electronic-payments-lower-costs-retailers)

 Minimum Dollar Amount for Credit Card Purchases

 A PCN cannot stop you from setting a minimum dollar amount for accepting credit cards for payment as long as the minimum is the same for all credit card issuers and PCNs, and isn't more than $10.

 **What's new about that?** PCNs sometimes prohibited merchants from refusing to accept a credit card as payment if the customer's purchase didn't exceed a certain amount. For example, if you accepted credit cards at all, the PCNs or banks might have said you had to accept a credit card for even the most minimal purchases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about [Lorena Hickok](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lorena_Hickok), who was almost certainly Eleanor Roosevelt's partner in the truest sense of the word, and also probably actually her lover? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out his reply to /u/39thversion in the thread just above this one...he also believes that permitting your wife to be forced into feeding your infant child in a public toilet is "moral." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I'm* not, because that would be ridiculous.  And fine...you got me; I'm exaggerating.  But not by much.

Here, just as a for instance, is a smoothie I commonly would make for customers at a local coffeeshop I used to manage:

1 cups vanilla yogurt (silken tofu, the other common base, works out to a very similar calorie count):  347 calories

1 cup diced frozen mango: 99 calories

1 cup sliced frozen banana: 133 calories

 cup diced frozen strawberries:  40 calories

2 Tbsp. sugar:  32 calories

Grand total:  651 calories

Can you make smoothies that are good for you and reasonable in terms of calories (especially for what people treat as a beverage instead of the meal that it is)?  Sure.  But most people don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoothies.  Commercial ones are just calorie-laden sugar bombs.  Even if you make them yourself, liquefying your food is a really just great way to make it quick and easy to down 800+ calories through a straw -- and has not a lot of other benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

What's Up?  ~For Non Blondes

Don't Stop Believin'  ~Journey

Before He Cheats  ~Carrie Underwood

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand partially corrected on the proportion of funding that comes from gun manufacturers; it's not the vast majority, it's just an awful lot.  And I can understand your skepticism of overtly biased media outlets, so will [*Forbes*](https://www.forbes.com/sites/petercohan/2012/07/23/the-nra-industrial-complex/#5a3960e12506) do?

 Over 50 firearms-related companies have given at least $14.8 million to NRA according to its list for a donor program that began in 2005. That was the year NRA lobbyists helped get a federal law passed that limits liability claims against gun makers. Former NRA President Sandy Froman wrote that it saved the American gun industry from bankruptcy, according to Bloomberg.

And I'm not calling out "corporate" as an inherently bad thing.  I'm calling out the NRA's marketing themselves as being of and for the little guy -- the rugged, American individualist (which is absolutely their brand) -- completely disingenuous if they've turned into little more than a front for the interests of big business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that it doesn't require it.  The fact that it permits it on that basis is the point.

IANAL, but I have worked with a number of attorneys practicing in this state who parse that passage exactly as I presented it.  The question wasn't whether unconstitutional statutes are enforced, it was where and whether they exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep reading...unless they don't believe in God, heaven, or hell.

So, an atheist? Can be disqualified.  A person who belongs to a religion that doesn't have a heaven/hell construct?  Can also be disqualified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religious tests of any kind to participate in civic functions are a violation of the establishment clause.  It doesn't have to be a particular religion or denomination.  Non-belief is protected under the 1st Am. as much as any belief is.  That's a fundamental purpose of the establishment clause...not just to ensure that no one denomination or faith is favored over any other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IANAL, but I am a Maryland resident with at least functional adult reading comprehension.

Our state constitution states, in part:

 nor shall any person, otherwise competent, be deemed incompetent as a witness, or juror,
on account of his religious belief, **provided, he believes in the existence of God, and
that under His dispensation such person will be held morally accountable for his acts,
and be rewarded or punished therefor either in this world or in the world to come**.

Yes.  Our state constitution says you can't be disqualified in court as a witness or juror -- *unless you don't believe in God*...or even simply don't believe in eternal reward/punishment.  How's *that* for a bare-faced violation of the establishment clause? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checker's (or Rally's, depending on where you are) [apple nuggets.](http://www.treasurenet.com/forums/attachment.php?attachmentid=303275 stc=1 d=1332399947)  They were basically just battered, deep fried bites of apple pie filling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, so conflicted.

I'm what most would consider pretty far left on the political spectrum, particularly in the U.S., but the 2nd Amendment is where I typically diverge from most people with whom I otherwise agree on a majority of issues.

There's a very good reason the 2nd Am. is in our Bill of Rights; the founders understood that the people's ability to arm themselves is a fundamental deterrent against tyranny.  This is as true today as it ever was.

Practically speaking, though, there are real problems with unrestricted access.  The rates of gun violence in the U.S. are horrific (in places that have both lax and strict gun laws).  In addition, the 2nd Am. has been co-opted by some very unsavory elements of our society, including not only corporate gun manufacturers (that's what the vase majority of NRA membership and money *really* is, not hunters and sport shooters), but also the subculture now referred to as the alt-right.

Even though I am, in principle, a staunch supporter of the people's right to bear arms, the face of the movement to protect it is repugnant and I have no desire to associate myself with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think for solid writers, minimum length requirements often are counter-productive.  However, professors are somewhat caught between a rock and a hard place on this.  Students in all disciplines struggle with writing and, if you listen to instructors, the proportion who struggle enough for it to impact their academic output and performance seems to be growing.  One symptom of this is not knowing how to critically assess what a writing assignment as asking for and making sure to go deep enough with one's response to satisfy the assignment's standard.  For this reason, I think professors often create minimum length requirements as a basic safeguard to ensure that less competent writers/students at least aren't failing because they didn't even understand the depth/breadth/level of analysis demanded by the assignment.

TL;DR:  Minimum length requirements are for the weak students/writers, not the strong ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spot on.  In fact, one major factor that has made the surge in shitty *and* fake news (they're not the same thing) possible is people's laziness and unwillingness to critically read multiple sources, instead always looking for an easy, single media pill to pop.  Turns out being an informed citizen is work and requires effort.  Weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 thoughts:

1. I doubt it's your *eyeliner*, even if that was the excuse she used.  

2. Just because she's married, doesn't mean she's straight.  You probably know that, but she might not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/poem_for_your_sprog  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2nd Circuit (again) finds anti-gay discrimination legal under Title VII </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look out, OP.  Don't take advice from anyone here who isn't a licensed attorney specializing in undead law.  Reddit is full of fake vampire lawyers, and you don't want to take a chance on advice from some hack, now do you?

Disclaimer: IANAVL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the website and did 4 tests with 4 different genres.

300 wpm as an average sounds reasonable to me.  I know I'm a very fast reader, and my scores on the 4 tries ranged from 509 - 837 wpm.

I wouldn't sweat it, though...there's a huge range of "normal" reading speed and as long as your comprehension is good, that's really what matters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And along these lines, courtesy of my Iowan relatives:

Sauerkraut on pizza is astonishingly not terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  That's what he's saying, and he's completely wrong.

As I mentioned in my reply to him, below:

  in at least the jurisdiction where I live, that's absolutely false. Disclaimers such as this one have absolutely no impact on the owner's liability for damage caused by objects ejected from the vehicle.

 Source: Worked for my state's DMV for 8 years and used to gleefully provide the insurance information for a given tag number when someone whose car got dented all to shit on the highway behind one of these motherfuckers would come in to ask for it. Those insurance claims were almost always successful because their warning means jack shit. Also, if a cop sees it, they will absolutely pull you over and ticket you, no matter what your stupid placard says.

Sorry for basically double-posting this comment, but it really grinds my gears when people A) make shit up that's false B) that shit can have real legal consequences for people and C) when called out on it, they get salty, dv, and try to argue some point that was never being made in the first place in order to save face.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat?

I didn't say it's a good idea, or recommended, for people to drive into the path of debris coming from the back of a vehicle.

I simply pointed out that your oh-so-confidently made assertion about *legal liability* is false.  Signage like this does **not** absolve the vehicle owner of responsibility for any damage their flying debris might cause -- which is what you erroneously said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Citation?

Because in at least the jurisdiction where I live, that's absolutely false.  Disclaimers such as this one have absolutely no impact on the owner's liability for damage caused by objects ejected from the vehicle.

Source:  Worked for my state's DMV for 8 years and used to gleefully provide the insurance information for a given tag number when someone whose car got dented all to shit on the highway behind one of these motherfuckers would come in to ask for it.  Those insurance claims were almost always successful because their warning means jack shit.  Also, if a cop sees it, they will absolutely pull you over and ticket you, no matter what your stupid placard says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are objectively wrong.  Further, you are not *only* wrong, but aggressively offensive in the way you choose to make value and character judgments about not those who *perpetrate* heinous crimes, but not about those who have violent crimes committed against them.

First, the body and brain respond to sexual assault as violent crime because that's exactly what it is, even if it's coercion rather than brute force being used.  Rape isn't about sexual gratification; **rape is about power**.  Having one's power (i.e., agency; consent to what is possibly the most intimate possible act, both mentally and physically) taken away by another person by their sexual violation of you **is** being the victim of a violent crime.

Second, we are hard wired to treat rape as a clear and present threat to our survival because in human history, rape is often a precursor to murder, *especially* when perpetrated by men against women.

Third, even if physical force is not used, rape poses a very real risk of contracting a sexually transmitted infection -- some of which are fatal.  This is unarguably an act of violence a person survives.

You do not consciously decide how your brain reacts in an emergent situation in which the fight/flight/freeze response is engaged.  That decision occurs in a split-second and it doesn't occur in your frontal lobe.  You admit you are uneducated about the matter.  Maybe you should take some basic (intro level -- my son covered this shit in high school) psychology, because that's the only background knowledge necessary to know how utterly, astoundingly wrong you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sexual assault and rape are one of the most psychologically damaging events a person can experience.  Some of the **most** terrible things that can happen to a person have nothing to do with physical pain, injury, or scars...let alone death.

What the brain is trying to survive is the absolute most primal form of **violation** that one person can perpetrate against another.  I assure you, this is a concept most people (who want to) are capable of understanding, even if, like you, they have never been involved in a rape and have "no formal education on the matter." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  Absolutely no need to shut up, but I *do* speak Spanish fluently.

Since I obviously can't help myself and we're already on the subject, a tiny correction:  Accents in Spanish have 2 purposes. The first is the one you describe -- a visual marker of which syllable receives the stress in pronunciation (but only when the word in question breaks the rules regarding this).  So "nu**me**ro" ("I count") follows the rules and doesn't get an accent, but "numer****" ("number") doesn't follow the rules and needs that accent on the last syllable to show you how it's pronounced.

The second purpose of the orthographic accent is the si/s example.  Here, obviously, there is only one syllable, so the accent cannot be indicating stress.  Instead, in words like "s" the accent mark functions as a marker of *meaning*, not pronunciation.  It is the only way a reader knows to differentiate between "ms" ("more") and "mas" ("but") or "se" (reflexive pronoun) and "s"  ("I know").

Most native speakers aren't even aware of this second function because it works intuitively.  People like me, who learned Spanish as a secondary or tertiary language, tend to rely on those cues a lot if we were taught about them early on.

Now *I'm* sorry and feel the need to shut up.   :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. "Porqu no los dos?"  Is a wholly appropriate reaction.  I'm changing my answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or pedantically, "S."

What you typed means "if."


:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/bigotemexicano, I think Zapata may have one up on you here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Fun fact:  Most people think that Billy Joel's "Uptown Girl" was about Crawford.  This is understandable, since she starred in the music video for it and they married just a couple of years later.~~

In reality, though, [the song was originally about a rival supermodel of ~~Crawford's~~ Brinkley's, Elle Macpherson.](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-1327163/Billy-Joels-Uptown-Girl-inspired-Elle-Macpherson-Christie-Brinkley.html)

EDIT:  I'm an idiot, and I'm also wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From another comment:

 So what do you learn about analysis if all you do is analyze without learning the actual fundamentals?

You keep alluding to "going deeper," "technical aspects," and "fundamentals."

I'm getting the sense, though, that you don't actually have any idea what you mean by that.  If you *do* know what you mean, please provide examples.  You said if you were to Google or read books on the subject you would necessarily encounter this more advanced material, so I assume you've done that, which should make it simple for you to be specific about what you think is lacking.

So far, you haven't done that at all.

In addition, just from reading your comments here, I feel perfectly secure in telling you that you aren't ready for anything more advanced than Freshman Composition, so I'm really not certain what your complaint is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a lifelong Maryland resident, I can't decide whether to be proud we finally made this change, or appalled that it took so long.

It's perplexing that prior to this bill's passage that Maryland's statute was so out of sync with other states on this issue, especially given how blue our state legislature is.  The article offers no insight on this...anyone have an answer/want to speculate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've apparently fashioned a hat out of it, too, which is even more perplexing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between this and the well-behaved fans gif, it's a pretty great week to be a Caps fan on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm learning via this thread.  Fascinating stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's super cool.  TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Rosie the Riveter, but with with a super cute grin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right?

Half-sleeping in a camp chair on the sidewalk (if you were lucky) or some folded blankets (if you weren't) *used* to be worth it.  Not anymore.

I still love live music, but I'm not gonna fight you for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IKR? (Nice interrobangs, btw.)  I definitely recommend it...it's on Google Play, but idk about the App Store...I'm an Android girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know about Shortyz?  It's a crossword app I stumbled upon that downloads crosswords every day from a bunch of different newspapers/syndicates.  It's free and I've never seen an ad.

I'll still do a paper crossword if I happen to find one, but that rarely happens anymore.  Now, I always have tons of crosswords waiting on my phone to save me from boredom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for me, but for my son, who does blacksmithing:

Scrap metal of almost any kind, even cables.  He can find a way to make use of it in the forge and is thrilled to get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a handsome guy!  Does he live at the shop or does he come home with you?

Also, am I noticing some [polydactyly](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Polydactyly) there on his paws?  Looks like he has more than the standard number of kitty toes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That link is staying blue, but if 'pro ana' means what it did the last time I checked, I'm skeptical that you can.

I'm sorry to pry, but is help readily available to you should you want it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is Jenny? Discuss "kisses" in the context of her existence.

Why are you not allowed to use the phrase "grilled cheese" on r/food?  What is the proper word for the food that is akin to a grilled cheese, but is definitely *not* a grilled cheese, and whose misuse makes people psychotic?

Explain the connection between the beloved candy Jolly Rancher and projectile vomiting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lefty-loosey, righty-tighty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my favorite because it was my great-grandfather's go-to insult, complete with his thick Yiddish accent:

"May you grow like an onion with your head in the ground." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pair of relevant usernames here is r/oddlysatisfying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely didn't start mine.

Definitely *did* reinforce it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Maybe it's just hockey fans in general?

There may be something to this.

As I mentioned, I'm a DC native, too.  I grew up in a 'Skins household--my people didn't watch hockey.

My son started playing for his local rec league team when he was in 5th grade, and from the very first game I went to, I immediately noticed something was *different* about hockey fans.  There's a sense of them wanting to involve you in the fun they're having and not taking no for an answer.

I knew nothing about hockey when my son started to play, but that didn't last for long because other parents would sit next to me, manically calling out the play-by-play with explanations.


In some ways, the sport has more than its share of asshole fans (and asshole parents -- I don't know if you remember the "magic hockey helmet" thing from youth hockey many years back).  But overall, they are weirdly friendly and welcoming, and just generally great.  It almost seems like hockey fans love the game in a different way from other sports fans, and they're eager to be nice to you just so they can share their love of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a bunch from this DC-native Caps fan hockey mom.

It really is a terrific crowd.  Come back and see us soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My stepmother was in the same year with Susan Sarandon at Catholic University.  They apparently hung out with the same crowd and had some mutual friends.  My stepmother always said that Sarandon was such an enormously stuck up bitch that -- despite acknowledging her genuine talent -- she could never watch anything she acted in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This maybe makes the most sense of all.  You ladies are so smart! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clever!  I'll have to remember that for when I move back into a place with a dishwasher, because that I might actually do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not necessarily recommending it, because I have better things to do with my Sunday afternoons, but I was raised by 2 women who were cheap and more than a little compulsive about cleaning.

I was taught that all hairbrushes and combs should be washed in warm, soapy water in the bathroom sink once a week, then left to air dry.  It's tedious as crap, and like I said...*i* don't do it, but it *does* work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was mostly joking, because poking at my own pain is how I cope. I'm scared for America's place in the world in a way I have never been in my 40+ years.

In all seriousness, thanks for the earnest answer.  It doesn't change the reality of the situation, but feeling a little solidarity coming this way is awfully nice. Most of us also deeply cherish the very special neighborly relationship we've had with you guys -- our geopolitical cousins, in a sense.  And even that feels like it is at risk these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an American, I can't shake the feeling that every Canadian is taking stock of our respective current situations and smugly thinking, "Yeah, suckers...how ya like me now?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a very interesting argumentation strategy; I noticed it in the thread with /u/cesarjulius.  It seems to consist of *slightly*, almost imperceptibly, altering your opponent's argument so that you can make the point you *are* able to support, rather than addressing the *actual* point being made.  So let me see if I can be crystal clear:

My point wasn't that punitive damages exist across all 50 states without exception.  I did not say that punitive damages are the law of the land regardless of jurisdiction.  My point was that, where they *do* exist (which, even by your data, is the vast majority of states), their purpose is unarguable. The whole reason that most states' civil codes provide for punitive damages in civil liability (and particularly product liability) cases is to punish those who committed the tort in a severe enough way that it actually hurts, thereby acting as an incentive to change their practices and a disincentive to repeating the tortious conduct.

You may think they are ineffective; you may have other philosophical disagreements with them as a mechanism of justice. Again, your criticism of their value and efficacy has absolutely no bearing on the express purpose for which punitive damages *do* exist with respect to civil liability, especially with respect to *product* liability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude.

I was born in DC and lived outside it my whole life (I'm in my 40s) until I moved to a very rural part of my state 2 years ago to finish school.

I have been baffled and bewildered since I got here.  

What's my secret?

In 10 weeks, I'm moving home.  No, seriously...I realized that even if I could find a job here, which I probably cant, I was never likely to find a girlfriend, let alone anything more than that out here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know any other way to be, apparently... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like in this case your username does not check out.

That's good, because he's full of shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, within reason.  But there are very, very few places in the U.S. (except *maybe* Hawaii and Alaska) where the cost of making a single hamburger from scratch doesn't work out to less than $3.  Yes, you probably have to buy enough meat and buns to make more than one burger, but it's not like you're going to let that other food go to waste, are you?

Eating out, even eating out as cheaply as humanly possible, is almost never a better deal than cooking your own food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the takeaway here, really.

If you feel the way I do about this, be advised that downthread is ugly crazytown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus fucking Christ.

At least read the motherfucking article before just spouting bullshit you made up because it agrees with your narrative:

 Her grandson **parked the car** so that Liebeck could add cream and sugar to her coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does it say about me that I *only* recognized this when I got to the "thwack"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can disagree all you like; luckily for the rest of us, facts don't depend on your approval.

In the civil justice system in the U.S., punitive damages are expressly intended as a mechanism to **punish** the entity that committed a tort. It's exactly as /u/cesarjulius describes:  the punishment is *supposed* to be large enough that the wrongdoer is provided with an actual disincentive to repeat the behavior and therefore, change their practices.

You may not *like* the fact that this is the specific, conscious intent of the existence of punitive damages, but that doesn't change the fact that it absolutely *is*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burger**s** *plural*, yes...I can see that.

If it's costing you more than $3 to make a single hamburger, you're doing it wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McDonald's coffee being decent is relatively new.  They used to be the poster child for awful coffee. That's where the whole "McCaf" thing came from -- they had to somehow sway public opinion about their coffee in a massive way.

The extra-hot brewing and holding temperatures *were* a cost-saving measure, but it had to do with hotter water extracting more flavor (although worse flavor) out of the beans, not discouraging refills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I saw that comment earlier.  That was in the same comment where you misrepresented the temperature the coffee was being served at.  You asserted that both parties agreed in court that the coffee Liebeck received was "just under 180 degrees."  Except it wasn't...as /u/EMorteVita had to point out to you -- the coffee McDonald's handed to Liebeck was between 180 - 190 degrees...which is **far** hotter than the 170 degree minimum holding temperature prescribed by your citation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is incorrect.  In fact, the *whole reason* punitive damages were awarded in this case is that McDonald's coffee was *well outside* that range. Their own corporate documents showed they were aware that holding coffee at the higher temperature increased the risks of severe industry to customers, but that their cost-benefit analysis suggested that it was less expensive to settle lawsuits than to reduce the temperature to within industry standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  r/badwomensanatomy is that way --- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (and I know you're a lawyer now because you're argumentative, used the word "commensurate," and are coming across as condescending with your "you still don't get it" snark)

Actually, since I am *not* an attorney, I choose to take this as a compliment.  It *is* interesting, though, that my use of a  very normal 4-syllable word (most often encountered in employment advertisements) leads you to conclude that that I'm a lawyer.  Your kneejerk anti-intellectualism is duly noted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blink twice if they're still there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you *still* don't get it.

No reasonable person would expect that any cup of coffee would be as hot as the one McDonald's served her.  While a reasonable person would likely know that hot coffee spilling could cause injury, she would have **no way** to know that a cup of coffee would be so hot as to to even have the **potential** to cause the type of injury she suffered.

She *was* acting with care.  She was acting with care that was commensurate to the amount of risk a cup of coffee **should have** posed to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
