<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9341</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because she's dumb AF? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend showed me a video of her asking Thatcher questions in 1990. I can't believe someone that incompetent has stayed in office for so long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diane Abbott just doesn't do numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that now, haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're really living up to your username in this post. You've had your house longer than I've been alive, that would really suck to have to leave it because of others' poor decisions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a kid I was really impressed with myself for 2 things I could do on my bike:  
1) Ride with no hands on the handlebars.  
2) Ride with no ass on the seat.  

It's when I tried to combine these that I ran in to problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took approx 2.8 seconds to fall.  

s = ut + 1/2at^2  
s = 0 + 0.5 * 9.8 * 2.8^2  
s = 38.4 m </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reminds me of a joke I once read... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that would have made much more sense. I think the rope thing was just there to be dramatic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you can be happy that you're in a position to leave, some of us are stuck with this mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just off the cuff:  
* you don't see 14 km/s space debris coming.  
* 14 km/s space debris doesn't just punch a hole in your face, it obliterates you.  
* the scene where they are holding the rope before Matt drifts away. That rope is in tension, why is he still drifting away when there is no outside force? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death comes for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savage! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the UK and we had to pay the equivalent of about $100 to hire a gown for about 3 hours. We had to use the approved gowns of the university. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew a girl who was top of her class in biochemistry at university, but she wouldn't rearrange a simple equation or change a lightbulb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even American, so I don't care. Haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could get the tip of my dick in my mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #1 in moon landings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong, with a projectile you also have to overcome gravity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Honestly anyone can put their dick in an inanimate object

All those women with dicks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR/ELI5: They're relatively unreactive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although you are technically correct, I think there is some confusion. Although the average life expectancy was much lower in the past, it doesn't mean that few people lived past reproduction age. [The infant mortality was very high, so this massively skewed the average life expectancy data.](http://history.howstuffworks.com/history-vs-myth/did-people-in-past-really-only-live-to-be-30.htm)  
For example, if you have 3 people, 2 of which die at age 1, and one who dies at 70, then their average life expectancy is 24.  
Average life expectancy doesn't always paint an accurate picture.In the past, if you survived the first few years of childhood, you stood a good chance of reaching a relatively old age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/raisedbynarcissists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only men can do the first one, and only women can do the second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is incredibly frustrating, the whole country is brainwashed. Lots of people have the attitude that 'being British means we're better than everyone else' despite most people being mostly unremarkable. I believe that the media have had a huge role in polarizing people against the EU. Most EU citizens I have met have been perfectly reasonable and respectful, yet they are demonized by our media.  

I visited Germany for a holiday last summer and had a great time. Everyone was so friendly and helpful and your countryside is so clean! In the UK, the sides of the motorways are full of litter, but I drove for miles down the Autobahnen and barely saw any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do we need humans to survive anyway? We have proven time and time again that we, as a species, cannot be trusted to look after this planet. Once we are gone, nobody will be around to miss us anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the media talks about is how amazing Theresa May is, despite doing next to fuck all while being PM.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see vigilante Facebook groups all of the time from my hometown. Where people will post CCTV of people who have had motobikes/expensive pedal bikes stolen and the police has done fuck all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I know a guy who knows a guy who knows a guy who has a list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What is delusional is that the people voting remain are either students, metropolitan employees, already rich pop figures, or people with a vested interest in existing European/UK trade/grants.  

This isn't delusional thinking.  

 Because we don't have anything more to lose.  

I'm not doing great, so I'll drag the country down with me. Great attitude.  

 It's a clusterfuck, and the EU has not helped this case.  

Please elaborate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's frustrating talking to Brexiters because they are all so delusional about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't the ones paying the price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither do half of us :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's about 0.93% argon, 300-400 ppm CO2 and the rest trace elements. Which is why I said close enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also it is still in the future...  

I'll rephrase it to 'The vote for Brexit'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brexit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask myself this every time I'm in these threads. What benefits are we getting from leaving? The answer is, very little. We already had an excellent deal within the EU, but the knuckle-draggers cannot see past our media's lies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is completely unfit to be in the position she is in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [SQUARK!](https://munguin.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/aend1.jpg?w=840) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you meant to say 'strong and stable'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop it with your 'facts'! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Isis vs Daesh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
