<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4635</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 07:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/rqHHb9J.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 15:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Store link: http://www.windowsphone.com/s?appid=e145af3f-2aab-4e78-8699-ce948e26d27f </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 07:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screenshot shortcut is WinKey + Print Screen. I think it's been there since Windows 8 came out.

In taskbar and start menu properties you can unselect Use the Start menu instead of the Start screen and you can use the Windows 8 start screen instead.

Also another useful shortcut. Control + WinKey + Left or Right to switch quickly between virtual desktops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 01:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 17:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He works for Twitch: https://twitter.com/fishstix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 23:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't use this thread. Use this one:
https://www.reddit.com/r/leagueoflegends/comments/2fxrj8/patch_416_notes/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just released a Twitch client for Windows 8.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 19:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just released a Metro Twitch client for Windows 8.1 that I have been working on for a while now.

App Store Link: http://apps.microsoft.com/windows/app/twixel/02c74012-7ac2-413b-ae79-6ebce5b8e3db

Also the source is available here: https://github.com/subject4635/TwixelApp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 04:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this situation it is similar to saying "Oh my God" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Haiku] Vertical </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 00:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 05:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've emailed support 5 times in the last year and every single time they have gotten back to me in 2 days or less. Actually only one support ticket was responded to 2 days later, the others were 1 day and one was even responded to in the same day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 02:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can email support to get private information. It's been stated multiple times by Riot. Riot also stated if you go into a public forum (forums, reddit, whatever) and ask about your ban the info will be publicized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 02:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently have 575 hours logged on Super Monday Night Combat. Was the first MOBA I played and I loved it. After most of the community left I moved over to League because most of my college friends played it but SMNC still will have a place in my heart. I even bought MNC on Steam when it was on sale one day to play it but I prefer the pace of SMNC (contrary to what most of the posts here say). I guess I like a more traditional MOBA. I heard that MNC had one hit kills and time to kill was faster. I feel like that makes it more frustrating for a new player to pick up the game. SMNC still was somewhat fast paced but it had somewhat of a laning phase or ramp up phase where you had to kill bots before you could start killing players just like in League or DotA.

If a SMNC kickstarter came out I would support it. I would rather the game stay closer to SMNC than MNC but it seems like more people like MNC's playstyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 00:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://www.reddit.com/r/leagueoflegends/comments/29q6ks/shoutout_to_moobeat/cinxfpq) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 00:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you throw your Q out onto a target and then E; if you make contact with the target when your Q hits them you will blind yourself. I've only had this happen to me once while playing Quinn but it happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 18:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wont be in 4.12. [They still have more changes to put on the PBE.](http://community.pbe.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/champions-gameplay-feedback/IYeaedu8-sona-pbe-update) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 07:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Lucian's changes probably aren't considered a gameplay update (meaning he will be played in next week's LCS if the patch comes out on Wednesday)

- Sona's rework will probably be in 4.13 which is probably 2 weeks from now and she won't be available for 4 weeks after she is changed. (Probably available the 27th of August)

- Fiora's rework hasn't hit PBE yet. We have no idea how far along that is but it probably won't make it onto PBE until Sona is ready to be pushed to live. Earliest I can see it hit live is the 13th of August. It will count as a gameplay update so wont be available Sept 10th.

- Nobody knows how far along Sion is. If Sion hits live after Fiora (super optimistic) it will probably be around the 27th of August and won't be available till the 24th of September.

- Worlds starts some time in September with the final on October 19th. Last year's Worlds started on September 15th and lasted 19 days so if we go by that this years worlds will start on September 30th. The last major patch before Season 3 worlds seems to be 3.10a which happened on August 22nd which was 43 days before worlds. This would put that patch around September 6th for this year. Following the two week patch release schedule that patch would be 4.13 (July 30th) or 4.14 (August 13th) anything that hits in one of those two patches probably will be allowed (Lucian was allowed and he hit 3.10a) so following theoretical patch release cycle I put up only upto the Fiora gameplay rework would be allowed in the Worlds patch.

So to answer your question. Unless the team scrambles to put Lee Sin changes up onto PBE for 4.13/4.14 cycle he won't be in worlds. Sona has been worked on for a while. The first time we heard that Fiora was being updated was early April so Lee Sin changes now would probably suck for everybody involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 07:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are multiple champion designers/game designers that work on different champs. For example one designer worked on Rengar and Skarner, another worked on Lucian, one is currently working on Fiora, one worked on Xerath. It's usually one or two people who do the major thought process and design behind balancing a champion but they do get help from everybody else. I'm sure one designer doesn't get to sign off on the changes before the rest of the team sees it but I wouldn't be surprised if the teams trusted that one designer's thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 07:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm betting the patch notes come out tomorrow. PBE was getting prepped for live launch last week (they took out new SR and any other changes that would not be in 4.12, Lucian's changes were not removed). Also since they probably will not count this as a gameplay update he will be available next week in LCS. People will be able to get used to him for playoffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 07:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riot doesn't want low interaction to have high rewards. Feral Flare allowed you to farm jungle in high safety (compared to laners who always have to fight somebody else) and get just as much gold as a laner who has to deal with another person. Same with many other strong junglers. Farm in safety, gank and get a kill. Outscale somebody who has to lane against another champion, deal with ganks, and CS properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 04:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://1drv.ms/1rPwcFD

Last time I updated it was for 4.10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 01:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to give some perspective.

[Chart of all ADC attack speeds](http://i.imgur.com/HtCOkop.png)

Graves is tied for last with Caitlyn, Corki, Ezreal, and Jinx. His level 18 base AS is 5th from last (Ezreal, Corki, Sivir, and Jinx behind him). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 16:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [LtRandolph posted on the forums about the Shen bug and his progress on fixing it.](http://forums.na.leagueoflegends.com/board/showthread.php?p=48009818#post48009818) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 14:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was near Ottawa, Ontario for vacation. 110 base ping with spikes upto 700 ping every like 10 minutes in a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 04:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently in Canada for a week on vacation. Been playing League and Civ V on my Surface Pro 1. I have a gaming PC I built sitting at home. Bringing my entire rig for a week is pretty unreasonable. But yes I do miss playing at max resolution and 60+ FPS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 03:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was learning League I bought a lot of champions because I wanted to get to play all of them and every new champ I bought I played a bot game first with them to learn how their abilities work and stuff. I feel like bot games have a place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 22:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The exact same thing was posted here.](http://www.reddit.com/r/leagueoflegends/comments/29ubsi/make_crit_into_auto_attack_damage_modifier_no/)  
[And also on the forums here.](http://community.na.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/live-gameplay/hbEj1jWi-can-we-finally-phase-crits-rngesus-out-of-the-game)  

I fully support this. AA damage will be theoretically the same with this idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 21:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have your math wrong. Currently if you crit you do 200% of your attack damage which you stated. What he is suggesting is that you do bonus damage equal to what your crit % would be now. So if you have 200 AD and 30% bonus damage (30% crit chance) you do 260 AD 200 + (200 * 0.3 = 60) = 260.

If you have 100% bonus damage (100% crit chance) and you have 200 AD you would do 200  + (200 * 1.0 = 200) = 400 which is exactly the same as it is currently. Remember it's bonus damage so that gets added onto your current AD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 21:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was also suggested here: http://community.na.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/live-gameplay/hbEj1jWi-can-we-finally-phase-crits-rngesus-out-of-the-game

For anybody who doesn't understand how this would basically be the same as the crit we have now.

If you have 200 AD and 30% crit that means 30% of the time your auto attacks would do 200% damage. Meaning 30% of your AAs do 400 AD instead of 200 AD (we are ignoring any resistances/runes/masteries etc.). If you AA 10 times you would be expected to have 7 normal damage attacks and 3 crit damage attacks.

200 * 7 + 400 * 3 = 2600 damage dealt in 10 AAs

Now if you do 30% more damage on every auto attack instead of crit each of your auto attacks would do 260 AD instead of 200. Now over 10 AAs

260 * 10 = 2600 dealt in 10 AAs.

This is a good solution because it is exactly the same as crit except it smooths the curve out. You don't get lucky and have many crits in a row or unlucky with no crits (there is a modified RNG in the game so you shouldn't get periods of no crit at all). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 21:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anymore.  
[Article](http://www.forbes.com/sites/bobbyowsinski/2014/06/20/does-the-music-business-really-need-youtube/)  
[60 FPS video](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T3ny9zIckP0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 23:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have complained about this in the past and I noticed that they have gotten better about posting context changes. (IE what the value was on the previous patch). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 18:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When new League news comes out you see many posts lead to the same page/information. I downvoted it probably because it was posted after an identical post to the subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 15:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't need to get exposed. [Moobeat posts links to s@20 all the time.](http://i.imgur.com/wf4NMLz.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 14:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/4DelpBY.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 04:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Urgot](http://images.wikia.com/leagueoflegends/images/d/d3/Urgot.move8.ogg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 02:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reported it on PBE when Buff Timers first came out there. http://community.pbe.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/bugs/eGpqgyzM-buff-timers-in-game-tip-at-beginning-of-match-displays-incorrectly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 23:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably weren't ready for 4.11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 21:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played like 25 games over the course of 4 days with Yasuo. After the first like 3 games where you suck you start to learn how to lane with him. Teamfighting with him is harder. A lot harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 21:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because the changes were not planned to hit for the 4.11 patch. Right before a patch hits they take out all the things that wont be in the new patch to test the real patch for stability. (The new SR also got taken out of PBE). Once the patch hits live you can probably expect a BT change to be back if they want to buff it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 03:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since it's only a map skin the underlying terrain geometry will be the same as the current SR so in some places your character may be too far away from a wall or inside a wall (probably won't happen too much or drastically because the map geometry is basically the same) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 01:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wukong and Ori with Yasuo. Their team has no chance in team fights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 06:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [As you can see they didn't change any of his numbers.](http://na.leagueoflegends.com/en/news/game-updates/patch/patch-46-notes#patch-twitch) Before the rework he was exactly the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 06:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, no timer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 04:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anybody wants to read his [preseason 4 tier list](http://blog.ibuypower.com/blog/2013/12/06/doublelifts-pre-s4-ad-tier-list/) He said twitch was shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 23:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they are going to do inhib timers as well with the new map. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 23:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure you know when these timers are but it's still player vs player interaction which they said they won't do timers for ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 23:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Gold and up is the top 17% of players.](http://www.lolsummoners.com/stats) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 23:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like you missed these sentences.
 On one side, a case could be made that map-level objective awareness is a significant aspect of skill  and to that, we wholeheartedly agree. We would not, for example, alert you when an opponent entered your immediate radius from fog, nor would we ever track enemy cooldowns for you. Your interactions with your opponents are sacred and we will always leave those interactions alone.

I'm assuming enemy team summoner spells, skill, and ward timers fall under opponent interactions.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 22:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they meant, "We noticed a lot of you complained when we told Curse Voice to remove buff timers, so we put it in the game on our own" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 22:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riot should remove the HUD and only leave the minimap as memorizing your ability cooldowns and knowing what slot your items are in is what separates the good players from the great players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 22:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adding 5, 6, and 7 to whatever time you killed the buff at is really hard right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reign of Gaming - Unofficial PBE Patch Notes for 6/23/2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 22:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 19:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pando Media Booster the installer installs is the old non malware version but still... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 11:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, people shouldn't point out the flaws in things! They should have blind optimism about ideas and Riot should follow through with them no matter the costs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 09:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could have something to do with [this](http://forums.na.leagueoflegends.com/board/showthread.php?p=47924302#post47924302)...but we still have 30 minutes until it's expected to hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 07:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jax is some random mercenary who happens to be [randomly placed into the League of Legends](http://leagueoflegends.wikia.com/wiki/Jax/Background#Lore) and became really good at fighting, the person who got him in [dissappears randomly](http://leagueoflegends.wikia.com/wiki/The_League_of_Legends#Structure), he became so good at fighting that the person who replaced the old High Councilor thought Jax was too good so he placed restrictions on him, that Councilor was imprisoned later on. Also the possible relation between [Aatrox and Jax](http://cdn.leagueoflegends.com/game-info/1.1.9/images/champion/backdrop/bg-jax.jpg). Also the fact that for some reason [Jax is listed under Ionia](http://gameinfo.na.leagueoflegends.com/en/game-info/champions/jax/) on the League website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 07:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of older champions lore is cool. It's kind of sad Riot stopped saying why champions joined the League of Legends. I feel like it makes the interactions between the champions and the world of League of Legends much stronger because they have a purpose for joining the League instead of it just being a thing they randomly did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 07:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually reading some champions lore a couple days ago. The potential relation between Zed and Nocturne is really interesting. The fact that Nocturne, Shaco, and Fiddlesticks are listed as friends, the fact that they all come from who the fuck knows where, and the fact that they just kill things without reason is terrifying. I can't wait to see if Riot expands on Zed and Nocturne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 07:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes.](http://www.reddit.com/r/leagueoflegends/comments/28ohsk/riot_using_curse_voice_is_not_permitted_even/cid2qnz?context=1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 07:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would Curse Voice know what players are in your game or when timers still existed how would they get timer info? They have to pull values from the League process to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 07:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The apps/websites that support replays basically log into the League servers as a spectator and spectate the game like anybody else would. They aren't getting any special client data. I have no idea why Riot wouldn't implement replays this way though (maybe because it would cause a huge load on the server because you would effectively double the number of people logged in) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 06:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timers and voice chat were never OK. Before Curse Voice existed Riot's policy on third party apps was not well defined and basically on a case by case basis. Once Curse Voice came around and it started to get really popular Riot decided to update their third party app legal jargon to ban any apps that do anything to the League client or game between pressing the play button and the end of match screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reign of Gaming - Unofficial PBE Patch Notes for 6/21/2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 03:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 00:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the new Baron from the [Twist of Fate](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tEnsqpThaFg) video was inspired by the [Baron](http://forums.na.leagueoflegends.com/board/showthread.php?p=47883994#post47883994) that was created for the new SR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 07:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you get a call from a shadowy figure that notifies you that the servers are down so you can jump into action?

Thanks for all the hard work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 23:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [They](http://community.pbe.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/bugs/6FAs0IyE-baron-bug-baron-dont-atk-back-from-over-the-wall?comment=0001) [know](http://community.pbe.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/bugs/2ZBh0lsf-bug-heimerdinger-can-solo-baron-at-15?comment=0000) [about](http://community.pbe.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/bugs/rL8MsbVE-bug-baron-doesnt-attack-caitlyn?comment=0001) [this](http://community.pbe.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/bugs/qmquFAQg-new-map-easy-kill-baron-nashor?comment=0001). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 07:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT DOESNT COUNT AS A HEAL. ITS SOMEWHERE ON THE PBE FORUMS BUT I CANT FIND THE THREAD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 09:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the lesson here is don't give out your account info. Ever. Even if an exact duplicate of you pops up and demands for your info don't give it to yourself.

For what reason would your gf need your account data anyway? Why would she ever need to log onto your account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 05:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to see if this was possible. Since patches are out around ever 2 weeks, if they continued releasing on a two week cycle we would hit 4.20 on November 5th. This is only of course they continue releasing on a two week cycle which will probably never happen. If they release on a 3 week cycle they would hit 4.19 on Christmas Eve which clearly will not have a patch...so we actually might hit patch 4.20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 23:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Violence is easy to explain to children. Don't do that. End of story. Sex is a little harder. You shouldn't have sex now but there comes a time when it's OK. When does that time come? How do they know it's OK?

Puberty is a whole mess of feelings and having sexual feelings towards other people is strange when before those feelings didn't even exit. It's a harder subject because it involves another persons agreement as well. Getting somebody to like you before you have sex is required.

Violence is simple. Don't punch your brother, don't kill your goldfish. But yes, the craziness about breasts is weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 21:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These aren't in the game files. These are from Data Dragon (riot's data thing that they use for all the in game data) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 21:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Morgana shield doesn't count for Ardent Censer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 21:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also with the fact that PBE patches have slowed down. The splash art for the new Draven skin hit on Friday and usually splash arts come last on PBE. It's also been close to 2 weeks since the last patch (patches are usually 2-3 weeks apart). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 21:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Seems like it wasn't coincidental lol.](http://i.imgur.com/EprUgWM.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 08:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T'was a normal game a while ago. Notice the AP Yi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 08:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Originally found this on Gawker but didn't want to have to link to that so found the source. Enjoy!

Note: I did not make these. These were created by [NJI Media](http://njimedia.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 06:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can blind yourself if your Q hits the target you E onto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 05:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually got my [first pentakill](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xxDKC0V9hMc) with Quinn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 01:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lumia 920. Sometimes hitting the search button crashes the phone. Also Internet Explorer likes crashing a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 22:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more global passives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 07:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://community.pbe.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/champions-gameplay-feedback/621miiU8-planned-410-item-changes-attack-damage-attack-speed-wardens-mail-support-itemization?comment=001b0000) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 07:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Riot is aware and they are planning to fix it: http://community.pbe.leagueoflegends.com/en/c/champions-gameplay-feedback/621miiU8-planned-410-item-changes-attack-damage-attack-speed-wardens-mail-support-itemization?comment=001b0000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 22:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nidalee spear width reduced from 60 to 20 on PBE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 20:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mirror's Edge](http://www.mirrorsedge.com/img/ME_Wallpaper_16x9_1920x1080_01.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 08:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also did the stat calculations and gold efficiency stuff. The strangest thing I noticed was that with the Dagger change the only upgrade you get if you buy Recursive bow is the fact that it takes up one slot instead of two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 09:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't going to buff Vayne since her late game is really good and buffing her early game would let her get to late game faster which would make her crazy strong. Vayne was too strong season 3 where she would rush Bildgewater and destroy in lane. She is in a good spot now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 09:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked and played golf a lot when I was younger. That's the golf part. I was 10 when I made my name. My younger brother was 5 and my youngest brother was 2. subject4635. My name is also about 10 years old now since I'm 20 now :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 22:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Poe's Law](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Poe%27s_law) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 02:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like salmon colored shorts would work better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 02:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'll poke my head in... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 20:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I turn 20 this month so this message is pretty weird. How did I learn to read and stuff in my coma. Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 12:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as we Windows Phone people believe you know we always get left out :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 01:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think about ADC itemization? Is it in a good place now or is Riot right in trying to add more items? What types of items would you like to see? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 07:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same exact problem that you do. I've read about it also and it seems like the only way to fix this is to do a reinstall/refresh. Going to try a couple last things tomorrow but if not time for a refresh :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 23:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god. I've heard this before for some other company while I was on hold. I just put my phone on speaker and walked away while I did something else. It's almost unbearable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 07:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chaox. He's the reason I really got into League and started playing ADC. I watched almost all of the champion marathon vids he did like 2 years ago (played every champ that over the course of 8 days). It was around when Vi came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 03:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same as me except with mid Karma. Shield nuking people before her rework. Q nuking people after her rework.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 09:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [\#rekt](http://i.imgur.com/HfVuC3c.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 08:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Supergiant uses some Monogame but it's probably heavily modified compared to the public version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 23:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm way too happy right now. I'm also really scared that people are going to pick her up now and be terrible with her. Or Riot nerfs her. Rito plz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 07:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they nuked the AP part of his kit (it's gone as it wasn't healthy). I think the design they want to keep with Sion is that he is this huge undead juggernaut lifedraining tank (his AD kit) rather than a AP nuker type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 01:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually don't want a release date. I would enjoy more gameplay or another trailer but without a release date hopefully DICE focuses on getting the game right instead of getting the game out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
