<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4131</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not, frankly it's the other drivers fault. I never choose to be an iconoclast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you mean driving, then I confess I love driving slow. To be honest, I'm not sure why, it's just something I've always done and enjoy. When there is a line of cars stuck behind me, I get like this power trip, like I control the people behind me and they look at me as a god. I know it sounds silly, but that's how it feels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently took a flight to the annual Jar Jar Binks convention in West Horton, Ohio. I did not want to pack my Jar Jar costume as it is extremely expensive, but it wouldn't fit in a carry on, so I had to wear it. First, the search at the airport was a human rights violation. The airport security was very rude, and made me give up the two blasters I had on, then got mad at me because of my elaborate costume, saying it took so long to search it held up the line. Then when I finally got on the plane, the stewardess said I couldn't wear my Jar Jar mask, and the two people sitting next to me (I was in the middle), grumbled because my costume took up too much space and had stuff sticking out. After takeoff, I got in the aisle, put on my mask, and danced and yelled to entertain the other travelers. The stewardess tried to stop me but I ran screaming down the aisle, and then dove into a bunch of peoples laps. I was restrained for the rest of the flight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know but I had no choice, ur persona is assigned to you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U should follow it, people like me r making millions bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is bro, my skills speak for themselves. Don't be jealous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I missed my 1 chance to become a pro gamer today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If u did then u prob banged her recently, no way u could get 1995 Jeanne triplehorn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Kevin Costner bro, It was one of my first 100 films.

Proof: I banged Jeanne tripplehorn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking for fellow serious, professional soldiers to team up with! I'm in, my Xbox name is TRUMPisUrGod!BlazeIt420. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was the main guy I'm Kevin Costner. Happy to meet a fan on the internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually in waterworld, one of my first acting roles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ur email is probably an aol address anyway. You've got mail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What!?!? Sorry for trying to help people be more aware of their surroundings! I guess the SS is back in business! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weight lifting is nice but I'm out there on the streets, and you got to be tough to survive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah right u would probably just get beat up. U don't know how to fight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's easy to say that when you have have 20/20 hindsight but if it happened to you, you know you would have done the same things I did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to prevent others from suffering like I did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angry birds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA Be careful when gaming on a mobile device in public, my life was ruined </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said that my wife and I aren't swingers and surely the lord wants me to live large,'so large  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing music over the mic is simply a good idea. If you have your own band, this is a great way to get exposure. When u r just starting out, it's hard to get people to hear ur stuff, but the other players will listen. If they criticize your work, ask them to be constructive and then take it to heart. If they tell you to stop, just tell them to shut it because the other players r enjoying it. Even if you don't have ur own band, play music that you enjoy. It will energize the team and let them know more about u as a person. All this adds up to better teammates and maybe, fans and friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a Peruvian on my team, and he died 5 times in the first 10 minutes. Did I freak out? No, I talked to him. I trained with him. I wired him money to help with his bills and family. A friendship formed. Now he is great player. I was invited to his village for his birthday, which was a great time. I ended up being intimate with a beautiful Peruvian woman. Life is about connections friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are important things in ur life inconsequential? FYI I know Kristen Stewart IRL and she's as brilliant as she is beautiful, and she is a very generous lover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You couldn't be more wrong. Like i already said I'm happy to talk about anything, it doesn't have to be money, women, or cars. It can be parties, vacations, fine dining, meeting celebrities, whatever they want. I'm just trying to make a more stimulating environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you are missing the chance to make a connection with other people if you do that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think conversation is seeking approval? You might want to consider less gaming and more education, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just trying to make conversation with them. I'm happy to talk about anything, it doesn't have to be money, women, or cars. It can be parties, vacations, fine dining, meeting celebrities, whatever they want. I'm just trying to make a more stimulating environment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I think ur right but I didn't want to say it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like many people would enjoy a more social environment, I don't understand why they always ruin it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't gamers be happy for other people success? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and your precious nyt writers aren't half as brave as Steve Rannazzis is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare you sir, me and Steve Rannazzis were there, running for our lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't make excuses for racism young lady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was with comedian Steve Rannazzis, we barely were able to escape when the towers came down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son decided to change his name which really bothered me. His given name was Karl. He said it was to help his career, he is an aspiring rapper. He changed it legally to Cash Money God, which I agree isn't a great name. I don't really understand it, we are well off but still. I am also an aspiring rapper and I changed my legal name a year prior to Superking, but that's a little more awesome and badass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I thought it was weird too, my wife never did a seance before and I had no idea she even knew how. Luckily she knew what she was doing and was able to avoid being injured during the ritual. I didn't check on her or go downstairs because she told me not to, as I could be injured by spectral energy if I interrupted the seance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate you trying to help friend even though you were wrong, there is no need to be rude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, spreading those rumors about my priest burned a lot of bridges for me. A different problem I had with my neighbor and the police didn't help my reputation around town either, so my options are somewhat limited. I think a Wiccan is my best bet, my town is kind of small too so I would have to go into the city probably to find one. I think there is a Wiccan bookstore by the train station. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I don't know if they would refuse but they would not be happy. When I first moved here I was was intrigued by a beautiful policewoman. Although I wouldn't be unfaithful to my wife, I wanted to get to know her better so I kept calling in crimes so she would come by, often I would insert my neighbor into the crimes as well. Like I would call and say my neighbor was dumping an old refrigerator in the woods or that was brandishing a firearm. Anyway the police got totally grumpy and made me pay all these fines and said any more and I would get in even bigger trouble. I would prefer to keep them out of it until I have more concrete evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The unfortunate thing is that the police won't help me either, because of a problem we had when I first moved in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The commandments were meant for regular followers, not for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said I was thee god, only that I was another god. You need to improve ur reading comprehension  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
