<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7426</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm working on a large collection of textures. I've posted about it here and have been updating it when I'm feeling inspired. I've also been adding textures created by other users with their permission and have uploaded the core textures as well with the mod's permission.

https://www.reddit.com/r/inkarnate/comments/5sth34/inkarnate_textures_gallery/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and me both! I am hoping that either Inkarnate expands the default assets or we are able to upload our own icon assets in the future like we can with textures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the biggest thing I've come to learn is to not worry so much about the big picture when whittling away at the coast. You likely won't lose the general shape of your map during this process and you are now creating little micro moments in your map with each section of the coast you work on. Just remember that you don't jump from a size 64 brush to a size 5 brush. Work your way down in increments to create the shapes you want and use the smallest brush sizes to define and shape the coasts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a link to a post where I've compiled these textures, the default textures, and some of my own creation. I plan on updating it with new textures as I find them in the sub and as I create them: Inkarnate Textures Gallery

https://www.reddit.com/r/inkarnate/comments/5sth34/inkarnate_textures_gallery/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am adding additional textures in my spare time - check back for them as I roll them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the blessings of /u/Spadie and /u/igagen, I have started compiling both core and user-made background textures for Inkarnate into one location. My hope is that, as more users create backgrounds, they would allow me to add it to the gallery where anyone can browse and select textures for their map. If you have textures you want added to the gallery, pm me or comment on this thread with a link to the textures.

Edit: I'm updating the image descriptions in the gallery with my thoughts and experiences working with each texture. Feel free to offer up your feedback and creative ways you've used each texture - I will add these to the gallery so that other users can benefit from our collective experience! (you may have to click through to see the updated descriptions)

Edit edit: Thanks for Reddit gold! Expect a large update in the near future in a new post. I'm hoping to have upwards of fifty textures in the gallery by then. Stay tuned! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your quick reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super! I'll wait for the blessing from u/igagen before posting just in case there are any objections there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just going to repost it on this sub as a way to aggregate all the texture resources into one post. I might be the only one that does this, but I like picking a color palette to use before making a map. Since we are limited in the number of color options we can upload to use, I thought it might be nice to get a "master list" of nice textures including the default as well as user-made ones that match in style.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey u/Spadie - Do I have your permission to repost these textures (with credit and link to this post) with the default Inkarnate textures? I pulled them all out and gave them "Crayola" names so a texture doesn't get pigeon-holed into a specific use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you can boot it up and open up the editor, the program isn't compatible with android devices (at least not mobile, I haven't tried on a a tablet). For the best results you're going to want to use a laptop or desktop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Festival Fishing Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fishing level is currently 3. Will I be able to catch the A-D prize fish at this level or do I need to level up? If so, what level should I be at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally had this epiphany on my way home from the gym today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a regional map I did using the updated Inkarnate program. Overall, I am very happy about how it turned out, though there are some things I noticed once I got my hands dirty. Here's my list of suggestions/feedback generated from working on this map. I apologize for any redundancies that may have already been shared in the sub.

* Item scale is an issue. While most of us agree things are just too large and can't be scaled down, many of the isometric objects don't follow any logical scaling within the set. The watchtower and and windmill are massive in comparison with the cities and other towers. The cities themselves do not scale very well (setting everything at the same zoom level). The towns are all much larger in scale than the capital city icon and makes for some very strange tweaking. In this map, all the icons are at 50% while the capital is at 75%. If I could have made the towns and villages smaller, I would have but alas.

* Obligatory comment about textures.

* Coloration for the non-isometric sketch-style icons is very strange for me. Why the rusty-red color? Unless you are making a parchment style map with the lightest parchment color or are "filling in" the sketches with a different texture color, they are often lost in a even the plainest background color. If some trees or mountains are added to a map, say goodbye to any sort of visibility.

* Object layering drives me up the wall. It is very fiddly to try and prevent trees/mountains/hills/icons/etc. to layer correctly and not overlap in unrealistic ways. Having "move to front" and "move to back" for icons is nice - I would love it if we could do that for individual terrain pieces like hills, trees, and mountains. That being said...

* Terrain relocation would be a godsend. There were so many times making this map where I clicked a mountain or hill into being only to delete it because it wasn't the shape I wanted. That, or the terrain feature needed to be shifted just a little bit. Being able to rearrange terrain icons after placing them would make creating organic landscapes even easier, especially if this is coupled with object layering for terrain pieces.

* Object/terrain mirroring would be great, especially for the isometric icons. This would allow for a lot more diversity in placement and usage.

**Extra bits:**

* I wish there were icons for caves and barrows.

* The grasslands and forest lands terrain colors are very similar and can be hard to differentiate from one another. Actually, scratch that. All of the browns look similar too. While I wouldn't cut back on terrain colors, I hope future additions create more dynamic options.

* Oh how I wish the images and text were vector based and scaled better when shrunk or enlarged past their preferred resolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summerset Isles w/ Thoughts on Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more you know! Thanks - I don't have RES on my work laptop which is what I'm usually browsing from. Guilty as charged...

Welp, then this is for the lazy and/or unaware shmucks like me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just in case anyone is ocd like me and wanted the list ordered by height.

Location|Height in Meter
:--|:--
Seath (First Encounter)|388.45
Anor Londo (Beginning)|207.2
Asylum (Starting Cell)|184.74
Iron Golem|82.85
Undead Parish Bell|75.37
Taurus|15.81
Sunlight Altar (Bonfire)|9.5
Andre|5.37
Undead Burg (Bonfire)|-10.02
Havel|-38.25
Door to the Depths|-54.25
Firelink Shrine (Bonfire)|-60.55
Laurentius|-68.46
Depths (Bonfire)|-74.12
Kiln of the First Flame (Beginning)|-79.13
Gaping Dragon|-100.07
Kiln of the First Flame (Bonfire)|-117.59
Catacombs (First Bonfire)|-119.08
Lower Blighttown (Bonfire)|-215.11
Blighttown Bell|-236.45
Daugher of Chaos (Bonfire)|-252.61
Nito|-265.05
Chaos Flame Ember|-304.28
New Londo Abyss (Bonfire)|-311
Firesage|-341.04
Centipede|-383.2
Ash Lake (Bonfire)|-408.27
Everlasting Dragon (Bonfire)|-413.94
Bed of Chaos Bug|-443.94 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my biggest concern is that we need more feedback from the devs moving forward. Their interaction with the community has been great following the update this weekend, but everything up to this has been large periods of silence interspersed with infrequent updates. I know that making too many hard and fast promises (regarding new assets, timeline commitments, etc) is too much to ask for because a lot can change during beta to screw up timelines. But if the devs can maintain transparency and even provide a loose road map that we can follow along with, that would be appreciated a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The program is called Google Drawings. If you have a Google Drive account, it should be one of the default programs that appears when you create a new file. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I mostly used the simple dot-based map marked but would love to see all the simple black map markers back and then built out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The struggle is real. My hope is that one day we will have such robust features that we can recreate our old maps with added levels of improvement not possible in the old version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha yeah I'm breathing deep sighs of relief that I finished this after seeing the update this morning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I collated the maps using Google Draw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 06:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was supposed to launch today but it hadn't this afternoon when I was working in it. Hopefully we will hear something from them one way or another soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh you're telling me. Naming everything took almost as long as making the map itself! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
