<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1245</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's definitely a theme of dealing with mental health issues in your film. Is this something you've dealt with personally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gordon Ramsay Challenges Amateur Cook to Keep Up with Him [9:08] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Worst Super Bowl: 1999 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The time of the orc has come!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ren   Stimpy: Never The Same Face Twice [7:31] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security Council Agrees to Send UN Monitors to Aleppo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 21:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crimetown is absolutely incredible. Each season is about crime in a different American city. This season (the first and current one) is about organized crime and corruption in Providence, RI. Basically it's about the New England Italian mob and the insanely corrupt mayor of Providence.

Bonus: it's by the producers of The Jinx (about Robert Durst). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 23:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this near Newark, NJ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 16 units in the building with no individual control of the gas and no electric heaters. I suggested to the Con Ed rep I was talking to that maybe we were getting charged for electricity outside our unit and she told me that if that was the case our bill would be much higher, like $700. 
Is there a way to verify that you are only getting charged for your unit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My con ed bill seems extremely high. Any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got a bill from Con Ed for $153 for one month in my one-bedroom apartment in Brooklyn. This does not include heat, which is a super-old gas system. While this bill is an estimate, our first bill was $95 (also extremely high) for just 20 days, so this is shaping up to be just a little more than what it would have been. We just moved into this apartment on October 1 and the tenants before told us that they were paying ~$80 a month consistently. We have a 36 inch TV, modem/router, PS4, microwave, humidifier and other basic appliances, all of which aren't huge energy users.

I called Con Ed and they basically told me 'tough shit'  and that I shouldn't compare my bill to the past tenants since we have different appliances.

I really feel like this is higher than it should be and don't know how best to proceed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
