<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1450</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had of taken more time Im sure I could have easily thought of something more elaborate. 
The sword to my affection, meaning my affections for her, someone I have never met, getting damaged many times because of this state that I am in, coming to view her, having her as an expectation or a mirage in the Desert.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can hear forced? Its understandable not to like a particular line that was thought and written within 1 full minute. I think the comma you used between hell and too sounds forced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sword to my affections, the cause for my reflections, the catalyst that triggered my desire for heaven.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://instagram.com/lauvdahl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://instagram.com/lauvdahl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sparse nights, spent engulfed in satin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And so.....it was done. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be right, out of 2k likes what I find funny is only  one person finds the need to tell me how I should title my post simply because they feel it will somehow help people discover a game. 
Furthermore, limiting their need to be social and just ask a question to invoke a conversation among people to discover the game instead.  
I guess what im saying is I see your point, yet after much digestion before replying, I see it as something I can easily pass by and continue to do it my way without having to feel as though im a standoffish jackass who only wants it my way. 
In my own perception, my way is equally if not more beneficial. Unintentionally.....but still easily rationalized into something good and completely normal.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I'm not that OP.....also there are multitudes of posts on here with like 20k and absolutely no mention of the title whatsoever. Mine has like 2k and only one person seems to have a particular hard on for title specifications. Im not saying I disagree with the context of what you are saying though. 
Im just used to being somewhat social and staying on top of my posts enough that truly I didn't even consider naming it. Plus I would not know which game to even put as the title, this fan art doesn't really imply which one, at least to my knowledge of those games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making love could be nothing more than staring into her eyes. The things I would give up to spend a day with her, be a pleasure to hear her thoughts voiced into reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seems intoxicated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Nye is confused greatly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Nye....yeah id be rude too prolly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much effort would it take for you to just ask? How much effort and time would that take apart from all the suggestions you leave? After all this time you could have gotten the answer like 30 times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like you are being over zealous about it not being in the title, and not simply just asking....instead you try to impose your title specifications on others. To be honest I posted it for people who know the game, im not trying to spread awareness about some old ass game, you're being difficult because you like things your way, and im just telling you im never going to do it even after you tell me. To be honest with you I never even bought or played the game myself more than a few hours...never played anything outside of Elder Scrolls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://instagram.com/alechugill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats why its social media, socially I don't agree with having to adhere to others title specifications, most things on reddit reveal all the details in the comments, thats why the comments of reddit are better than the majority of the content.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thanks to people like you, you can tell them for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't pay me, screw them, if they wanna pay me to find fan art and repost....then I might mention them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares, lets watch this motherfucker burn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
