<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4888</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Guys I am seriously freaking the fuck out as I am typing this.

 Me and my boyfriend (we can call him J) were sitting in bed, he was playing a game, and I was eating a bowl of cereal. That was when he got a call from his mom, saying that his job had called her. He said that was odd because they didnt call him, mind you this is like at 10:15, and J never works at night. They chit chatted for a bit then ended the call, when J recieved a notification that he had one missed call. It was his job. He hadnt heard his phone ring, or anything.
 
So J calls his job, and the first thing he hears is a shrieking, scream. It was so loud I could hear it from across the bed. Chills went up my body and down my spine. We looked at each other in daft confusion, and he waited another moment for the dial tone. He hung up, and then his phone said that the call had failed.
 
 Luckily enough, J has a friend who works the night shift, and J shot him a text asking what the fuck was up? He explained the situation to his friend, and said friend went to find the supervisor. The supervisor said that no calls had been made, nor received. Guys that isnt even the weird part, his job doesnt have his moms cell phone number. At this point we are totally freaked out, I mean what could be the explanation for this?
 
This isnt the first time that weird shit has happened to us though. The other month we were in the same sort of situation. I was sitting on the bed, with my back up against the wall when I felt a solid thud. I mean I felt that shit physically. J heard it clear as day as well and we both lurched up and away from the window. Then we heard a tugging on the back door. We called his dad and one of my friends, and they came over and checked the place out. There was absolutely nothing, and I dont know if at this point we are just going crazy, if I am being paranoid, or if I am overreacting? Im so scared right now I dont even want to go into the bathroom alone, he has one of those foggy windows in there right beside the toilet. I am terrified of looking up and just seeing a face pressed up against it.

 Oh also there is one more thing, there's a GOAT HEADED BLACK MOLD SHAPE IN THE ROOF OF HIS CLOSET. I can shoot a picture out if you guys want, once i figure out how to do that since ive never posted to reddit before. Could that be it? Do we just have black mold poisoning, are we hallucination? As I am typing this, I feel like I hear footsteps in the kitchen and little knocks. I dont even want to mention it to J, because I dont want to freak him out more than he already is.
 
If anything else weird happens I will keep you guys posted. I just dont know what the fuck is happening.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
