<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject983</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 21:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second way has 3x as many words as the first one though. If I had all the time in the world, sure I'd write them a novel. But in the middle of a match, you have to be concise to get your point across, and there isn't always time for the fluffy language. Don't presume conciseness = rudeness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain how competitive teams are formed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 05:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just faced a team of a four man premade all level 30 bronze star and two solo level 20 bronze stars vs my team of all level 50-60 solo players no bronze stars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 04:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, did not know that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 04:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a spare one that would be awesome. Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blizzard, can you please offer a $20 upgrade from the regular to the origin addition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 04:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first bought the game, I wasn't sure I was going to like it, mainly because I was not a huge fan of TF2 in the past. However, I had a few friends recommend the game to me on PC, at since it was only $40 I decided to give it a shot. I have since fallen in love with the game, and would really like to get the origin edition skins, but as it stands I would have to buy the whole game plus the origin edition for $60 to get those skins and other benefits. Is there any possibility of offering an origin edition upgrade for $20 so that those of us who would like to upgrade can? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 01:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Human Body </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I add a small amount of salt to water before I drink it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 00:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 19:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dissection is exactly along the lines of what I was looking for, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 19:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know of some good bands that have black metal style guitar/bass/drums but vocals more in the death/melo death style?

I was looking at shreddits top 15 albums from 2001-2015, and I really liked the way the instruments sounded on the "Ominous Doctrines Of the Perpetual Mystical Macrocosm" album, but the second the vocals came in I had to stop listening, they sounded like total ass.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else on NA having connection issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 02:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even log on to the game. My platform is PC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rail commuters of Reddit, how do you pass time on the train? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 03:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was that not icing at the end? Power play ended with 10 seconds left and the icing was at about 6 seconds left  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck was that not icing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 03:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it actually a penalty if a player steps on another stick and trips or was it a bad call? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 05:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was shopping at JC penny's earlier today and found [these pants](http://www.jcpenney.com/dockers-modern-fit-slim-tapered-pants/prod.jump?ppId=pp5006930368 searchTerm=men+dockers+slim+fit catId=SearchResults _dyncharset=UTF-8#link_swatch) (specifically the Khaki ones).  

They fit really well, but as a recent college starting a new job it's hard to justify spending $58 on them, since there were no sales going on in the store.  So I've been looking all over amazon, the dockers website and the internet in general trying to figure exactly what type of pants these were, but I can't seem to find them anywhere else.  These pants weren't like typical chinos, they were made out of a very lightweight material (I think they had flyweight branding on them) which made them go great with button downs as well as v-necks, which is awesome because my office where I'll be working is extremely casual.  Does anyone have any experience with these pants and know where else they could be located?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 19:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who is considering moving on to MTG from hearthstone (just graduated college and got a job with a nice salary so I'll actually be able to afford cards) what are the recommended sites to buy from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 03:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I need to do any type of backup incase the driver doesn't reinstall properly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SP3: Extremely slow wifi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 256gb 8gb ram SP3, and my wifi has been so slow recently that my surface is basically unusuable. I'm talking 45-60 seconds to load a single web page like Facebook or Reddit, and if I try to watch twitch or Netflix the stream just doesn't load. I know the issue is with my surface pro 3, as my roommates are all able to use their laptops and have absolutely no issues while I experience the ones listed above, while we are both connected to our aprt's wifi. The issue exists even when I'm the only one connected which leads me to believe that the issue is solely with my SP3.  

I have the extended warranty for my surface, should I consider sending it back? Or is there an easy fix out there? I don't have a USB/Ethernet adapter so I have no way to try a hardware connection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 03:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you make the glaze for the pork? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 21:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have a good freeze list for standard? I tried running the torch list replacing scientists with kin'tor mages (one that makes your next secret free) but I kept getting killed before having the chance to set up the combo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another benefit for keeper is removing c'thun.  Say they drop a 14/14 c'thun and you humility it.  They can still play cards to buff c'thun (buffs are WHEREEVER he is) so its not uncommon that they will be able to get c'thun up to 4-8 attack over the following turns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 04:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a couple late game plays where I've had a coin from a pillager and could throw down a sylv shadow caster turn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm somewhat happy with rogue so far, but the lack of viable healing is really killing me.  Using your weapon is a necessity to keep the board clear in the early/midgame, however, I'm finding that my health dips way too low and its game over from there.  I've lost my last three games having 3-4 minions on the board myself while the opponent had zero and getting killed by spells.  Earthen ring, refreshment, and the new shitty board dependent healbot just don't seem strong enough to warrant being included.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 05:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think it's worth running any deathrattle taunts in standard? They all seem subpar to me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 02:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 01:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iPhone 6S iOS 9.1. Lost 3 packs due to this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 01:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you running a highlander list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are people doing with n'zoth rogue? Overall I'm having decent success with mine, but the biggest problem I'm running into is survivability. With no good class taunts or heals, having to use my weapon to clear results in my life total dropping too low, and without any good class or neutral heals its impossible to recover. If I'm able to gain the board first, I usually come out with a win. However, if I lose the board/initative, I usually have no way of coming back

http://www.hearthpwn.com/deckbuilder/rogue#33:1;87:2;280:2;286:2;378:1;382:2;385:1;395:1;471:2;525:1;14434:1;27220:2;27229:2;33134:1;33135:1;33139:1;33180:1;35194:2;35195:2;35241:2;
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 00:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are people doing with n'zoth rogue? Overall I'm having decent success with mine, but the biggest problem I'm running into is survivability.  With no good class taunts or heals, having to use my weapon to clear results in my life total dropping too low, and without any good class or neutral heals its impossible to recover.  If I'm able to gain the board first, I usually come out with a win.  However, if I lose the board/initative, I usually have no way of coming back

http://www.hearthpwn.com/deckbuilder/rogue#33:1;87:2;280:2;286:2;378:1;382:2;385:1;395:1;471:2;525:1;14434:1;27220:2;27229:2;33134:1;33135:1;33139:1;33180:1;35194:2;35195:2;35241:2; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sylv or carnie could be great additions as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 20:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got corrupt Nat, Hazal, and n'zoth from about 35 packs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I got booted.  I was in for maybe 10 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep getting the playful sprite error.  I was in and opening packs and I randomly got dropped, now I can't get back in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3100ish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rogues have no class taunt, no class heal, and no efficient board clear (vanish lol). I doubt they'll make it above tier 3 unless it's some boring c'thun deck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you elaborate? I think the lack of reliable board clear is a huge blow  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just that maly/oil are rotating out, it's that they were the only decks that played like it and they're now dead. For example, the card nerfs so far hurt midrange Druid a lot. But if I want to play a midrange deck, most other classes have a somewhat competitive midrange deck. There are no other classes that have a play style like maly rogue or oil rogue did  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is maly rogue has no reliable way to control the board. Vanish is trash, FoK + thalnos is only 2 damage, and dark iron has no spell power synergy like blade flurry did. The core of maly is still there, but without reliable board clears I can't see it being a competitive deck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will deathrattle rogue be playable? Maybe. But it's just another generic midrange deck. Maly/oil were unique play styles that are now completely dead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way oil will exist in wild with the blade flurry change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could that be a thing? Possibly. However, it's still just slamming down c'thun minions on curve then playing a finisher. It plays nothing like oil/maly which are being killed off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 22:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about what's strong or not, it's about the death of the archetype. Is aggro shaman good? Yep. But there is also aggro hunter, aggro pally, face warrior etc. If they decided to nerf aggro shaman, I could still find another deck that fits the aggro play style. There are no other classes out there that played like miracle maly rogue or oil rogue, so now that they are dead it's not possible to get a similar playing experience  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 22:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if the tempo warrior that was in the last snapshot stays, it might see play in that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 22:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, maybe deathrattle rogue will be a thing, but I really liked playing oil/maly rogue. With the current nerf/releases those archetypes are most likely dead. I'm really not interested in playing another generic midrange deck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 22:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it worth killing two whole archetypes of the class (maly/oil) and severely weakening the class for 6 months until new cards are printed? Sure deathrattle rogue will exist but if I want to play a boring midrange deck I can play pally or Druid   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 22:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but now rogues are in a shitty place until the next adventure comes out. Its disappointing because I know any rogue cards I open aren't going to get used at all   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 22:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They killed a whole archetype though. Sure, deathrattle rogue may become a thing, but it'll be no different from any other midrange deck that slams down the most powerful minion on curve. Maly/oil rogues had a completely different play style that just got straight up eliminated. If I wanted to play powerful minions on curve I'd just play secret pally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're ok with rogue being useless for 6-12 months until new cards come out? Cards this expansion pretty much blow for rogue besides the legendary, and they only have vanish as their boardclear with this change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you'd be ok with rogue being basically unplayable until blizzard releases some actually good rogue cards in the future? Until the next adventure, rogue will basically be useless  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 18:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not a fair comparison, as with shadowflame you can power overwhelming a 1/1 or 2/2, then do a 5-6dmg boardclear for 5.  Rogue has no way to get enough attack on their weapon to make this viable, as they need deadly poison to clear minions as well in the early game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 06:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean there is vanish (unplayable), dark iron saulker (situational) and FoK + thalnos, but none of those are consistent enough compared to other classes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 06:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 card 4 mana combo to deal 3 damage to all enemy minions? Seems a bit underwhelming compared to flamestrike or consecrate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 05:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How will rogue survive in standard? Loss of blade flurry really hurts maly rogue, oil rogue is gone due to loss of oil, and raptor gets hit with leper nerf and loses creeper, egg and shredder.  The only thing I can think of is maybe tempo rogue becoming a thing but overall it seems like it would be pretty weak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 01:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it 10am pacific time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 19:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blade flurry nerf is huge and makes the card almost unplayable. Considering you need to drop 2 mana for a dagger, at least one for deadly poison and then 4 for flurry, you're paying 7 mana for a 3 dmg boardclear, as well as two cards. Compared to flamestrike this is trash. There is a chance you could combo with the second deadly poison for 8 mana 6 dmg, but then you can't use deadly in the early game to maintain board control. RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 22:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you take out the flame imp for void caller over taking out argent squire? The one thing I think the deck I'm running from benefits from is that most zoo decks are running boom/Giants, so people will play around trying to setup a play for when boom/a giant drops and it never does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I should have been more clear.  I meant with zoo losing cards like imp gang, implosion, egg and creeper, I wasn't sure if it would be worth crafting those cards just for zoo when we don't know what the state of zoo will be like after the expansion drops,  with blizz now confirming the expansion will release on the 26th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the zoo list I've been running with mixed results, do you think its worth cutting stuff for dark iron dwarf or voidcaller?

http://www.hearthpwn.com/deckbuilder/warlock#85:2;170:2;305:2;340:2;422:2;473:1;500:1;507:2;542:2;577:2;7738:2;7746:1;7756:2;12302:2;14443:2;27214:1;27243:2; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a good zoolock deck that I can run without enhanco, sea giant, gormak or leeroy? I don't want to craft any of them with standard coming soon where zoolock might fall off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 05:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I add the onion and the liquid that it releases partially deglazes the pan, should I still add the wine or is it not necessary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 05:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that helps a lot. Most of the guides I've seen kinda hand wave at the last step </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 02:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The oil or shallots burning could be a possibility. And yes this is cooking in a stainless steel pan after cooking meat. Also my ratio off wine to stock was off, I only had 3/4 cup for a 1/2 cup of wine. How much should the liquid be reduced by one the stock is added? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to make a pan sauce on an electric stove? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 01:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a pretty new chef and I've gotten a decent handle on cooking meat and vegetables. However, when it comes to pan sauces it's a complete disaster. Most things I cook, even if they turn out not great, are at least edible. The sauces, I've attempted on the other hand, I've thrown out immediately. The formula I'm using for pan sauces is saut one shallot in canola until brown, salt a bit while sauting, deglaze with a half cup of wine, reduce by half, add stock and reduce, finish with a pad of butter. The main problem I'm having with my sauce is that it tastes extremely bitter, as if the alcohol hasn't cooked up, and I've noticed since I'm cooling on an electric stove, I've never seen the flames shoot up when the alcohol is added like what happens on gas stoves in the videos I've watched on the topic. Is there something different I need to do on an electric stove to cook out the alcohol, or am I royally messing up something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 19:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking of taking boom out of midrange Druid and replacing him with an ancient of war. Plus side is no BHG targets and a solid taunt, downside is if boom/bots left unanswered it leads to an extremely strong combo. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 21:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a good deck to climb with based on the current meta? I really like playing control priest/control warrior/Murloc pally, but the games take forever so it's not super efficient.  I'm looking for a deck that I can use to climb to around rank 5-10 with before switching over to my control decks.  I was thinking of doing zoo but I don't have any sea Giants  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any good videos or video series for beginners? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 02:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking through the FAQ it seems that cook books are covered in pretty good detail, however, I was wondering if there are any videos that you all recommend that can be of help to beginners.  I'm not looking for recipes, I'm more interested in generalized versions, IE where it is explained how to pair spices and herbs and such, or introductions to different kinds of sauces, or more technique oriented videos such as one's dealing with knife skills or similar topics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surface pro 3 extremely slow wifi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 04:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a surface pro 3, and seemingly out of the blue the wifi has become extremely slow. I'm talking about an average download speed of 200-300 BYTES PER SECOND, not kilobytes or megabytes, bytes. I have not downloaded any new drivers or updates recently, the wifi also works perfectly fine for all my roommates. What steps should I take to solve this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Want to teach my girlfriend guitar but no idea where to start </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 04:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently 22, I've been playing guitar since I was 12, and I've also taken drum lessons for two years and I'm a self taught bassist as well. My girlfriend really wants to learn guitar so I want to give her lessons, the problem is I have no idea what an absolute beginner should be learning. Should I be teaching her chords (basic or barre), major/minor scales or arpeggios, the intervals between frets so she can build scales herself, fundamental technical exercises like chromatic scales, etc. It's been so long since I've taken guitar lessons (I took lessons for five years then self taught from there) that I don't remember what should be taught first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 22:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around 60 for me, no arena list help either. I drafted a stellar pally deck that took me to 12-1. I played for a couple years before venturing into arena so I already had a good idea of game concepts before going into arena  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 16:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some sort of scry mechanic, ie scry(1) would be look at the top card of your deck, and either keep it on top or place it on the bottom of your deck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 18:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have a good suggestion as a replacement for flowers on Valentine's Day? My girlfriend and I are in college (dating for one year) and budgets are a bit tight, and it seems like most places want $20 minimum for a bundle of roses. I have no qualms spending $20, but I'd rather put it towards something more permanent that wouldn't die after a week. What would some other cool somewhat-sappy Valentine's Day gifts for a 22 year old girl in college be? I'm thinking I'll most likely just get a single rose for budgetary reasons, but I'd like some other stuff to accompany it. I already got her a really cool main present so I'm looking for more sappy or trinket-y type ideas  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Linux Distro for software development in VirtualBox? (Surface Pro 3) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 02:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone,

I've been trying to do node js software development in Windows, but due to some current difficulties in a couple node modules I'm using I'd like to switch over to Linux.  I have a good amount of experience with Linux (Senior studying comp sci) but I've only used the setup provided in the labs at my school and know nothing about the different distros.  I've tried installing a couple different ones so far, here's my experience with them:

         Ubuntu: I like the OS but it was running very sluggish in the VM, even with a i5 256gb SP3.  I think it had to do with the unity desktop.  Also had a bunch of bloatware I wouldn't need.  

        Xbuntu:  The OS ran smooth as butter, but the xfce desktop environment didn't appear to have support for hi-resolution screens.  While changing the font sized help a bit, the taskbar at the top of the screen, and the taskbar at the top of windows like Google chrome were just too small and made navigation difficult

        Mint:  Installed pretty well, but it's still running slow, lots of bloatware as well.  No graphical lag like on unity though, just slow overall.  Also having issues with VMware where it has a notification that it cannot find the GPU and that it is doing all the rendering through the CPU.  

Overall I'm not sure what distro to run with, as the lightweight distros don't seem to support hi resolution displays well, but the ones that do have a lot of extra crap like libreoffice that I don't need.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 03:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goaltender interference  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But so are all the other decks I listed....I've definitely faced more mill rogues climbing the ladder then all of the other decks I listed combined. Due to the long game lengths it's definitely not optimal for climbing, but I've had great success with it against decks like freeze Mage, Handlock, control priest and warrior, and other decks that have high hand counts for a majority of the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 19:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is mill rogue never included in the meta snapshots? It seems to be an overall decent deck and a bit more consistent then some of the t3 and t4 decks in the snapshots. I would rather play mill rogue than raptor rogue, hobgoblin zoo, burst priest or midrange shaman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are everyone's favorite resources for getting better at the game? I'm mainly interested in things like website guides, lethal puzzle sites, streamers or VODs, forums etc.  The reason for this is the wifi at my college can be a bit spotty sometimes so playing on my laptop is not always a possibility, and I'd like some sites I could visit in between classes.  The main places I browse right now are comphs, the main hs sub, and watching Trump's stream.  If it matters at all, the decks I'm currently playing are namely zoo lock and control priest. My highest rank last season was rank 8, so I'm at an intermediate level.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Course Explorer Down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 05:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the course explorer down for anyone else? I tried accessing it and got a page displaying a null pointer exception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 05:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Senior in Math/CS here.  I would definitely take 347 before 444 or 447, as there are a decent number of proofs in those classes, depending on the professor.  I took 412 (Graph Theory) as well and there were a lot of proofs in that class.  347 also covers some elementary real analysis so I would definitely recommend it before 447. 

I personally didn't think 347 was that bad, it can be quite difficult if you are not familiar with the basic concepts of mathematical proofs though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 05:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know how I could get the photo of the tie fighter pilot resized to be my iphone 6S background? I tried saving the image but if I try to set it as my backdrop it makes me zoom in so far that only the guys head can be seen on the wallpaper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 20:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went from GNM to Silver 4 :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 08:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could look into getting an amphead with a built in crossover and getting an 18 inch cab, then use the crossover to send everything below 80-160hz to the 18 inch speaker and the remaining frequencies to your current 410 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 07:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 05:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I find info such as that on detection ranges?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 20:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How am I supposed to survive as a destroyer? I've had decent success when sneaking up on BB's, but it seems like if I get hit with a single shell my engines are always incapacitated, and if I use my repair kit my engines instantly get incapacitated again and then I'm just a sitting duck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 05:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on my experiences with their 400 level courses (Probability Theory, Diff EQ, and Graph Theory) they seem pretty on point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also would you recommend US or Japanese as first nation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like that was the case </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing co-op :/ 

Didn't even realize it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the best way to rank up without spending money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 23:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I've been alternating playtime between WOWS and Steel Ocean, and overall I like the mechanics and slower gameplay of WOWS better.  However, the one area I'm having trouble with is the leveling system.  In Steel Ocean, I usually get around 600 ship exp for a loss and around 1k for a win.  In WOWS though, I maybe get 400 for a win and 200-250ish for a loss, which means it takes 3-5x as many matches to unlock a new ship, and I'm finding that grind to be very dull, as many ships don't get interesting until above tier 5.  While I understand it make take awhile to unlock high tier ships, are there any tricks to expedite the leveling process from tiers 1-5?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 04:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have suggestions on a good midrange druid for climbing? I'm currently running the tempostorm version, but with it having double combo, only one aspirant and one shade, that I'm often getting stuck with dead hands, and it seems like deck is more optimized for rank 5 to legend.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 00:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you take out to make room for the deathlords? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 02:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would the best deck be for climbing right now? I was playing dragon priest but I started hitting a lot of midrange pallys/reno locks around 11 and I've fallen back to 14.  Any other suggestions on a deck I could run to climb to around 5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 04:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright sounds good, thanks for the reference  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 00:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What decklist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 00:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would a good substitute for Vol'jin be? Only card I don't have on the list </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 23:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have some good guides or videos to watch that explain Reno lock? I get the general idea of the deck, but I'm getting shit on by aggro decks currently. If anyone knows of some good streams or videos that pros have done those would be helpful too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to get full screen videos in Echo360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 03:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's somewhat annoying to not be able to watch videos in full screen, and I can't seem to find a way to make this happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried both solutions, neither worked. In firefox if I use the dev console it still shows no stylesheet on the page if it is "2+ tier".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Node JS, Express] CSS styles not appearing in certain routes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 03:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the process of making a website using node, express and ejs.  I have put things such as my header into ejs partials for easy inclusion in all of my main ejs files.  If I try to access a "1-tier" route with app.get and res.render, such as "/about", "/pdfs", or "/", everything works perfectly.  However, if I try using a "2+ tier" route, ie "user/:username" or "forums/:subforum", the html loads on the page but no CSS styling is included.  I am using a common header partial on all my files that includes my css stylesheets, so I'm unsure as to why this is occurring.  I've tried Googling for solutions but I haven't been able to find anything. 

Gist with code: https://gist.github.com/Challanger2/62fd0c649bde9885ef84

EDIT: I looked at the website in firefox's inspector, and it shows the stylesheets in the noscript in the html part of the page, but if I go to stylesheet it says that there is no stylesheet on the page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you actually need a registry cleaner on your PC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 04:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a CS student so I know most PC cleanup things are compete scams. However, I've been installing and uninstalling a bunch of software on my laptop and I'm not sure if after running an uninstaller there would still be registry entries left over that might need to be removed   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the big O run time of Knuths Dancing Links Algorithm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 05:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been reading the original 26 page paper on it as well as browsing the web but I can't locate the big O runtime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
