<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1861</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Bibimbap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi OP! I'm living away from my family (at Uni) so learning how to cook simple meals is a must. 


Quick Breakfast Ideas:
- Banana milkshake (banana + milk + sweetener like honey if you need it)

- Yoghurt with a bunch of fruits and nuts (e.g. avocado, pine nuts, chia, cherries, banana) and honey if you need a sweetener

- If you wanna bulk up during the weekends try making sausages, beans, eggs, toast, mushrooms and bacon by frying them separately. You can also make pancakes or French Toast which are very carb-loaded.


Lunch/Dinner ideas
- Fried rice (use spam/bacon and eggs, and day-old rice) 

- Cream based pasta with mushroom and chicken (this is a house favourite - fry up bacon and mushrooms, then use the drippings to make a sauce by adding double cream) 

- Potato salad: boil potatoes and eggs, cut and mix with mayo, bits of ham, olive oil, cherry tomatoes, etc. 

- Curry: buy instant curry packs (you can find them at regular/asian supermarkets but I like Japanese curry the best) - cut up some veggies and add the roux and water. Let boil and then reduce to a simmer for 20 min. Goes great with rice, pasta etc. You can store leftovers as well. 

- Olive oil based pasta (I add lemon juice, pepper, garlic and shrimp that is precooked) 

- Carbonara 

I don't have a cast iron skillet so I just put my steaks into bake mode for 15 mins at 200 degrees, creates a great medium-rare steak. You can pair it with blue cheese onion sauce, etc. or eat it as is. You can also put salmon in the oven along with some carbs (oven fries?) as well as pork tenderloin and chops. The oven is your best friend (if you're too lazy to pan fry stuff). 


If you want to use the frying pan, I'd suggest making some pan fried beef, fish, pork. If you want more oriental stuff oyako-don is really easy to make, as well as Chinese sesame chicken. 


I don't really have snacks but I do like a cup of hot chocolate. I do bake so I eat those from time to time (brownies, cookies can be done in an hour/ 1.5 hours easily). If you really want to carb-load you can try making bread as well but it's more time consuming. However, I do find that I'm more motivated to make food that tastes food (vs quick food) if I want to eat more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Eggs Royale with Chives   Caviar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The egg yolk with mustard maple syrup mixed with crispy duck skin made for an oddly satisfying taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
