<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Trashes Sustainability Twice In Two Weeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Like a slow death': families fear pesticide poisoning after Trump reverses ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure. 

To find the Republicans who are playing ball - admittedly, to varying degrees - one cool place to check is the membership of the Climate Solutions Caucus, which is, per membership requirement, 50% Republican.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressman promotes a Charles Darwin Day to fight science skepticism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressman promotes a Charles Darwin Day to fight science skepticism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressman promotes a Charles Darwin Day to fight science skepticism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said. We need to get through to their kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why scientists are fighting back. We've had enough of Trump's war on facts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Trump Appointees, a Raft of Potential Conflicts and No Transparency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MOAB :) Mother Of All Buffoons  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is idiocy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House demands carriage ride when Trump visits the U.K. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Origin of Easter: From pagan festivals and Christianity to bunnies and chocolate eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Origin of Easter: From pagan festivals and Christianity to bunnies and chocolate eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Jeff Sessions wants to crack down on medical marijuana, hell have to battle more than half the country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump-era damage to the EPA appears increasingly brutal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond the Origins of Totalitarianism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They Marched, Now They're Running </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colo. drops marijuana club plans over Trump admin uncertainty: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Now it's Bannon's fault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.nydailynews.com/news/politics/trump-james-comey-good-hillary-clinton-article-1.3046663 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you feel better. I know you're down about not attaining certain things, but just want to point out something: you are exceedingly introspective. Introspection is a wellspring for many talents, and those few that possess your level of introspection often don't realize this because they are consumed by their self criticism. 

Talent is inner energy turned outward, in a positive fashion. Some examples of upsides to introspective personality types are empathy, discernment, groundedness, dark humor, and a knack for writing. 

I hope you can foster an understanding of, and appreciation for, the upsides to your internal monologue of self awareness, self criticism and self analysis. Those upsides are your talents. And for all I know they may be just a few of the many. But for sure, they are very real and significant. Find them, and channel some of that significant internal energy outward and into them. If you practice this stuff enough you will find your balance. And that's the goal. Because balance is really what happiness is, you know? Staying true to yourself, listening to yourself, learning your nature, and also connecting outwardly, positively, to others, and sharing your gifts....Balance. 

As an aside...and you probably know this, but just in case: Introspection - like depression, and like good grammar, and like good writing - is also a mark of above average intelligence. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fear of death is lowest among atheistsand the very religious, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time for decisive steps to end bigotry, hate crimes in US: Indo-American Congressman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump should make a wall out of hillary's emails... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing I find surprising is that his affair wasn't with a teenage boy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The knives are out for Steve Bannon  as they should be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump removes Steve Bannon from National Security Council post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is The United States About To Bomb North Korea? The White House Says The Clock Has Now Run Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great many well articulated comments. Seriously, some of these could and should be published. Hoping some of you are communicating by op ed, and via email / voicemail to political representatives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.K. Betmaker LadBrokes Accepting Bets For Trump's Impeachment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.K. Betmaker LadBrokes Accepting Bets For Trump's Impeachment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps budget: Say goodbye to U.S. tech pre-eminence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reflections From a Champion for Separation of Church and State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The families fleeing from Trump's America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treason: The New Normal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least you have r/opieandandanthony upvoting you for referring to blacks as negros, hating blacks, marginalizing women (physically and mentally), jeering the mentally handicapped, etc., ad nauseum. It would seem that you're stuck in two worlds: one, where you think of yourself as a man of reason and fine temperament, awash in a a tsunami of media bias and liberal intolerance, and two where you are quite content as a bully, a bigot, a womanizer and a racist amongst others of your ilk. 

Your problem is not r/politics. Your problem is that you are conflicted. A part of you wants and seeks validation from nice people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Germany Goes Nuclear, Blame Trump Before Putin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fire This Man Now!: Fmr. White House Lawyers Accuse Trump Aide of Violating Law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Trump Nears Day 100, Existential Chaos Looms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Black hole at heart of Trump government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer Scientist Explodes Trumps Russian Bank Connection with New Records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Unlikely Rise of an Alt-Right Hero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel it, too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Political Walls Are Closing In On Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Not Trying to Prove He Is a Good President, He Is Trying to Show He Is the White President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it weren't for those meddling kids, he might have gotten away with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh....Martyrdom! Let's hope not! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll float a theory: He's enjoying his remaining days as a free man. Even if he walks, he's knows the future is grim. He is going to be an outcast. Treason is like the Scarlett Letter. So, he golfs. He rants. He continues to go to his one move: to double down. 

We have all been asking ourselves how in hell is he able to win. Now it appears to be the case he's 'winning' because he's 'protected' by Russian mob money and influence. Tit for tat, however, and he's almost exceeded his usefulness. They know we know. He knows we know. I think his sole remaining ambition is to golf and plunder until he inevitably goes out in cuffs. It's less the golfing and more the plundering I'm worried about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend sorting these comments by best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson Lifts Human Rights Conditions for Lucrative Arms Sale to Bahrain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps lies on energy will catch up with him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Isn't Just Failing: One Chart Shows That His Presidency Is Clinically Dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, sorry. It somehow passed through my "within 24 hours filter". I should've double checked. Deleting now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, sorry. It somehow passed through my "within 24 hours filter". I should've double checked.  Deleting now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, sorry. It somehow passed through my "within 24 hours filter". I should've double checked. Deleting now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, sorry. It somehow passed through my "within 24 hours filter". I should've double checked. 

Deleting now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Kremlins Man: A Unified Theory on Donald Trumps Russian Connections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Kremlins Man: A Unified Theory on Donald Trumps Russian Connections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are a few examples. Forgive brevity, 2am:

Xmark - Uher - campaign payments - Trump
"Yet until now, no one has pointed out that before he went to work for Trump, Uher ran Sater;"

Trump - Lynch - Caldwell - Moore - Morgan Lewis - Trump;

Semion Mogilevich - Alimzhan Taiwanchik Tokhtakhounov - Vyacheslav Yaponchik Ivankov - Trump Tower.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not without a hint of irony that you have my upvote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ Sums up aptly, imo. I was initially hesitant to post and later quite tempted to delete (upon criticism, anticipated and warranted). 

I'll add that my general disposition is that r/politics is better served by articles that are way less fringe than this. 

Still not entirely sure why I posted it, but also still not deleting it. The conclusions within the piece are, well, bereft of evidence. However, I see value in the way the author introduces and arranges the data. A shame he presents his conclusions as facts, rather than asking open questions for his readers to ponder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I concur. The title gave me a laugh. Although unfamiliar with the source, clearly dubious. I clicked, guiltily, expecting 1-paragraph clickbait drivel, but instead encountered an interesting read. 

As an avid follower of the ongoing investigation of  Trump, I see some nuggets in this piece - but, to be clear, the nuggets should have been presented at face value for the reader to think on, not as prerequisites to then leap into broad and dramatic conclusions. 

It's absolutely nuts for anyone to walk away from this piece with anything more than that takeaway. That's the problem with conspiracy fans positing as real journalists: they sometimes do great digging but then they let their imaginations marry the story, rather than simply presenting their research, asking open ended questions, and continuing the hunt for answers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. I knew I friended you for a reason. I click over to your comments from time to time, brilliant and funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trump became the Russian Mafias bitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2007....I just googled the abstract: 

The Assault on Reason is a 2007 book by Al Gore which brands conservatives as "enemies of justice and truth" engaged in a "systematic attack on the role of reasoned debate in policy and public life"[1] in America. 

....Appears that, once again, Gore was way ahead of me in even more respects than I have given him credit for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the one where the Steins survived glacial melt.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that our NSA recognizes climate change as one of the greatest threats to global stability...one would expect that behind the scenes our intelligence community is working to mitigate the wanton destruction of our planet under the current "leadership". One. Would. Expect. 

....At the expense of digression from topic, I'll add that if I don't see Trump in handcuffs by the end of this, I may well be applying for Canadian citizenship. I'll fight like hell for this country, but if our beaches and aquifers and, ultimately, my home is literally consumed by ocean water while Trump, Rick Scott and people of his ilk plunder and pillage this country to the delight of half of its citizenry, then I will have little recourse than to pick up and take my family some place sane and safe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inconvenient Sequel Trailer Presented by Al Gore at CinemaCon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is on a rampage to endanger the planet. Now its up to us to save it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Its Become So Hard to Get an Abortion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst humanitarian crisis hits as Trump slashed aid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Trump Executive Order -- pointless grovel to polluters, a poke at our planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Trump Executive Order -- pointless grovel to polluters, a poke at our planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is out of control. And we are paying the price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps big new executive order to tear up Obamas climate policies, explained </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oregon, Washington governors vow to fight Trump rollbacks of environmental protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! This post cited a show that aired this last Friday, and the topic is Trump. Not sure, but thinking this post may have been removed because of the reference to the 1930's as, at one point, Tim Snyder says, "we are in the 1930's", but it this is only because he's citing how history is repeating itself. Wil you perhaps give this a second look in case it can be restored? Either way, thanks! V </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump an 'embarrassment' - Richard Branson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of valid points here. You're likely right - and if pressed to wager on the outcome of all this, I'd wager he's going down and that we will build a stronger Democracy as a result of the burgeoning activism this has fostered, and with the benefit of hindsight. 

Chance favors the prepared mind. So, in the pragmatic spirit of hoping for the best while also planning for the worst, here is a link to a list of Snyder's 20 ways to defend against tyranny:

http://www.dallasnews.com/opinion/commentary/2016/11/21/learning-history-can-save-america-tyranny
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plenty of YouTube links to see the interview. Here is a link to a list of Snyder's 20 ways to defend against tyranny: 

http://www.dallasnews.com/opinion/commentary/2016/11/21/learning-history-can-save-america-tyranny


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's hope. Snyder issued a warning that the next move to watch for will be from the Reichstag playbook, a play designed specifically  to short out those checks and balances.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you see Bill Maher on Friday? Timothy Snyder, author of On Tyranny: Twenty Lessons From The 20th Century, offered a chilling analysis as to how Donald Trump reminds him of Third World dictators. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Maher Gets No Grins From Tyranny Expert: Im Not Going To Laugh at Any of That </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I think that the title provokes a strong reaction and I'm not surprised to see that many feel it is an overreach. Looking past the title, the author offers a careful and studied analysis; I invite anyone who hasn't read the article to not judge this book simply by its cover.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is an American Assad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LGBTQ Advocates Horrified By Trump Administration's Civil Rights Appointment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like a lot of this. I think there are a great many Republicans who "believe" that the heart of the party ascribes to the premise you describe. I also think that the Republican party is, at present, spending way too much time, money and resources suppressing science, art and humanities, civil liberties, thwarting necessary oversight and regulation, blurring the line between church and state, and running routes of obfuscation and disinformation on the middle class to keep them thinking that (R) is still in the business of seeding their ability to flourish. I hope to see this imbalance to hit a dead end and soon, and for a retracement. 

If we do ultimately get a "greatest hits"'of (R) and (D), I think this great American experiment will be a resounding success. Right now, I think our democracy has cancer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And showers of Russian gold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, with that chainsaw and flame thrower he really is a master of tact and diplomacy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump only likes big shit shows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Trump Told Freedom Caucus To 'Forget The Little S***' In Repeal Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certain imminent death versus witness protection. He chose wisely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Manafort To Testify On Russia As House Intel Committee Drama Continues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Big Tobaccos Academy of Lies, the Inventor of Alternative Facts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure it will turn out very well. Shame to hear of infighting but also sounds like a lot is being addressed and rectified. In the end, a record shattering display of a diverse group of scientists across so many cities will send a powerful message, and that is what will leave a lasting impact, and what history will remember. That, and I can't wait to see the signs!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a good example of a lobby that engages true conservatives. They use the hard data to demonstrate why taxing carbon is a good business decision. They've actually gotten quite a few high ranking conservatives on board. 
https://citizensclimatelobby.org/about-ccl/


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is so true. They are literally factoring it in and waiting on our government to implement this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make America Great AgainTrump Must Go! #8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are actually quite a few conservatives getting behind measuring the cost of carbon. But there's a long way to go.  And we don't have a lot of time. And Trump is doing everything he can to hurt this effort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump refusing to even measure economic cost of climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch his eyes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been hoping she would join us. That's awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noted, and with a bit of glee. This is a bit of a one two punch, then, given this morning's absolutely savage WSJ opinion piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's the cornered guy, shouting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist: his wife also told him to wire tap Trump Tower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, glitched (below). You get my drift, though, I think :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 08:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am proposing that Reddit offer subscription-based journals, periodicals and newspapers a platform wherein Redditors could unlock paywalls on a paid-per-article basis. The transaction would be processed by Reddit, and - less a cut to Reddit - remitted to the publication. The benefit to the Redditor is to gain access to an attractive / compelling article that he / she would normally be unable to read, simply by paying a small amount on the spot, rather than to have to subscribe to an entire publication. 

I am also proposing that within each Redditor's membership profile is an option to confirm one's pre-existing subscriptions, up front, thereby unlocking paywalled publications as per each Redditor's profile. 

Lastly, an "unlock this paywalled article for other redditors" feature would be nice, whereby the person who has posted the paywalled article can pay for others to view the paywalled article. Let's say I post a paywalled article. It's something within a subscription based periodical. Well, most can't read it so it may not gain any traction. Well, let's say I want people to read that article. I'd be willing to pay to unlock it for the first hundred readers. That would generate discussion, upvotes (hopefully). After 100, the article converts back to paywalled. However, redditors can now at least gauge the excitement level based on the upvotes and comments, as a basis to determine whether they want to pay to view it. 

I hope that is a better explanation. 

As to how it is built, well, that's not something I'm qualified to answer. I guess like anything one has to understand the idea first, which I may or may not have just accomplished. Step two is determining if it's something that others would want. So, your opinion would be great, if you get what I'm proposing. Only then does feasibility become critical. Nothing I've suggested is new, and therefore it's entirr

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, based on your reply it's my mistake. I spend most of my time on subs that don't permit paywalled articles. Thought it was universally forbidden to post 'em.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know your question is non rhetorical but I'll take a shot at it, for fun. As crazy as it sounds...I think they are too far gone. Heads will roll if they tap the breaks on the dark passengers to whom they are indebted. I see a desperate, fever pitch frenzy to feast, and when the blue flashing lights and sirens arrive they will be stuffing White House silverware into their fat pockets. 

The adage 'Eat, drink and be merry...for tomorrow we die," surely applies here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nasdarovje! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allow posting of paywalled articles. Redditors who wish to unlock a paywalled article simply pay the fee (which is whatever Reddit has pre-negotiated with each paper). Like, say, 0.5 to read a WSJ article. Those of us who already have, say, WSJ could... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...register our subscription w/Reddit so it's not charged to us. 

It could work as seamlessly as gold. 

Also, bonus: let's say I really want to post a WSJ article and make the entire article visible to the readers. It would be cool if I could give it gold (or some sort of paid trophy) and essentially buy the first 100 views for readers. Sort of like priming the pump. That way it gives some people a glance, and they can then start the process of liking or hating the article. They pave the way so future people can gauge the upvotes and comments and decide if they want to pay to see it. 

What got me thinking about all of this was tonight's scathing opinion piece on trump. WSJ. I'd have posted that for the world but, of course, I can't. Then I started thinking of the other rags that simply cannot afford to release free articles, and started bandying about this idea. 

I'm not so obtuse as to think you all have not already considered this. But in this moment of inspiration wanted to lend my voice to any existing momentum behind such an effort. 

Love ya, Reddit. You're awesome. 

Regards,

V </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. So wish we could post WSJ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit: I had to check your post history to be sure this was sarcasm! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I imagine the bot will delete this post soon, as the auto title failed. I should've checked it :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Journal editorial: Donald Trumps credibility questioned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WSMFJ!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Presidents Credibility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Presidents Credibility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wall Street Journal compares Trump to 'a drunk' clinging to 'an empty gin bottle' in scathing editorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was about to type the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Russia, ground comes to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Republicans_who_opposed_the_Donald_Trump_presidential_campaign,_2016

^ list of Republicans who oppose Trump  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.forbes.com/forbes/welcome/?toURL=https://www.forbes.com/sites/reneemorad/2017/02/14/want-to-boycott-trump-friendly-companies-these-apps-can-assist-you/ refURL= referrer=

^ Trump friendly companies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Donald_Trump_presidential_campaign_endorsements,_2016

^ politicians who endorse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://trump.kimalbrecht.com/network/

^ Trump: All business ties  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, christ, 3Effie412. You followed me from r/Michigan. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soon, in addition to each weekend, Trump is going to start golfing during the weekdays, too. He knows what's coming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article is on Page 26.

It's hard to display the article, so here is an excerpt:

Yet its really not even that complicated. Whites, and I include Asians here, have chosen winning economic and social strategies that often out-performed the social and economic strategies of those groups with whom theyve been in intense competition for centuries. There has been a competition, and one group, at least for now, seems to be in the lead. If its a privilege, its a hard-won, fully-earned privilege.
Now if you are a member of that group and you want to feel horribly guilty about winning, well you go right ahead. But please, Lily, dont expect me or anyone else to do the same. Yet the race is still being run and the privilege of being out front is up for grabs.
White Just Another Brand
When you boil it all down, and somebody really should do this for Lily-White, its all about reputation; its all about branding - a subject </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White Privilege: Feel the Guilt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does remind me of a theme that persisted from
Ancient times through the Middle Ages, of depriving the people of access to books (and stifling literacy). Nowadays the trick is to feed the people disinformation, propaganda, obfuscation...all straight out of the Big Tobacco playbook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're all in with every hand. Scorched earth poker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans seem willing to betray any principle to defend Donald Trump from the FBI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, sorry to hear. If it's any consolation, I've been right where you are. Hope you can pull through. Just read a few of your prior posts and you have a job, so that's cool, and hope that leads to a better living arrangement soon. 

Don't know how to make you smile. I can tell you my own deal, though: keeping a journal, learning a social trade (like bar tending, baristo, barber), and using that trade to see some new places helped me. I liked having room mates, too - once I got enough of a footing to pay rent. Having good people around kept me more upbeat. 

With my depression, I've noticed keeping my expenses well below my income helps keep my stress low....although I've failed miserably in this regard! 

I hope you continue to fight the good fight, and swim up, and that one by one you get your wins. They won't all be home runs, just base hits, right? 

Cheers,

V </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Roll tide!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was an excellent read. I love it when the interviewer is as good as the interviewee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spalpeens and sycophants. Awesome. Until Trump came along, I had no idea Esquire was so chalk full of great writing. I guess that's something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's hope that the second two months culminates in handcuffs. Bonus points if Bannon goes, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Double true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White evangelical Christians believe they are more discriminated against than Muslims, US poll finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde formula won't work forever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, China's been taxing carbon in 7 districts for several years now. There is no speculation here. They've come right out and said that the science is real, invested heavily into solutions, and signed the Paris Agreement. They've stated that their current pollution levels in major cities are in crisis, fossil fuels force them to rely on foreign powers, and that part of their role as a superpower is to lead the world in renewable energy technology (which they are doing, and have been doing). 

Nothing I've stated above is speculative. These things have happened and are happening. The US has been behind in this arena for a while now. India is in similar straits (as China) and is fast tracking renewables, and for the same reasons. 

Now, I'll offer my opinion as to why these countries are able to see the forest for the trees: these countries aren't oligarchies, in bed with big tobacco, oil and the military industrial complex. Yes, they have their own problems...but in this arena we are the jack asses. Until people like you see this, we will continue to stagnate and risk being an empire in decline. I, for one, choose to fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde formula won't work forever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China is way ahead of us on investment into renewables, and not just in dollars but also as a percentage of GDP, and has been for years. China is implementing a national cap-and-trade system this year. They've pledged for clean energy to represent a minimum of their total energy production by 2030. After the Paris Climate Agreement, old fears that developing countries like India and China wouldn't act on climate change became outdated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for: I talked with Bazzy after we taped Michigan Matters, airing at 11:30 a.m.  today on CBS 62. She and Oakland County Executive L. Brooks Patterson traded terse words on Trumps immigration ban and the need for it.

I reviewed Reddit's lengthy definition on spamming. No, I am
not spamming. One can place articles into multiple communities if they are topically relevant and if one engages in dialogue in each community. I do both. So, yeah. Wrong-o on both counts. And, finally, lest I forget to mention (again) that this is my second post in r/Michigan, ever. The first post generated 287 upvotes and some great dialogue, which is unsurprising, given that Michigan is thriving with people keen on civil rights, climate change mitigation and other things about which I am passionate and well informed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Casual lie by Trump White House can't derail FBI's Russia probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hobbies are starting, building and then selling companies...and yachting, snow boarding and off roading. 

Thank you for evaluating my post volume and for your concern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
