<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject695</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it speaks volumes that liberals are the ones who tend to believe this and conservatives don't and this is why we will lose elections like 2016 and 2000. My fucking right wing sister admitted that she sees voting for "her" Republican party is like rooting for her favorite football team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like all of the Clooney ones are classics. Ocean's 12 is not regarded as being a very good movie and started out as a screenplay for a non-Ocean's movie. They just changed the names and threw the Ocean's title onto it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 07:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to /r/3dshacks to find out if you can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 03:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the dumbest thing I've read today and that says a lot. There's no reason the current Democrat president wouldn't want people to vote for the Democrat candidate running to replace him. Do you really think Ronald Reagan did not campaign for George H.W. Bush? The reason George W. Bush didn't campaign for John McCain was because he was toxic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 01:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet you still ended up with climate change denier Tony Abbott and Dick Cheney's twin a few years ago. I think his name was Howard. Your voters are just as stupid as ours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 06:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, thank you so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 05:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then, what would you call this: http://media.salon.com/2016/10/wikileaks_shirt.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DQ VII - I have the ultimate key and I can't find the secret treasury room in Estard Castle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 04:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's supposed to be a secret treasury under Estard Castle that has a mini medal, Seed of Strength, Platinum and King's(?) Sword. I can't find a way to get to this room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An even more recent witch hunt, was a few weeks ago, when Reddit was so sure it was a woman who threw a beer can onto the field at a Toronto Blue Jays playoff game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way he was calling out Katy, he creepily reminded me of Kilgrave in Jessica Jones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 19:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem, glad to help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youngstown is Northeast Ohio not SW.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's looking pretty scary here in the Mahoning Valley which used to be a heavily Democrat area. Bernie is going to be here Thursday to help get the youth out. The problem is that this region is becoming more of a old, white demographic as most young people are leaving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has something to do with him and former guitarist of Blink 182, Tom DeLonge, discussing UFOs. I heard Podesta previously saying Hillary would declassify all documents about UFOs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 05:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He caused innocent people to get fired in the past, too. Some have sued and won.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then he should have no problem releasing the unedited video. All of his other videos turned out to be fake, why would this be any different?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 03:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That unfortunately is true and is very annoying. Hopefully it dies down after the election. Considering how people have been acting, I don't know if it will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 03:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doctored video footage doesn't constitute as quoting a person. Sorry to burst your bubble, but the only paycheck I receive is from the U.S. Air Force. 

Edit: so, I'm apparently being brigaded by centipedes that came crawling out of /r/t_d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 03:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you customize your frontpage more to your liking by removing subs that you don't want to show up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 03:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or it could be that Project Veritas has been proven to be not credible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't they see it as the government forcing something on them though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 23:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all? I always thought Utah had a higher percentage of Mormons than that. 

Edit: Oops, I misread Idaho as Utah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 21:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of Stein supporters are antivaxxers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 03:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely the title of a new James Bond film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 02:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Juggalos wear them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 05:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank goodness we have her because Trevor Noah is lackluster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Wallace practically told the audience to shut the fuck up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 04:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and in general i don't think isaac lived up to it's hype at all due to it's laughably bigoted story



How does it have a bigoted story?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this will turn out to be the case. I'm from a mostly Democratic city in northeast Ohio and every Trump supporter here is unabashedly loud and proud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily the best episode from gas leak year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 08:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a Russian Trump surrogate on tv quite a bit named Boris Epshteyn. 

http://mediamatters.org/research/2016/09/15/media-host-trump-adviser-boris-epshteyn-russia-without-disclosing-his-business-ties/213113 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 03:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sniffling appears to be back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 08:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering the same thing. It's as if he/she believes boys don't get erections until puberty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 05:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Hillary would easily defeat Pence due to him being a theocrat. I do think McMullen and Johnson may split enough of the votes to keep Trump from winning Utah. Plus, I read that a lot Mormons plan on writing-in Romney's name 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 05:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jason Chaffetz from Utah just did un-endorse. I could see Donald coming in third place in Utah. They have their own Mormon independent candidate, Evan McMullen, on the ballot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Uncle Pete is my hero." - Ben Roethlisberger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 07:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe Larry David?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 18:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Dragon Quest vii with orchestra soundtrack and it's not really that much bigger than the midi version. Roughly about 200mb bigger. I know this because I downloaded both versions. It most likely is because the composer doesn't want his music used outside of Japan. He's known to be eccentric and a shitty person. Great musician though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 05:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That had nothing to do with unions and everything to do with the Chinese dumping cheap steel into the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has three save files.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the helpful info. It cleared up what I knew about Ron Paul and same-sex marriage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 22:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't Ron and Rand Paul against same-sex marriage?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 04:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate deus ex machina. I know this is an unpopular opinion, but this is one of the reasons why I didn't like season 2 of Fargo as much as season 1.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is wrong with you? Get help because you sure as hell need it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 04:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 22:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what you are talking about. I have a Samsung Galaxy Note 4 and YouTube does display vertically. 

http://m.imgur.com/vaDjRTL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
