<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4418</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sure was. The recession was world-wide. The US had the best recovery to date. Expect a ton of inflation under Trump. 

Obama was handed a mess, not Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear leader Obama was handed the worst recession in US history, courtesy of GWB and the republicans.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americans want price when they buy things. They don't care about your job. Food budgets are stretched these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US 'deeply concerned' after Turkey bombs allies in Iraq and Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Trump says he employs these people because "American workers are inferior".  Our kids won't do anything that can't be done on a keyboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you willing to pick strawberries in the field? If so you can have that job. How much are you willing to pay for strawberries? These people are vital to keeping food costs down. Without them much of our fruit would rot in the field. Trump uses them in his wineries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanctuary cities rely on these people for labor. They do jobs no American wants. They are important to the local economies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "For builders, it'll increase the cost of construction by about $3,000 on the average home, which unfortunately will be passed on to consumers," said Jerry Howard, CEO of the group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New home buyers will pay for that new Canadian lumber tariff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that it's there what are we going to do with it. Bomb another inanimate object? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Sessions can figure this one out. Are we sure he's a lawyer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can't follow what he doesn't know. He's probably in wtf mode right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanctuary cities are complicated. Who knew? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge blocks Trump order to cut funding from sanctuary cities like Seattle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The price of lumber has skyrocketed in the last few year. Expect new home prices to rise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no military options in N. Korea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would kill a whole bunch of US troops and millions of innocent people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven people were shot during a span of an hour Monday, a day that saw a total of three people fatally shot and 12 others wounded, Chicago police said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is US President Donald Trump backing himself into a corner on North Korea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an appearance at the University of Chicago, former President Barack Obama unloaded a  barrage of complete sentences in what was seen as a brutal attack on his successor, Donald Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Is Writing Fake Executive Orders Because He Doesnt Know How to Be President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might have been had Trump not fucked up so badly. It will take 20 years to repair the damage he's done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man, woman, 3-year-old child dead in murder-suicide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea threatens to sink US aircraft carrier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps approval rating sliding, latest WSJ/NBC News poll finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people are coming illegally across the border, how would we know how many of them there are vs last year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Indians, Trumps America Is a Land of Lost Opportunity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She bombed Syria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spending bill is DOA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel sorry for the young children of America, you care little about them or their future..

https://futurism.com/governor-louisiana-declares-state-emergency-states-coastline-disappears/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $90 million is an expensive now now. Assad couldn't care less about an airport. The airport was in use the following day. All Syrian aircraft were moved to a Russian airbase in Syria. It was useless without a followup plan. 

The Pakistan attack was also useless as it's a one time deal. At least it only cost $16 million. ISIS is all over the world. People who butcher others fear no one. Least of all Trump. They would love nothing more than a fight to the death.

Trump said he would be everyone's President. He should certainly listen to what scientists have to say. Do you consider coal dust in your water a good thing? How about pesticides being approved that cause autism and brain damage in children? Do you believe global warming is a hoax? 

Trump only is not listening, he's working to destroy all records scientists have collected. What's he afraid of, things like clean coal is a hoax?

Our kids future is at stake here, he better damn well listen.

These are not all scientists anymore than the woman's march was all women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stores are closing at an epic pace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an airbase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once again the world joins in our anti-Trump protests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See The March For Science Protests Around The World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said he would eliminate ISIS in 30 days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bebe to shut all its stores </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March for Science draws big crowds across U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's 'big announcement' on tax to be broad principles: official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as planes are in the air there is the possibility of a confrontation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, maybe he can highlight all the things he claimed could be done in 100 days, but failed to do. Things like, well, everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They won't be near anything like the biggest ever. Most will be sadly disappointed. He's run no numbers on how they will effect the deficit and economy. Fortunately, some people will and clearer heads will prevail. Trump thinks he can wave his magic wand and make things happen, but it just doesn't work that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://abcnews.go.com/International/russian-aircraft-close-alaska-4th-time-days/story?id=46939351 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We bombed an airport, ISIS must be shaking.. LOL

So far I have not seen a coherent position. He said he knew more than the generals then turned the decisions over to them. He said he had a great healthcare plan then turned that over to Ryan and the republican Congress. Sooner or later you'll see the BS artist that he is.

Defense funding was cut by the Republican sequester.

Now he says the largest tax cut in US history. LOL  His budget is DOA in Congress.

I agree it's early and he surely will fuck up a lot more. He's illiterate on most every subject.  How many Presidents have you seen scientists protest? ROFLMFAO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has not shown restraint. He bombed Syria with NO provocation. Another campaign promise broken of not getting involved in other countries wars. Yet another lie you bought. To his credit it may have been Ivanka's decision-Sad

I have 150,000 shares of Boeing. Boeing is not strictly a defense stock, but it's the closest thing I have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing has changed on immigration or trade. 

Trump going to get his ass kicked allowing the military guys to do as they please. One of these days the people we bomb will shoot back. Enjoy your wars under Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin building massive Arctic military base </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently everyone can be because he gave to most all of them. Trump is indeed a politician.

You understand that Trump was never going to put Clinton is prison, right? That was just a ploy to get his morons to vote for him. So was most all of his rhetoric. He never had a healthcare plan for all. He never had a plan to defeat ISIS in 30 days. He didn't know more than the Generals. Just how many lies are Trump supporters willing to buy?

He'll get crushed on tax reform because the jackass has no idea of the cost. Healthcare will fail again. It should be an interesting week. I'm certain you'll buy all his excuses for these failures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He gave them money to buy favors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TLC fines Trump-touting cabbies for tirades on Muslims, liberals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have plenty of reason to believe he's a criminal. Trump told us the Clintons are fine people. He liked them so much he's given them millions over the years. Trump is getting wealthy at taxpayer expense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Students Are Losers from DeVos Rollback of College Loan Protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This goes far beyond sex.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying Republicans would turn a blind eye to Treason charges against Flynn and Manafort?

Before you get on your high horse, "we control Congress", remember there is an election shortly and one every 2 years after that.

So far Trump has done nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget Congress, concentrate on the FBI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ErhVB35EAtI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, it will be more like the middle of his second year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two things define you: Your patience when you have nothing and your attitude when you have everything.  Unknown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What GOP plan?  Is it the one Trump said was "easy"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration happened. Our 1st class train wreck that can't seem to get out of it's own way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will be impeached, but not because of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patriots player: 'No interest' in meeting Donald Trump after 'disgusting' comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 90-year-old woman shot after argument over chicken bones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paging the Trump Armada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Trump warned North Korea, his 'armada' was headed toward Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes he has, but only for himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh well, there goes our tax cuts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bold promises, fewer results: Trump's executive orders don't always live up to his claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is not making the decisions. He's turned that over to the Generals, who will get blamed for everything that fails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> North Korea will not be deterred. They don't think rationally. We're dealing with 2 irrational people here and one of them is our President. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Donald Trump U-Turns In The Last Two Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Russian investigation is not going away just because we bombed someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good news is we haven't bombed anyone today, but it's early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's 1/2 Million dollars apiece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pulitzer-winning combat journalist warns of medias hype songs and war toy cheers after Trump drops MOAB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hard is it to drop something? Did we hit anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 88 year-old Walmart greeter fired after wild turkey enters store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $16 million more down the tubes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama made him do it /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Easter, Afghanistan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bomb, Bomb Iran, Bomb Bomb (Fill in the blank) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US drops mother of all bombs on Isis target in Afghanistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, just stating a fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has done more to spread hatred of Muslims than ISIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ROFL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the real world, Donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did Trump flip flop on Yellen? She may be the dove he needs, analysts say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, who knew you would need to assess the cost of things before making budgets? Math is difficult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump couldn't run his businesses without fraud. How did you expect him to run a country? Now he's lifting his hiring ban because he has decimated every agency in the country. He has no idea what he's doing in any area of government.Your better choice may well destroy the country.

Ron Paul would have made a better President. For all Paul's flaws he was a sincere and honest man without a large ego. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton would have installed a no fly zone. Then we would have known who is friends with whom. A no fly zone would have prevented his tragedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically you were conned. Trump has always been a bullshit artist. You should have done more research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Healthcare tackled Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably which ever way has a tailwind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump loves immigrants, for as he's always said "American workers are inferior".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assad did it, and Russians have a problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fact aren't important to trump supporters. Spicer just said "even Hitler didn't use chemical weapons"". ROFL

You were conned by a pro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They spread false news, like Pizzgate, and Trump validated it. Americans bought his BS because they were desperate. You obviously bought plenty of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. Russia feared Clinton more than Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see, a 9 iron looks good. Bang! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get this bimbo out of the WH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd just launch and see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Far cheaper than a Trump round of golf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their accuracy is not good. The nukes are powerful no matter where they detonate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People always overreact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That won't scare Trump, he has no idea of their destructive force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if they are underground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is leading us to a war with Russia, and N. Korea and Iran. Hillary was correct, a no-fly zone would have prevented this attack.

We blew up an airfield, so what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll just have to wait and see how Ivanka reacts to this situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple? LOL

The FBI will nail Trump and his cronies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They mostly planted false news about Clinton, as opposed to pro-Trump news. They found a a wide-eyed ignorant group who actually believed Trump wasn't a politician. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's misleading voters. They just hit a group of voters dumb enough to believe anything. Not since Ron Paul have there been a more uneducated group. Now Eric tells us this was all Ivanka's idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what Donald thinks about his son telling the world Ivanka is in charge of the military? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would this kid even comment on this. Pure stupidity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some believed the 40% unemployment rate, some believed there were 100,000 Syrian refugees pouring across the border. There is no sense to the things his supporters  bought. Go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hes not a good influence on the president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: Man, 19, charged after shooting friend in the head during argument </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea warns its ready for war after U.S. sends in ships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea warns its ready for war after U.S. sends in ships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For survivors of past Syrian gassing, new attack brings back horror and despair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student one of 3 dead in San Bernardino school shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's not just Syria. Trump is ratcheting up wars across the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
