<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2433</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 17:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been on Facebook for over a month now. I'll admit, it definitely helps. The only think that makes me compare myself to people now is when other brag about their lives IRL, or even if they just mention the awesome things they have done in casual conversation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 13:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 23 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can I do to love myself, so that I can stop giving a fuck about what other people think of me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 00:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a lot of thinking it seems that all the fucks I give about stupid things come from the fact that I don't like myself. a lot of the advice I see around here requires you to love yourself or asks if you do

the fact is I don't love myself, or have confidence in myself. maybe its because of all the mistakes I've made in the past, or maybe its because I'm overweight (I'm working on it), maybe its because I always compare myself to other people

I don't know exactly the reason, all I know is I don't know how to love myself, and that doing so is the first step to not giving a fuck

any advice is really appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 21:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When's a good time/place to randomly talk to someone at the gym? In the locker room? The person on the machine next to you?

I can be socially stupid at times so I don't want to weird people out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 20:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any tips on meeting or sparking conversations with people at the gym? It would be nice to have some friends to work out with at the gym

Problem is its hard to talking to random guys I don't know either, and I definitely feel intimidated if they are in better shape than I am. I think it may be because I feel inferior to them and think they view me as inferior </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HTNGAF about being overweight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-27 19:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I'm not saying I don't want to lose weight. in fact I'm working on it right now. the fact is though, I'm still going to be fat for a while as I'm waiting for the pounds to drop off.

my weight has always been something I'm self-conscious about. I mean, why the hell would a girl want to have anything to do with some nerdy fat guy. even if I'm just trying to make friends with other guys I feel self-conscious about it. I'm always worried about other people seeing me as being 'fat' and nothing else

how can I overcome this in the meantime? my last year of college is coming up and I want to spend this year being confident and crushing my social anxiety </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
