<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9140</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How America executes its prisoners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT expert claims latest chemical weapons attack in Syria was staged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know you, but I love you JarkJark </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Secret </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Praise Jeebus on this His holiest of days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Golden Axe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General Mills wasn't kidding when they said Lucky Charms were "Magically Delicious" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You received *A LOT* of heavy handed answers but truth be told, it's more fun to root for the bad guy.

Whether it's because you enjoy the idea of  unchecked power, doing what you want or believe that the good guys are lame and predictable, the villain is always more interesting/dynamic.

Darth Vader, from the minute he steps on the screen, takes over. Even in Rogue One, his 90 seconds of light saber attacks are the highlight of the movie.

Luke is introduced as a farm boy and Obi Wan as a drifter in the desert. 

People to this day like Han because he "shot first." Like a villain, he didn't play by the rules.

The Villain is more enjoyable to watch, plain and simple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks suspiciously like Rachel Dolezal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh how I love when people respond to my comments and they clearly didn't read the article </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be more inclined to believe this coming from *any* other hotel CEO IE one that doesn't have close ties to Mitt Romney.

http://www.npr.org/2012/04/05/150058865/for-romney-family-ties-to-marriott-heirs-pay-off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed my ass off at the idea of Crest or Colgate saying: "Try triple action whitening paste in your T-Zone" or "Freshen up your T-Area" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Because I'm in Tokyo and there aren't garbage cans *anywhere*" should really be an answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United Airlines Changes Policy for Displacing Passengers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alabama Thunderpussy

(How on Earth am I the first to say them!?)

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alabama_Thunderpussy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But can it stop the Spanish Inquisition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conker's Bad Fur Day. 

Basically the entire game, but especially when he's trying to enter the rock club and the bouncer asks for the password.

Conker turns to his friend for the password, and in a nod to the infamous Eyes Wide Shut orgy, says "Fellatio?" to the bouncer.

Then his friend corrects him and he says the *actual* Eyes Wide Shut password, "Fidelio." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Monroeville Zombies" hockey jersey in "Zach and Miri Make A Porno"

Both that movie and the original "Dawn of the Dead" were filmed in Pittsburgh

"Dawn of the Dead," more specifically, was filmed in the Monroeville Mall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A stupid pair of fucking sneakers just because a tall guy has his name on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back to work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are expectations for Ivanka Trump any higher than they are for Paris Hilton, Kim Kardashian or the Hadid sisters.

Her parents were wealthy. That doesn't make her talented, intelligent or qualified to do anything.

I'm not saying she isn't *potentially* all of those things as I don't know her, but let's all be honest with ourselves: she's a rich kid that probably never had to work much for what she wanted.

Why would we expect **anything** from someone given **everything**? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bah! Her questionable use of Tyrian purple for the outfit ruins this authenticity of this for me.

How can this be true cosplay? Tyrian purple comes from predatory sea snails and *every* Legend of Zelda player knows that no such enemies exist in canon. Good effort, I suppose.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tyrian_purple

(If you've read this far, then I'm hoping you realized I'm joking 3 sentences ago)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part of anyone seeing this and immediately howling "Muslim Prayer!!!!" is that they don't even understand the **basics** of Muslim prayer!

All Muslims pray towards Mecca.

These kids are facing in different directions.

So either the tweet about it being Muslim prayer is wrong ORRR half the kids are mentally incompetent.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Christie is country's least-popular governor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicago and Detroit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The suit says "Jurassic world"

But the face says "Flashbacks to filming Oz" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The luck of Seth MacFarlane

http://shortformblog.com/post/43956956785/seth-macfarlane-9-11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Dr. Pepper's no-talent brother-in-law Mr. Pibb?

*Couldn't even hold down his job as a Walmart greeter.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Intelligence Republicans Boycott Briefing From FBIs Russian Double Agent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in all fairness to Kushner (did I just fucking say that?), unlike Bannon, he can't choke his wife when she dissents. His father-in-law is, after all, the leader of the free world.

http://www.snopes.com/2016/11/14/steve-bannon-was-accused-of-domestic-violence/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you familiar with the phrase "water temple"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only this is not mildly interesting, it might be one of the most interesting things I've *ever* seen on Reddit.

I never considered what paint looked like prior to the mixing process. This is **far** more interesting than I expected! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex-wife and I used to work for the same company and she was performing a phone interview (on speakerphone.) When my wife asked about her technical qualifications, the candidate responded with a fair amount of indignation.

"I Excel! I PowerPoint!"

When an IT jobseeker uses "PowerPoint" as a verb, then you can pretty safely assume they lied on their resume.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish this video was set to the "cha cha slide" and the truck exploded at the end.

White people are **FUCKING LAME**

Full disclosure: I'm white and forced to live among us. If we would do the "cha cha slide" in public, then imagine how lame we are in private!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would counter with the need for an article as inane as this:

https://www.philly.com/philly/columnists/20151115_Philly_won_t_be_overlooked__Give_us_a__road__sign.html%3Famphtml%3Dy

(And having not always lived here is why I know the inferiority complex exists) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone loves a martyr, even if that martyr is a moral absolutist.

The comedian was definitely an asshole in many ways, BUT he was by far the more complex character.

Rorschach, despite his penchant for comic book level violence, is still black or white (ironic given his name is literally a test about interpretation) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going with a comment I saw on Twitter.

To paraphrase: maybe readers are just tired of the Uncle Ben died **again** storyline.

Marvel could try to be...creative

BUT they are owned by Disney now...and Disney seems content to just remake *every* cartoon as live action. 

Coming soon...a new animated version!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Philadelphia could be described in a single phrase, then it would be "inferiority complex"

...and the sad part is that Philly sucks more than it realizes or cares to admit 

Source: Me...I live here...sadly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why isn't this already posted in

r/ANormalDayInRussia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Chris Pratt and Anna Faris in Hawaii right before Guardians of Galaxy came out.

If I hadn't seen them together, then I never even would have noticed they were there.

*took a lot to not approach Andy Dwyer that day* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump pulls back Obama-era protections for women in the workplace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dentistry...dentistry never changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When something shows up on the "Popular" front page and your only reaction is:

"Huh? That's photoshopped, right? Or there's some meme I don't know. This can't be an actual screen grab? It is? Where's my medication" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls could wear skirts but boys couldn't wear shorts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The solid yellow light on a stop light should be replaced with a yellow number that counts down to zero. Then drivers would actually know whether or not they would "make the yellow." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who baptize their kids strictly because *they were* baptized.

Do you honestly believe your child is doomed to an eternity in limbo because an 80 year old virgin didn't sprinkle some water on their head? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop using logic you *monster*!!!

That's not why we have the internet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japan loves KFC too!

I went to Hanshin Tigers game and the line for KFC was *out of control*

The line for authentic Japanese stadium food was comparatively non existent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So companies can raise money without issuing more debt. Or more simply, they can raise money without being legally required to pay someone back (which is how debt/loans/bonds work).

In exchange for you buying stock, you have ownership in that company...albeit a *VERRRRY* small percentage.  That's why owning a stock is called "having equity in a company."

As an equity owner, if the company goes out of business, it's basically "sucks for you" because you're an owner now.

Net-net: companies need money and people that buy stock give it to them in exchange to be part owner of the same company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid is as stupid does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in that instant, Cowboy Keith understood why the other men called that bronco "Divorce" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay Chad, you stick your hand in a bag filled with Icosahedrons and are bitten by the deadly Black Mamba. You need to roll a 12 or higher to...

Chad...

Chad...

*CHAD!!!!!!!!!!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Thank you kind sir! When the Overmind let's slip the fury of the hives, your name will be on our protected scrolls!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn in 2016: Immunity 'means you probably committed a crime' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking touch me! I can buy anything else I see! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for him!!!

And I bet if we compared to him to your average adult, he **crushed** them by way of books read!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I saw this nightmare fuel before bed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading this reminds me of one thing:

Kevin MacCallister and his rollerskates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things this artist clearly does not suffer from: OCD

Proof: I see no eraser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all fairness, Zordon was known to pal around with Robert Mapplethorpe and experiment at Studio 54.

I'm impressed your kid is so knowledgeable of homoerotic photography, but the internet has expanded the minds of many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon to start collecting state sales taxes everywhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kushner company, Chinese firm call off development deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's no moon...it's a battle station! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House intel panel chief Nunes says he will not divulge his sources </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That test of course being, "Can Samsung blow an airliner out of the sky with a battery meltdown?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes BUT only because your knives are full tang.

Smart move going for quality!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminded me of the video series "Faces of Death" except I'd call it "Faces of Regret" or "Orgasms + 60 seconds" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine that, people irreparably harm their bodies doing something *THAT FUCKING KILLED* the first guy who did it (supposedly)

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pheidippides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to make the same joke as you but then I saw your innocent joke was counteracted with nerd rage at not knowing "HAN SHOT FIRST YOU LOSER."

I upvoted your comment because the struggle to find people with a sense of humor is real! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bad news is that the child appears to be wearing an Ed Hardy t-shirt and is almost certainly a Paulie D wannabe. If he could talk, then he would say, "If I didn't park there, then some fat fuck who wasn't handicapped would"

I'm SO sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's referred to in common parlance as: "death" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Mexico is installing X-rated train seats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like watching NBA Jam in real life

*...I was only missing the trampoline* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monster cables for anything.

The *MOST* overpriced, average quality product ever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charles Barkley: My dying wish is to kill Skip Bayless on national TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dented cans of food.

Think of them like botulism grenades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not far off from the truth.

Every time I pull it from the drawer I swear under my breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AP Exclusive: US probes banking of ex-Trump campaign chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada just bought half of Puerto Ricos main airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump set his lawyers on a teenage girl who made a fun internet game about him and kittens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abused shelter dog a hero for finding naked girl shivering in cold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Labor nominee cut deal with billionaire accused of having sex with minors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now it just needs a way to synchronize with the phones of the user in each stall.

Then, when they've completed their current level of Clash of Clans, it can send an alert to those waiting in line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he's anything like my friend growing up, then his resume listed his gas station work experience as "Petroleum Engineer."

BEST. RESUME. EUPHEMISM. EVER. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly this is true.

If Edmund Kemper were ever paroled, then he'd be the most popular guy on Tinder (he's 6'9")

Of course, he's also a serial killer and necrophiliac with crippling social anxiety around women BUT I bet most girls on Tinder would just say "oh Ed's just shy"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeaaaaah...I think even Hansel and Gretel would have avoided going in the candy house if the old woman's candy dish was from the Ed Gein collection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first time I can recall seeing her as a young woman.

Given the amount of time I've wasted watching movies over the last 30 years, I have to ask "How the fuck is that possible?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What they don't realize...he's shorter than them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To answer your question simply:

If you were to put the $60k in an interest bearing vehicle, and that vehicle would pay you more than the interest charged by the loan, then, no you should not.

As the above is highly unlikely, you should pay off the debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That horse's name: Aragorn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your retirement benefits have been terminated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive anomaly lurks beneath ice in Antarctica - Could It Be Cthulhu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trainee bomb detector puppy shot dead at New Zealand airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paid for by Jason Chaffetz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, if irony were on the side of Christy Mack, the judge would impose a sentence for this POS that includes a tattoo which reads:

"Property of the State of Nevada"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can. 

We don't have the actual news story about either.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A young, and awesome, Charles Dance (Tywin Lannister) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol my concern is that x number of years from now my former mother-in-law will say "you know you still have my spoon" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it marrying a woman?

Do publicity stunts count?

You know...like this Reddit post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valet: "you can't park your car here"

HST: "is this not a perfectly acceptable place to park"

Valet: "you're on a sidewalk!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this hilarious because I have a spoon I *refuse* to use for anything.

It's a tablespoon different from all of my other spoons.

I have no idea where it came from.

And it sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMAO! Oh god YOU JUST **KNOW** at least one American read this and thought:

"Well duh! Of course imperial months convert to metric months"

Edit: full disclosure: I'm an American (with a sense of humor) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and Harrison Ford </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The owner of the truck is also missing commas to separate "where your from" in the sentence.

As correct usage of "you're" is beyond their grammar skill set, perhaps I'm kicking a man when he's down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a couple that has an open marriage. Both seemed happy when both were younger and could easily meet people.

As they've gotten older, her ability to sleep around has diminished and the open relationship is quickly losing its allure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the misconception.

I was a valet in high school/college.

As an adult I work in Finance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 05:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a person that lives in Philadelphia (the actual city, not the burbs) and did not always, allow me to give some insight on this issue:

Most would agree Schools, teacher salaries etc are typically funded by real estate taxes

Philadelphia is *legendarily* bad at collecting real estates taxes

Example: https://www.google.com/amp/www.phillymag.com/news/2015/04/15/paying-taxes-philadelphia-optional/%3Famp%3D1

Further, property values are either depressed or undervalued I.E. what taxes are received are far below what receipts should be

As a result, because nothing is paid in, nothing is paid out IE teachers get nothing because money still doesn't grow on trees.

Philadelphia as a city is WOEFULLY mismanaged from a fiscal perspective. Additionally, if you want to see the long term impact of one political party running everything, then look no further:

https://www.google.com/amp/www.phillymag.com/news/2016/11/19/donald-trump-philadelphia-democratic-party/%3Famp%3D1

I'm originally from NJ and the thing I say to everyone in Philly is, "In NJ we all know there is government corruption, but at least *we get something out of it.* In Philadelphia, no one is getting anything."


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) My family members were original founders of 2 counties in US in 1600s

2) I've saved people's lives twice (one from choking, the other from drowning)

3) I've driven Ferraris multiple times (as a valet, hence why it's douchey)

4) I have a genius level IQ (which is without a doubt, the *douchiest* thing anyone can ever say)

5) I eat out **every** meal of the day and have never used my stove.

Edit: number 5 for extra douchebaggery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always said CVS should package:

Tampons

Midol

Tissues

and chocolate

Together in a single box called "The Period Party Pack"


Almost there!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motherfucking SpaghettiOs!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Russian is weak to say the least, but I'm going to guess that's actually a liquor store based on the pictures of wine bottles next to the words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed this 10x more than the actual John Wick movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As funny as the main image is, I laughed my ass off at the Russian sign in the background that simply says "Products."

*And in Russia we shop at products store. It is having all life's needs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Resident Evil 4 on the Nintendo Wii**

IMO, This is the high point in the Resident Evil series 

Additionally, the Wii controls are vastly superior to the standard RE tank controls that can make it a frustrating console game.

**Bioshock**

A very original FPS with probably the best storyline of any game in its genre.

Bioshock 2 and Infinite are also great, but this game is an all time classic.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish the last line of your comment had been:

"Reddit sickens me"   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the luxury equivalent of living in a van down by the river! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My new favorite mashup! Replacing this:

https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=NN75im_us4k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally worth it if you also go up to the mountains outside of Matsumoto for a hike (monkeys there too, albeit running around and not in hot springs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This sex doll will make you feel inadequate in the sack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call the Comcast switchboard at headquarters in Philadelphia.

Tell them you want to speak with the "executive care team"

They will resolve your issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So either they won't share any scenes together OR Tom Cruise is getting Chinese leg lengthening surgery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's exactly the reason why Philosophy is considered a joke major in colleges: the belief that it's value is in opining on the unknowable to come to a specious conclusion simply because *logically* it makes sense.

I'm not saying it isn't interesting to discuss those topics, but one of the points of this article is for philosophers to show *meaningful progress* to questions around which *a consensus* is being built.

We who love philosophy can circle jerk all day about the intangibles of existence, but until we provide *actual* value to a conversation people care about, and stop trying to turn every disagreement into an elenchus/teaching opportunity, the entire concept of philosophy will remain either too abstract, or worse a joke, to an every day person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying a person can't abandon a belief system.

I'm saying me *trying to convince someone* to abandon their belief system **and succeeding** is unlikely as it is construed as an attack on their faith.

I know many people that have become more secular as they've aged, but I don't know a single one that ever said, "People making me constantly question my faith is why I became more secular"

It's usually something that just evolved out of personal experience.

I guess what I'm saying is, I would consider it unlikely that a person would change their beliefs strictly based upon a priori knowledge and theoretical discussion (as opposed to knowledge gleaned from life) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm by no means against teaching epistemology, *but* many of the challenges in our current political climate arise from secular vs. religious approaches.

No amount of discussion on epistemology is going to convert a person's belief system if that belief system is based on faith.

Net-net: I agree with your point in that epistemology is important, but that's probably only because I consider my own points of view to be justifiable.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a person that majored in Philosophy in college I wholeheartedly agree with this.

Even on Reddit, most of the Philosophy threads I see make the front page are stuck up posts that have *zero* bearing on modern life.

In our current times, ethical and political philosophy are the only "useful" areas of thought and should be frequently discussed.

If the people that *actually know* philosophy are sitting around debating topics like metaphysics, then *it is* our fault that philosophy is disappearing because we're essentially jerking ourselves off, saying "I'm so smart", and providing no direction toward **worthwhile** discourse for a regular person.

TL;DR -

Aristotle (ex.metaphysics), Hobbes, Locke, Mill, Kant - Yes

Descartes, Heidegger (Nazi), Wittgenstein - No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like buying a used VCR and finding the tape from The Ring still inside.

"Hmmmm, wonder what's on this tape..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a fellow lover of electronic music, but thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like those tracks, then there are free services on web that rip tracks from YouTube and convert to MP3.

The last 4 I suggested you can easily buy on iTunes but the other edits, as far as I am aware, are not able to purchased anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
