<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7923</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Americolor soft gel paste food coloring. You can get them a box of 12 colors from Amazon for relatively cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pierre Herme is sooo good. My idol! Thanks for the compliment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two posts ago I think? Don't sell. Just give away to lab mates  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 10:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol no way I'd be able to visualize how to paint them otherwise!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just really lazy and hate waiting. I haven't seen a noticable difference in their quality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I've failed so many batches as well. I am just finally getting a handle on them I think. Only took 2 years _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same username! subject7923 :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disappoint? lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very florally. The food coloring is tasteless :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be due to many many factors. Overmixing, undermixing, wrong temp of your oven, wrong ratio of almond flour to egg whites to sugar, humidity. BASICALLY, every variable can go wrong. lol. What does not macarony mean? Like exploded shell? That's from not resting long enough. If it completely collapsed on itself, could be multiple factors. Undermixing is sometimes my culprit. If it was thin and brittle, that's usually overmixing in my hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha are macarons eaten often? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. I ask myself the same question every time. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not supposed to be shiny though! Do you mean smooth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matcha is probs the most trendy hipster thing right now. Ube is upcoming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from a jank hometown so we never had these growing up. I went to college in LA and experienced them for the first time. SO GOOD. I was just a fatty dessert enjoyer until 2 years ago when I started running and figured I could start baking. Macarons were the second thing I tried tackling. Still trying to get good at them. Almost there :p.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> someone posted this earlier! so cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who says I wouldn't steal a car :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But actually tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just normal gel food coloring :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd have to be one eating them :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I question my life choices some times haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just normal gel food coloring :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saddest part is that I started baking at like 9pm on Sunday. Didn't finish pictures/ clean up until like 4:30am. #dempriorities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. They did temporarily stain your mouth with the food coloring :p. SO maybe not the most advisable for a wedding lol. I felt bad for my friend who ate the black macaron lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. I mean, my lab mates get free desserts at least once a week :p. Actually sometimes more than that because there are three bakers in the lab. Yeee. #somuchsugar. And yeah, I spend way too much time on figures when I make presentations or apply to grants. When my paper comes out, it's going to be beautiful! lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right?! How is a baker supposed to figure out new stuff to do! :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't you heard, yo-yos are making a resurgence! Idk actually. But I did love yo-yos in 5th and 6th grade :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Well to be 100% honest, I wanted them to be just rose. But I added way too much rose water, so to counteract, I added in some horchata extract (yeah, it's a think..doesn't super taste like it tho). So mostly, the ganache was florally, but subtle notes of horchata. :p. An horchata ganache could easily be done though. Just incorporate that flavor into the cream before adding to the white chocolate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, it's food coloring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was totally my struggle throughout lol. Wanted to rage quit multiple times :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha buttercreams are too sweet! My preference is usually fruit flavors and curds :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels bad if you eat one directly from this set up. BUT, if they're all just in a box and you don't have the context, it's much easier :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmkay. Recipe is below. A few things: I'm actually only going to give you the recipe for 10 macarons. I scaled it up by 2.5x to have enough macarons for this. Also, I suck at ganaches. I always split them so maybe following my recipe for that isn't the best. I think my issue is that the cream is too hot when I add it to the white chocolate. Just a head's up. (Normally recipes will tell you heat up cream and pour that over chopped up chocolate.)    
 nbsp;    
**Macaron Shells:**  *For about 10 1.5 inch macarons:*  
46 g almond flour (sift, no big almond pieces)  
43 g powdered sugar    
35 g egg whites (room temp)  
25 g granulated sugar  
 nbsp;  
1. Oven to 325F. Measure out and sift your powdered sugar and almond flour. Whisk together and set aside.  
2. Make your meringue. I speed warm up my egg whites by putting them in a small container and then putting that container in a bowl with hot water. Takes about 5 min to bring up the temp and doesn't cook them.  
Beat/ whisk your egg whites until frothy and start to incorporate the granulated sugar a bit a time. Beat until stiff peaks.   
3. Macaronage. Look up on Youtube if you're unfamiliar on how to do so.   
Fold about half your dry ingredients into the meringue until just incorporated and then add the rest and continue folding until just incorporated. Now would be the time to add food coloring. Gel or powder, not liquid. Fold until you get a lava like consistency. Fold by scraping along the edge of the bowl to deflate the meringue a bit and then scooping the batter. Repeat. You should be able to pick up the spatula and have the batter fall down in a ribbon. The ribbon should incorporate back into the main blob after about 10ish seconds. If it doesn't fall correctly, I do a few more folds. Put into a piping bag with a tip.  
4. Pipe out your macarons. I use a silpat (would highly recommend). Rap the baking sheet against the table a few times.  Pop any air bubbles with a toothpick and swirl the toothpick around a bit to have that hole close up.     
5. I hate waiting for the shells to dry, so I cheat and dry the shells using the oven heat. I do this by opening the oven and holding the tray in the oven, rotating it every 10 seconds or so for about a minute. My hands usually get hot at that point. I take them out for about a minute. Then back in again, rotating, for another 30 seconds. This quickly dries out the shells and makes a skin without having to wait 30 minutes at room temp (especially if it's humid!) :p.   
You want to be able to touch the shell and have it not be sticky. Make sure it doesn't shine and you're probably good to go.   
6. Bake for 9 minutes at 315 and drop to 300 for another 9 minutes. (The macarons worked out well using these parameters, but all ovens are different, so you have to do a bit of your own troubleshooting .)  
 nbsp;  
**Horchata Rose Ganache**          
60 g white chocolate  
30 g heavy cream  
a few dashes of rose water  
a few dashes of horchata extract  
 nbsp;  
1. First of all, yes I know the horchata extract (vs legit horchata) is a sell out. But I had it, so I used it :p.  
2. Put the white chocolate over a double boiler and mostly melt. Take off double boiler when there are a few unmelted pieces remaining.  
3. Heat cream, rose water, and horchata extact in a small saucepan until it reduces to about 20ish ml. If you wanted to use some horchata mixure that would also work. (for my 25 macarons, I used 125 g white chocolate and 40 g cream I think..but ran out at the end and had to fill some very skimpily).  
4. Let cream cool a bit and then add into the white chocolate mixture.  
5. Fold together and transfer to a piping bag and chill for a short while to firm up before piping onto the macaron shells.  
 nbsp;  
***Notes on Painting:***  
1. I used normal Americolor gel food coloring and a paint brush set I use for desserts. I used a big plate as a palette.    
2. My diluent was vodka because it evaporates quickly and causes it to be less sticky than if you use water.  
3. Check out http://imgur.com/a/GLCu9 for progress pictures. You can sort of get a sense of what I did.  
4. I made a template for how I wanted to set it up on Photoshop. This served as my "grid" as a painted them.  
5. I started with a base coat on lots of them with a diluted food coloring. Then went back using less diluted food coloring to make brush strokes.  
 nbsp;  
Overall, was pretty, but a lot of work. As a one off thing, this is pretty chill, but I would never wish this pain upon someone doing this on a regular basis :p.  
If anything, make the macarons because they're tasty!  
Gluck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here are progress pictures] (http://imgur.com/a/GLCu9) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9/10. pretty good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll post recipe later. And I will also upload the progress pics/ the template I made on photoshop. In terms of the painting, it's really just taking the time to paint a layer, switch to a different macaron, and repeat. I set up the blank macarons and had my laptop so I could view the template.  My Clean Bandit playlist helped keep me motivated. haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I hadn't painted for a long time. So there's that. Also, I wasn't sure how to use gel food coloring as a media..I was initially diluting it to a watercolor consistency. Except with that, I didn't know how I'd replicate the brush strokes... Then I tried using it more like acrylic paint, which was okayish. But yes. Just painting took about 3.5 hrs _. I was angry the whole time hahah. (It was also almost midnight when I started :p) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol not sure. I wouldn't wish this on any baker though. haha. Too painful. It would probably be easier to just have a grid of macarons all touching and paint them like that. I wanted a bit of depth/ some on their sides so decided to set it up like that. I do sometimes wonder how much I'd charge, though I haven't really done a cost calculation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMGAH. that's magical! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :3 thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! and haha. That's what all my labmates said. It's slightly easier to eat when you don't know the context of it though :p.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week I made raspberry swirl macarons and my friend said it reminded her of The Great Wave off Kanagawa..which got me thinking maybe I could totally do that..or other paintings as well. And thus, the Starry Night. The macarons, themselves, are horchata rose flavored :p. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Starry night Macarons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Spookychilies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
