<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6420</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just throw my literal army of animals and just shoot the thing to death. Works every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/ShittyLifeProTips  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can probably add Auckland to the list as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The disapproval on his face is palpable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also cringe when they put the brand not as Pokemon but as Pokemon Go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word 'tomorrow' was a nightmare to type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in my day if we wanted to find where a street was, we had to look it up in a book. Then we memorized the route and then drove there. We didn't have any of those fancy GBS or your Gugle Maps. We had to work to get to where we wanted to go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blah Blah Real joke Blah Blah comments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colony McColonface </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can feel the salt running through your veins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure they said they detected academic misconduct or something like that which includes cheating in 10% of the exams. So not even straight up cheating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry. I saw a Dragonite in my radar when I was in the car on my way to work. I wasn't driving so I had to let it go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which Ouroboros are you talking about? There one I could find was one by the creator of Binding of Isaac but it doesn't look very NSFW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more bothered by the fact that they tried to lie and pretend the wipe didn't happen and only come clean once they realised the lie didn't stick. Had they done pretty much anything else, it wouldn't have bothered me as much. For me, the only thing worse that they could have done would be to end the series right then. They could have addressed the reload the day they released the video or with the video itself; they could have accepted the wipe and gone with a B team; they would have worked the wipe and reload into the story i.e. "it was all a dream", or like when they played Road to Boruto with the "Man, it would suck if it went like that", or maybe some time travel alternate dimension shenanigans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, Scott likes strong trainers so he probably just moved on to the next promising trainer. Probably Brendan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thought actually had occurred to me when I was rewatching it. I never knew it was a fan theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THAT'S A GIRL? I thought the one with a raven was a guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This goes on a lot in China as well. We took the flowers off the stems to arrange it around prettily. Some people just tear the flowers up a bit and scatter petals around the grave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that's why I don't have many friends, I have been smart all along and they were just jealous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
