<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8764</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 20:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I still think it sucks. I'd understand the idea of passing the ball if you didn't have one timeout left. You run on second down and if you don't get in, call timeout. Pass on third down and on a potential fourth down, you have the Patriots playing the ultimate guessing game. 

It's no guarantee Seattle gets in from there - see the Packers/Seahawks game - but your best player needs to touch the ball at least once in that final stretch of plays. Add in the fact Lynch almost got in from the 6 and it's even bigger no-brainer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 20:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. If Tony Romo threw that pass, Twitter would have broken down .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 05:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Promise kept.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 03:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the first time I watched Virginia this year. Very impressive team that definitely is on the short list of teams for Kentucky to watch out for. Bennett is a great basketball coach and the way that team plays together is fun to watch. Nice rebound win after a tough loss against Duke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 00:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Judging quarterbacks by rings is stupid. No one talks about the game-winning drive he should have had against the Giants in the first Super Bowl. He's been in my Top 2 since 2008-09 with Montana. 

And for what it's worth, the talking heads on ESPN would not be positive on him today if the Seahawks don't blow that game late.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 22:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Triangle and 2 defense he ran on North Carolina in the 2012 Elite Eight is up there in his best moves. Roy Williams looked lost in the second half trying to adjust to that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 21:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't match last night, but Popovich's decision to sit Duncan late in Game 6 in the 2013 Finals was bad. He's the greatest power forward ever and one rebound ends that series. The Spurs coming back to win it in 2014 kind of softens this mistake, but that was a bad move, especially coming from one of the three best NBA coaches ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 09:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Bevell's play-calling could have been more physical too by handing the ball off to one of the best short-yardage backs in the NFL. He may be right about the wide receiver, but it's pitiful blaming him for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 09:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the "everyone is against us" mentality a lot of Boston fans seem to have. They complained for years and years about being cursed about the Red Sox, while Celtics, Bruins and Patriots were winning championships.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 09:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The argument about the salary cap era also benefits Montana in a way. Those great defenses he faced in the NFC - the Giants, Bears, Redskins and Eagles - remained the same. They benefited greatly from continuity and being in the same system all those years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 09:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brady is the best of this generation/era for sure. He will be unless Aaron Rodgers can get two or three more rings. 

All-time, I still prefer Joe Montana. This is no criticism of Brady, but Montana played in an era where defensive lineman could hit the quarterback as hard as they wanted. Montana played in an era where defensive backs could be physical with wide receivers. Rod Woodson once said Dan Marino would throw for 100,000 yards in this era with these rules. 

I don't like the idea of rings validating a player. In my eyes, Tom Brady's legacy would not have changed one bit if the Pats lost tonight. But for those who want to do rings, Montana was 4-0 in the Super Bowl and never threw an interception. Brady has now thrown four and it took him three attempts to win ring #4. Montana, while having great talent at the end of his tenure in San Francisco, won his first two Super Bowls without Jerry Rice. If you look back at his first Super Bowl team, it was not exactly stacked. 

Montana and Brady both benefited from great coaches, so that part of the debate is out the window in my opinion. 

I'll take Montana, but Brady definitely deserves to be at the table in this debate. It's down to those two, in my opinion, and you cannot go wrong with either. I just prefer the guy who played in a tougher era for quarterbacks. But I think those who say this debate is definitely over are incorrect. Both sides have great arguments and the answer lies in what you value more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 08:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he was going back to Seattle before tonight, but I'm 50/50 on him staying there or going back home to Oakland. Not getting the ball in that moment is a bitter pill to swallow. 

I don't really know, but I do think the chances of him leaving tonight increased.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 05:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep....how crazy is it the Cowboys had only the third cruelest loss of this postseason? Any of those four are memorable losses and now they're just footnotes compared to Seattle and Green Bay. I still think Green Bay's was the worst considering all the missed chances, mistakes, ect. This was just one bad play-call.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 05:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When looking at it historically, I think it's in the Top 3 of worst Super Bowl losses - up there with the 18-1 Pats and the Norwood Bills. There's a reason Marshawn Lynch is called "Beast Mode." I think it's the worst call in Super Bowl history for sure. What's even more interesting is I wonder if the Pats would have conceded the score on the ground to save time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 19:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they have the talent for sure, but I still think Jim Caldwell holds them back. His conservatism makes Mike McCarthy like like Don Coryell. Lost in that officiating controversy was the fact Caldwell's coaching performance was very bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 21:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patriots fans will still find a way to claim Woodson is disrespecting Brady.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Kansas Libertarian Lt. Governor candidate says integrating direct primary care would help state save money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 07:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 05:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's unknown about the Patriots having deflated balls, but it's clear that Richard Sherman has brass balls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 01:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious if this is Chad Ford doing this or ESPN doing this. Ford, I believe, is one of the ESPN Insiders. That's a premium subscription deal. If ESPN edits his draft boards, they can promote it as "the most accurate" draft board on the Internet. Thus, they could make it easier to sell subscriptions to ESPN. 

It'll be interesting if someone tries to dig up Kiper and draft boards from other sports.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 23:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seattle's owner is not a buddy of Goodell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 23:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We are not the New England Patriots." ---- ISIS statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 00:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say SF/SEA in 2013. It did not have the craziness of SEA/GB or even MIN/NO, but I thought both teams played a very good game, turnovers aside. It was the climax of one of the league's best rivalries and it was damn good game. I also think it's clear those were the two best teams in the league.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 00:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barnwell is learning well from Bill Simmons. Both are great writers and intelligent, but both are incredibly thin-skinned as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 06:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Payton believes Belichick should be suspended a full year without pay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 06:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I don't get is why the Patriots did this. They have absolutely owned Indianapolis since Peyton Manning left there. Indy was one of the weakest "Final Four" teams I can remember in a while. This is the sports equivalent of Nixon trying to sabotage a very weak field of Democratic candidates with the Watergate scandal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 03:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's hoping one of New England's punishments would be banning TV networks from showing Robert Kraft 1,240 times during a game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 02:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both defenses stepped up for sure, especially Seattle's for keeping Green Bay out of the end-zone. I think Seattle beats Green Bay at least 7 out of 10 times if they play on a neutral field considering the Hawks played a terrible, terrible game on offense and still won.

But the narrative is rightfully placed on Green Bay's feet. I cannot recall a championship game where one team or coach missed so many opportunities. Green Bay kicks a field goal two times after a drive stalled inside the two. Most coaches go for it at least once. A Green Bay defender slides and gives up a potential "pick 6" or at least better field position. Aaron Rodgers throws two bad interceptions, including one to Richard Sherman in the end-zone. Bad decision. The onside kick. The screw-up on the two-point possession. The play-calling late in the game. Green Bay's defensive meltdown late in the 4th quarter and early overtime. 

I think Seattle is the better team and they're my pick two weeks from now, but Green Bay choked. Sorry. This is a game they had to win based on Wilson's 4 interceptions. But Mike McCarthy had his "Grady Little Game" on Sunday. If McCarthy did not win a ring already, he may have been fired today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 10:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile, Mike McCarthy coached with deflated balls during the NFC Championship Game. 

EDIT: Thanks for the gold! And sorry, Packers fans. It reminded me of Gruden's conservative coaching in the Tuck Rule Game and the year before against Baltimore. Hang in there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 08:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked New England and New Orleans, so half right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 08:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one of the two or three most devastating losses I've seen an NFL team take in the playoffs. There were about 10 plays where if just one went the Packers' direction, they win. I can't remember a game that had as many heroes and goats as this one did. And in the case of Russell Wilson, a goat becoming a hero.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 07:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seahawks. Nothing against the Patriots, but I love the way they play with emotion, especially BEAST mode and the Legion of Boom. Plus, I enjoy the irrational hatred most NFL fans have for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 07:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though they were division rivals back in the day, I actually like Seattle. These Seahawks and the defense they play are not supposed to happen thanks to the rulebook being so slanted in favor of quarterbacks and the offense. Them repeating, especially beating Manning and Brady in back-to-back years, has to secretly piss off Goodell and the other NFL owners who want high scoring games.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 01:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Russell Wilson is a capable quarterback who knows how to throw? Part of the Tebow backlash was everyone, particularly Skip Bayless, for promoting him even though it was clear he was a bad quarterback.

Entering today, Wilson had the highest quarterback ranking in postseason history. I think that's one of the big reasons why Wilson doesn't get the "hate" Tebow does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 01:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game this reminded me of was the San Diego/New England playoff game from 2007. San Diego controlled that game most of the way and should have won. But dumb coaching and dumb mistakes from individual players cost them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 10:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 2015....why are there even prostitution stings, any way? Just seems like a waste of resources and law enforcement manpower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 09:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good scene. Watching Season 1 again after you know the twists involving Rudy/Brian is fun. There are some fun things to look for when rewatching it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 22:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LeBron James and Kobe Bryant might have the flash, the points and the marketability, but this is why Tim Duncan is the best player in the post-Jordan era in my opinion. 

The guy took less salary to keep San Antonio a contender. He took less of a role to benefit his team. He's the most coachable superstar perhaps in NBA history. There are middle-school level games with him. He just wins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hospitals hope Kansas will follow recent red-state trend on Medicaid expansion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 11:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 23:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fact: This guy won a conference title with Jake Delhomme at the QB position and a playoff game with Tim Tebow as a starter. I get that Fox was conservative and he wasn't a great coach. But if a Denver cornerback doesn't make an all-time boner of a play against the Ravens two years ago, Fox might have made two Super Bowls in four years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 23:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing. Both coaches I'm sure had flaws....but when "Super Bowl or get fired" is the criteria, this league is getting out of control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 04:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the two keys to this game is how Ohio State handles Oregon's pace on offense and if Urban Meyer and his staff commits to the run. They dirty secret in Oregon's blowout win against Florida State is that FSU was running the ball very well before the melted down in the 3rd quarter. 

Not taking away from Oregon's staff, but I think Meyer will coach a terrific game. My gut opinion is he'll commit to the run, control the line of scrimmage and grind it out. I think this ends up similar to the first UA/UO game and it's a lower scoring game than most think. 

Ohio State 28, Oregon 24.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 03:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traffic might be backed up in New Jersey tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 02:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New England/Seattle. Seattle having the chance to beat both Manning and Brady in a Super Bowl would be a fantastic story. If they did that and held Brady in check, that defense would have a legit argument as the best ever. The Bears and Ravens defenses beat bad quarterbacks in Super Bowls. Seattle would have knocked off the two best in the post-Elway/Marino era.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 01:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps, but let's say they win that Super Bowl against Baltimore. I would imagine tensions would be considerably less if they won a Lombardi. I could be 100 percent wrong, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 01:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one of the great what-if's in recent NFL history. Do the Niners' win at least one Super Bowl? Does Harbaugh stay there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 00:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call by the officials there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 00:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Fox is going to get fired if Denver loses this game, but most of the blame deserves to be placed on Manning and the Broncos offense. No urgency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 00:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Arkansas was very solid up front this season. Good things are happening there for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 00:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bielema's track record with offensive lineman going back to his Wisconsin time is impressive. Not surprised a talented lineman would want to play there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 22:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was Tuck Rule II in my opinion. Technically the "Right" call, but an absolutely garbage rule. Three moves and a dive for the end-zone = football move in my mind. If that's not a catch, I don't know what's supposed to be a catch. 

That said, Aaron Rodgers was phenomenal in the second half. It shouldn't take away from the game he had the Packers would have had 3 minutes left to respond.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How will the Chiefs replace all those touchdowns he had this year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 02:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this Tweet from Bill Simmons: https://twitter.com/BillSimmons/status/551903885778903040 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 02:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so sorry, Detroit fans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 11:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "College" from the first season of The Sopranos. That is the episode that got me hooked. "Pine Barrens" was stellar, but if you asked me to pick an episode of the show to make someone a fan, I'd select that one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 18:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If laughing makes me a bad guy, I'm a bad guy. 

They were not making fun of rape or the woman who was raped. They were taunting Jameis Winston and made fun of one of the single dumbest chants in sports. I thought it was funny and clever. Sue me. 

Plus, a side bonus: It indirectly brought attention to the case and how the Tallahassee Police Department screwed up the investigation. That was not the reason they did it, but it brought the subject back up and it's worthy to discuss. 

I find it fascinating that these kids will receive more punishment for this than Winston received for this entire investigation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 22:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations to Minnesota on a great season! Kill is doing good things at that program and I hope to see him stay there for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 00:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fair point. This is hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 23:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I think he's trying to get his way on something, whether it's David Blatt or a roster move.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 23:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or....he is being Machiavellian and sending a message about the coach/franchise? He and Wade probably talk regularly. He knew those cameras were there. I think this was intentional and not some "slip up" that was discovered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 23:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the NBA equivalent of the Zapruder film. I've watched it seven times already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 00:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al had his issues, but he doesn't deserve to be included in a comparison with York. Al made a lot of bold hires in his hay-day and actually did win three Super Bowls. York ran off the best coach the Niners had since Bill Walsh. (Sorry, but Siefert was asked to not wreck a corvette.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 09:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Season 5 gets a bad wrap from a lot Dexter fans, though not necessarily here. I like the idea of him helping out Lumen as a way to exorcise his own demons about losing Rita. I liked the Lumen storyline and as someone who had a good friend raped violently years ago, I enjoyed it each time one of those guys were murdered. 

I do hate the cop out they did with Deb at the end, but still a solid season that's above Season 6, Season 7, Season 8 and in my opinion, Season 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 08:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A wild thought I had....one I doubt would actually happen, but worth bringing up. 

How about the other Harbaugh? Lost in the whole Ray Rice scandal was apparently a rift developing between the Ravens front office and the Harbaugh in terms of how to handle the Rice situation. The Ravens and John Harbaugh denied, of course. 

But if the Raiders are willing to fork over $9 million to Jim Harbaugh, why not John Harbaugh? He's won a Super Bowl championship and outside of one year, he's made the playoffs every season he's coached. Even though they made the playoffs, that team is not as good as it was just a few years. No Ray Lewis. I think Flacco has proven to be unworthy of that contract. 

If he comes to Oakland, he'd have a ton of cap space to work with. Derek Carr is young and performed well in stretches during his rookie season. There's young talent and some veterans on that defense. 

I doubt it happens....but why not throw the kitchen sink at John? There'd be compensation for him in the form of picks, but as long as it's not the #1 pick, let's consider it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 04:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think for one year, it's very possible. When Bill Callahan took over the Raiders team, the Raiders improved and made it to the Super Bowl. I think this situation is very similar to the Gruden/Al Davis fallout. That fallout distracted the Raiders during the '01 season. I think the same thing happened this year to you guys. If you hire the right coach, I would not be surprised at all to see the 49ers get back to the postseason. 

However, my concern is the long-term ramifications of this move. Like Harbaugh, Gruden took over a bad situation and made it well with a combination of veterans and younger players. After that one great season under Callahan, the bottom fell out quickly and the Raiders haven't been back since. 

Now, Al was losing it in his final years, so that contributed to the downfall. But the 49ers better have a plan and bring in a credible coach. Josh McDaniels does not fit that bill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 23:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Simmons is speculating about this same scenario right now on Twitter. I don't see it happening, but it does open the door up for this scenario.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 23:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It honestly reminds me of when Al Davis and Jon Gruden had their falling out. It's probably the best comparison considering Gruden turned around a dump of a franchise. Gruden wanted more money and power and similarly, there were leaks during Chucky's last season. 

If the comparison holds out, the 49ers will have ONE winning season in the next 13 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 18:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this ends up bad, I wonder if they make a run at Calipari again after the NCAA season. I've read him and LeBron are tight and when Kentucky wins the title this season, Calipari would have accomplished just about everything he could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 07:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am. I think they beat Dallas in the NFC title game to get revenge from this season's loss and I think they'll beat Pittsburgh in the Super Bowl to get revenge on that screw job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 06:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking a Pittsburgh-Seattle Super Bowl, with the Seahawks repeating. Don't know the exact path, but those are the two teams that are playing the best right now in my eyes. I think we'll have a Steelers-Patriots AFC title game and a Seahawks-Cowboys NFC title game. Romo gets the big game monkey off his back, but falls just a bit short in Seattle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 06:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 49ers are stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 06:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pardon the dumb tinfoil like thinking here, but would Jim Harbaugh have been fired if you guys were still waiting to get a new stadium? They gotta know most of the 49ers fans HATE this move. Just find the timing curious. Reminds me of the Miami Marlins fiasco.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 04:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone not as good. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you generally, but the 49ers were horrible in the eight years prior to him. He won more games the past four years. His 8-8 record this season was the best record the Niners had during the Harbaugh stretch. 

It's not impossible for this to turn out OK, but it sure looks bad forcing him out now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pretty clear York or the GM were leaking that information. They were setting up the narrative for this all season.

I hope there's an epilogue that includes Jim Harbaugh's side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Jerry Jones. Jones is still getting crap for firing Jimmy Johnson after two Super Bowls and some older Dallas fans still hate him for firing Landry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Sad Sunday in San Francisco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saban is a defacto dictator at Alabama. He's not going into that mess, especially after a very successful head coach was fired. 

The only way I see Saban leaving Alabama is for a ton of cash and a ton of power, but even then I doubt it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't feel bad for Harbaugh in the slightest. His life is still pretty good. 

That said, I do hate this move because it's clear he was being forced out after three 12-win seasons, three NFC title game appearances and 1 Super Bowl appearance. It sends a bad signal to coaches out there and the fact it appears the players and fans really liked him speaks volumes about the arrogance of those running the organization.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 02:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Raiders have had three 12-win seasons and 6 postseason wins in my lifetime since I was born in 1985. Jim Harbaugh had three 12-win seasons in San Francisco and five postseason victories in four years there. 

Such a dumb move by a franchise that was on the rise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> COMMENTARY: On marijuana legalization, Kansas should stay out of Colorado's business </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 03:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 13:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll only jump recruiting wise. I think that's a given with Harbaugh's track record and what Michigan football is about. 

What I'm curious about is the potential domino effect this has on the quality of conferences. I've long believed the single biggest reason the SEC became what it was is coaching. This started with Steve Spurrier at Florida, then picked up when Nick Saban was hired at LSU, Urban Meyer going to Florida, Mark Richt at Georgia (I know he hasn't won it all, but still a great record), Les Miles to LSU, Saban to 'Bama, ect. The SEC is what it is because of coaching. I don't necessarily buy the "warm weather means everything" argument. I think Nick Saban would win if he coached college football in New York City, Iowa, Idaho, ect. Oregon, Ohio State, Wisconsin and Missouri have all had 12-win seasons the past decade and they're in the cold. It's about coaching and vision of a program. 

I think the Big 10 could be back if Michigan hires Harbaugh. Ohio State with Urban Meyer is very, very good. I like James Franklin to turn Penn State around down the road. Mark Dantonio has Michigan State playing great football. I actually think Mike Riley could be better than many think at Nebraska. Kill's doing some very nice things at Minnesota. I also think Harbaugh and Meyer will force programs to up their games and make big time hires. I could see Iowa making a run at Bielema, for example, in the next few years. Saban's presence in the SEC made the other schools ante to sign coaches and to keep them. 

If Harbaugh lands at Michigan, the Big 10 profile will benefit in a big way. It'll still take a while to overtake the SEC, but the gap would close considerably with Harbaugh at Michigan. 

That, and the Ohio State-Michigan-Michigan State triumvirate will make for some awesome rivalries and recruiting battles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 12:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Find a way to get Amare Cooper. Draft analysts are saying he's the best wide receiver to come out since Megatron. 

2. Land Jim Harbaugh. It sounds like Harbaugh's going to Michigan, but I still have this little doubt in my head he's using Michigan as a way to get out of San Francisco without a trade. 

3. Land one more pass rusher. This helps Mack as well. 

4. Some luck. It's rare to go from three wins to 11 or 12. I think a proven coach, a good coaching staff and a wide out can get this team to 6-8 wins. By luck, perhaps Peyton Manning retires?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 08:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call. For some reason, this slipped my mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 06:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both Denver (14-2) and Green Bay (11-5) were really good in 1998. Green Bay lost on a last second touchdown pass against San Francisco (Yes, Rice fumbled on the drive) and Denver repeated. In its division, Green Bay also had a historically great Vikings team that's one of the two or three best teams to never win a Super Bowl. Packers didn't win the division, but they were still pretty good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 02:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but I'm just pointing out the memory card. Maybe it comes out that Dar was behind the release of that video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 08:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more libertarian than Republican, but here goes:

Equating the Religious Right to the Taliban or some other Islamic extremist group is one of the dumbest arguments ever. I say this as a person critical of the Religious Rights' view points and I think the government should stay out of marriage as a whole. 

But the worst Christians in America are still far and away more acceptable to Western Society than Islamic radicals are. Some Christians may loathe the homosexual lifestyle, but you it's policy to punish homosexuals by death in 10 countries in the Middle East/Africa. The common theme? Islam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 08:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The I know many Dexter fans were happy she was killed off, but this is the reason why I wish she would lived a little longer: her reaction to finding out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
