<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4276</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so is it vague?  Reading an article should also help any doubts to what the subject means, preferably before commenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hazardous chemicals go unregulated in routine oil and gas operations . Chemical regulations that govern hydraulic fracturing do not apply to numerous other uses of the same chemicals on oil- and gas-development fields </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most of the Sunday news shows failed to cover the worldwide March for Science protests, an international demonstration partly meant to draw attention to President Donald Trumps disregard for evidence-based knowledge and climate change denial. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most of the Sunday news shows failed to cover the worldwide March for Science protests, an international demonstration partly meant to draw attention to President Donald Trumps disregard for evidence-based knowledge and climate change denial. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ENVIRONMENT Almost Half of Trump Voters Want the U.S. to Stay in the Paris Climate Agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we have so proof that you are indeed a former oil and gas professional like you say? No disrespect but its very easy for some people to discredit a subject pretending to be or know something. Anyone else an oil or gas professional who can prove this study or evidence is fake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hazardous chemicals go unregulated in routine oil and gas operations. Chemical regulations that govern hydraulic fracturing do not apply to numerous other uses of the same chemicals on oil- and gas-development fields </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Internet addiction affects as many as one in eight Americans. It is associated as a compulsive activity involving excessive use, withdrawal and negative repercussions including social isolation, lying, low achievement and fatigue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senators seek data on Americans caught up in surveillance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 12:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camarillo tied a heat record of 91 degrees on Friday as Ventura County sizzled under unseasonably high temperatures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 12:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 1978 Several hundred American Indian activists and supporters march for five months from San Francisco to Washington, D.C., to protest threats to tribal lands and water rights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time ever, the network of streams, ponds, and lakes across Antarctica's surface have been mapped, and the extent of the water flow is worrying to scientists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UCLA-led research has found that students in a college mathematics course experienced a phenomenon similar to repression, the psychological process in which people forget emotional or traumatic events to protect themselves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about mindfulness based therapy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your opinion on EFT and how it affects your own thoughts and beliefs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Just Breached the 410 PPM Threshold for CO2. Scientists project that the monthly average will peak near 407 ppm in May, setting a monthly record. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your saying the link i showed you is all false. Right,  get back to me when you can provide evidence which backs your claims up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who downvote or do not believe in any of the issues raised including climate change, and science,  do you think by supporting a political ideology makes you exempt from any of the effects it has caused and will cause? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your saying all of those statistics are untrue. Including the research done by behavioural scientists. Can i ask,  do you have any evidence which can back up your claims. Preferably by professionals who have covered this topic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The longer one experiences unemployment in the United States, the more likely they are to report symptoms of psychological unease, according to a recent Gallup poll. The poll also found that one in five Americans without a job for a year or more report that they have been or are currently undergoing treatment for depression. This is roughly double the rate of depression among those who have been without a job for fewer than five weeks. 

According to research reported in the Journal of Vocational Behavior, unemployed people are twice as likely as employed people to suffer from psychological problems (34 percent to 16 percent). Blue-collar workers are more distressed by unemployment than those who've lost a white-collar job. Additionally, middle-aged men and women, especially those who are unemployed, experience the highest levels of psychological distress.

http://www.healthline.com/health/depression/job-loss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmm so  getting a divorce or losing your job wouldn't cause depression. Can you explain why that would be the case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Learned helplessness is a condition in which a person suffers from a sense of powerlessness, arising from a traumatic event or persistent failure to succeed. It is thought to be one of the underlying causes of depression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research at Oregon State University empirically demonstrates that a variety of mechanisms for engaging nature significantly contribute to a persons overall well-being. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Water Shortage A Concern With 34% Of Florida In Severe Drought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A topic which is quite interesting. This article shows how terrorists are using the current climate to their advantage, enabling them  to spread more harm on people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boko Haram terrorists thriving on climate crisis. As farming and pastoral livelihoods suffer, the legitimacy of state governments has eroded and the region has become a ripe recruiting ground for Islamic extremism and the illicit trades in drugs, arms and people that sustain it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hottest April ever recorded. Larkana remained hottest place in the country where mercury rose as high as 50 C ( 122 F). Experts predict further increase in the intensity of heat wave due to abundance of sunshine and lack of significant rains. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heatwave claims nearly 40 lives in Telangana. Heat wave conditions hottest at 45 deg C ( 113 F ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March for Science: Trumps environmental policies turn scientists to political activists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study suggests that colder and less sunny regions of the world have higher rates of alcoholic cirrhosis, a disease caused by excessive drinking which results in irreversible scarring of the liver. Europe is the heaviest drinking region in the world in terms of the prevalence of alcohol consumption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just viewing super-size meals can promote overeating. Studies show that the more food there is on a plate, the more someone is likely to eat. Nutritionists call that the portion size effect. It doesnt matter what kind of food it is. It also doesnt matter what age or sex the diner is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient stone carvings confirm that a comet struck the Earth around 11,000BC, a devastating event which wiped out wooly mammoths and sparked the rise of civilisations. The markings suggest that a swarm of comet fragments hit Earth at the exact same time that a mini-ice age struck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ahead of Earth Day, most Americans pessimistic about environments future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump says he is great friends with opera legend Pavarotti, who has been dead 10 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Dutch court ordered prosecutors to open an investigation on Thursday into whether a Shell, Exxon joint venture bears any criminal responsibility for earthquakes triggered by production at the country's largest gas field. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research finds colour photos of bloody scenes elicit disgust, which colours jurors decisions. A crime-scene photograph can provide jurors with useful information  or evoke a visceral reaction that biases them in favour of conviction. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Debt among over-65s to pass 100bn in 6 years, research finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research underlines positive impact of press freedom on stock markets. Free press is not only good for the overall economy but is an essential part of democratic societies and policymakers should encourage an independent and fair press </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Sends the World Muddled Messages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to  1.3 million Americans  who lost their homes due to foreclosure as lenders and loan companies repossessed mortgaged properties when the borrowers failed to keep up their mortgage payments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The cost of the financial crises in 2008 cost $2,800,000,000,000 ( $2.8 tn ) to the worlds financial institutions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which explains how legalising drugs may lead to some dire situations with some people. The article provides some interesting analysis and statistics on the subject.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I used to support legalising all drugs. Then the opioid epidemic happened. Americas worst drug crisis shows what can happen when a dangerous, addictive substance is made easily accessible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boko Haram terrorists thriving on climate crisis. As farming and pastoral livelihoods suffer, the legitimacy of state governments has eroded and the region has become a ripe recruiting ground for Islamic extremism and the illicit trades in drugs, arms and people that sustain it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old are you may i ask? Do you have anyone close to you, family/friends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Literally Wants to Read Your Thoughts. Facebook wants to build its own brain-to-computer interface that would allow us to send thoughts straight to a computer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you not being given any help off an agency/professionals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ensuring water security is becoming an urgent task for Vietnam in the context of climate change impacting all aspects of life, heard a conference on Wednesday. River water and ground water levels are decreasing, while sea levels, flood tides and salt intrusion are on the rise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surge in bets for Jeremy Corbyn to become Britain's next Prime Minister </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump accused of 'shocking ignorance' as he repeats Chinese claim that Korea was part of China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research showing almost one in four young Australians are likely to have a serious mental health problem. The findings confirm that mental illness is one of the biggest challenges of the 21st century, and one that has to be tackled by the community, health services and families </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The findings refute the theory that the brain always behaves optimally. How the brain adjusts learning, has long been thought to be driven by the brain's reward system and its goal of optimizing rewards obtained from the environment or by a more cognitive system responsible for learning the structure of the environment.

Synapses are the connections between neurons in the brain and are responsible for transferring information from one neuron to the next. When it comes to choice in evaluating potential rewards, your learned value of a particular option, reflecting how much you like something, is stored in certain synapses. If you get positive feedback after choosing a particular option, the brain increases the value of that option by making the associated synapses stronger. In contrast, if the feedback is negative, those synapses become weaker. Synapses, however, can also undergo modifications without changing how they transmit information through a process called metaplasticity.

Previous studies have suggested that the brain relies on a dedicated system for monitoring the uncertainty in the environment to adjust its rate of learning. The authors of this study found however, that metaplasticity alone is sufficient to fine-tune learning according to the uncertainty about reward in a given environment.

"One of the most complex problems in learning is how to adjust to uncertainty and the rapid changes that take place in the environment. It is very exciting to find that synapses, the simplest computational elements in the brain, can provide a robust solution for such challenges," says Alireza Soltani, assistant professor of psychological and brain sciences at Dartmouth. "Of course, such simple elements may not provide an optimal solution but we found that a model based on metaplasticity can explain real behaviors better than models that are based on optimality," he added.

To understand the neural mechanisms for adjusting learning, more specifically, how learning and choice are impacted by reward uncertainty and volatility in an environment, the researchers created a model based on metaplasticity. They tested this model against a behavioral dataset from a recent Yale University study of non-human primates in which the probabilities of obtaining a reward were switched to create environments with different levels of volatility. When things change frequently, a large learning rate is required but this reduces precision, whereas, a stable environment requires a small learning rate, which improves precision. The study illustrates how metaplasticity can mitigate the tradeoff between adaptability and precision in learning.

The metaplasticity model also demonstrates how the learning rate might be different for each choice or option. If a particular choice continues to give reward for a while, the learning rate on that option becomes larger for rewarding outcomes and smaller for non-rewarding outcomes. That is, if the environment does not change, the synapses needed for changing the preferences become less sensitive to feedback in the opposite direction. In addition, the model also predicts that different options or actions could maintain their own learning rates.

This study demonstrates that learning can be self-adjusted and does not require explicit optimization or complete knowledge of the environment. The authors propose potential practical implications of their findings. The brain's inability to modify its behavior may be attributed to the slowing down of plasticity due to metaplasticity, which can occur in a highly stable environment. For behavioral anomalies such as addiction, where the synapses might not adapt flexibly, more carefully designed feedback may be required to make the system plastic again, illustrating how metaplasticity may have broader relevance.

https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2017-04/dc-tbs041717.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study has found each time we get feedback, the brain is hard at work updating its knowledge and behavior in response to changes in the environment; yet, if there's uncertainty or volatility in the environment, the entire process must be adjusted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When people are extra open to new experiences  a trait thats also been linked to insight and imagination  things can look a little different. Their brains are able to flexibly engage with less conventional solutions a new study has found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which shows how the countries climate is getting warmer, complete with graphs and relevant analysis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The nation is immersed in its warmest period in recorded history. The U.S. is enduring a stretch of abnormally warm weather unsurpassed in the record books, and it shows no immediate sign of ending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The nation is immersed in its warmest period in recorded history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. is enduring a stretch of abnormally warm weather unsurpassed in the record books, and it shows no immediate sign of ending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The nation is immersed in its warmest period in recorded history. The U.S. is enduring a stretch of abnormally warm weather unsurpassed in the record books, and it shows no immediate sign of ending. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA seeks to scuttle cleanup of coal power plant pollution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Maps is strongly advising people to avoid Kevin Webster's garage in Coronation Street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Water companies warn parts of UK could see drought this summer after the driest winter in more than 20 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Telecom lobbying muscle kills privacy rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homing pigeons may share the human capacity to build on the knowledge of others, improving their navigational efficiency over time, a new study has found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone forgot to tell NOAA that climate change is a hoax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists to take to the streets in global march for truth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study emphasises the relative scarcity of lake water. The mean depth of lakes is 30 per cent lower than previously estimated. The water quality of the largest lakes on Earth are subject to degradation due to human activities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March 2017 was the second warmest March in 137 years of modern record-keeping, according to a monthly analysis of global temperatures by scientists at NASA' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March 2017 was the second warmest March in 137 years of modern record-keeping, according to a monthly analysis of global temperatures by scientists at NASA' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global Warming: March heat burns record as scientists warn time running out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March 2017 was the second warmest March in 137 years of modern record-keeping, according to a monthly analysis of global temperatures by scientists at NASA' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers estimate that approximately 13.1 million people could be displaced by rising ocean waters, with Atlanta, Houston and Phoenix as top destinations for those forced to relocate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou for this. Very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Ok , what can an individual do in the meantime which would be beneficial to their overall mental health, which doesn't cost money. From a psychological point of view? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote. Whats your philosophy and aim? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In Mexico a cartel drove two pick up trucks onto a rush hour highway and dumped 35 dead bodies in the street. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Dr. In your opinion do you the current administration will offer support for the Paris climate deal?  Several large companies across the country ( financial, Coal, Oil etc )  have asked that we do not scrap our pledges. If the current administration does not offer its support, do you think climate change information will be suppressed from the public?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linked study http://ps.psychiatryonline.org/doi/abs/10.1176/appi.ps.201600260?journalCode=ps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Americans than ever before suffer from serious psychological distress, and the country's ability to meet the growing demand for mental health services is eroding according to a study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which details how technology could potentially advance the discovery of victims of Mexico drug war. This article highlights some of the desperate statistics of people who have  been victims to what it seems a never ending conflict. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunting for Mexicos mass graves with machine learning. As many as 300,000 victims of Mexico's drug war could be hidden in fosas clandestinas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A story which is well written and ultimately reminds us of the heroes who go to work everyday in an attempt to help and possibly save lives. All the while putting their own lives on the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the morning of June 30, all 20 members of Prescott, Arizona's Granite Mountain Hotshots headed into the mountains to protect the small town of Yarnell from an advancing blaze. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders: US can't 'act impulsively' on N. Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In Alabama, it is illegal to wear a fake mustache that causes laughter in church. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study has found life skills, such as persistence, conscientiousness and control, are as important to wealth and wellbeing in later life as they are when people are much younger. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 Is Set to Be the Hottest Year in Recorded History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats fear that Trump has barred key federal workers from speaking to them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research investigates the neuroanatomical basis of forgiveness. The study examines the role of a brain area called the anterior superior temporal sulcus (aSTS) in forgiving those who make unintentional mistakes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 12:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which informs the reader about how mental health is often overlooked, and early signs of psychosis can lead to dire consequences if not been treated and flagged up early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctors Aren't Taking Young People's First Mental Breakdowns Seriously. People under 30 who have experienced first-time psychosis are 24 times more likely than their peers to be dead within a year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 12:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antidepressants prescribed far more in deprived English coastal towns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World power whiplash: Trump reverses views on Russia, China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know that he hasnt? Would be good if he replied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you show us the research? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bird population in Vermont's forests has declined 14.2 percent over 25 years, largely due to several factors, including invasive species, climate change, and the natural cycle of maturing forests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 2014, cigarette and smokeless tobacco companies spent more than $9 billion on advertising and promotional expenses in the United States alone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA head Scott Pruitt calls for exit from Paris climate agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.psychologytoday.com/blog/happiness-is-state-mind/201704/true-story-living-obsessive-compulsive-disorder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which explains a disorder from a first person perspective living with the condition. This article for me helped me gain an insight into  what OCD may be like to live with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A True Story of Living With Obsessive-Compulsive Disorder. "During the summer of 2002, not one thought was left unfiltered from my conscious. Thoughts that didn't even matter nor held any significance were debilitating to me and preventing me from accomplishing the simplest, most mundane tasks" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In two studies, researchers found that adults were very good at remembering information they were told to focus on, and ignoring the rest. In contrast, 4- to 5-year-olds tended to pay attention to all the information that was presented to them - even when they were told to focus on one particular item. That helped children to notice things that adults didn't catch because of the grownups' selective attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children notice what adults miss, study finds: While adults focus their attention, children see everything. Children are extremely curious and they tend to explore everything, which means their attention is spread out, even when they're asked to focus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starving to death. Wars in four countries have left 20 million people on the brink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it pretentious? Can you prove that whats happening in these countries are opposite to what the article contains?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting comment. However i would say people who read the actual article know that its about certain particular countries dealing with the problems in the article ( again in highlights this in the text ) this article does not represent a viewpoint of the world on average. How come people have to compare certain countries to their own country, when events and landscapes are so much different? I didnt think people would find it that hard to do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you associate war and violence?  I would say from my point of view there is. Greed can be produced in many ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read the article?  it explains much more than a word in the title, although greed plays a part but not in the context your thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gambling addiction is a mental disorder characterized by excessive risk-taking despite negative results. Addicts have a poor ability to assess and adapt to high risk situations. According to a new study. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting subject. Id like to know how so many people can shun the idea of aliens visiting Earth, and call people conspiracy theorists and mad people.  These aliens who could be so advanced than us we cannot comprehend their technology and way of being. When the very spectacle of humans going to Mars is often celebrated, humans lack in imagination, in the thought that every living thing in the universe has to be compared, using unique human thinking. Go figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Randomness peaks when you're in your 20s, study finds. Scientists believe creative ability could be linked to age and at their peak, humans "outcompete" many computer algorithms in generating seemingly random patterns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm,  I would like you to consider how you would feel if you and your family was starving. I doubt you would hold that mindset on the brink of death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you even read the article all listened to the news regarding the countries mentioned?  I'd like you to show me this isn't happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A in depth article which shows the devastation of millions of people in the Middle East, something which is hardly ever bought up on Reddit for some unusual reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 million people are at risk of starving to death. Heres how it got so bad. Entire generations are at risk of lasting damage stemming from the vicious cycle of greed, hate, hunger and violence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Expert: Trump's Use Of Massive Bomb In Afghanistan Clear Warning To N Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is an up-vote for raising awareness. Interesting video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A new study of young adults in seven countries shows that media violence is a strong contributing risk factor toward aggressive behavior, regardless of culture. The findings are published in the journal Personality and Social Psychology Bulletin.

For the study, researchers at Iowa State University (ISU) surveyed 2,154 adolescents and young adults in Australia, China, Croatia, Germany, Japan, Romania, and the United States. The average age was 21 years old and 38 percent of participants were male. Participants were asked to list their most frequently watched or played TV shows, movies, and video games, and to rate the level of violence. The researchers also collected data on aggressive behavior and empathy.

The research team identified four key findings from the study:

Violent media use was positively and significantly related to aggressive behavior in all countries
Exposure was related to heightened aggressive thinking and lowered empathy
Media violence remained significant even after controlling for other risk factors
The effect of media violence was larger than all other risk factors, except peer delinquency
This is strong evidence that the main psychological processes that cause repeated media violence exposure to lead to increased aggressiveness are essentially the same across cultures, at least during normal times, said study leader Craig Anderson, an ISU distinguished professor of psychology.

However, we believe that local cultural and social conditions may influence such processes when those conditions are more extreme.

Anderson went on to explain that in war-torn societies, media violence exposure may have heightened effects due to the real violence children and teens experience on a daily basis. On the other hand, the media violence effect could be smaller in such extreme conditions.

In addition to measuring media violence, the research team looked at five other risk factors of aggressive behavior: neighborhood crime, peer delinquency, peer victimization, gender, and abusive parenting.

Combined, these factors significantly predicted aggressive behavior and as a group were more powerful than any individual factor. The findings show that media violence was the second most important predictor.

Below are the six major risk factors of aggressive behavior and how each contributes to overall risk:

Peer delinquency  28 percent
Media violence  23 percent
Peer victimization  17 percent
Gender  12 percent
Neighborhood crime  11 percent
Abusive parenting  nine percent
The findings strongly suggest that media violence is similar to other known risk factors for aggression, said Douglas Gentile, an ISU professor of psychology and one of the co-authors.

Thats not to say media violence deserves special attention, but that it should be considered as seriously as other risk factors such as coming from a broken home. What matters most, however, is not any single risk factor, but how they can combine to increase the risk of aggression.

Anderson notes that although the findings were based on self-reports and the study was cross-sectional, the large, diverse sample allowed for direct comparisons of media violence effects across many cultures.

The study also disproves claims by the entertainment industry that dismiss all media violence effects.

There are highly motivated groups dedicated to denying scientific findings of harm, such as the tobacco industrys decades-long denial of harmful effects of their products on cancer, Anderson said. This study clearly contradicts the denialism that currently dominates news media stories on media violence effects.

https://psychcentral.com/news/2017/04/13/cross-cultural-study-strengthens-link-between-media-violence-aggression/119034.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study of young adults in seven countries shows that media violence is a strong contributing risk factor toward aggressive behavior, regardless of culture. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study http://www.europsy-journal.com/article/S0924-9338(17)30343-7/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! do you have any links which you recommend as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study has found Mindfulness group therapy has an equally positive effect as individual CBT (cognitive behavioural therapy) for the treatment of a wide range of psychiatric symptoms in patients with depression, anxiety and stress-related disorders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New machine learning models can detect hate speech and violence from texts. The study shows that natural language processing techniques can help detect antisocial behaviour, which is a step towards its prevention in society. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change Deniers Have President Trump's Ear. But Now They Want Results </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou for the link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldnt the pregnant woman know what its like not to have kids, hence she has decided to have them and made that choice? Same with parents of children. With someone who is childfree and doesnt want kids they see it from just that point of view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at University College London have found that emotional stability, determination, control, optimism and conscientiousness are the foundation stones of building a positive life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Murray Gell-Mann Amnesia Effect is a phenomenon that afflicts mass mediaits unlimited, unearned credibility, and that media carries with it a credibility that is totally undeserved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elephants body awareness adds to increasing evidence of their intelligence. Asian elephants are able to recognise their bodies as obstacles to success in problem-solving, further strengthening evidence of their intelligence and self-awareness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they may never know unless they are in the situation. However going by logic, you would know about not having kids before your a parent, and then by being a parent you would then know what it is like to have kids and not have kids. The questions are not to provoke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin Says U.S. Ties Have Deteriorated Since Trump Took Office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 09:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi do you have any links to doing this in Mexico and the best way of going about it, please? I appreciate your comments and thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all, i was asking how they would know they wouldnt be happy without ever been that situation themselves. How would that be insulting?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is at strange question to ask? when the original poster is saying that he wouldnt be happy if he had kids ( without even trying) as for your example at least the pregnant women knows what her state of mind is without kids, and then gets pregnant when she knows this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can i ask, how do you know you wouldnt be happy with children? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In your view what are the psychological consequences of not having children when you get older? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No right or wrong answers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study is the first to link specific differences in brain structure to what is common across many types of mental illness. Studies consistently show that up to half of people with one mental illness also experience one or more additional forms of mental illness at the same time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Alcohol is the most highly abused drug in the United States. 7.2 percent of American adults have an alcohol use disorder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being overweight at any point in adulthood increases risk for death a new study has found. The authors say that these findings are important from a public health perspective, given that about one-third of adults in the U.S. and more than a quarter of the world's population is overweight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emerging nations urge rich countries to honour climate finance pledges - statement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fascinating  in depth analysis of how a disaster played out  a few years ago  and the dire consequences on the environment from the incident.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The role a melting glacier played in Exxon's biggest disaster, when 11 million gallons of crude oil spilt into the waters of Prince William Sound. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL For some people with OCD doubt is what fuels the fire for their disorder, as they may feel the need to have total control over everything in their lives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Blocks G7 Climate Statement As White House Waffles on Paris Deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study has found that a temperature rise of 2C above pre-industrial levels would thaw about 40% of permafrost which covers almost a quarter of the land of the Northern Hemisphere, releasing billions of tonnes of carbon into the atmosphere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1m mortgages rise 24% year-on-year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
More information here

To understand the Casimir Effect, one first has to understand something about a vacuum in space as it is viewed in quantum field theory. Far from being empty, modern physics assumes that a vacuum is full of fluctuating electromagnetic waves that can never be completely eliminated, like an ocean with waves that are always present and can never be stopped. These waves come in all possible wavelengths, and their presence implies that empty space contains a certain amount of energy--an energy that we can't tap, but that is always there.
Now, if mirrors are placed facing each other in a vacuum, some of the waves will fit between them, bouncing back and forth, while others will not. As the two mirrors move closer to each other, the longer waves will no longer fit--the result being that the total amount of energy in the vacuum between the plates will be a bit less than the amount elsewhere in the vacuum. Thus, the mirrors will attract each other, just as two objects held together by a stretched spring will move together as the energy stored in the spring decreases.


This effect, that two mirrors in a vacuum will be attracted to each other, is the Casimir Effect. It was first predicted in 1948 by Dutch physicist Hendrick Casimir. Steve K. Lamoreaux, now at Los Alamos National Laboratory, initially measured the tiny force in 1996.

It is generally true that the amount of energy in a piece of vacuum can be altered by material around it, and the term "Casimir Effect" is also used in this broader context. If the mirrors move rapidly, some of the vacuum waves can become real waves. Julian Schwinger and many others have suggested that this "dynamical Casimir effect" may be responsible for the mysterious phenomenon known as sonoluminescence.
One of the most interesting aspects of vacuum energy (with or without mirrors) is that, calculated in quantum field theory, it is infinite! To some, this finding implies that the vacuum of space could be an enormous source of energy--called "zero point energy."

But the finding also raises a physical problem: there's nothing to stop arbitrarily small waves from fitting between two mirrors, and there is an infinite number of these wavelengths. The mathematical solution is to temporarily do the calculation for a finite number of waves for two different separations of the mirrors, find the associated difference in vacuum energies and then argue that the difference remains finite as one allows the number of wavelengths to go to infinity.

Although this trick works, and gives answers in agreement with experiment, the problem of an infinite vacuum energy is a serious one. Einstein's theory of gravitation implies that this energy must produce an infinite gravitational curvature of spacetime--something we most definitely do not observe. The resolution of this problem is still an open research question.

https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/what-is-the-casimir-effec/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. Im glad you have improved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any good sources which shows this to be a fact? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any information in the way of sources/links which backs up this belief? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new scientific paper published, is shedding light on a strange force impacting particles at the smallest level of the material world. The findings relate to an area of theoretical nanophotonics and quantum theory known as the Casimir Effect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that psychological conditions like depression and neurosis are far more prevalent among people with debt, compared with people not in debt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An article which highlights the problem we have with debt, it gives clear warning signs that this issue will not go away and will perhaps lead to big trouble ahead for many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Credit card debt hits $1 trillion as economy expands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. households will soon have as much debt as they had in 2008. The Federal Reserve announced Friday that the U.S. has $1 trillion in credit-card debt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York, California lead state efforts on climate change as Trump retreats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Mexican drug cartels reap $19 billion to $29 billion from U.S. drug sales alone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study https://academic.oup.com/schizophreniabulletin/article-abstract/doi/10.1093/schbul/sbx009/3111212/Twelve-Month-Health-Care-Use-and-Mortality-in?redirectedFrom=fulltext </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study shows that young people experiencing first episode psychosis have a much higher death rate than previously thought. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An in depth look into what goes on in the Sinola Cartel. This article delves into the philosophy of the cartel and looks at some of the mindsets of the individuals associated in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Behind the Scenes of Mexico's Sinaloa Cartel. "After killing so many people," says a hitman in a pink polo shirt who is said to have killed hundreds of people, "it turns into a vice. If you don't kill, you feel anxious to kill someone." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico has enlisted the US military in its war on heroin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmm, not really. From the article

The study suggests that women value physical attractiveness in a potential mate far more than they say they do, said study author Madeleine Fugre, a professor of social psychology at Eastern Connecticut State University in Willimantic. 

Previous research on this subject has given conflicting results. Some studies have suggested that both parents and their adult children (especially daughters) may say that personality is more important than looks in a potential mate, with these individuals typically ranking physical attractiveness lower on a list of personality characteristics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new test could now provide solid evidence for dogs being able to adopt human perspective. By adopting the position of a human and following their gaze, dogs understand what the human could see and, consequently, know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A study suggests that women value physical attractiveness in a potential mate far more than they say they do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA Reportedly Eliminates Program Helping Cities Deal With Climate Change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deep brain stimulation decreases tics in young adults with severe Tourette syndrome. Tourette syndrome begins in childhood and many patients improve as they get older. However, for some, the symptoms become so severe that they become socially isolated and unable to work or attend school. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now this is going to be very interesting. I wonder who owns that water?  and in particular how would there be conflict about  outsourcing if other states were in dire need? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok, attack the source but dont mention anything about the topic, including the study from the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study in the article, 2nd paragraph down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a source or link for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL East Germany's secret police, who were called the Stasi had 2.1 million informers who helped with the surveillance of its population. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vital groundwater depleted faster than ever. Global use of irreplaceable groundwater is exhausting the supply so fast that researchers say it will drive up food prices and hit international trade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Appetite for Mexico's Drugs Fuels Illegal Immigration. According to the Treasury Department, drug trafficking generates an estimated $64 billion annually from sales in the United States. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Growing Skepticism: Already 150 New (2017) Scientific Papers Support A Skeptical Position On Climate Alarm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus that sounds terrible. Thats a story and a half. What was her background, abuse etc early in life? It sounds like you may of needed therapy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou. I will check it out. Indeed iv heard alot about mirroring and adapting others behaviour. Iv some people   can be very much seductive as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Environmental Groups Take Trump EPA To Court To Force Ban Of Brain-Draining Pesticide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study has found mating patterns caused spouses to be more genetically similar to each other than might otherwise be expected, and that the genetic structure created by these mating patterns in the population has decreased over time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can i ask, people with Bpd what kind of romantic partners do you tend to attract? Is there a pattern? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol , reposted it. Better link, more informative </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An informative yet touching article regarding how the soldiers communicated with their loved ones back home 100 years ago during WW1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World War I Letters Home From Generals to Doughboys Carry the Sorrow of Fighting a War </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like you have been burnt by an experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear you are getting better. Can i ask in what way how you found the best treatment, talking therapy? medication..even meditation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK thanks anyway for being honest. I find this topic quite fascinating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? What have you experienced? I hope your better by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you elaborate please? what did you experience? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, just offering a counter perspective. No right or wrongs here, thanks for your thoughts. Im curious,  do you have any tips recommendations on how to sit and examine negative experiences, to enhance overall wellbeing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm interesting, i would like to say however that this topic is in its early stages. Obviously its healthy to be cautious, to knock it at this stage i dont agree with.

 Look at anti depressents. Could you not say by your logic that many people with depression just need to buckle up and get on with life. Im sure people abuse these kinds of drugs as well. Measuring personal struggle is very risky, no one size fits all. PTSD i can imagine be an absolute nightmare for an individual. I would take a guess  a large number of people cannot deal with to much mental struggle. They may use  distraction techniques,  thought supression, abuse of drugs etc etc to get away from pain. How can one measure what is healthy and normal regarding dealing with negative thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL People with Bordeline personality disorder are often terrified of being abandoned or left alone. Even something as innocuous as a loved one getting home late from work or going away for the weekend can trigger intense fear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
