<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject670</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, its only "Socialism" if the government (or 'community') owns *literally* everything? Which country has that ever been true for? Even Socialist Russia had *some* private ownership... didn't it? Or am I still confused? Can you elaborate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are just deeply confused.

Which is why I am asking questions. I asked you to tell me how many programs America would have to have to be Socialist. 
Someone that read "all" of the literate would know. Yet, your quote from Carl Marx doesn't address America, nor the number needed for a country.  You say I am confused. Alright, educate me. Let me ask the question a different way:

Would America have to include ALL programs to become "Socialist?" Or is there some critical number? By having *any* "socialized programs" have we already started down the path of Communism already? If 'yes,' should we back off the path and start privatizing things like the Army and courts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If America included in its 'socialized programs' medicine, would we become 'Socialists?' Or would we have to include more programs? If so, how many more?

By having *any* "socialized programs" have we already started down the path of Communism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are conflating 'Communism' with 'Socialism.' But, alright I'll go along. So, at what point does something count as 'Socialism' then?

If America included in its 'socialized programs' *medicine,* would we become 'Socialists?' Or would we have to include more programs? If so, how many more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, to a degree all countries have some level of socialism.  If you have your government do 'something,' that 'something' is socialized.

America has socialized courts. America has a socialized military. And, America has socialized police and firefighters, which makes it weird we don't want to socialize our hospitals too. Since those three things (policemen, firemen, and doctors) normally go together in culture.

That what is meant by "socializing medicine," it means you put the hospitals in with the police and the firemen.  This is what England has done. They have many socialist programs (and a [strong socialist party](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Liberal_Democrats)), but they are still capitalists as well. You can be both, and most countries are both. Just the *degree* of which is varied.

That is the point of this video. The English -by and large- know that "socialism" isn't a bad word, just the EXCESS of socialism (AKA "Communism") is bad. Just like an excess of capitalism would be bad. Unless you feel that the courts and the police should be run by Google, you're not a pure capitalist either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think the military should be run by the government, not a corporation? Then you're a socialist. Do you think the police should be run by the government, not a corporation? Then you're a socialist.

Do you think the courts shouldn't be run by people that own the most stock in Courtsus? 

Then you're a socialist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but at least he is wearing a flag pin.

That's what Fox cares about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a scale from "Flag Pin" to "Birth Certificate" I wounder how outraged Fox New should be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logic isn't concerned with popularity, only true and false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logic isn't dead.

And, being logically inconsistent still makes you objectively wrong, regardless of party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hypocrisy? I am **not** mad that Trump is spending vacation money, anymore than I was mad at Obama for doing it. I **am** mad that the people that *were* mad at Obama for spending vacation money aren't mad when Trump does it at x12 times the rate.

How is that hypocritical? Being mad at someone's [Special Pleading](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Special_pleading) is hypocritical now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but the **hypocrisy** should bother us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked how he conflated "morally good" with "liking me."

And in the above statement I am conflating "liked" with "am terrified." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's meant to imply one person (and people here already know it's one person because of the [Trump joke](https://www.reddit.com/r/Jokes/comments/5ubjkn/a_russian_spy_a_sexual_predator_and_a_billionaire/) on the front page). The attempted funny part is the pun when you expect the bartender ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A General, conspiracy theorist and traitor walk into a bar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Flynn says: "Ow." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's an alternate universe somewhere where he's president.

http://shadowrun.wikia.com/wiki/Arnold_Schwarzenegger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't Trump say the words "Domestic Christian Terrorists?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen anything happen yet that leads me to believe they will not still be traditionally powerful at the end of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who, our current president or a retired mulatto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we get Mexico to pay for NASA instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You going to blame Obama for everything during these next 4 years too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Protest_vote#Protest_vote_in_various_countries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Favorite 'Darkseid Vs Superman' Moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The issued visas and greencards were done under faulty conditions

Right, as I said, you think we should 100% trust Obama when it comes to suspicious countries, but 0% trust him when it comes to [good people that helped us](http://www.bizpacreview.com/2017/01/28/iraqi-translator-detained-airport-stuns-reporters-surprising-answer-president-trump-441477) in those suspicious countries. Those people need to be stopped, you know, for the *symbolism.*

 he needs to ban them temporarily to ascertain their legitimacy.

So, how many extremists have been caught using this method? Have we caught more 5-year-olds than terrorists?

Also, back in 2015, December, he called for a 3 month ban ["until our country's representatives can figure out what is going on"](http://www.vox.com/2015/12/7/9867900/donald-trump-muslims). Dec2015-Jan2017 is a *long* 3 months for this "temporary indefinite ban."

Let me put this in easier terms: Your boss just got fired for being a fuckbag, new boss comes in and sees what the fuckbag has done, new boss decides to rollback the damage.

Expect when it comes to which places the new boss should shit on. Then the old boss got everything 100% right. It's just the [people who RISKED THEIR LIFE aiding the company](http://www.vox.com/first-person/2017/1/30/14431650/trump-visa-ban-american-resident-stories) that the old boss liked. Fuck those guys, 'cuz symbolism.

Yeah, I'm fine with footing the bill initially, it's a tiny one

Oh, can I have a billion dollars then? I mean, if 12-20 billion is so small... Anyway, maybe the money should be used on... IDK, roads? Oh, right, Trump plans in outsourcing that too, [for more toll roads.](http://thehill.com/policy/transportation/313145-toll-roads-poised-to-boom-under-trump-plan) He'll get us US citizens to pay for the wall we don't need, and the roads we do need.

Mexico will be kicking up a tantrum before they succumb

[As will the US citizens who's land you will be seizing to build that wall.](http://www.theblaze.com/news/2012/10/15/landowners-along-u-s-mexico-border-claim-govt-is-abusing-its-power-to-take-land-at-unfair-prices/)

Empathy regarding what? 

Humans. I guess I will have to wait until he does something to effect you, personally, before you'll care.

Wasted tax dollars or families of illegals mooching off of our welfare when it could obviously go to American citizens?

Well, your ~12 billion dollar wall [will not address your 113 billion dollar illegal problem](https://www.wired.com/2017/01/wall-alone-cant-secure-border-no-matter-pays/) (but I guess you don't read citations, or make them). Anyway, so, the plan to fix wasted tax dollars is to wast more dollars? [I mean, illegals pay more in taxes than Trump.](http://www.politifact.com/punditfact/statements/2016/oct/02/maria-teresa-kumar/how-much-do-undocumented-immigrants-pay-taxes/) So, we are back to my original statement:

If you want to get rid of wasteful moochers, we should deport HIM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ban doesn't have anything to do with illegals, only LEGALS. People getting their counterfeit visas from Saudi Arabia are unaffected. If you want him to do something to illegals, he should [start the Raids like Barry did.](http://www.latimes.com/politics/la-na-immigration-raids-20160512-snap-story.html) He shouldn't ban people who have already gone through the legal paperwork.

Anyway, [Trump is already planning on having American consumers pay for the wall.](http://fortune.com/2017/01/26/donald-trump-mexico-pay-tax-wall/) But, I am glad you are showing a complete lack of empathy and understanding when it comes to your "symbolism." Makes it easier for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barry's admin considered them threats, at least on paper. So, it was a safe bet for Trump.

Barry didn't think the [war heroes](http://thefreethoughtproject.com/iraq-war-hero-humiliated-travel-ban/) and [5-year-olds](https://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/compost/wp/2017/01/30/sean-spicer-is-right-that-five-year-old-refugee-has-diabolical-plans/?utm_term=.ee2998a50f97) in them were a threat. But, I do think it's funny you're blaming Obama for something Trump did. Keep it up for the next 4 years.

Personally, I think that it's mostly about the symbolism, much like the wall.

Ah, nothing like a [12-billion dollar symbol.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vU8dCYocuyI) I hope he outsources Trump Real Estate to build it. I hear those guys do good work.

The symbolism of ripping families apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loki? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the one that is saying we need 100% trust in Obama when it comes to identifying countries, but 0% when it comes to identifying people.

Trump trusts Obama enough that he goes full-hog on all of the countries Obama was *suspicious* about. But, when it comes to the people in those country Obama **trusts,** Trump and his supporters give 0 fucks.  Is that about the long and the short of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just explaining why a lack of education leads to Trump. Something the founding fathers knew well. That's why so many of the worked hard to set up public education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the policies that gave Trump's dad a green card were ineffective. Can we deport his whole family? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Trump's wife? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, ones with Green Cards and Visas? As in, the kind getting banned?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, ones with Green Cards and Visas? As in, the kind getting banned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Socrates explains why a Candy Salesman would be elected over a Doctor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope is an easy sell to the hopeless.

Trump was all pie-in-the-sky pomp, and Hillary was all realism. [This video explains it.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fLJBzhcSWTk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stock Slavery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If corporations are people, owning one is slavery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like pizzagate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, since my post was down voted into oblivion before being deleted for *not being creepy....*

...Unless that was all done "sarcastically" as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you say that? You don't even know me....

I wanted to know the answer as much as you do. That's one of the reasons I posted.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what the image was called on imgur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it creepy because I don't know what is going on. I just found it on a random image search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trumps voted for Hillary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I went to bed.

But, I don't know anything about it myself. I found it on imgur. It creeped me out. I couldn't find out anything googling. So, I posted it here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Day 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not voting up or down. Anyway, they've detained several hundred.

So, what % of those are terrorists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, how many of those have it stopped?

I've only heard about it stopping 6 year old's and war vets. How many shady people has it stopped? Why isn't that Trump's narrative? Where is the "poster boy" for why the ban was a good idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many terrorists have they caught with the new ban? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zero? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, ty for letting me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 18:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm.... What does that even mean?

What counts as a "regulation?" Are they discrete entities? Couldn't you count 100 different rules as a single "regulation?" And, count a single compound sentence as "2 regulations?"

**Ex:** *New regulation:* Water must have no lead, be 97% H20, be free of termites, and be storied in a cool environment.

*Removed 2 regulations:* Water must be 96% H2O and may or may not be free of termites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spell echo doubles Vaal Skeletons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 12:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said Islam was trying to conquer Europe in the past? Well Europe HAS conquered the Middle East.

Anyway, the immigrants from the Irish Potato famine to the US were not well educated. And, they experienced a lot of push back in the US as did the Germans immigrates. So much so a whole new political party formed to stop them. One that was anti-Catholic, as you are being anti-Islamic. *The movement arose in response to an influx of migrants and promised to "purify" American politics by limiting or ending the influence of Irish Catholics and other immigrants, thus reflecting nativist and anti-Catholic sentiment. It was empowered by popular fears that the country was being overwhelmed by German and Irish Catholic immigrants, whom they saw as hostile to Republican values and as being controlled by the Pope.* [[1]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Know_Nothing)

There have been similar groups in Europe (most notably in Germany) in response to an influx of Orthodox Jews. They never seem to lead to anything good.

But, back in the US, the Germans and the Irish immigrates did eventually accumulate (or their children did, anyway). And their dependents ended up being a big help in stopping that German movement a century later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hillary would be still been terrible in different ways.

But, not **this** terrible. While you might be against a 'Dem/Rep dichotomy,' I've been against the 'false equivalency' one. Trump is a loon, and should have never been on the same stage as Hillary. Yet, you give a guy who believes the Earth was created 6,000 years ago the same airtime as one with an actual degree in radiometric dating, and the public will say they're "about the same." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name a country in history that was solely conquered by refugees. And, no, "Troy" wasn't a country, nor was it conquered by refugees.

Anyway, read ANY economical analysis of the long term impact of immigration. Or, maybe cite a source, like I did. *(I mean, I know you will not. You're clearly just going to continue cherry picking things you remember from your middle school history class. But, I feel obliged to ask.)* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 14:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more asking "why DON'T we care about the fatal?"  We've had lots of fatal attacks, why not ban THOSE countries?

Only one of those counties banned has someone with a non-fatal attack anyway. If this is about saving lives, shouldn't it be about saving lives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 14:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on our two economies, probably yes. In the short run, there are problems. In the long run, immigrants help a country.[[1]](https://www.manhattan-institute.org/html/economic-benefits-immigration-5712.html) [[2]](http://www.bushcenter.org/catalyst/north-american-century/benefits-of-immigration-outweigh-costs.html) Just look at the US after it got that influx of immigrants from Europe. There was trouble with assimilation (all the 'littles' in NY, gangs, poverty). But, those immigrants made us a super power in the end.

Of course, people now a days don't seem to be looking to the past to predict the future. They are obsessed with the present. So, people living-in-the-moment want the immigrates out, sure. They cause problems in the 'now.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 14:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet, there have been many fatal attacks from countries that aren't on the list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They(Saudi Arabia) buy apartments from me," Trump said. "They spend $40 million, $50 million. Am I supposed to dislike them? I like them very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cuz he let people who already had green cards and visas come in. Obama affected NEW immigrants. Trump is affecting OLD immigrants, who are already legally allowed to be here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 05:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Whenever the Vice President and a majority of either the principal officers of the executive departments or of such other body as Congress may by law provide, transmit to the President pro tempore of the Senate and the Speaker of the House of Representatives their written declaration that the President is unable to discharge the powers and duties of his office, the Vice President shall immediately assume the powers and duties of the office as Acting President.* [[1]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Twenty-fifth_Amendment_to_the_United_States_Constitution#Section_4:_Vice_Presidential.E2.80.93Cabinet_declaration) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean, go back to work and school? Most of the people immediately affected by the ban are people with valid work visa and international exchange students. (Like, those currently being detained in airports) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, there have been no fatal terror attacks in the U.S. by immigrants from the 7 banned Muslim countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zombie Dance: Team Necrophilia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your ability to score well on an IQ test is directly correlated to good political decision making? Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 01:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But time makes everything a zero-sum game. 

I guess that is why multicellular organisms never evolved.

I mean, if my liver-cell gets more, than that means my heart-cell must get less. And, my muscle-cell wants to know why the brain-cells keep telling it what to do! This is zero-sum! My muscle-cells need to revolt, and my Liver-cells need to know it is 'liver first!' Working together is for SUCKERS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Emperor couldn't do it because it's an exclusive light-side power.[[1]](http://starwars.wikia.com/wiki/Force_Ghost) Dark-side users have [Transfer essence](http://starwars.wikia.com/wiki/Transfer_essence) or use [Sith holocrons](http://starwars.wikia.com/wiki/Sith_holocron/Legends) instead.

The Emperor was a very strong dark-side user, but he wasn't strong enough in the light-side to become a force ghost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More proof he doesn't go pass his own perspective for the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [If they are at work it's because we've had steady job growth for 8 years.](https://ourfuture.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Monthly_0208_0514.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had, it looked, honestly it looked like a million and a half people, whatever it was it was, Trump said. It went all the way back to the Washington Monument.

I don't think he knows what a million people look like. Mainly because a "million people" is a silly big number of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or morons that say:

We had, it looked, honestly it looked like a million and a half people, whatever it was it was. It went all the way back to the Washington Monument. I turn on (the television) by mistake, and I get this network and it showed an empty field. And it said we drew 250,000 people. Now thats not bad, but its a lie. We had 250,000 people literally around that little ball we constructed, that was 250,000 people." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ich pack hier einfach noch jedermanns Lieblingskopiernudel ber Berlin dazu, damit die ganzen Amerikaner auf den ersten Blick denken dass wir hier hier eine hitzige Diskussion fhren und sich dazu gezwungen fhlen den Text zu bersetzen.

Yeah, it worked, you got me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any evidence he really did sign the correct papers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miss Me Yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Miss me yet?](https://i.redd.it/w7pgoyfxcway.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miss Me Yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miss Me Yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, even Superman killed Zod.

If you're looking for a perfect superhero, you're going to be looking a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump was a Dem a few years ago. [[1]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Donald_Trump#Political_affiliations) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 15:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't really have "a party," or--at least--not the Democratic one. He has the party he is currently building, but he wasn't a declared Democrat until 2 years ago.  If you want a Democratic Superhero, [here you go.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Elizabeth_Warren#/media/File:Elizabeth_Warren,_official_portrait,_114th_Congress.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [We have Superheroes.](https://images.successstory.com/img_quotes/It-s-better-to-show-up-than-to-give-up_1449662905.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 12:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, sure, in that context "anti-bourgeois" doesn't make sense in the post I originally responded to. But, I maintain that isn't the context meant. I maintain it is the normal American definition of the word, comrade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm just going off of the #1 definition in the dictionary here:

[*a member of the middle class.*](http://www.dictionary.com/browse/bourgeois) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm just going off of the #1 definition in the dictionary here:

[*a member of the middle class.*](http://www.dictionary.com/browse/bourgeois) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think in this case "bourgeois" is meant to be the "working middle class." In this context I am assuming "anti-bourgeois" would mean "to make the working middle class the working poor class." 

Which seems like a reasonable goal for a bunch of oligarchs trying to maintain being oligarchs. Buyout the local mom and pop store to make mom and pop work for you. Decrease wages to increase profits. Let big business strangle little business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless I am mistaken, "bourgeois" means "middle class."

So, I'm not sure what is so unbelievable about the super-rich (oligarchs) being anti-middle class. They could easily be trying to create a noblemen-serf dynamic, not a upper-middle-lower class dynamic.  The noblemen-serf dynamic stagnates movement (both up and down). So, if you're on top, and want to stay on top, the noblemen-serf dynamic is more appealing then the upper-middle-lower class dynamic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, you're not going to be winning any major wars with them; you just get billions of dollars at the bottom of the ocean.

http://www.bbc.com/news/magazine-18237029 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 14:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, ~87% of NASAs budget over 5 years, or 10% of NASA's budget in 5 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of his picks make sense now that we know Putin is pulling his strings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 18:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  no brainer

There is your answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our founding fathers committed treason and didn't want to pay taxes. Trump is more American than any one of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 03:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in that case I guess I just wish we were deterring the rest of the world from getting moon bases instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 03:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went back and added the appropriate "/s." Apparent, you didn't pick up on my sarcasm.


But, even within my sarcasm, I was being contestant. If you believe--as you claimed--aircraft carriers will matter greatly in a war between the US and China, then the US has nothing to worry about.

However, if you believe--as many do--that aircraft carriers will matter little in a war between the US and China, then the US has a lot to worry about.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 03:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess I just wish we weren't fighting the wars you need 10 space stations for instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 00:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're the only country that currently has ANY fully functioning supercarriers, and we have 10. The last one cost us ~16 billion, ~87% of NASA's entire budget.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 00:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to pull a "[duck season](https://media.giphy.com/media/YaXcVXGvBQlEI/giphy.gif)" thing on me? **I** am the one that said I didn't think a war would go well because I don't think aircraft carriers are as important as US military spending would suggest. I guess I need to go back and put a "/s" in my last post to make the sarcasm clear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 23:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess we have nothing to worry about than, since they've built 0 supercarriers and we've spent ~50 billion on 10. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then I am sure you're happy to hear the last aircraft carrier we build cost ~ the same as NASA's **entire** budget. *$12.8 billion + $4.7 billion R D*  [[1]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/USS_Gerald_R._Ford)

I mean, China doesn't even OWN a supercarrier[[2]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supercarrier). So, I don't know how China gets *any* respect. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think war with anyone will go well. I also don't think it will come down to who has more/bigger aircraft carriers.

But, if it does I guess we'll win since China doesn't even own a single supercarrier.[[1]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supercarrier) Clearly showing how important they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 20:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You don't need a 13 billion dollar floating city to do that.](http://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-us-navys-new-13-billion-aircraft-carrier-will-dominate-the-seas-2016-03-09) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, since our next nearest spender is China, I don't think we'll have to worry too much about having to fight those kinda future wars either. Unless it's with aliens.

In which case we'll REALLY wish we'd spent more on NASA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kind of wars we've been fighting the last half-century aren't the kind you need 10 aircraft carriers to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [We *waste* about as much as China spends.](https://www.washingtonpost.com/investigations/pentagon-buries-evidence-of-125-billion-in-bureaucratic-waste/2016/12/05/e0668c76-9af6-11e6-a0ed-ab0774c1eaa5_story.html?utm_term=.1c2b48961e8e
) We waste 2x NASA's budget.

So, I'm not sure "flexibility" is the issue. The issue is that we are a politically minded society, and its easy to sell to the pubic military spending. So, that is where our money goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is unrealistic. I know the numbers don't add like that and science doesn't scale like that. And, I know my fellow scientist will be picking this video apart like true pragmatists.

And, that's why we don't get any money. The public stops caring the moment you start getting realistic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think 18 billion would be enough to prevent a 3rd world country on the other side of an ocean from concerning us. If nothing else, it could be used to maintain the navy we already have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If 18 billion, in your estimation, is a shitload of money and you can do just about anything with it, why does the military need 600 billion? Maybe just ten times as much as 18 billion, which is about what china spends?

How is 600 billion a year not enough to get us ISIS, or hell, even World Domination? That's a shitload of money, the military needs to figure their shit out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we pay taxes to our state and to our federal government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wouldn't have to turn it off. Just edit it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you were done with me?

I don't know who to trust anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you see the FOX clips I showed you as anything other than fabrication, I don't really have anything else to say to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By this logic CNN says nothing about Trump, they just reported on it.

I see nothing in your links that CNN is, unequivocally, 100% sure and that their claim it is an undoubtable truth. So, I guess Trump shouldn't be all up in arms about it? Right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you missed this:

http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2016/07/07/photo-obama-in-muslim-garb-shows-deep-ties-to-faith-oreilly-says.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  None of the videos in the first link show fox news attacking Obama about where he was born.

The links on the first link do. [For example](http://mediamatters.org/video/2011/04/15/hannity-helps-promote-trumps-birtherism/178748). But, I mean, you're really claiming no one at Fox News questioned Obama's linage? 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qC0g5l9kq94

And, I'm not calling anyone "racist." I am just saying if you don't like the press giving the president a hard time, there are 8 years of Fox New clips you should be getting upset about first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 12:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find Fox News questioning Obama's birth place? Ok, after 30 seconds of googling:

http://mediamatters.org/research/2016/09/16/flashback-how-fox-news-promoted-trumps-birtherism/213152

You can click the links on that ^ page to watch the videos.

Find them saying he might be a secret Muslim terrorist?

http://americannewsx.com/fox-news/foxs-johah-goldberg-twist-obama/

But, I guess you conjecture is that Trump has been attacked more in the last few weeks that Obama has been in **8 years?** So that Trump's response is justified, but Obama wouldn't have cause to do the same?

Just so we're clear:

Obama is a Muslim Kenyan = Reasonable accusation

Hillary is running a kiddy sex ring out of a pizzeria = Reasonable accusation

Trump hired a Russian Prostitute = OUTRAGEOUS LIES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 05:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you'd have wanted Obama to call out Fox News attacking him about everything from where he was born to accusing him of possibly being a Muslim terrorist sleeper-cell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like you let the cat train YOU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, sorry, I often don't remember usernames.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IDK, does it for you? You are the one with the definition based on physical DNA; I already explained my definition of a human is independent of physical DNA. So, my answer is trivially "no." But, what is yours? How do you justify saying all fetuses are human, but something with 1% difference isn't?  I mean, the different races of humanity have differences in their DNA; would you claim some races aren't human?

I ask, because I am legitimately not sure how your particular definition based on physical DNA works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, it was half of my DNA. At one point,would you say half of 'me' was sperm. Does that mean that sperm is half a person? Flushing one sperm cell down the toilet would be half as bad a murder?

See, "your DNA" is a fine arbitrary definition of a person. But, its not the arbitrary definition I use to define a person. My consciousness, my mind, is much more important to me than my physical body. Brain death, to me, is tantamount to real death. And, if you found a way to download my consciousness into a different body (with different DNA) I would consider that new body to be "me."  I also don't think cutting out cancer cells, with their unique human DNA, is the same as murdering a person, since--again--I would arbitrarily define a person as a consciousness.

With that in mind, thalamic brain connections, which mediate sensory input, form in fetuses typically after 26 weeks.

*In 1997, the Guttmacher Institute estimated the number of abortions in the U.S. past 24 weeks to be 0.08%* [[1]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Late_termination_of_pregnancy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 03:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was I sperm too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 145% isn't "tripling," it isn't even *"time-and-a-half,"* though it is almost that. But, "almost time-and-a-half" isn't "tripling," and making it seem so would be a form of propaganda.

Anyway, are there better plans people could switch to? What plans are we talking about *specifically* that are tripling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, are there better plans people could switch to? What plans are we talking about *specifically* that are tripling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, are there better plans people could switch to? What plans are we talking about *specifically* that are tripling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its repeal would achieve "BETTER" automatically.

Well, no, because people could be rejected based on preexisting conditions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that is true, why didn't they come into existence the decades before the ACA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you legitimately can't afford it the government will subsidize you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are probably reasons he is out of work. Like being bullheaded, ornery, and dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd rather handle their own ethics now, thank you very much.  It's easier when no one is breathing down your back. You can really get things done then.^^/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [If you feel this was taken out of context for the Book of Deuteronomy, you might want to reread that book with fresh eyes.](http://www.skepticsannotatedbible.com/dt/21.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was "mostly true" as in, some rose, but none as much as **tripled,** which is the claim currently in question.

u/mopok0000 claimed his rates TRIPLED. I am asking for more information about which rates tripled. In part, because I assume u/mopok0000 could probably find a better deal somewhere else. We might be able to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 03:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked them over at ask a conservative why they'd want to repeal it at all:

https://www.reddit.com/r/askaconservative/comments/5kzybn/why_repeal_the_affordable_care_act/

I had some followup questions, but they didn't seem to have follow up answers :( Since I firmly believe people are--on the whole--rational, I really am trying to understand the logic of wanting the ACA gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't they come into existence the decades before the ACA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, do you know what specific plans have **tripled** under the Affordable Care Act? Politafacts did a study about it:

http://www.politifact.com/wisconsin/statements/2016/dec/20/ron-johnson/testing-ron-johnson-claim-under-obamacare-premiums/

That seemed to indicate none "tripled." But, u/mopok0000 claimed his did. I was wounding which plans were in the "tripled" range. I don't need to know HIS plan, specifically. I was more just asking for which ones--in general--fell into that category.

Do YOU know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you feel confident 'better' or 'best' will be put into place around the same time it is repealed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
