<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4585</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's trendy/cool right now but will be looked back as cringe worthy in 5 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 02:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just gave me a movie style flashback  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree that kurapika is boring but you shouldn't get downvoted for stating the fact that it's an opinion whether he's boring or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a wrestler but I am a well built short guy. Everyone i know who wrestlers says I should wrestle because I'm short yet strong which means it's easier for me to stay level, low center of gravity, and to get into different advantageous positions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, I don't have everyone's character sheets with me. I could have things wrong. I'm trying to find out what the DM should do rather than dissect why his character is OP. I'm fine with his character being OP. My issue is he controls TWO characters that are OP.  I know the DM won't get rid of that character all together. I just wanna know what options I can give the DM.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's game altering because it's used a lot when you don't have enough people. Like less than 4. So I can't say it's rule breaking because everything else online says it's good with the rules  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a cleric who's cantrips which cause damage are 1D8 until lvl 5. My mace is 1d6+5. So 11.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all level 3 currently. We've done modules but every made new characters for this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have his character in front of me so I can't be sure but I believe barbarian for his main but I do know the lowest attack he rolled was a 9 because he commented about it being a bad roll.  He easily does between 15-25 damage every turn, per character, while everyone else's which I will admit aren't as attack oriented do 10 at a max unless using one of their two high level spells.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's put every stat and upgrade possible in constitution (I think that's health type stuff) and strength for one and then for the second switch strength for dexterity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking it up now. It's actually just a second character, which anyone can supposedly do, but he calls it a companion. I think he calls it a companion instead of just another character because it's the bitch boy of the first character and does whatever he wants. But still what I said stands. How do I stop this without being a killjoy because it's killing my joy for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My DM, who knows at least more than me, explained a companion as a secondary character you can make during character creation that you control. This secondary character usually, but not always, is a part of the first characters backstory. The guy made his secondary character as basically a Lydia (skyrim reference) who carries things and does bitch work like reading maps but during character creation made him hella OP in fighting, along with his first character, and my issue is that I don't find it fun or fair that he has two extremely powerful fighters under his control. I posted this hoping to find a way to stop this without being a "dick who just doesn't like that my friend is having fun". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm saying. One guy agrees with me but is quiet, others are too engrossed in their own stuff to care and the DM seems to think it's okay but says he'll fix it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5E and another character which he controls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is 2 full characters. Our DM says I can do the same but I don't want to cuz I feel like it ruins the fun. I wanna roleplay as my cleric and chill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the melee has little intellect and the like but the owner isn't dumb.  The bowman is the best overall. We mainly use him for reading maps and shit we don't wanna waste time on. I like the characters but I need to know how a DM can make it more fair and fun for other characters in battle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do we handle companions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my friends are fairly new at DND. We've all played at most 10 sessions. One friend, who's house we play at, looked up online how to make the best battle character. Which is cool and all since it helps against tough enemies but he made a companion who's equally as powerful but uses a bow instead of melee like the other. Both of these guys are able to one shot every enemy aside from bosses. Me and another character had a "practice fight" where you could be knocked out and revived but not die  against just one of his characters. We both died twice before giving up. How do we handle this huge power they have which usurps all fun during battle? The DM said he'd do something but I doubt he has a clue what to do or will do very little. What can he do? If the monsters get more powerful as needed to harm the two then no one else will be able to do anything and die quickly. How do we handle this because I doubt the DM will want to incur the rage of the house owner if he takes away one of his guys? Or am I just being a baby? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a dungeon master but was apart of the game. We had a guy who's character was a dark elf thieving rogue. So it was pretty obvious my friends high elf lawful good wouldn't like him. We all were in character, maybe the dark elf wasn't. His normal character was very similar to him. After hours upon hours of my friends character being a dick to the dark elf the owner of the dark elf put his head down and started crying. He just wasn't able to understand this was a roleplaying game and no matter what we told him he thought my friend just hated his guts. He has not been invited back to my knowledge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omfg it's so good!!! I'm all upset though because I lost my place so I've been trying to find it forever. 10/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One cum, two cum, red cum, splooge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that you or someone else took the time to draw this makes me want to take a gun, shove it into my butthole and open fire. I'm all for free speech but goddamn. Just goddamn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some compliments people give that you don't know how to respond to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the exact same, I weight lift and am fairly strong with a nice body but if you throw a ball to me I won't be able to catch it 9/10 times. My dad once even considered sending me to a coordination camp, apparently that exists, to fix the issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna sound like an ass but I've said this and youre exactly right. It's usually because I don't feel like I can be myself around a lot of women because a few bad eggs are assholes about me having a penis so I almost feel ashamed when talking to ones that I don't know if they are that way. For me atleast it just means I enjoy your presence and am not worried about scrutiny over small things anymore. It's weird how a few assholes can really cause you to subconsciously be stigmatized to a group.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 17:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the anime machi says it but in the manga the narrator does. Hisoka can't tell how strong others are compared to him because he thinks himself is the strongest to be. He even thought he would be stronger than the chairman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh damn I wasn't aware of that. Thanks for explaining it so nicely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does it say he can die if he uses emperor time too much? I was under the assumption that it comes on whenever he has scarlet eyes so he could train while angry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 14:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ging. We both love The thrill of a mental challenge. Also I'd leave my son in a heartbeat if I think my staying would be detrimental to him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 14:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emperor time is so powerful because with it kurapika could make a separate hatsh using all types which could arguably be EXTREMELY OP. His ability is all about potential. Imagine if kurapika trained even half as much as netero while having all the nen types. Too strong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
