<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "wahhhh I think Bernardi is a bigoted shitlord so this didn't happen" is a pretty weak argument

Agreed, though Bernardi (and his pals) being a bigoted shitlord is a good reason for Gichuhi to refuse the invitation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You live in the Big Banana Fun Park?


That explains a lot.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll have to pry it...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your proposal is acceptable. Location? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tubers in general are quick to believe that which they wish to be true.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you say Dutton frequently [chymes](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chyme) in unwisely?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spud pro quo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has an unlimited supply of dead cats cling-wrapped in his pockets.

Even this discussion now is a distraction from the rest of the LNP's economic faux pas, and won't distress most LNP voters at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Georgina Tunny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A modern day Guy Fawkes with a better sense of timing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kiwis should definitely be given special status in Australia.


Like a Kiwi hunting season, you mean? Could be entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never underestimate the stupidity of muricans.

[;-)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vWcEUPIQNJA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very soon APVMA Private, a division of Monsanto, will ensure approvals are much faster.

It'll cost more, of course, so pesticide companies will get taxpayer subsidies to ease the burden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labour have placed the Liberals in a position where they have to effectively;

* Do nothing

* Agree with Labour

* 1-up Labour (by say wholly axe-ing negative gearing)

or:

* Negotiate with Labor and crossbenchers to release an effective and sensible budget that addresses the most pressing issues in a fair and equitable way.

Nah, just kidding. Your options are the only viable responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA moving Opportunity rover to 'Perseverance Valley' to see Martian erosion in action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it part of the Star Wars franchise?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given Australia doesn't have any official language, Truffle/Dutton/Hanson should draft a policy called "language dictation test", which would allow the government, at the discretion of the minister, to block migrants by forcing them to sit a test in "English or any indigenous language".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OneNation squared?

Nope, FTFY: 

OneNation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scott Ludlam's comment in the GQ interview is on point, as usual:


**Describe Tony Abbott in three words.** 

Sad and pointless. 

**Why wont he go away?**

I just dont think he has the imagination to go away  and what other life has he got apart from this? I think he actually cuts quite a sad figure these days. He had his moment, he was shit at it and they got rid of him before the Australian people could dispatch him. And thats what hes got to live with. 


http://www.gq.com.au/success/opinions/scott+ludlam+malcolm+right+wingers+gq+interview,50235 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTFY:

As long as the department no longer works, privatise to a LNP sponsor and refund to 300% of original cost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ethics?


Nah, just kidding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a man.

The rest could still be true.

http://www.news.com.au/lifestyle/real-life/news-life/man-says-he-was-speeding-so-he-could-get-to-nandos/news-story/708c54b357f19d4d49859d88c7ebbe27 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 10th Anniversary iPhone Sounds Like A Samsung Clone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Chinese Microsoft Store is selling Xiaomi Android phones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be cheap as well. They'll be able to reopen [St Josephs and St Marys again](https://www.findandconnect.gov.au/guide/wa/WE00945). 

Dunno about Moore River though. The new owners might not see it in the same light.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Enthovens will probably pick up her tab and thank her for the free advertising.


Speaking of which, some sneaky Kiwi has edited the Nandos Wiki page to show [Australia as a subregion of New Zealand](http://imgur.com/a/Wp6dF)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be a large geodesic dome on either side, to better illustrate the true goals and dreams of Gold Coast property developers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.

I'm a cynical prick, but even I have to admit there's definitely a scale of self-interest, with Libs and Nats being worst, and Labor not far behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they want to understand that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You win, they did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth it then. He's cost so many other people their livelihoods, it'd be good to see the boot on the other foot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not all of them? That triumvirate, along with a few others, has a lot to answer for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish you'd told me that yesterday.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft will soon be selling Linux-based devices in their US Stores </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 09:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was working on a job in the Pilbara, and the local hotel wouldn't accept a PO for the same reason. We ended up putting accommodation and food for 12 guys on my Amex card, until Amex pulled the pin on me for spending more than $30,000 on a "bar tab".

That took some explaining.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a majority of Australians support it, why are people elected by a majority of Australians scared to support it? The headline doesn't make any sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had family working for airlines, so have had access to family rates. The rules for getting the cheap flights include getting bumped if a full-fare paying passenger needs the seat.

It'd happen occasionally, and I'd take the next available seat. I suspect Australian airlines prioritise fall fare customers over deadheads and staffies, which is why we see fewer issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is something we need real journalists to investigate. Why is our government so desperate to gift Australian  taxpayer money to wealthy foreigners?


It's such a core tenet of the Abbott/Turnbull administration, they have to have a deeper reason than the usual "jobs for the cronies after politics" that drives most of their actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 08:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except blowing it up would actually **be** cheaper.

No point doing it if you can't launder a big bunch of taxpayer money into a future employer's pockets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would.

There's no way he'd make them pay for it themselves, even with a billion bucks subsidy. He'd make the army lift it with taxpayer Chinooks, and probably slip the asylum-seeker populations of Nauru and Manus under it before they dropped it back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll take a bit. One of the reasons Chinese buyers are getting into Australia is that their bubble is even bigger. 

http://www.newgeography.com/content/004576-housing-affordability-china </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 08:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should be jailed for corruption.

Morrison actually said: 

"You cannot make the reckless 'trust us' assumption, as the Labor Party have done, that making significant changes to negative gearing would not have a negative impact on rents and the availability of rental stock."

This from the man who's desperate to reduce corporate tax despite refusing to show any evidence that it will make Australians better off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of us as a first iteration. 

And like most people, I blame everybody else except myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still apparently not a path to a baked-crust scenario:

Conceivable levels of human-made climate forcing could yield the low-end runaway greenhouse. A forcing of 1216 W m2 would require carbon dioxide (CO2) levels to increase 816 times. If the forcing were due only to CO2 change, this would raise the global mean temperature by 1624 C with much larger polar warming. A warming of 1624 C produces a moderately moist greenhouse, with water vapour increasing to about 1% of the atmosphere's mass, thus increasing the rate of hydrogen escape to space. If such a forcing were entirely due to CO2, the weathering process would remove the excess atmospheric CO2 on a time scale of 10^4  10^5 years, well before the ocean was significantly depleted. Venus-like conditions on the Earth require a large long-term forcing that is unlikely to occur until the sun brightens by a few tenths of a percent, which will take a few billion years.[10] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently not likely.

However, simulations indicate that no plausible human-made greenhouse gas (GHG) forcing can cause an instability and baked-crust runaway greenhouse effect.


https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Runaway_climate_change
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just changes the time scale. There have been carbon-driven mass extinction events before.

The Paleocene-Eocene Thermal Maximum (PETM) is the one most similar to what we're going to have happen, and we're in the process of putting the same materials into the atmosphere, just a lot faster than nature did back then.

A few million years afterwards, there'll be a whole new ecosystem full of wonderful things. You should hang around, it could be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't work that way. We'll just make the place uninhabitable by humans and let the wildlife take over again.

In fact, the long-term result will be an oceanic oxygen-starvation event that will lay down new beds of carbon-rich shales and organic layers that will eventually become coal and oil to fuel the next cycle. 

Hopefully our replacements will do a bit better.


http://www.bgs.ac.uk/discoveringGeology/climateChange/greenHouseEarth.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't like the trend.

https://data.oecd.org/hha/household-disposable-income.htm

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the owner of the phone requested and paid for it, then clearly it's authorised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The burial grounds are already overflowing. 

They're also trying to hide the family trust scam that lets them invest in businesses that directly benefit from their portfolios.

Transparency chief executive Serena Lillywhite said:  "This may explain why it's taken so long for a regime to be developed to clamp down on the use of trusts and shell companies".

http://www.smh.com.au/national/investigations/maybe-this-is-why-politicians-wont-act-on-family-trusts-20170406-gvfctr.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't collapse like the US. Our banking and debt resolution structure is very different, so our collapse will be somewhat unique.

There are many opportunities for Australia's government to manage the bubble burst to protect homeowners as opposed to investors. The reasons they're not making those choices include most politicians also being the same wealthy developers who benefit from the shameful scam in the first place.

Australians need to ignore the divisive boomer/millennial baiting that's being propagated to mask the real culprits and start working out how to take down the real scammers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actively work to collapse the housing bubble. It's a shameful scam perpetuated by wealthy developers and politicians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you bury Debbie? If she's under the avo, you'll need to fix the soil balance with a few spadefuls of dolomite and some gravel for drainage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple facing court over error 53 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soon WA will be a separate country, free to fly like the Eagles, not tethered to all those turkey states that keep dragging us down.


Free Westralia

Land of the vast horizons,

Land where the reef gold gleams,

For chains awaits thee glory

Dominion of our dreams

We will heal thy wrong

By a justice strong

And our victor song, 

Westralia, Westralia, Westralia shall be free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonorrhea is more popular than syphilis, but I'd still rather not have either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debunked already.



The economic theory only works in times of full employment and a closed system  not when there is excess labour in a globalised economy.


Edit: you can downvote if it makes you feel better but it won't change reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good quote:

The BCA and government keep trotting out dubious Treasury economic modelling that claims more than half the corporate tax burden is borne by workers through lower wages. The modelling has been effectively debunked but a lobbyist hears what he wants to hear and disregards the rest.

The economic theory only works in times of full employment and a closed system  not when there is excess labour in a globalised economy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no native squirrels in Australia. The closest equivalent is a kind of possum called a squirrel glider, but even they had to evolve wings to avoid being eaten.

There's no record of them killing anybody yet.


http://www.arkive.org/squirrel-glider/petaurus-norfolcensis/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got more toys than Teruhisa Kitahara... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man has both legs amputated after white-tailed spider bite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As big a blight as all this Westfarmers spam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you like spam with your spam? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out by a few orders of magnitude.


https://www.reddit.com/r/australia/about/traffic


Spamming here is about the cheapest per-eyeball advertising there is.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't care. They just want name exposure on social media.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have Westfarmers spammers in Ireland as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then what's the answer to the constant Westfarmers spamming team presence here? There's more of them every week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can they be infected by spam, like /r/Australia has been?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now they'll promote this post to the top, to push the anti-spam messages down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can you treat them with to stop them spamming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't care. They just wand you discussing their products. That's why they keep spamming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, OP is a marketer, not a customer. 

This is yet another Westfarmers spam, a little early this week.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Natural gas: How Australia is being screwed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, thing is, Trumble's said he can't work with her, so she's obviously going to have to cave in agree to his demands.


http://www.afr.com/news/policy/industrial-relations/malcolm-turnbull-says-he-cant-work-with-new-actu-boss-sally-mcmanus-20170316-gv06gu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh. I didn't expect this to be needed again so soon.

the BCA and government keep trotting out dubious Treasury economic modelling that claims more than half the corporate tax burden is borne by workers through lower wages. The modelling has been effectively debunked but a lobbyist hears what he wants to hear and disregards the rest.

The economic theory **only works in times of full employment and a closed system  not when there is excess labour in a globalised economy.**

http://www.smh.com.au/business/the-economy/an-inconvenient-truth-gets-in-the-way-of-the-company-tax-cut-chants-20170314-guxhis.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither. I'm a writer, not a fighter. This is a discussion, not a gang war. 

The LGBT people involved want nothing from me, conservatives want millions.

You're welcome to doubt. I'm criticising you for repeating conservative drivel that will cost millions and benefit nobody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's on the backbench undermining his PM and promoting the same kind of drivel you're repeating here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Blood Test for Autism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not angry, he's just hurling deceased moggies onto the table.

The story here is that business leaders are as fed up as everybody else and feel the need to contradict LNP policy. This is the government's putative base telling them they're wrong and should change.

Dutton's feelings on the matter are irrelevant and should be ignored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, Dutton's always got a spare dead cat cling-wrapped in his pocket. 

His response is typically meaningless cant. 


That business leaders feel the need to contradict LNP policy is what's important about this story. This is the government's putative base telling them they're wrong and should change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video of exploding iPhone surfaces amid growing battery safety concerns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 09:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 07:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minimum utility consumption has been used in similar circumstances. This isn't unprecedented.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Dutton and Turnbull got shirtfronted by a gang of business leaders as well.


20 business leaders from banks, finance companies, legal teams, Telstra, Optus, Qantas, Apple, Amex, Holden, accountancy firms and sporting bodies urge him to legislate for marriage equality so the government can get on with its core economic agenda.

http://www.theaustralian.com.au/national-affairs/sparks-fly-as-chiefs-tell-turnbull-marriage-equality-good-for-business/news-story/cc843643440604ee5b794cf5f49c7493 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Principle*. Though there's no surprise there, the principal characteristic of Liberals seems to be a complete lack of principles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not any more. These days it's "Want a Volkswagen but more reliable".

http://www.autocar.co.uk/car-news/industry/skoda-named-most-dependable-uk-car-brand-2016-jd-power-survey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 09:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This quote needs to be pinned to the front of /r/Australia and to ScoNo's forehead.

the BCA and government keep trotting out dubious Treasury economic modelling that claims more than half the corporate tax burden is borne by workers through lower wages. The modelling has been effectively debunked but a lobbyist hears what he wants to hear and disregards the rest.


The economic theory **only works in times of full employment and a closed system  not when there is excess labour in a globalised economy**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clever. They even put Midvale in the right place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abbott wasn't needed to get rid of the mining tax. He was just a handy tool.

In the WA election, there was no equivalent wrecking ball, so the mining companies attacked Grylls directly.


Mr Grylls also says he has no regrets as he wasn't "just applying for a job" and was trying to be a policy maker.

"The people that won the election didn't put a solution forward to the state's finances - the people that did got their heads chopped off," he told the broadcaster.

"I'm happier to have tried to put forward the plan and lose than sit quietly in the corner and win."

He estimates the Chamber of Minerals and Energy spent $5 million on its campaign against the policy,



http://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/latest-news/no-mining-tax-regrets-for-wa-nationals/news-story/91aa6cb2967b3e47d0568340a11072b2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work sets you free! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.


So why are governments so keen to privatise public assets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the free market hasn't slashed power prices (and what to do about it) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 04:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have told Brendon Grylls that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knew. He just hoped you didn't.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it wouldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think I should have added /i /s ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just the pitch. It's mainly the process around preparing, selecting and defending the pitch.

* Curator SB Singh banned Australian players from taking photographs of the wicket on Tuesday

* Singh prepared three wickets for India to choose from, and confirmed to Australian media yesterday that the BCCI is indeed responsible for making the final call.


* In Australia, the concept of choosing or ordering pitches is unheard of, with local curators the sole decision-makers.

Additional comments from journalists include: 

The match pitch looked as though it had been played on, with what appeared like footmarks already present.

there are clearly defined bare patches on this wicket custom made specifically for fellow spinner Ravi Ashwin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so you're outraged at these sorts of headlines.


How do you feel about what's happening in Myanmar? A bit meh?

Killings, beatings, rape, sexual violence, shootings, stabbings, and wholesale destruction of home and property. 52 of the 101 women interviewed reported being raped or subjected to sexual violence. Seven of them were girls who had been gang-raped. Some of the raped girls and women were killed afterwards.

The report contains many personal stories. A woman said, They killed the baby by stomping on it with their heavy boots. Then they burned the house.

A 12-year-old boy said: I was at home with my 13-year old uncle, when the army broke into the house. They beat us with sticks, metal rods and kicks. We were crying, pleading for mercy. An army officer hit me hard with a metal rod on my right arm, causing severe injury. We were dragged out of the house, which was set on fire. My uncle, who attempted to flee was caught, beaten and thrown into a burning house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indian pitch doctors take their craft to a new low in Ranchi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia should consider shorter working week, Greens leader says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Join /r/trees </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.wvcommerce.org/energy/renewable_energy/solar.aspx

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it doesn't. It sounds like faux tech puffery put forward by a marketing committee.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What could possibly be in the diary that's worse than the consequences Brandis is about to face?

[Edit] And look at that. He's off out of the country do discuss the Islamist terror threat. What a surprise.


http://www.news.com.au/national/politics/brandis-faces-contemptofcourt-threat-over-ministerial-diary-foi/news-story/bb0262a5b598bfd282c5cb7ae67117eb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the same ReachTEL who said:


An exclusive ReachTEL poll of almost 1700 residents shows Labor's lead over the Liberals has narrowed to 52-48 on a two-party preferred basis.

The poll results would still see a 9 per cent swing to Labor compared with its 2013 election results, but, crucially, **it would fall just one seat short of the 10 the party needs to win government**.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ca you link to them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been here forever already. All that happened with Mediscare was the faux outrage from the LNP got publicity.

Every era has its children overboard, mosques everywhere, WMD, budget emergency, etc etc. This is no different.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're well aware of how badly they've behaved. That's why they're attacking anyone who points it out.

Paywalled, so open in incognito window, but Anne Hurley's article In the Australian is informative:

However, when I recently became Internet Australias executive chair I was subjected to an unprovoked Twitter assault by one of NBN Cos corporate affairs executives. This was followed by a bizarre attack by NBN Co boss, Bill Morrow, who made false and defamatory comments about me and others at Internet Australia under Parliamentary Privilege.



http://www.theaustralian.com.au/business/technology/opinion/nbn-path-broken-beyond-repair/news-story/2e6c2fb2e51a0294b32d07378de0d324 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd normally agree with you, but Grylls isn't your typical Nats oxygen thief. 


He has a reasonable history of representing his electorate and trying to work for his state instead of corporate interests. He's also made it clear that the WA Nationals won't be a Liberal lapdog, and that he would have no problem forming a coalition with the ALP if their policies aligned.

Now, his loss is going to stand as an object lesson and a frightening example of corporate interference in Australian politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why is Brandis covering up whatever's in his diary?

Whatever it is, it's either something that's worth the risk and publicity of a contempt of court prosecution, or something completely innocuous, and he's trolling Dreyfus hard.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's part of it, though there's also been a litany of Lib incompetence over the past few years. 

The Nats might have picked up more of the slack, but the single biggest spender of the campaign was the mining industry trying to sink Brendan Grylls for suggesting they pay tax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, 10 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't read either article. One was tfa, the other was the nuclear power industry's own numbers. 

Which do you think had inflated costs for wind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kind of interesting.

I based the 15c number on the service life and lifecycle cost of the offer Tesla has made. That suggests either the Hawaiian contract has a 25% profit margin, maybe for reinvestment, or that costs of the grid-scale systems have fallen since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not while you're awake. 

When you're asleep and don't know we're watching, they sound like the cutest little balloon you can imagine.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 08:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 15c/KWh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 07:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an industry average, and includes amortised costs of older plants still being built/running. 

New installs are already below $100/WMh, with onshore costs even lower.

Vattenfall's record-low offshore wind price of 37.2 ore per kWh [49.9 euros/MWh, $53/MWh] for the 600 MW Kriegers Flak project has shown how falling costs and new tenders are spurring intense price competition in the offshore wind market. Other projects, such as those in deep UK waters, are going ahead at higher cost, and this explains why the global benchmark, while falling rapidly, is well above these recent figures from Denmark and the Netherlands.


The unsubidized LCOE for wind energy ranged from $32/MWh to $77/MWh in 2015, 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that article, it's trotted out by nuclear power astroturfers at every opportunity.


Problem is, it was based on Brian Wang's analysis in 2011, and is long obsolete given how much new wind and solar has been installed.


Even when it was written, some of the early criticisms were that it didn't account for lifecycle statistics, which meant that construction fatalities in new renewable industries weighted more heavily than those in nuclear generation, which has been running far longer, as well as unrelated accidents, such as road deaths, that were counted against renewable industries. Likewise fatalities incurred in very small scale remote area, marine, and industrial installs that aren't part of mainstream electricity production were counted against renewables.


TLDR: It's and old and busted news story. You should stop using it and find something better. If you can.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, Did you RTFA? 

This article is about cost, not capacity contribution. It shows that falling construction costs for building offshore turbines makes them as cheap or cheaper than nuclear or coal. The cost is also still falling, making it possible for companies to sell offshore wind power at close to half the price of nuclear.



Vattenfall AB last year agreed to supply power from turbines in the North Sea at 60 euros ($64) a megawatt-hour in 2020. 


EIA estimated the total system cost for an advanced nuclear energy facility to be $108 per megawatt-hour of electricity produced, compared with solar energy at $144 per MWh; and offshore wind at $221 per MWh. Onshore wind is less costly, at $86 per MWh, but its also less efficient.

https://www.nei.org/Master-Document-Folder/Backgrounders/Fact-Sheets/The-Value-of-Energy-Diversity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The inability to backtrack or apologise is somewhat inherent to conservatism.

The researchers concluded that not only are conservatives less prone to apology, but also less moved by someone else's apology.



Hornsey tried to offer initial explanations. It seems that conservatives are more hierarchical and accept power difference more readily. So if I hurt someone lower than me, ach, that's the way of the world.


That lends them a propensity to malicious schadenfreude when the opportunity arises, and some of what we're seeing is basically gloating at the adversity they're creating for those they see as powerless people.

Having said that I have no doubt that all of your choices and more are in play in the current situation. They're not mutually exclusive.



https://www.cnet.com/news/liberals-apologize-more-than-conservatives-study-says/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 06:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of happy it's just a ship for killing people and smashing stuff. 

When I read the headline, I thought it was about an Abbott protege being touted as a new LNP leadership candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of blurred, obscured vocals, guitar distortion, feedback and an indistinguishable undulating wall of sound make it almost impossible to filter. Any conversation recorded next to it would become just part of the mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 06:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you can just play shoegaze or similar music through the speaker when you put it in the microwave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're saying is that "the LNP has... done their homework".

That's adorable! You reckless optimistic fool, you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 10:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter, he's about to hit the big time...

http://www.couriermail.com.au/news/breaking-news/one-in-five-back-turnbull-as-liberal-boss/news-story/ed1316a13599024b1b4358d97180caf4

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
