<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6945</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make them Garden Salsa and throw in a Mountain Dew Code Red an we have a deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I am the Devil, and I am here to do the Devils work."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let the fact that Kyrie Irving thinks the word is flat and the Warriors blew a 3-1 lead distract you from the fact that the Atlanta Falcons blew a 28-3 lead to the New England Patriots in Super Bowl LI.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Kurt Warner is a nice lady!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since the Fappening yeah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I was smoking a cigarette :p  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody know what Trombone Shorty's setlist was at Buffalo last night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be the NFL equivalent of the Sacramento Kings trading Demarcus Cousins to the Pelicans for Buddy Hield, Tyreke Evans and two draft picks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 02:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kawhi and PG13

Kawhi and Draymond

Kawhi and Wall

CP3 and Klay

CP3 and KD

Blake Griffin and Westbrook 

Lebron and KD

Lebron and Curry

Melo and Butler

Curry and Harden

Harden and Melo 

List goes on. 

Brb gotta change my shorts. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I'm glad I actually got to have a civilized discussion on this topic for once. Take care. Fuck the Broncos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it depends on your definition of GOAT. To me, Kareem is the GOAT as far as career goes. Probably the undisputedly best college player ever and has the career accolades and numbers to support him being the GOAT NBA player. On r/NFL you see people argue Moss over Rice because of physical dominance and peak and I feel like it's the same thing with MJ and KAJ. 

Games Played: 1560 (second all time)

Points:	38,387 (first all time) - 24.6 ppg

Rebounds:	17,440 (fourth all time) - 11.2 rpg

Blocks:	3,189 (third all time) - 2.5 bpg

6 NBA champion (1971, 1980, 1982, 1985, 19871988)

2 NBA Finals MVP (1971, 1985)

6 NBA Most Valuable Player (1971, 1972, 1974, 1976, 1977, 1980)

19 NBA All-Star (19701977, 19791989)

10 All-NBA First Team (19711974, 19761977, 19801981, 1984, 
1986)

5 All-NBA Second Team (1970, 19781979, 1983, 1985)

5 NBA All-Defensive First Team (19741975, 19791981)

6 NBA All-Defensive Second Team (19701971, 19761978, 1984)

NBA Rookie of the Year (1970)

NBA All-Rookie Team (1970)

2 NBA scoring champion (19711972)

4 NBA blocks leader (19751976, 19791980)

NBA rebounding champion (1976)

No. 33 retired by Milwaukee Bucks

No. 33 retired by Los Angeles Lakers

NBA's 50th Anniversary All-Time Team

And that's not even including his college stats

TLDR (imo) Moss = MJ, Kareem = Rice
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brb making Lebron Bell in Madden.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao I knew I should've turned off autocorrect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On offense I'd go with either Lebron Bell, Gronk, Julio, Antonio Brown or Rodgers. 

Defense would be so fun honestly. JJ Watt, Aaron Donald, Earl Thomas, Richard Sherman, Suh, Justin Houston, the list goes on. 

In all honesty most if not all NFL players would crush NCAA. But those are the ones I'd like to see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you say that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I see other people saying MJ but you definitely argue that Kareem is also up there for the GOAT. I personally think it's Kareem but I can see why others think it's MJ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last night was double date night for my GF my roommate and his girlfriend. 

We watched:

*The Exorcist 3*

Pretty good honestly. Very tense, atmospheric and after that one jump scare my GF had her head in my chest for the next 20 minutes. Very surprised this one isn't talked about enough. Enjoyed it as much or even a bit more than the original. 

*Banshee Chapter* 

Holy. Shit. This movie was something. From the creepy stress inducing intro to the jump scares that we're just right. The Hunter S Thompson-like character and the sound design. I really liked this movie. Filled me with a sense of dread I haven't felt since the first time I watched Sinister. 

Speaking of...

*Sinister*

The girls hadn't seen this yet, it's in my top 5 for horror movies all time. The music, the acting, the reveal of Bughuul, everything about this movie was great imo except for the scene with that one scene with Ethan Hawke and the children. Love this movie. Love love love love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly? The Eagles. As much as I despise them, their fans, and everything they represent, the city of Philadelphia needs a title. 

Just kidding. 

Redskins. My uncle is a huge redskins fan and I'd love to be able to see the look on his face when they win, he has an inoperable tumor and doesn't have many years left. Actually, fuck Uncle George. 

Let's go with the Giants. I think it'd be funny if Eli ended his career with more rings than Peyton.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 01:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then keep the other team from scoring. 

If a team truly deserves to win then they should have no problem keeping the other team out of the end zone so the offense has a chance to win the game. 

Don't give up a blatant PI call in OT in the most important game of your life.

Don't blow a 25 point lead in the most important game of your life. 

The OT rules are fine. The only reason people are pissed is because the Patriots won again. 

Nobody says shit when this happens in the regular season. Or when it has happened to the Packers 2 (maybe 3) times in the playoffs in the past years since the rule change. It's only because it was the Super Bowl. 

I'd rather have the NFL OT rules than the NCAA. Start every drive at what the 25? Fuck that. Flip a coin, if you get the ball score a touchdown. If you don't, get the ball back and score. 

In a perfect world they'd play a whole extra quarter like NHL playoffs IIRC but that's too much risk for an already dangerous sport and the brass would never approve that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody know what Trombone Shorty's setlist was at Buffalo last night? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 03:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well inm a lumberjck and a big wolf ffan lets go wolf labron and kyle are both god playmakes but whatat is slacking is is constancy. Somtimes i need to havve a beter axe for chipping trees and other limberjacks to helpp even the best lunderjecks make mistakes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kansas State Football 8/10

Kansas State Football with rice 10/10  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 04:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terry Tate: Office Linebacker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Chris Paul

2) James Harden

3) Lebron

4) Draymond Green

5) Anthony Davis

* Bonus 6th man * 

Russell Westbrook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvin Lewis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Mark Sanchez.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK YEAH DUNKIN'

I live in central New York, not a Starbucks to be found unless you go to syracuse. Not only does starbucks patronize everyone that goes in for a regular cup of coffee but they have shit coffee anyway. 

America runs on Dunkin' for a reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 02:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's the moonlight butterfly boss and then there's a section of the late game where there are smaller(?) moonlight butterflies everywhere. 

I think it's a no go unfortunately. :|  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish we could've gotten rid of QB hits before 2015. Poor Romo :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reggie White. Without a doubt. Arguably the greatest defensive player of all time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get a Brady! You get a Brady! Everybody gets a Brady!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's gold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a shame. Understandable but a shame nonetheless. 

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to original? That was an emotional rollarcoaster. I was expecting a fight in the comments  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 23:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're totally friends now. Fuck Bernard Pollard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have pride. But I don't want to not watch football until next year. Go fuck yourself buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 18:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off the top of my head there are none, but the [Soundgarden](https://g.co/kgs/bnmjka)  isn't too far, it's right on Jefferson street! It's a local favorite, place is pretty fucking awesome. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers buddy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like I must not have

REMEMBERED THE TITANS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Why would you ask?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm dehydrated and my mother was an abusive alcoholic. Misanthropy is the result. 

Fuck the Bills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> POLAR EXPRESS! MORE LIKE TOM BRADYS FUCK ROGER GOODELL EXPRESS!

name pending  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My uncle is a Saints fan. His name is Frank. He is a dick. Fuck the Saints.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an Ex that's a Ravens and she claimed you guys cheated in the 2014 playoffs with the ineligible/eligible receiver plays even though IT WAS OKAY IN THE RULES. 

That's not why we broke up, but it wouldn't have been a bad reason. 

Fuck the Ravens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to get a Pats jersey so bad. I want to get someone that I remember from when I was a kid though. 

Someone like Vinatieri or Deion Branch. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh captain my captain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something in my heart is telling me to trash talk you due to your Eagles Fandom, but I'll set it aside for now. 

Go Pats! Fuck the Giants! Fuck the Redskins!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BRONCOS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAY IT WITH ME </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I was expecting somebody to say it. I was just waiting for someone to notice that I didn't remember the titans. Cheers buddy! Go Pats!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a man lmao, but fuck yeah!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand them this year. I don't know if the game has changed too much for Boeheims zone to keep up or if it's a personnel issue, all I know is they've been tough to watch so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man! And I agree. Dak didn't look like a rookie last night. I can't wait to see him next year. 

I'll try and answer these the best I can. 

1) I know we have Tyron signed until 2020, but his cap hit is gonna be a problem in two years. Fredbeard and Martin will be signed soon because their rookie deals are ending. 

2) Pass rush. Without a doubt. Implying we keep Claiborne and Barry Church, Brandon Carr doesn't retire and Byron Jones improves our secondary will be pretty good. They played very well this year and if they all stay then I don't see why they wouldn't improve. 

3) PPR I'd have to go with Shady simply because Dez doesn't get many receptions, although I could be wrong as far as stat comparisons go. I don't play in a PPR league (although my commissioner is going to bring up changing it at our leagues next get together) by I don't think Dez would be an advantage. I would go with Beasley before Dez in a PPR league personally. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Oklahoma State!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... /r/Cowboys is a weird team subreddit. It's all serious, no jokes or shitposts or anything fun. 

Sorry about that :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're god damn right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 02:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the best feeling ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers buddy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grandfather is a Giants fan from Queens. When my dad was little he rooted for the Cowboys (during the Don Meredith and Roger Staubach years) to make my grandfather mad. Dad stayed a Cowboys fan and I became one when he got me into the Triplets and Landry and Staubach when I was little. 

It was cemented when I was 11 and at the Cowboys vs Bills game in Buffalo. Nick Folk kicked a 54(?) yard field goal in the final seconds that was iced, then he kicked the redo even prettier than before, right down the middle. 

I've been going to a Dallas game every other year since. In the off years we go see the Patriots and Bills play because the pats are my Grandmothers favorite team (she's from Boston).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha okay buddy. I was worried for a second. My list is real short though:

1) Cowboys
2) Patriots

The only bad thing is in my twenty years of life I've rooted for New England in the super bowl more than Dallas  not like I've been short of opportunities for the former though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see why it would do that. They're just a team that I like to see do well. Is there a problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Also, FUCK BERNARD POLLARD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feels good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys fan hopping on the bandwagon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was asked who I was going to root for after Dallas lost yesterday. I knew my answer straight off. 

The Patriots. 

Always the Patriots. 

I want to watch every sports pundit, every journalist every non Pats fan on every brand of sports media cry out in agony as the Patriots win their 5th title. 

I want to see YouTube videos of kids in steeler jerseys and Falcons jerseys and packer jerseys alike crying because their favorite team didn't win it all. 

The Patriots are my second team exactly for that reason. One of the greatest dynasties of all time and nobody appreciates that (other than you guys). It seems like once a week ESPN or whoever is trying to poke hole in the Patriots, make them seem like they're washed up, but they just keep killing it. And I love you guys for that. 

I want Brady to cement his legacy as the GOAT (even though we all know he already has). 

I live in Syracuse, New York. Place is crawling with Jets, Giants, Eagles, Bills and Steeler fans. I want them all to suffer.

The only team that gets hated on as much (if not more than) Dallas is New England and I don't want any of you guys to deal with all of the "Fuck you Fuck Dallas" types messages popping up on my phone and on my news feed. 

I want every meme during this offseason to flame all other 31 teams for not being able to stop Brady and BB again. 

That's the only thing that will satisfy me. 

When the world burns after they win, I'll be the first one to play in the ashes. 

Fuck the Bills. Fuck the Bears. Fuck the Bengals. Fuck the Buccaneers. Fuck the Chargers. Fuck the Chiefs. Fuck the Colts. Fuck the Dolphins. Fuck the Eagles. Fuck the Falcons. Fuck the 49ers. Fuck the Jets. Fuck the Jaguars. Fuck the Packers. Fuck the Panthers. Fuck the Lions. Fuck the Giants. Fuck the Raiders, Rams and Ravens. Fuck the Saints. Fuck the Texans. Fuck the Steelers. Fuck the Vikings. Fuck the Redskins. Fuck the Browns. Fuck the Seahawks. Fuck the Cardinals. 

Go Patriots. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patriots. 

Always the Patriots. 

I want to watch every sports pundit, every journalist every non Pats fan on every brand of sports media cry out in agony as the Patriots win their 5th title. 

The only team that gets hated on as much (if not more than) is New England and I don't want any of their fans to deal with all of the "Fuck you Fuck Dallas" types messages popping up on my phone and on my news feed. 

I want every meme during this offseason to flame all other 31 teams for not being able to stop Brady and BB again. 

That's the only thing that will satisfy me. 

When the world burns after they win, I'll be the first one to play in the ashes. 

Go Patriots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I deleted Facebook off of my my phone after the game specifically because everyone is jerking it to the final score. It makes me think of how boring other people's lives have to be to hate on Dallas for entertainment. 

I can even post a "GG Packers" without getting flamed on FB. 

I thought I was immature. But there are legitimate adults cussing me out on Facebook for being a Dallas fan. 

Feels bad man, I'm only 20 so they haven't been champions since before I was born and I still get shit for it. 

But it'll be okay, because one day we'll be on top again and it will be fucking glorious. I'm never gonna stop bringing up our next super bowl win. Fuck all the haters. WeDemBoys

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charles Woodson for Michigan. 

Marvin Harrison for SU

Honorable mention to Prince Tyson-Gulley for his amazing game in the Pinstripe Bowl against WVU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you guys live where you have data caps?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Color Rush Tyron Smith.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a glorious dream that would be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wolf Cola </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You let your kids drink Jack?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting a promotion at the nursing home I work at which includes a $2/hour raise, straight days and full insurance. 

Finally completed two months of living on my own after two years back home due to dropping out of college. 

My therapist says all signs of my depression are gone for the most part so I don't have to be put on medication anymore. Just biweekly counseling. 

I survived 2016 after attempting to take my own life in 2015. 

Got the phone number of a nurse I work with that I've been crushing on for months, she's coming over for the CFB championship next week. 

Pretty alright I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 12:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like /u/horrorshowjack had said, Irvin retired in the top ten in receptions and yards. However, he was also one of the Cowboys "Triplets" that won 3 Super Bowls. 

He was one of (if not THE) most aggressive receiver of his time. It didn't matter where the ball was, if it was anywhere near him he was going to find a way to catch it. They didn't call him the Playmaker for nothing. This was all also in an era where receivers were getting mauled down the field during the play. 

Also, he had 5 Pro Bowls and 3 AP awards (one first team and two second team). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was tough once I got past Tier 3

Tier 1: Jones, Beckham, Brown

Tier 2: Green, Hopkins, Evans

Tier 3: Bryant, Landry, Nelson

Tier 4: Hilton, Cooper, Fitzgerald

To be completely I could probably consolidate 3 and 4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 00:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Eagles can get a receiving threat or two in the offseason they're going to be tough next year, especially with Wentz getting some more experience under his belt. 

Also, for Eagles fans, what's your guys' RB situation? Are Sproles and Mathews gone after this year?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 01:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm up 107.3 to 96.8. 

He has Zeke. I have DT. 

Im Nervous as all hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Big XII of the NFL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny enough. My entire [lineup](https://imgur.com/gallery/TuMdp) besides my defense was drafted by me, if I played the Bengals D it'd be my whole team. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jerry Jones firing Jimmy Johnson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the red dot? I used to have directv and I can't remember what it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 00:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God dammit. It's gonna happen again isn't it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McNabb. I live in syracuse and always loved watching him play. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 16:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WE WANT BAMA  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. But I have family that went to Michigan. 

Grandfather, uncle and two cousins. 

It just came naturally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $250,000 is more than double what my parents house is worth, so I'd say it'd be a pretty good one here. 

My grandmothers is worth about half a million and that's a 4 bedroom 3 bathroom with an inground pool, two car garage, a furnished basement and a pretty big backyard with a pond in the back. 

I think my uncles old house was worth about 200k and was 3 bed 2 bath with an above ground pool, 2 car garage. 

I'd say somewhere in that range. I'd say a $250,000 where I live would get you one of the nicer houses in the city. 

I live in a small college near Lake Ontario for reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember those days. My favorite game was Combat Arms by nexon. So many hours wasted playing the zombies mode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> QB - Roger Staubach

HB - Emmitt Smith

FB - MOOOOOOOOSE

TE - Witten

TE - Novacek

WR - Irvin

WR - Dez

WR - Pearson

LT - Tyron 

LG - Larry Allen

C - Frederick

RG - Zack Martin

RT - Rayfield Wright 

HM

Terrell Owens

Tony Dorsett

Raghib Ismail

I would've put TO on the first team but he wasn't a career cowboy (even though he set our season record for TDs)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 07:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Witcher 3. 

The story is cool. The game is beautiful. The characters are great. But I cannot stand the combat. 

It felt too button mashy for me. Like I was just trying to press square faster than the AI could attack me. 

The weird thing though is that the combat in Skyrim didn't bother me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised tbh. That game against you guys showed that Zeke and the Oline CAN be stopped, but it also showed that there is more to the Dallas Offense than Zeke. 

For what it's worth, I think you guys have the best D in the league. Weddle was a great signing by you guys, any word on Jimmy Smith? If he's healthy you guys will be able to slow down anybody. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 08:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would root for tOSU for a new NCAA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 08:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bama is alright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 21:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. But as we saw last year with TCU, the committee is pretty fuckin whacked sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 20:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Alabama (I don't think a loss will knock them out, not due to personal belief but I don't think the commute would do it)

2) Clemson (Barring a loss) 

3) Ohio State (again, I don't think the committee will bump them, could be decided by the B1GCG)

4) Washington (could be the B1GCG winner, we'll see) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 22:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it'll probably even out if he gets more carries as the season goes on, but as it stands this year he's only averaging 3.8 YPC which is half a yard less than his career average. 

Obviously it doesn't mean much seeing as he only has 61 carries, but it's not great considering some people think "anyone can behind that Oline." Evidently Morris hasn't been doing well. 

That being said, I don't think he's mediocre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 08:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add rather watch a Golden Retriever than Fitzpicksix this year /s

All kidding aside, unfortunately I haven't watched many Jets games (I usually watch them when Dallas isn't on since I live in Syracuse but I've been working too much) what's changed for him? Is he just having a down year or what? I figured he'd perform a lot better considering you guys added Forte.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 05:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. Reffing was awful. After the 2PC attempt I was cursing Thortons name and it wasn't even flagged, fucking stupid, and this is coming from a guy who's team benefited from that. 

This is gonna come back to bite us just like the 2014 Playoffs. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 08:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's embarrassing lmao. My apologies!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 08:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 08:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shame Bowlen was dealt the hand he was dealt. He's a great man. Fuck Alzheimer's. 

EDIT: Bowlen not Bowles. Oops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chip Kelly played wide receiver?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the people we've played against seem like they're in their 60's (not that I'm one to talk, I'm not that good haha).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Like I said above I knew about the rank decay but must have missed the rank reset. 

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. That was the thing i was most concerned with. 

I knew about Rank decay but didn't know if it was permanent. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I eat back into gold nova? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't a shit post or troll post. I'm genuinely curious. 

Before I stopped playing CSGO (around April 2015) I was GN Master. I finally got my rank back two nights ago after getting to Rank 2 and it put me in silver 1. 

Now I understand there's rank decay and all, but is that normal? 

I'm stuck in silver now and I don't want to brag but it isn't even fun. My friends and I were all GN 3/Master and we're all in low silver. Games end in 20-30 minutes and we'll be in the 60s or 70s as far as our score goes. 

Ive played about 10 matches since then, winning all of them and being top two in the scoreboard in each one and I've only gotten to Silver 2. 

Is there a "Rank match" where I only rank up after X amount of wins? If so that's understandable. I don't mind playing more seeing as I'm going to be playing a few games after work every day anyway. I just want to know why it takes so long. 

And again, this isn't a troll. And I might be complaining a bit but I'm just confused. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Offense: 

Larry Allen just because I want to see Zeke rush for 2500 yards. 

Irvin (or Terrell Owens if he counts) so we can have an elite WR across from Dez. 

Emmitt Smith for a two headed monster rushing attack. 

Defense: 

Charles Haley, Randy White ,Too Tall Jones or Bob Lilly for Dline help. 

Deion Sanders or Darren Woodson for secondary help. 

Demarcus Ware for pass rush :( 

Special Teams: 

Raghib Ismail for kick and punt returns. 

If I had to pick one it'd be Ware so long as we got him in his prime, if not then I'd really like to see Irvin across from Dez.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
