<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4538</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a 19 year old staying up to write two assignments. I'll answer any question you throw at me! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 08:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do do da doo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 15:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I just failed the accounting test I had today, but it's only the third week of school so if I work hard I can make up for it with the next test. I'm going out to Roosters tonight with my friends and I'm having some vodka gummy bears Friday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 05:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? I'd be down for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let me just shout out into the void real quick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or that's what this feels like anyway. I dunno. I feel really stupid. I told myself I'd be better but I do that all the time, so it doesn't really carry any meaning.
I skipped my morning class today cuz it looks dumb heading into class crying all the time.
Maybe I should've traveled around more before coming here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wonderful thing about tiggers, is that I'm the only one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had a whole episode on Arthur about her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fairly short at the moment, only a few inches past my ears, but I'll definitely try it when it gets to shoulder length and longer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so beautiful! Really makes me want to grow my hair out so I can try this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People don't want to struggle anymore. There's this general feeling of apathy, especially (maybe mostly) among the younger generation. I don't know a single person my age who actually likes either of our political candidates. There's terrorist attacks in foreign countries and police brutality in ours. There's no optimism, no clear good guys and bad guys. And this is just general stuff that's happening in the world today, I'm not even talking about personal problems we all have. Self-esteem issues, body image issues, etc. Why should we try to push through our problems and self-medicate with other crap when we can take a pill to help us through it? I take antidepressants and I can count over ten people I know easily that take them, not even including close friends. I'm not saying we take prozac to help us deal with politics, but when you've got your own issues with depression and the world seems like it's going to shit and every other friend's on prozac, you give in after a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue raspberry is the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank u my beautiful son </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true, I died with an elderly Indian woman looking through my vagina. It was neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking the pill messes me up cuz of the hormones, and the copper iud has none. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm alive! Sort of! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Edit: They weren't able to put it in :( my cervix opening is closed up, so they gave me some drugs and told me to come back in a few days and they'll try again. Sorry y'all :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things. Many things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am literally about the have a copper IUD put in me, AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 15:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang, that looks beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the elections in the US are rigged. I can't remember the details, but there was a mathematician or something who said it was very easy to mess with electronic voting machines and alter the results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither of them can truly "fuck up the US" in the ways that people imagine. We don't live in a dictatorship. Some kind of oligarchy, maybe, but not a dictatorship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fila flip flops in the summer and then in the winter usually my old black vans or my beat up timberlands I found at Plato's Closet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burritos definitely, but soft shell tacos are rad too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same man! It's really nice to hear actual positive things about us :') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg I wanted to try these when I was like 9, they looked so cool :o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a good set of shoulders is nice. Broad shoulders and strong arms and back are very appealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 16:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does this even mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 21:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg I loved this game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sound so arrogant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 06:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fried chicken and a waffle, a bowl of orzo noodles with Parmesan cheese, butter, and salt, a slice of tourtire, and a chocolate milkshake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oui seigneur!! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow, I've never actually had poutine nor have I ever watched a game of hockey in its entirety, so I can't really say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh, my bad. I didn't know that! It's been on my "to-read" list for a while now. Thank you for reminding me of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 01:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean traveling? Or driving in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 22:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> French-Canadian-American. I love maple syrup, my entire family is from Qubec and we all speak slang-filled, "hillbilly" French at home. I apologize when someone bumps into me. Some of my favorite foods are tourtire, smoke-meat sandwiches, and maple cookies. My dad routinely complains about American culture. I don't think a single person in my family (immediate and extended) is religious, but almost everyone over the age of 40 was raised Catholic and left the church (and home) when they were teenagers. I also get really sad when I see people complaining on the internet about how Qubcois people are awful or rude :(. I guess some of us are jerks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Never-Ending Road by laventadorn. It's a Harry Potter fic that basically rewrites nearly the entire series where Harry's actually a girl and has a crush on Snape. It sounds ridiculous by the premise, but it's probably my favorite fic ever. It's really well-written and fleshed out, and manages to be heartwarming even when the situation's grim. Snape is also fantastically snarky.
Edit: link - http://archiveofourown.org/works/536450/chapters/952621 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 03:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, same. I've been reading The Never-Ending Road for a while now and even if it's not really smutty at all, I can't exactly say to people, "Hey, I'm reading a fanfiction about an alternate version of Harry Potter where he's a girl and has a crush on Snape. You should totally read it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *have* been told I'm a good therapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole Tom Hiddleston/Taylor Swift thing going on is weirdly engrossing. I saw speculation that it's for a new music video, and I honestly hope that's the case cuz all the stuff I've seen about their relationship seems weird so far. Tom's "I heart T Swift" shirt, how publicized everything seems to be, already meeting the parents, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mandarin or Cantonese or Russian. I speak English and French the best and can hold a solid conversation in Spanish, so latin languages aren't too hard. But learning a language with a totally different set of characters/alphabet is difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it depends on the pajama pants tbh. If they can pass for regular sweatpants or joggers or something, they're alright. But if they look like genuine pajama pants, I'd leave them at home.
It also depends on the time of day. If it's early morning or late at night, I wouldn't really judge, but it's 4 in the afternoon it's a little weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. I should look into the other machines and exercises and see what's interesting when I go. I've mostly stuck to the treadmill just cuz I feel like it's my main "problem area" - my stomach is flat and my arms are lean, but my thighs are pretty flabby rn. Thanks for replying :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man :) you're totally right. I guess it's easy to think everyone's making judgements, but in reality they're more occupied with their workout than how this person or that one looks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every day I tell myself I'm gonna go to the gym, and every day I don't. It's so dumb. About half my reasons for not going are dumb excuses (my hair looks bad, I'm sleepy, I didn't wake up early enough, etc.) and the other half are insecurities (my legs look bad and I'll get judged, I'll look lazy and unhealthy for only jogging on the treadmill compared to the other girls my age). It's ridiculous. I'm not even overweight, I'm on the lower end of the bmi for "normal", but I still look bad because I'm not toned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 05:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aliexpress (although thoroughly check reviews and sizing first) and h m are excellent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 03:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I got raised in the US though, and I remember after learning English in school, by about 2nd grade I'd argue with my parents over speaking English at home instead of French because it was easier to me. English is so straightforward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Female 5'4". Most - 115, Least - 100. My weight doesn't change too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 18:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first started having sex, it was pretty terrible. I tried both in relationships and in open pseudo-relationships (fwb) and whatnot and it was uncomfortable in every way. Strangely, I was actually very sex-positive and my family was very much not religious, but I still hated sex the first few years. I would agree to it only because it was offered and I didn't want to seem lame and say no. The idea of sex was nice, but as soon as he or she would enter me it was terrible. At best, it was mildly uncomfortable and boring, even if they were eating me out, and at worst, with penetration, it was horribly painful and still very boring, no matter how attentive and sweet they were. Nothing felt good. I would go from being extremely wet to mentally planning out my schedule for the week within minutes. I've only been able to legitimately enjoy sex with my current boyfriend, and I think part of may have been this mental block I developed on it and the association of all the other unpleasant times I agreed to sex for the benefit of the other person.
Tl;dr Don't be like me and spend three years agreeing to sex even if you don't enjoy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 19:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not gonna disagree with you man, there's definitely women out there that live their lives like this. But the way you write about it, it's like you've got this personal vendetta against them. It's a bit creepy. I don't think that was the tone you were going for, but it's what you conveyed all the same. Especially that bit at the end about the "little piggies".
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't doing well last semester so I got an email saying I had to have a meeting with a counselor and get a physical evaluation. I did neither of those things during the semester and from talking to my RA director, it didn't seem mandatory anyway. Fast forward to early june - I get an email saying I now absolutely have to get those two appointments done by July 15th or else my fall classes will be canceled.

I got the counselor meeting done on Sunday in secret with the help of my boyfriend driving me (I live very far from campus), but now I have to go to a doctor to get a physical and bloodwork. I don't even have a current doctor, and I haven't been to one in years anyway. There's no means of doing this without my dad finding out cuz my parents'll get billed for it. It's absurdly stressful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 22:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was one of my favorite actors :( I honestly really liked him. This is really surprising. Rest in Peace Anton :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, no. My periods aren't too bad, and added to that I already feel kinda bad when I turn my boyfriend down for sex when I'm not in the mood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, no. My periods aren't too bad, and added to that I already feel kinda bad when I turn my boyfriend down for sex when I'm not in the mood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -That extra little bit of fat that sticks out on my inner thighs when I wear shorts. I managed to get rid of it for a while in 11th grade when I started running a lot. Trying to get back into it so I can lose it again!

-My face shape has always seemed weird to me. It's sorta oval or rectangular-ish and it bugs me. I wish it was more heart-shaped.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boxer briefs are pretty awesome. They let me appreciate my boyfriend's thighs and I like the material they're made out of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, none.
Unless there's some extenuating circumstances, there's usually some pretty good reasons why they're your ex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 00:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part of Montreal tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 17:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burn Gorman, Alan Rickman (RIP), Jeremy Irons, Idris Elba. I don't think these are too weird but I'm 19 too so they're all way older than me haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 04:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was awesome. Super innovative and honestly a joy to just look at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm worried about being a finance major </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 20:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I chose finance as my major largely because I didn't much like my other options. I genuinely love theology, art, psychology, and linguistics, but there's no real guaranteed, well-paying jobs in those fields. So what fields do offer those jobs? Medicine, mathematics, physics, engineering, IT, and finally, finance. I took classes in high school in each of those other fields and didn't really enjoy them except for economics and such, so I picked finance.
Now I've heard finance is a very difficult field to get a job in. I don't know how to make myself more valuable, I guess, for a company to want to hire me eventually.

I'm 19 and I'm curled up in my bed like a child. I'm not set to take any actual finance courses until after the coming semester. I'm worried for the future.

What can I do to help prepare myself for a career in finance? Are there any certificates I could get online this summer?

I thought about posting this in /r/finance but that sub seems to be mostly made up of news articles and such, not whiny questions from confused students.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 19:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad Burn's nice, I love that man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 06:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably got the stomachache from a combination of stress and spicy food.
If I don't do the homework, I'll collapse into a little pit of self-loathing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 06:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'll try anything at this point. I'll update on how it goes when I get some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 06:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a mix of having a mcdonalds frappe and really spicy ramen in the past two hours, plus nerves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've got a bad stomachache but I've gotta stay up all night to do homework, so AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 05:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please keep me awake, y'all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the past few weeks, my depression got really bad and I was considering attempting suicide again.  A friend of mine told the RA Director I wasn't doing well, and the lady had a meeting with me the next day. It helped immensely. She was extremely kind without being patronizing like some counselors do (e.g. "you're such an inspiration!") and she filed an incidence report for me telling the counseling team and the dean of students about it. In the same two days or so, I talked more about it to some of my friends and my parents and they were really supportive. I feel so much better - like I'm not so afraid of failure any more. I feel loved. I've got this big support group now. I have a list of things to complete - seeing a counselor, doing old math homework, etc - and people who love me and encourage me as I do them.
:') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't feel close to my mom at all sometimes. Especially right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 00:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno if this is normal or not. I'm 19, away at college. My mom came down to have dinner with me cuz she had a business thing going on in a nearby town.
I don't really want to have dinner with her. I don't have anything I really want to talk about. I'd rather go hang out with my friends or work on homework. I don't want to force small talk - it'll just make her uncomfortable/feel unhappy because it's a reminder our relationship isn't close.

She's just an automaton. My dad wins the arguments with her at home cuz he shouts the loudest. Sometimes he makes her cry, though I guess I've done the same. She cries more easily though. She works all the time, long hours. He makes her feel insecure about her weight sometimes cuz his sisters are teeny tiny (they fit into children's clothes, no lie).

She lets herself get walked over. She never stands up for herself in arguments with him. If I fight with him, I stand up for myself! I fight back just as hard and just as loudly as he does, and sometimes I win. Even if I don't, at least I put up a fight. She doesn't. It's sad. It makes it hard to respect her.

I recognize that this isn't normal. The home dynamic is skewed. I guess my dad could be classified as emotionally abusive, or at least he was up till a few years ago.

I'm just frustrated. Sorry. I just wanted to get this out. I swear, I'm not spoiled - I've never directly told her this stuff. I'm respectful in person.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody got examples of a person doing an incredible amount of work in a short period of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 01:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 01:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...The part where you didn't pass ain't too inspiring  man, but I'll take what I can get. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have any examples of accomplishing crazy things in a short amount of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 00:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta pull an all nighter tonight, no way out of it. I would really appreciate stories or personal anecdotes of people doing incredible amounts of work under pressure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 18:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on how far along technology has come for robot arms. Could I have a bionic arm, or an automail arm like ed from fullmetal alchemist? Cuz that'd be pretty sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! :) This is helpful.
I'll do my best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess so. I tried killing myself about a year ago, but it didn't work. I can't kill myself now. My boyfriend loves me too much. I can't do that to him.
A few weeks ago I went on birth control and I've been really depressed since then, more than normal. I think the hormones messed me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect the man who wrote that. My grandpa and grandma (on opposite sides of the family) both suffered for too long before their deaths. I don't want my parents to die like they did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk. My perspective on everything. I need to go running more. I need to stop cutting in the shower. I need to do better in my classes -I gotta talk to my math professor and my lit professor today. I need to stop calling the suicide hotline and hanging up on them cuz I get too scared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 to 6. It's not bad. But it was due two days ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An argument for assisted suicide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am an 18 year old girl writing a paper today and trying to get my shit together, ama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 16:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I don't want to bug you though or anything, seriously. I know how draining it is to talk to people who wanna die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I'm always living for other people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First it was for my parents. Then my girlfriend. Then my next girlfriend. Now my boyfriend. If I were to die, he'd struggle. He'd be sad and beat himself up for it. He loves me so much.

But it's never for myself. I'm not living for myself. I'm so selfish. I should be dead. I waste resources. I'm a waste of time, effort, money, love. People don't get back what they put in me. I'm like a malfunctioning vending machine. That's kinda funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 18:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. 18F here. Pretty sure I'm messed up. Low spatial awareness, anxiety, clinical depression, and probably an eating disorder. It's a matter of time. In theory, I could do it now, but I've got a boyfriend who loves me too much - I can't do that to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 21:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pine trees, wood cabin, buttermilk, homemade soap, dusty carpet, ground coffee, dusty church carpets, concrete after rain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 13:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, we ain't all bad. I'm sorry if you've had bad experiences with some of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 18:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should probably check if my oatmeal's ready. I also gotta do the four math assignments online - really, I just need to get them over with. They're not too hard, just long and tedious. I hope I don't have to take the test on paper when I get back at school. It'd be way easier to do it online.
I wonder when Syberia 3's gonna come out. And is the new nancy drew game gonna be any good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 16:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm alright, I think. I used to be self-absorbed, but now I think I'm not. I try not to shove my problems onto people, I try not to discuss my problems unless they are relevant and/or asked about in conversation. Sometimes I think I'm awful, other times I'm okay.
My boyfriend looks at me with all this love in his eyes and it's the best feeling ever - I hope I can be what he sees in me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 19:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, this is absurdly beautiful. The outfits, her makeup - she looks like a princess!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 23:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, I love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 00:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stepping on legos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm so concerned with what my dad thinks of me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 16:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Remorse]: If you feel bad 

He basically raised me. Almost all of my childhood memories involve him in some way cuz he stayed home while mom worked. He's been the main influence on me throughout my whole life so far. I'm not close to my mom.

I'm clinically depressed. I can point fingers and say he started it by pushing me at school to be smarter than I actually am, and berating me when I couldn't meet his standards. He's caring. He'd spend hours helping me memorize and study and review things. He's always tried explaining things like how the stock market works and how to fix a car, but I was never interested enough and couldn't pay attention, or I'd forget what I'd learned within days.

I'm never good enough for him man. Never ever. There's always something. My head's always in the clouds. I'm very spacey and clumsy. I'd study for hours to remember and do well on stuff other people could understand in just one. Even when I got high grades, 95s and 100s, they had to be higher, come on, why can't you do better, are you stupid or what?

Why do I fixate on this so much? Why does it bother me so much that I can't be the daughter he wants me to be? I'm 18. I'm supposed to be adult, he says. But I can't do it. I feel like I'm so defective. I don't think like an adult. I'm not observant and I'd rather live in my head or in a book or a movie than in real life.

Outwardly, I'm okay. I'm lean and fit. I have good hygiene, and I've been told I'm attractive. I guess I could be a housewife or something. Despite my parents' best efforts to make me independent and modern, I genuinely wouldn't mind it. I don't really enjoy sex, but I'm okay with going through it to make the other person happy. I could do that.

God, I'm sorry for writing all this out. This is terribly depressing. I tried killing myself a year ago but it didn't work. I only took 40 pills cuz I was scared I'd take too many and end up in that limbo where they can keep me alive but I'm brain damaged or a vegetable. Shit I'm supposed to hang out with someone today. But I feel bad cuz it means I'm gonna have to lie about it cuz my dad doesn't like that friend. I just wanna curl up in a hole.

Man I'm sorry about writing all this. I've talked about it on reddit before and now I just feel like I'm complaining. I'm not even good at replying to PMs cuz it feels like I'm actively complaining to a person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 22:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, this is me exactly. I can imagine sex and get off from it sometimes (not these days, but definitely in the past) but the act of sex is terribly boring and does nothing for me "down there", if you will. And if it's with a guy it's pretty damn painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 02:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To reduce greasiness, make sure you massage the shampoo throughout all of your hair as well as you can, and then rinse thoroughly.

Idk if there's any way to really make your hair thicker, but I've heard taking biotin and multivitamins can help, at least with the overall healthiness of it.

I've also heard dry shampoo - the kind that's in the aerosol can, like a hairspray - is helpful in adding volume and reducing grease, so you could try that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
