<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject757</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the classic joke...I assume everyone knows - once you have knowledge, you no longer have a choice. The reference above was him saying people went "somewhere in between" and me assuming that meant people went to purgatory, which I believe is a catholic concept. 


^("then why did you tell me??") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purgatory in the Bible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catholic school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys crack my shit up. 

Amazing foresight for a username 5-years-ago btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what other purpose you would expect a subreddit dedicated to Biden to serve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The university is 100% liable in this case. They are lucky he doesn't have a lawsuit for not protecting his PII sufficiently. I suspect after a lawyer sees this article this story may continue though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Relgious semantics' are just some of the hundreds of roadblocks, false paths and propaganda on this sub. If you chose to follow a path that leads to discussion about religous semantics you always have the choice to break it off at any time and choose a different path. There are an infinite number of paths and every one is at a different stage of their journey. 

You've decided what's best for you in regards to content; let other folks do the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll stand by a comment like that all day long. It shits all over the assigned narrative they need to propagate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems expensive. 

I feel like if I shitposted it it were my job I would have no problem knocking out multiple 1K+ posts daily just by sheer volume as many of the bots on reddit do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have lots of opposing views in this subreddit. It's the lube that keeps the machine working. If you don't like to deal with dissenting opinions there are safer spaces to express your ideas available to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [No shortage of videos](https://www.youtube.com/results?search_query=jeff+sessions+inauguration+protests). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clickbait: A 61-year-old woman who showed up in her vagina outfit with her KKK buddies with the intent to cause a disruption and be arrested, caused multiple disruptions and was arrested.

She was then charged and convicted of her crimes in a court of law.


edit: [videos for the doubters](https://www.youtube.com/results?search_query=jeff+sessions+inauguration+protests) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personal attack in response to a factual comment. It appears your argument needs work. 

Have an upvote and try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since their migrant population has increased by more than 50% they can rest assured they are on the virtuous path.

At least they aren't racists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Embassy cat is so confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Hannity and a cameraman are exactly two, and if anyone would "take one for the team" to help Assange, Hannity would be at the top of that list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5th amendment and all that. All fun and games until the grand jury. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would be doing better than most in America in that case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears there is a claim that [Theophilus London](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Theophilus_London), "started doing heroin plus you a whole child molester". Furthermore, [Mr. Ian Connor](http://nymag.com/thecut/2016/06/ian-connor-rape-fights.html) and Mr. London appear to have some history. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't understand why this is important.

Clearly. 

My point is that it appears that a private citizen was trying to convey some information and it appears there may be some sort of...conspiracy to stop him from doing so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, got it, I'm still dumb as rocks. Always will be when talk to a guy with all the answers like you. Gullible too.

When I want to protest against the KKK my first thought is not to bring my KKK outfit and disrupt the inauguration of the top law-enforcer in the land. I'm probably just jealous...of something though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, sometimes the redpill tastes like rape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typical intro, yes, we all know I'm stupid. Took me damn near 40-years to get that way too. Now that we got that out of the way, thanks for lowering yourself to comment. 

However, as a guy local to the scene, that has visited a few protests over the past few months, it seems to me that protesting by trying to interrupt legitimate business garners more bad will than good.

That's my opinion. It appears you might have a differing opinion since you imply there is some right being removed from someone else. I don't see any basis for that so I'll just assume you're responding because you're young and emotional so I hope that works out for you one day. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your posts. The best outcome I can hope for is a balanced discussion and you're doing you're part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to argue with the man on any front. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since this keeps getting reposted I think it's fair to repost my comment. 

Clickbait: A 61-year-old woman who showed up in her vagina outfit with her KKK buddies with the intent to cause a disruption and be arrested, caused multiple disruptions and was arrested.

She was then charged and convicted of her crimes in a court of law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This sub has a narrative that includes Satanism to cause an atheist to challenge their spiritual beliefs in addition to the normal parsing of what is "true" that is needed to consume this information. Is this something you've felt or do you find you must dismiss certain ideas to fit your worldview? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest question from a guy with some experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I scan it all and look for the patterns. TPTB agendas come to light as well as glimmers of "truth". I also wrote some software that helps me to this by scoring articles based on source, keywords and reputation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW, it looks like I've given you more than a few dozen upvotes so hopefully that helps with the balance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you were done with this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone is stalking your votes. Usually they get bored and go away after a day or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post is a journey in itself. Thanks for the quality, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clickbait: A 61-year-old woman who showed up in her vagina outfit with her KKK buddies with the intent to cause a disruption and be arrested, caused multiple disruptions and was arrested. 

She was then charged and convicted of her crimes in a court of law.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 61-year-old woman who showed up in her vagina outfit with her KKK buddies with the intent to cause a disruption and be arrested, caused multiple disruptions and was arrested.
She was then charged and convicted of her crimes in a court of law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 61-year-old woman who showed up in her vagina outfit with her KKK buddies with the intent to cause a disruption and be arrested, caused multiple disruptions and was arrested.

She was then charged and convicted of her crimes in a court of law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But isn't money as we know it just a construct that Rothchild creates and controls anyway? If everyone stopped paying their taxes or stopped using their currency or banks wouldn't then the elites shift to the gold that they've been stock piling for centuries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So all of the other data points should be discounted and the the whole thing written off to stress? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ive been sent here to give yall the truth. Jay Z, call me, bruh! You still aint call me! Jay Z, call me! Jay Z, I know you got killers, please dont send them at my head. Just call me! Talk to me like a man! - Kanye - 11/19/2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It was at this performance](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jKoe_GteC2I) and they took him that very night. 48-hours prior to this [Kayne made a quick solo trip to Russia](http://archive.is/XDPqi). He was locked up at Resnick Neuropsychiatric, who's [owner's are shown to be top Clinton donors](https://search.wikileaks.org/?q=stewart+resnick). He has been reported to have experienced memory loss (consistent with electric-shock treatment). Immediately upon release he went to see [Donald Trump](http://archive.is/gDolX) where he was either delivering a message or seeking reassurance and they haven't let him out since. 

This is happening in front of the world, for all to see, and the message is clear; there is isn't anyone that is going to stop them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're in the wrong neighborhood. I suggest you turn around and go until you hit the main road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone aware of a compilation of people that have released information but then were killed shortly thereafter for (obviously) what they knew? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be a combination of whistleblowers, conspirators, traitors, spies, etc...hard to pin down and thus the question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National Security Advisor McMaster May Accept Role as Army Vice Chief of Staff, Receive "promotion"... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of Germany aside from the kanji. 

I wondered if it was actually NK so I looked up some of the license plates and took a closer look at the [banners posted down the street](http://imgur.com/a/FTM33). Seems to match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It must be lest snowflakes frantically label all speech they don't like as hate speech....whoops, too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one of about 10 accounts that you'll always find in the same thread pushing the same narrative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go back to /r/politics snowflake. You're projecting again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play stupid games, win stupid prizes.

^(And now I have to clean this up...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Him first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One hand fapping. 

Youth is wasted on the young. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any reasonable person that thinks this is true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Psychotic animals' would be a better description. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. no one that knows stuff thinks this. There are metro tunnels to other sites and none of this matters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a fair bit of thought and strategy went into that shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Looks like they feature different artists each month](https://www.lifewtr.com/) for their designs. I agree wholeheartedly with the meaning of the symbolism, but it seems the [specific artists](https://www.lifewtr.com/artist/craig-karl/) would be responsible in this case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I likely agree with Flynn on most politics but from someone in the business; taking money from foreign Governments under any circumstances is going to force you to change your business. 

Determining foreign influence is literally the single most important aspect of a clearance. There's no question or doubt he understood the ramifactions, tried to hide it and got fucked for being greedy. 

RT isn't even an issue, but when you write a op-ed that's pro-Erdoan then there's no question you've been doing business with the wrong team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone bother to read the source for this article? A rabid feminist student at Yale made up "stealthing"  for a school essay. This is "the study" they reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's against Government regulation of the Internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he keeps going and deregulates it to the point that any company can get a line to your house and fire up competition then it won't matter. Hard to get the latter without the former though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W0QoocyfJWI)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there was ever any denial. They are using google translate so I can't imagine they will influence it more than the Russians did the US election.

How long do you think you have before they ban you from this sub again for ban evasion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? I love Niall Fergiesmam!

"BREXIT WOKE ME UP"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading through your post history provides an interesting perspective. Thanks for posting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The abused become the abusers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one thing to realize it, but I suspect it might be another to experience it on the front lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a religious guy (but I have been and may be again), but I sure am praying with you tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you offer any keywords that highlight your journey? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear there is no shortage of evidence for drop bears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a terrible piece of journalism!

How do you say that a guy died due to complications for his lung transplant due to being denied a lung transplant. There are two sides to this story and this "piece" is trying so hard to only tell one that the story doesn't even make sense anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes? Something has clicked for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To what other humans must my money be transferred to so that they might be convinced to save humanity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will never be enough evidence in a single picture to prove anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has someone experienced a transition from the normal every day conspiracy theorist to confirming something that changed your life? Has anyone felt like they discovered a higher level of knowledge, understanding or power due to what they have learned? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking your normal first 10 stages of redpill, I mean that you've felt like something deeper has clicked for you that generally is going to be impossible to explain to someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 01010011 01101111 01110010 01110010 01111001 00100000 01000100 01100001 01110110 01100101 00101100 00100000 01001001 00100000 01100011 01100001 01101110 00100111 01110100 00100000 01101100 01100101 01110100 00100000 01111001 01101111 01110101 00100000 01100100 01101111 00100000 01110100 01101000 01100001 01110100 00101110  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked an actual question. You responded with an ad hominem attack. 

No further responses required for everyone to see the evidence of your agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you? How is it that "government and corporations" are "causing GW" while not blaming humans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should I conclude that humans don't control governments and corporations? 

Is this conspiracy about to get really good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  needs a massive effort

To do what? 

To what other humans must my money be transferred to so that they might be convinced to save humanity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If "dreamers" are kids following the law, integrating and getting an education I see benefit to America and to the kids.

It's not hard to see the other side of the coin on this issue and with most tough issues, they are tough because both sides are right in some ways. Grandkids soften you up a bit too.

Meanwhile, if Assange gets arrested, and it's not just a ploy to get him to safer ground, while Soros, Clinton and Obama continue to wage open warfare on the state without any real action, then our story will have taken a turn and I suspect the hearts of many people will also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tldr; I think this is the heart of it:

"On 24 February, he told the crowd: Our real friends in the world speak English. The next evening he had dinner with Trump at the Washington Trump hotel and tweeted a photo of him with the Donald in the early hours of the morning.

Eleven days later, he headed off to the Ecuadorian embassy. BuzzFeeds story dropped at 1.31pm. And, 57 minutes later, at 2.28pm, WikiLeaks made an announcement: it would host a live press conference by Julian Assange about his latest leak, Vault 7."

e.g. Trump's 7D chess board is using Assange as the tip of the spear for one of his battles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling Mr. Nye's demons will catch up to him sooner rather than later. It seems like he's on a march towards some great end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it when they affirm that folks are making the right choices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine, he broke my heart slobbing knobs in Dupont Circle...and someone got it on video.

I think his situation is one of the most stunning things I've heard but I'm too numb to react appropriately. There's just no happy ending to this story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The truth will come out and it's not much use in speculating until we know more. I'm 100% sure there is more to be learned here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking hell, what did they do to him? Can his family not be protected? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Doctors confirmed the men have anal cancer".

And now I think I have it after reading that "article".
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google maps? If so, you need to tell it to not remember your location history both on the app and under the settings of any google accounts. They'll still track you of course, but at least they'll hide it from you and pretend they don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you are punished for being unable to manage and grow your finances. Many of us start with these same "raw deals", but over time learn to build credit and responsibly handle larger amounts of money. 

It costs money to deal with people that don't know how to handle money, and that is reflected in the cost to provide them services.

edit: poor people are salty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, rough translation of Russian: "I don't give a fuck". 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never fap in the dark again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if they don't believe anyone? Until it becomes a law that you must have a social media account to enter the country, they will either need to take my word for it or have a process to prove me otherwise or validate it for themselves. 

They could try searching or maybe they examine my devices for apps, but both would turn up nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking flashlight, so maybe center of palm. You could send messages and if you had more than color your options increase exponentially.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folks aren't using social media because they want to maintain their privacy. 

Never creating a facebook account has been one of those investments that keeps paying off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if I could make a body part glow on demand that would be pretty damn cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Palmer would be in the cell to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks - they posted after I did so I missed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those shiny little tables? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Secrets in Plain Sight by Scott Onstott

Watching it now. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with a few decades on you, imagine growing up under the lies without being given any reason to question them since the sheep were so well herded. Then one day, you realize, the herd is a lie and the dogs marching them around don't have their best interests at heart. Word spreads throughout the herd...and then...

well, that's where we are now. I'm excited to see what happens. Word is spreading and we may actually be in for a [fourth turning](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Strauss%E2%80%93Howe_generational_theory).

Word has it that your generation leads us back into another 20+ years like the 50s where everyone* gets to prosper and feel good about it.

^(* Caveat: life is always going to suck for some percentage of the living.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've woken up at the perfect age. For some of us much further along the journey (of life, not necessarily truth), we wish it would have happened sooner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reddest of all pills? I'm not even a fan of cinnamon gum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 666 Everywhere? Is everyone in on this except me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow - I hope it was enough money to change their lives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Moldylox" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Working link](http://www.mystatesman.com/news/state--regional-govt--politics/travis-county-custody-case-jury-will-search-for-real-alex-jones/rnbWzMHnFCd5SOPgP3A34J/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
