<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4306</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was about 7 years old, my brother convinced me to lock him in the trunk of my dad's car to see if he could get out (he had seen it in a movie). I did so and after a few minutes, he banged on the door and I opened it for him. I wanted to try, but he said no.

A couple days later, my dad came home from work and I stole his keys and locked myself in the trunk. I figured I was way smarter than my brother, and even if I wasn't there would be a little handle for me to pull and the trunk would open like my mom's car. Little did I know, my dad's car was older and there was no such handle. It was the middle of summer and I was in long pants and a sweater; I felt like I was in an oven. I remember kicking the door and screaming to no avail. Our neighbour just happened to be running a skill saw at the same time, so nobody could hear me screaming, even if they wanted to. I just remember thinking that I was so dumb and I couldn't believe I was going to die never having stood up to the bully in my class. Weird but that's where my 7 year old brain went.

After about 15 minutes my parents came looking for me and somehow heard me screaming from the trunk. When they opened it, I was *completely* drenched in sweat and sitting in a puddle of it as well. Now I never climb into the trunks of cars unless I know for sure that they have a release handle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People don't change until they're uncomfortable enough. He is *very* comfortable. He doesn't have to do anything at all because if he neglects it long enough, he knows you'll be there to pick up the slack. The problem is, you can't exactly ignore your crying child until he finally pays some attention to her.

Is there any way you could leave? If it's possible, find someone to stay with and meet somewhere neutral and explain to him that things need to change if you're going to stay married. This is not acceptable. 

A couple people have suggested that his medication is not working properly and he is experiencing a depressive episode. I have depression myself and work in the mental health sector, and this part stood out to me:
He'll study obscure German air force history from ww2 for hours, but won't read a short article on parenting. 

I don't know about you, but I haven't met many depressed people that are able to focus and remain engaged and interested for longer than 15 minutes, let alone hours. Even if it's something that he doesn't care about, there is no way he is so incredibly depressed that he just can't read a short parenting article. I don't know your husband personally, so I could be speaking out of turn, but it sounds like his lack of parenting stems from deadbeatdaditis, not depression.

You've mentioned that you feel like a single parent, and the reason why is because you are. That's not okay. Your husband helped bring this child into the world and now it's his responsibility to nurture and care for her until she is capable of being on her own. No ifs, ands, or buts. You don't get to just change your mind about being a dad, and what makes it worse is the baby was planned. The level of respect you deserve and that of which you're receiving are two vastly different things.

I empathize with you and I truly hope that both you and your daughter have a really great life, whether you decide to leave your husband or work on things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize what the ages were until I was finished the post and I'm astounded. This sounds like a bunch of 16 year olds. Why are you still with this guy? This much drama and you've been together for 6 weeks? Also, for future reference: "my ex is just soo crazy" is usually code for "I'm a big piece of shit." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it kind of strange that really nobody else has mentioned the ring thus far. Like, she wants to go on a break but she's going to keep your grandmother's ring? That's not how it works. I agree, he needs to just get the ring back and then they can stay out of each other's lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend and I recently took a trip to my hometown for a concert and it was so awesome. I haven't been there in about 10 years so it was so nice to see everything from my childhood and my old house (not how I remembered it? I thought it was yellow but it's apparently peach. I think they painted it and everyone is lying). It made me feel really close to him to show him the places I used to play soccer when I was 6 years old. We also visited somewhere he lived when he was 4 so nothing was how he remembered it, but it was cute seeing how excited he got about thinking something looked familiar. I really, really love him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I've been thinking reading this whole thread. It's like the equivalent to holding up your menu to say something private to your boyfriend when your friend is sitting across the table. It's just rude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 08:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop rushing me, when the time is right! I'm not in love yet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love Must Not be Forgotten by Zhang Jie. I read it for the first time in grade 10 for English class and it's stuck with me since then. It's just so beautifully written.
A little excerpt:
"No matter what form they may take, they still love each other. Though not bound together by earthly laws or morality, though they never once clasped hands, each possessed the other completely. Nothing could part them. Centuries to come, if one white cloud trails another, two blades of grass grow side by side, one wave splashes another, a breeze follows another... believe me, that will be them." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I washed the floors and he walked through the room like .5 seconds before it dried and left little footprints all around the apartment. But he went to kiss me today and I sneezed on his face so I think we're even.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 09:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my wisdom teeth out this morning and my boyfriend is sick, so we're both just pathetically cuddled in bed with our cat. I would love to be not in pain and also have a cat that doesn't think my swollen and bruised face is the most comfortable sleeping position in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 10:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend and I just moved into a new apartment and I cleaned the entire thing, top to bottom, today while he unpacked and organized. It's 3am and this is the most time we've had to relax since we moved in last week. It's worth it though, to get to have a sleepover with my best friend every night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever think there might be a reason she has so many ex boyfriends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 08:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure that this person that you're dating is a fully grown adult woman and not a 14 year old girl? 
My GF and I where painting and sipping and I was particularly into my piece of art - I was really trying to make it good! Half way through my GF saw my picture and said "It's excellent! it's even better than mine" and then she drew a thick black painted happy face on my canvas. 

I've gone to a few paint and wine nights with my boyfriend. I have the talent of a blind 6 year old while he's able to construct masterpieces by flicking paint over his shoulder. I cannot ever imagine a time or place where I would have the audacity to wreck something that he put SO much time and effort into. Your girlfriend does not respect you, nor does she care about your happiness. Do you really want to be with somebody like that?

Your issue here isn't that your girlfriend has 'mood swings'. Your issue is that your girlfriend is *mean*. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 08:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that mean, she won't allow it? You don't need her permission to stop dating her. The only thing you need to do is tell her that you aren't happy being with her and then block her. She's resistant because she loves you, but that doesn't mean that you should stay in relationship purgatory until she's ready for things to be over. It's going to be hard to do it but it needs to be done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
