<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2044</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a really good movie idea? If you do, I would recommend outlining it, structuring it, creating some compelling characters, then having a bash at writing it. Then, once you've written one, read about screenwriting and see where you can improve on a redraft. The reason why I think its better doing it this way round is that you'll learn so much more having your own experience as a foundation to build upon, also if you get too bogged down in rules and formula it might repress any spark of passion you have which is sometimes needed to carry the motive through to finish a project.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt the same internal reaction. It got under my skin to a level where I actually had to remind myself it was just a film, and imagine the crew just off screen - which sounds crazy in writing. Have you seen Eden Lake? It triggers similar feelings of absolute helplessness and terror. There's a similar scene at the start of the film [Outlaw](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0758771/?ref_=nm_flmg_act_42) as well which is just horrible to watch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interpreting the last scene of Stalker (1979) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't read on if you haven't seen the film!  

I recently saw the brilliant film Stalker and am still 'feeling' it. I wanted to just share my own interpretation on the last scene to see what others think who are no doubt more clued up on this film than I currently am. The scene shows the Stalkers child (called Monkey) seemingly moving glasses on a table top. 

I feel that on the surface its supposed to look like telekinesis, and that the child has adopted the Stalker's unwitting skill as implied at the start of the film also. But actually its a really clever symbol of the Stalkers dilemma, and puts us in his place. Initially, we want to believe in something, have faith in something outside of ourselves, in the same way that he wanted to believe that he has a sense of greater purpose, and can find some kind of soulful/spiritual connection with the people he guides to the zone. But ultimately, he's devastated and disillusioned because these people, who he looks up to and envies, are ultimately just as flawed, insecure and racked with self-doubt as he is. In the same way, the film is inviting us to want to believe the child has telekinesis. But there's the sound of the passing train, and the glasses all move in the same direction, thereby likely caused by vibrations. It can't be a coincidence that the same sound of a moving train can be heard at one point as they're approaching the Zone. So as the child watches the glasses, perhaps convinced he or she (I couldn't tell) is moving them (being causal) they're actually just observing, because causality is out of their hands. The glasses are consequential just like everything else. This is also what the idea of the Zone threatened to reveal, which the writer and professor became increasingly aware of (as well as the Stalkers wife), that ultimately happiness relies on illusions rather than absolute truth.  

I just wondered what others made of this scene. Perhaps its supposed to be completely ambiguous so that viewers see what they want to see. This is my first Tarkovsky film so am looking forward to seeing the others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a really interesting shot in LH in the first half where you see a cloud of red mist/fog emerging above a staircase. In any other film it would seem strange, but in LH it just fits, and implies this idea of something unknown and frightening gradually emerging. That kind of seed, well sewn, can be so powerful on your unconscious imagination in terms of triggering things that relate to you personally. Then the ideas of distrust, some external threat, implied in such an unnerving way that again the imagination starts to process those ideas in the background. Lynch is a master at creating that kind of weird unconscious anxiety, where your own imagination starts processing and associating in ways that continue behind what you're actually seeing. So by the time of the party scene, you're feeling just as unsettled as Fred is. 
I saw Lost Highway at the cinema on release with a class of fellow lens media students, and I was the only one who loved it. Everyone else hated it, including our teacher who unfairly criticised the hell out of it afterwards (which really infuriated me). Its still one of my favourite films, and soundtracks, of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As there's so much to write about, it might be useful to focus on one film. I would perhaps recommend the shining, as there's plenty of visual motifs, symbols and compositions worth writing about, as well as a lot of existing analysis and theories. There's a website somewhere (you'll have to find it yourself!) where a guy breaks down almost every aspect of the film, with all sorts of theories about the length of specific shots by the frame, the use of numbers (especially 42 and 21), pop-culture references, mirror-structured editing and all kinds of symbology. If you delve into that, hopefully you'll have your own ideas emerge about what interests you most or what would be good to right about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Directors Cut of Abyss is a strange situation as far as DC's go, in terms of how it changes the whole point of the story. The theatrical cut is about this kind of justifiably cautious xenophobia against an unknown lifeform, but then they turn out to be helpful (hooray!) This is weird story to tell though because the lifeforms *could have* just as easily eaten the fuck out of the crew or drowned them with controlled water if they were that way inclined. But then of course the DC changes the point entirely to being about man's use of violence. I find the DC weird though in that the aliens threaten to create a fucking tidal wave, then change their minds because of *one* man telling his wife he loves her.  It makes the aliens are more gung-ho and unnecessarily violent in terms of how they were planning to react. Plus their perspective seems really imbalanced if they just record all our news about war and nukes etc, but not the nicer stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 10:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Abyss, Silkwood, Miss Sloane, Suffragette, Underworld, Silence of the Lambs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stalag 17 is such great fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished it (did you see it on Film4 also?) It was long for sure, but once I was settled in there was plenty to ponder on. I found it truly unsettling with the stuff about self-perception, self-worth, achievement, wanting to connect to people, I didn't expect it to delve into the human condition quite as much as it did. I'm definitely glad I saw it, and will hit Solaris next. I notice The Mirror is on Film4 in a few days too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its just pointless. I could say anything reminds me of anything, and a certain mindset gunning for a fight would delight in trying to shred my thought to pieces. Its not coming from a frame of trying understand, at all, why something might have a certain opinion, its coming from a frame of right/wrong, agree/hate, which is not the kind of debate I want with something as innocuous as this, its just completely pointless. To judge my reluctance as snooty, having already written the things you have, seems hypocritical to me, and shows that you really are just gunning for a fight. I do hope you get to go down your well trodden 'road' of arguing Kurosawa/Silence with someone else soon, and that it provides you with the outlet you are looking for. Have a good day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's why I don't get involved in discussions with people like you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I'd misjudged the audience, and it felt more rational to retract my comment than to enter into a pointless explanation. Not that there was a valid question to answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I actually tried watching Stalker last night, but was just way too distracted by pressing thoughts to be able to fully immerse myself in its ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it hard to understand why someone *wouldn't* notice the comparisons, especially flat out refute them (some people just like to be contrary, especially around these parts). You might find [this](http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/heat-vision/dark-knight-heat-comparisons-revealed-video-972620) and [this](http://variety.com/2016/film/in-contention/heat-christopher-nolan-michael-mann-al-pacino-robert-de-niro-academy-1201854410/) interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you ever see Mann's earlier version called LA Takedown? Its worth seeing, its so interesting how he developed it into Heat. Heat is a great film, but I've watched it so many times now that I don't feel I can get much out of it. I like seeing President Palmer freaking out in the cafe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Even Nolan said he was influenced by Heat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely! Make sure you get in. There are two ways around this. 1) Get someone else to get your ticket for you, in advance, via a credit card (say at Odeon). Pop along, pick up your ticket from the machine. Getting through the ticket-tearing guy is easier than the box office, because s/he'll have loads of people tickets to tear and won't care. 2) Get a ticket for another movie, like Guardians of the Galaxy or some shit, thats showing at a similar time. Then just go into the "wrong screen" and not realise until the film starts, then be too embarrassed to leave. OR go on a saturday, see a film that starts before Covenent, then sneak into it afterwards. Make sure you see it though, as an Alien fan you owe it to yourself.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely! Man I havent seen that film for ages but remember it being great fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always liked Psycho III too. It has an unashamedly 80s chiller vibe, and was directed by Perkins. The scene where the sheriff pulls icecubes from the box, right from the dead girls palm, and eats one not knowing theres a spot of blood on his lips, is a great moment. Jeff Faheys intense wannabe rockstar is fun too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for her. Between her work with David Lynch and co-writing/acting on the amazing show Enlightened, shes very talented.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You aren't seriously suggesting that if I get through the wire...

For a nanosecond there, I thought you were about to say that once you've worked your way through all five seasons of The Wire you'll have time for long films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have! I love them both. I'm actually waiting to rewatch The Great Escape on bluray, and Silence also!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schindler's List is actually very rewarding. I know that sounds weird because its such a horrible subject matter, but the writing, photography and direction are absolutely brilliant, there is always something to admire in every frame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are still a few classics that I haven't seen, like Lawrence of Arabia, Gone With the Wind, Stalker and Solaris, that I procrastinate on watching because they just seem too long a time investment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the problem with walking that line, its that kind of film. If it tried to be super edgy and contemporary, it would be a different (and lesser) film. It was nice to watch a film like this that was so confident and secure in its own skin, without trying to please too many audience groups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Presented a scarily-accurate depiction on where our world is heading.  

I felt that Disconnect did this admirably, as well as the humanistic elements of Black Mirror.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first Inception teaser was brilliant. The little glimpses of the spinning top, and the half glass of water tilting were so cool and mysterious. The main trailer, with the Mind Heist music by Zack Hempsey, was brilliant - I've watched it so many times (and enjoyed all the mash-ups with Toy Story 3 etc).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The eyebrow thing is ridiculous, I'm not sure what crazy school of acting that comes from. If you're ever unfortunate enough to see "Me Before You", Emilia Clarke's eyebrows look like excited caterpillars in some courting ritual throughout the entire movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he was great in Deepwater Horizon recently, really became the character which he doesn't always get a chance to do. I actually think he's a little out of place in Death Proof and Hateful Eight, I can imagine Tarantino dancing around him shouting "its snake fuckin' pliskin, alright?" so Kurt seems a little more self-conscious because he knows he's supposed to be all cool and self-referential.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who?   
The Hidden  
Capricorn 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually when when someone pulls shit like that, my first reaction is, I wanna punch his fuckin' lights out. But you know something? YOU'RE ALL RIGHT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read an interview with Emma Thomas the other day where she said "we're currently outlining an idea of Chris's, a true crime story that takes place on an airplane. He had the idea in his sleep and is very excited about it".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found The Hateful Eight almost satirical in how self-consciously Tarantino it was, ridiculously drawn out and proud of itself, whilst being distractingly annoying in all the wrong places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I did also like her role in Room and The Girl With The Dragon Tattoo as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great to hear it was good! I wish I'd gone now just for that poster. I've seen Alien three times at the cinema in my life, twice the directors cut, and its been incredible every time. Such a cinematic experience, and so claustrophobic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you obsessed with Emma Watson? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you overestimate the masses. Its more likely that the marketing will get cranked up to 11 by late May.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the film. If its a thoughtful, subtle film then I mostly enjoy getting immersed alone. If its an event kind of movie (opening night of Sicario or Trainspotting 2 or something) then I love a shared experience with the *right* kind of crowd. Not a bunch of idiot teenagers on their phones (e.g. any horror film) but decent people in sync with the film. Its SUCH a great, memorable experience when it works well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its written by David Mamet too. I feel that the love interest/cheating angle was a little cliched and clunky by Mamet's standards, but its still good fun.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colonia? I thought it was an otherwise good film, not great but suspenseful enough and a great premise. But her acting wasn't convincing at all, she just didn't emote, and couldn't create any credibility that she actually cared about the guy she was rescuing. I kept imagining how much better the role could have been (e.g. a young Jodie Foster) and how much it would have lifted the film. It could have been *so* much better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have spent ages trying to get LG to give me an unlock code - they now want proof that it was bought unlocked. It doesn't mention it on the receipt - even though it WAS unlocked. They're being annoying as fuck. I've had to just go on ebay to solve it because they're useless unhelpful jackasses. The girl was smarmy as fuck as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Give her time to work and grow as an actress.

That's not a luxury the vast majority of young actors have, so why should Emma Watson be any different? She's had many chances to prove herself if she had any talent at all, but she clearly doesn't, hence the general disdain for her shitty acting skills and annoying presence in films.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have... ugh it was terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with your post.  

But just wanted to add I find it odd how when people are talking about the awesome caving horror film The Descent, they tend to spell it as The Decent. Just now on a thread about people giving up on things, someone said "being a descent person". Out of all mentions of decent or descent that I see, over half seem to be incorrect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comic book movies. I'm done with all that blurry slick CGI fanboy pandering bullshit, and only have time for good stories in films now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not too keen on caving?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...from this weeks frontpage? Thanks for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah mine went last week, and when I looked there were LOADS of people having it happen. Maybe its always like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm UK also and just got mine back from DPD. How are you getting on? It looks like mine is locked to a network (it was bought unlocked) so that's fucking annoying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think of Emma Watson's acting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her acting in the trailer of The Circle kills all credibility of that film. Her English accent waivers in and out of lines, she has no real emotional expressiveness except "mild concern" like she can't log into Facebook or something.  

I just don't understand why they cast her - aren't there enough talented American girls to nail a role like this? Anna Kendrick for example?  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *really* enjoyed this film. Not that the her journey was enjoyable, but it was incredibly engaging and refreshing to see a script coupled with an excellent performance that dealt with a very nuanced mental health issue. I've known a few people with similar traits but never seen it captured so well on film like this. It was really uncomfortable at times just how real it all felt, Rebecca really did disappear into a fully-fleshed character. Absolutely deserved an Oscar nom for sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT MOTHERFUCKER WHAT? CAN'T YOU SEE I'M BUSY KILLING PEOP - I mean yes, detective, what is it now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad Max Fury Road - The Animated Version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Columbo rocks! I love the way he points out some little problem, leading the murderer to anxiously solve it for him on the spot.   

"What baaaathers me, is why the victim would leave her house, but not lock the door?"  
"Why Columbo, I'm sure she was just in a rush and forgot! She, er, took her coat, is that not enough for you?"    
"Hmmm, yeah, I see. But then there's the - ah, nevermind, I can see you're busy".   
"WHAT COLUMBO? WHAT WHAT?!" (sweats) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Match Point is a curious choice - I thought that wasn't a mystery whatsoever but more a suspense about the central character dealing with his situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tie the arm inside a pillowcase full of hornets, they're good for eating away dead skin cells.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't really looked after myself, my body, my career, my knowledge and skills for years. But looking for a man who has excelled on all these aspects to treat me like a princess! What? You don't want to? Fucking *asshole*, just like *all* men downs another G T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daft Punk in Tron Legacy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taylor Swift as a ghost in that Jeff Bridges movie based on a teen book from a couple years back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Chase also had Henry Rollins, Keidis was also in Point Break, and Flea in Big Lebowsi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Lost Highway and The Chase </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I really don't think he thought that one through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok but its kind of our loss too (of time and effort) if you come here with stupid questions like this without exercising a bit of common sense about the reliability of your source.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does indeed. There are some really hilarious segments written by witnesses of encounters with Uri, like meetings in hotel lobbys etc, where they describe what he did and how he responds to various things. One time, he is trying to bend a key on his chair when the other people step away, and shuffling his chair forward (as the excuse for grabbing the seat with the key in hand) he has to widen his knees due to a close coffee table and rips his pants! But then just makes a joke of it and carries on milking the slightly bent key. The way he gauges his response to successes and failures to always be in his favour is cringe-worthy at times, but audiences lap it up. Its like he sat down one day and thought "wow, people are schmucks, I bet I could con the hell out of them in the most ridiculous ways and they would never see it. All I need is good lawyers to control the skeptics" (i.e. the same idea as Tony Robbins, Richard Bandler, Peter Popoff and many others)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I trust the online "players" to be honest else it's their loss.

I have no idea what this means.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A while ago I was chatting with a girl   

Its more likely that the girl was making this shit up for attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Hardy chases moped thief before shouting 'I caught the c**t' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This viral video annoys the hell out of me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hzgzim5m7oU  

This video was forwarded to me by someone as being "so powerful". The video and its youtube comments depress the hell out of me. Its all completely fake and obviously stage, designed to get an emotional reaction on behalf of some marketing company about "the power of words". But its staged so says NOTHING except for "hey, this is another way of writing something". That people are "crying" in the comments, and attacking anyone who can see through its manipulative viral-marketing efforts is so annoying! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to enjoy Basterds each time I see it, but its just strange. I enjoy individual scenes and performances, but it just doesn't come together as a satisfying whole for me. Too many moments reek of Tarantino being self-indulgent and showy, which distracts me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to see Kylo dubbed with the 'where's my fucking money Denny?' lines. The scene where the nurse is tending to Chewie, Tommy popping in and saying "hai doggie"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you must! I think it would work best to read the book first, then watch the movie. They're both excellent in different ways, and I really appreciate how the film adapted it for the screen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a sub? Where is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seemed clear that his intention with the book was to expose Geller, rather than teach or educate the reader in magic or method. He even states this early on. Those subtleties emerge more between the lines, particularly in other people's accounts of their moments with Geller and how other people responded. Its actually more the things that Geller does, in knowing how to manipulate the impression in people's minds, than anything explicit Randi writes about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Randi's book "the truth about uri geller" is so good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been reading this the past few days and think its terrific. Although not his intention, it really delves into the subtlety and nuance of the presentation of magic in terms of "showing the process" (reminding me of Derren Browns' Pure Effect), the psychology and manipulation of belief and how it dovetails with desire and imagination. All the while riffing on irrationality, the human condition and some classic methods. Also of course, what a bonkers sociopath Geller is.  

Just thought I'd highly recommend it for anyone who likes that kinda thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you ever part of Disney junkets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should check out Short Circuit 2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally these kinds of threads get torn to pieces by people unable to comprehend such a thing, thinking it some fanciful conspiracy theory. I absolutely think it goes on. Its known that PR junkets can be very manipulative towards positive reviews (implicit bribes via gifts and treats), but I'm sure it happens within marketing teams as well (i.e. its someone's job to boost marketing via "positive PR" which the person helps fulfill via a bunch of fake IMDB accounts).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prisoners is a great film, with a similar dark and gritty atmosphere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the Twilight Zone episode called Five Characters In Search of An Exit. I think its season 4. It was the first TZ episode I watched, after a Cube discussion, and it got me totally hooked on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Public Enemies never seemed to "click" either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yah? What replaced it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like something is weird there, it takes a few seconds for me (LG G4).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried watching it recently, and the only way I could make sense of it was as a weird corporate satire in the same universe as American Psycho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Michael Mann's Miami Vice film will develop more cult status in time, and be thought of alongside Thief, Heat and Manhunter as among his best. It has a very unique and thought-out style and depth, its world being so trodden in and tired that exposition is thin on the ground and most of the substance is implied. I've really come to appreciate it much more on rewatches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chill out man that's a ridiculous thing to get peeved about. It's kinda boring when some smart ass gets the Blu-ray out to make it some official viewing, it's nice just having stuff on TV sometimes. I remember owning all the Bonds but would still tune in when they were on TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the hell would glasses-free 3D work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw Their Finest and you're so right - it was such a boring, flat, empty and pointless-as-fuck film. They didn't even *try* to make the story have a point. The bit with Sam-I-can't-fucking-act-to-save-my-life-Caflin dying was so amazingly stupid in how it was handled that I wondered if the whole thing was supposed to be some meta-level satire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, the twists aren't that interesting. I'm sure I've seen similar in Wachowski's Bound and Side Effects.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt similar. Its one of those meticulous clockwork narrative plots that leaves you thinking "ah, how clever!" at best, but not particularly engaged on any emotional or meaningful level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This cat reminds me of that quietly spoken lady in Police Academy who suddenly screams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you being serious?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had all the scenes ever, and you choose a two-second jump cut? The bone doesn't even *line up* with the orbiting bomb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who mentioned anything about superiority? Just saying its a different experience is all, and one I enjoyed. Why did you have to inject some weird superiority right/wrong angle into it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did indeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I'm saying *all* films, just the ones it suits. Films like Heat, Silence of the Lambs, The Prestige and Hateful Eight would work well. Films like 2001 not so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   former

Glad you took care of that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed on both! My local cinema is showing Black and Chrome next week, the surreal nightmarish quality would be insane on the big screen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really depends on the film and your own taste, certain films do look great. Silence looks incredible and with very high contrast. Also, The Man Who Wasn't There was shot in colour before conversion to B W for release, and looks great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gravity and The Revenant. Both are about a person with a four digit male forename (Ryan, Hugh) and five-character surname based on a material (Stone, Glass), who experience an endless "single shot" chaotic event, a person dying who later revisits in their imagination, a long, troubled task of finding their way back to normality for the remaining runtime, a "rebirth" process (floating foetus shot, climbing out of dead horse), a shedding of skin (spacesuit/bearskin), a random touching scene involving a chance encounter with a stranger (howling/snowflakes on tongue), submersion in water before final salvation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a beautifully produced film, that can't really be denied. I fear a lot of people watch it for the first time on a laptop or tablet, whilst whatsapping people and checking facebook, then think "meh" which is all they deserve. On a big, sharp screen with surround sound, it really is an experience. When I bought a decent VR headset and virtual cinema app, Bladerunner was the first thing I watched in it.    

Story and structure wise it is pretty simple, but there are plenty of details and deep ideas that are there to be discovered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great film (except for the very end). Crap post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this. I just checked into this sub for the first time, having read Sam Harris' book recently, so this is great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great film. I read the book by her siblings too that the film was based on to get a more balanced idea of events. The film does an excellent job in implying or distilling events to efficiently tell the story in its runtime. Great soundtrack too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try and track down a rare TV show called Day Break with Taye Diggs. It's one season, really well planned and written, and a total Groundhog Day version of 24. You'll love it, it's so clever and packs some emotional punches too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On IK+ on the Atari ST and Amiga, if you pressed "T", the fighters trousers fell down and they looked at you [confused](http://www.ausretrogamer.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/IK_plus_pants.jpg). Back in the day, this was ground-breaking stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy who shined shoes and knew everything in Police Squad. I imagine him to be like bradley cooper in Limitless, shining shoes as a way to stay out of trouble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The border and tunnel scenes of Sicario had the whole screen of the cinema in anxious silence, it was incredible. Also, I felt loads of anxiety watching Gravity in 3D, I just felt like I was there and sharing all the horrible panics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to the premiere of the (terrible) sequel at London's FrightFest, and got into a conversation with the actress that plays Juno afterwards (the cast/crew introduced the film). She was really lovely and sweet. Then she just left on her own, into a bustling Leicester Square, like a *normal person*.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, it actually works really well in B/W. I could easily watch the whole film like that. Without the distraction of colour, compositions and framing seem to leap out more, and are more interesting.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
