<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3387</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
~ is a more polite form of ~. 

Just to add,   is a conjugation of the verb , the same verb we get  from. 

The verb  is the more polite version of the verb 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a YouTube called Bilingual Chika who uses both English and Japanese in her videos. 

Also AskJapanese is good for street interviews with Japanese and foreign folk. Japanesepod101 is great for beginner vocabulary. Taught by a native who also speaks English called Risa.

For pure educational purposes, there is no better than Nihongo no Mori in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I was learning Japanese for several years before I started a year of formal study in university. Up until that point, I had never heard of transitive and intransitive verbs, even though I was using them correctly. Of course my Japanese friends being native speakers also had no idea what transitive and intransitive verbs were. 
I guess my point is that constant exposure leads to idiomatic use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pay 10 a month with Meteor for unlimited data and I find its all I need. 

The odd time I'm in a situation where somebody doesn't have a smart phone and I need to send an SMS, I just log into my webtext. I make phone calls using Viber Out which have great call rates. Can be a bit patchy at times but works great for almost all situations for myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I know it's only BoI. I tend to select Irish as well just for adding a bit of excitement to my day (my day is usually terribly boring).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  is the present plain form of the verb. In the sentence , there is no indication of of whether it implies future or present and meaning is subjective to the reader.  does indeed make it present (continuous) however. 

Come to think of it, I would even be weary of saying "present plain form" as the ambiguity between present and future meaning exists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They possibly own both accounts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a similar house on the top of Bandon Road where it meets Magazine road. Look in from the front door and you'd see the stairs totally sinking downwards to the left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you respond to her request with "ah, oui oui."?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention the fact that the rental prices in Cork are rising at a ridiculous rate but the pay scale is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repetition and it'll become second nature! Keep up the good work though, you're doing well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply one is past tense and one is present tense. Just like we use in English.

E.g.
It seems like it'll rain VS it seemed like it would rain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ?  

Be careful not to use  in "". Although is "ha", in the case of following , , etc., it's pronounced as "wa".  

Edit: spelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 00:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's still blood on the walls of that house even with new tenants letting it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clonmel - the best of all possible worlds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plagiarism and a cocky attitude, that's why the downvotes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 12:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Profit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 12:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two words - Hugh Mungus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My yukidaruma-sama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puns! Being able to get and make puns is a huge measure of fluency. Puns are essentially elements of language which carry 2 or more levels of meaning within them. You need a solid understand of language to understand them.

Also just being able to express your humour and personality as you would with your native language is great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 12:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not going to lie, this was a good few bites in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Succulent Kebab from "Planet Kebabish" - Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Southern Ireland doesn't bother me in the slightest. Lumping us in as part of the UK however makes me pop a vein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it meant to be omelette au fromage as well? If so, I can imagine how that would double annoy you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 99designs is where I got my logo done. Truth be told, I wasn't blown away, but I did find the experience better than fiverr and am pretty happy with the logo design we got. (Kanzen Asia Consultancy is the company if you want to see.) I think I still have a refferal link for 99designs if you're interested.

Fiverr is good for a lot of things; just the other day I got some incredible voice-over work done. In my personal opinion however, I'd avoid logo designs unless it's for a temporary thing.  

Edit: wasn't blown away  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alcoholism for a start I'd guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
