<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4242</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah that was 'Stan' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ask this question in r/tipofmytongue/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My combat experience wasn't in the field, so to speak.  I read somewhere recently, someone speaking to having PTSD but not from combat; she expressed a sense of guilt, and that she didn't 'earn' it; made me cry because I could relate; unspoken and unregistered in my mind until that point.  So yeah,  its a thing all right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my friend, also a bully (out ranking the one who drove the Caddy) was just back from juvie, and I inadvertently  terrified her during this process.  She later told me that people were writing my license plate down, and I told her then I knew what had happened, one of two things:  They decided they wanted none of me, or that when she soon came out for lunch they learned who owned the car in question.  "Well, why didn't you say so?!" 

She had picked on them probably, too. And she had the same lunch, so I missed her by a minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the opening sequence, the music, always screamed YAY!!! in your face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *me too*   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> certain they weren't people in camo sneaking thru? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sweet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very cool, I learned something today, as well as what [**this**](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bicameralism_\(psychology\)) means </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A saying I've heard: How you treat other people, that is their karma.
How to react to being treated by other people is yours.
 Right on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are good, you know how to offer just enough detail without dragging it out, the right words for the emotion...well done, writing does help with the whole PTSD thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Queen   David Bowie [1981] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 1987 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a photo, because no one had portable cameras in their pockets in 1987; I was a junior in high school. Over my lunch hour, I learn that two Cadillacs have angle parked my Chevy Malibu into a non-angled spot(they were *all* non angled spots).  They formed a V around my vehicle. I couldn't move an inch.  

So, using Reverse and Drive, I literally bashed my way out as a thanks.  The Caddy on the left took the worst of it; it was driven by one of the school bullies, I won't say her name.  Maybe she's reading this. :D 

Today,  that shit would have been videoed 12 times over and probably made the news.

It felt *awesome.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Karl Jung would be ecstatic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the future is comprised of the events of today/decisions made today/actions taken or not taken today.....that is the fabric of tomorrow.  So to some degree, yes, our futures are predictable.  I don't know of that as deja vu, per se.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a stylist, but I'm invested in my hair (lol) I swear by Fekkai.  The glossing variety; it gets expensive, but omg.  Results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One night/morning after bar close, a one night stand, he told me to strip in his car and walk naked to the apt. complex.  2am.  He parked as far from his door as he could.  I did it.  Wearing heels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> glorious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only just realized that episode is titled 'Face Off'....lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever my mother in law calls 'family meeting' (and she does) (I hate that shit) (she forbids Kool-Aid/I'm 47)  I think of Shane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so surprised.  My people couldn't stand it while it ran (the camera shaking really bugs some folks).  I haven't had an emotional roller coaster like it since; not even Breaking Bad hooked me that deep.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *finish....the fucking story!!!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one my three favorite scenes is in season three, when Hank gets the phone call in the parking lot; that scene was set up so well!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dutch boy listening to 'Hungry Like the Wolf', then Mackey saying to him later, "Just attack it. Like you're hungry. Like the wolf."
 
edit:
Of course I have more than one favorite, but it is hard to choose.  I really like how Shane and Vic 'devolve', their relationship; the screaming into their phones at each other, Shane telling Vic how his family is real, and that Vic's family can't stand him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I cannot believe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that there is an active 'Shield' thread here!  YAY!  I loved that show!  Dammit, now I have to watch it again.  My family will cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he makes reference to painkillers in the note, they do not say what kind, nor how much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> having a large enough operation as they do (lots to lose), having served the time uncle Jack has served ('I ain't going back' is a common mentality amongst ex-cons), the AB (in the show) hates law enforcement that much...collateral damage.  Perhaps a sense of invincibility...that bunch was definitely sampling their own product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hat...Heisenberg, to become solid, needs Walt to wear that hat.  (I am being figurative while being silly) ...but, kind of, seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how can someone know who downvotes where?  I would like to know....;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you caught that too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shane Vendrell, *The Shield* ... he's  not the main character, but close. And he cycles from psychopath back thru to person of conscience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a female, and y'know, I didn't identify w/ Skyler or Marie.  Not that I would have been happy about the lying, I just would have handled it differently.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my SO is an electrical engineer and science whiz, he has said yes to this question before....it's his habit to break shit down as he watches.  For the most part, yeah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, but I'm not so certain about Pinkman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you must be from a rough crowd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if I could afford to gild this, it would be done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *nice* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a chick?  I feel like that woman in an eyeglasses ad, the one who lets a raccoon in to snuggle, thinking its her cat?  

So its not a chick.  And I thought I owned cats, they are not. They're possums.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dammit! now that shit's on the tip of my tongue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [True Nightmares?](https://www.investigationdiscovery.com/tv-shows/true-nightmares/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [the rest of what he drew](http://www.konbini.com/us/entertainment/ralph-steadmans-breaking-bad-illustrations-completely-gonzo/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steadman draws Schraeder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how intriguing I love finding subs this way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you know that's right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ralph Steadman draws Walt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait...what

I had no idea!  I thought the chick in the bed looked, well, really afraid; the pyramid hats threw me off.  This actually happened, and these are the waxworks, do I understand correctly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had some, I have no clue... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all right, now *this* counts as creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea, me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ....what </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> my collection, minus *Lurid, Sapphire*, and the silver one in *Pulp Fiction* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when the orientation is in an auditorium, filled with a who's who of unhirable or naive people....people who couldn't cut it at McDonalds. And they have hired you w/o seeing you first.  You're gonna be selling expensive vacuums door to door.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps Begbie had been held back in school due to a learning disorder, like dyslexia.  It would explain some of the characters anger issues, maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, I suppose this is good news...thank you!!  Glad you're not sick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to the mods, don't let it get to you.  At least try to not let it get to you.  One of my first posts, the immediate response was rude and insulting. The other redditors chewed his ass for it, that made me feel better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> s'all right just curious if anyone else anywhere else had experienced this.  Maybe its regional to the midwest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how curious!  I would have never guessed that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right?  I'm trying to read my two people (they're not mine, but you know what I mean...my peeps) and they aren't giving any indications....so it could just be me this time.  I am on penicillin. (should have mentioned this before now? maybe)  But the other times recently, I was not on any anti-biotics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we do the acetone washes from time to time, and while that helped a little with the batches that made us sick, it didn't fix the issue... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heartburn, nausea, my stomach just starts turning, hard sometimes.  Only with certain dope....today the resource was slightly different than usual, and here it is again. Feeling sick all over again.  It happens immediately.  I don't want to say anything to my SO, it sucks to get stuck with something like that, and it could just be me...but it has happened enough, and I didn't feel sick until we began smoking.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had it happen a number of times over the last couple of months; I wish I could find a variable, but it seems to be the drug itself.  Or something cut into it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so....I always hold in anything I'm inhaling, tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right? Someone said something about this being mass produced toy, and that information by itself it creepy as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clive Barker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Bowie featuring Trent Reznor "I'm Afraid of Americans" [1997] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's spelled just like it sounds
Take out the probably it makes me sound wishy washy
Goddamn your drunk tests are hard
I can't fuck a gorilla! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good question...and Lagos was about 13,000,000 people, last I heard, so ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no coincidences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> map of world internet traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more like LSD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least our weird ass experience of similar details didn't end in blood!!  1981 a stark ass naked dude showed up on the property, my SO was 13; naked guy is on the back deck, readying himself to slam a picnic bench through the sliding door, screaming for 'Grandma' to just let him in.  SO grabbed a double barrel shotgun and leveled it at the guy (universal, he finally understood what that meant) and put down the bench.  Walked up to the carport, started the hose, and washed the garbage cans.  Naked as fuck. Then took SO's moped out for a spin up and down the street while cops were called.  
Turns out he had a head full of LSD.  They found his clothes in the woods in our back yard.  Cops rolled him up in a scratchy army blanket like a burrito and tossed him into the back seat of t heir squad car.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all of them; the expectation of fireworks during their performance would be intimidating to them, and invariably disappointing (somehow) to us mere mortals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you want betrayal?  fuck the bedroom, look to a courtroom.  That's where it's at, betrayal. And by surprise every time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man With Two Brains...1982/1983 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disturbingly hilarious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and no other mentions in society?  cool...thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, can't make everyone happy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nasty....especially if they are on a lot of drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been listening to Joy Division a lot lately...good call </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yesssss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to agree, not to pat myself on the back, but it looks kind of boring here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been doing that.  kk!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, my cat is puking *right now*.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'm still flabbergasted that these things are 'toys'.  For real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see this thread revive, but I cannot think of anything clever enough to post right now :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think whoever did the downvoting *was*... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how exactly to I cross post?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok...google couldn't tell me. thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think you were, but someone was downvoting your comment....*that's* what I'm talking about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why is this being downvoted? (this comment) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the risk of people knowing how dumb I really am, what is TAT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> wtf? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ???????  eh? ??????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been posting for almost a year, and following links from bots, I myself have the same questions. ?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
