<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty much saying that everything we know is only what the mind is seeing it as. There was a very good explanation here: https://www.reddit.com/r/Buddhism/comments/65c0b9/jay_garfield_explains_the_three_natures_of/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved that mental projection study he talked about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name of the breed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Feel Like the Future of Good Lock Isn't Looking Good For Us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Good Lock hasn't been updated for a while, and I've been hoping for an update to come out with more of a Nougat style (edge to edge notification shade and lock screen notifications, no gap above the quick toggles, etc.) however, even if this happens, us Note 4 users probably will not be getting it.  
  
Samsung's Nougat UI is already pretty close to stock, especially with a material theme it could look almost identical. This is making me wonder if Good Lock is even going to get an update at all. Also, the Note 4 doesn't even officially support Good Lock and all the devices that do are getting Nougat upgrades, so if there is a new build of Good Lock at this point it will probably be only installable with Nougat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really surprised. A large majority of Samsung phones I see are s5's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, how very big of you. You're an alpha male, are you? Well, let me clue you in on something: Alpha Males haven't been in charge for a good couple of decades. Obviously, this tirade is directed on a High School level. Once you get out of high school, and begin working at your dead-end office job, you know who your boss is going to be? That's right, that pasty nerd you made fun of. It's funny, you see. The majority of the women you are talking about, despite the blatant lies you've slipped in, and the generalizations which remain moderately untrue, are frankly, idiotic sluts. The fact that you're trying to taunt us with them is inane, because while they sound appealing in text, in reality, we wouldn't want anything to do with the *ing skanks. And furthermore, thank you for "ing every girl in the school (I bet you can bench 2000 pounds too, amirite?)." Honestly, thank you. Why, you may ask? Because, by taking away the easy route, you have brought pain upon us. You have brought us misery, you have forced us to adapt to that misery, and to grow as people. Luxury doesn't incite growth, pain does. So while you're busy sticking it in your AIDS-ridden skanks, we're studying, learning, gaining skills that are necessary for life. You may scoff at this, call us stupid nerds for not getting the pussy while it's hot, but guess what? We're going to get it eventually. You said so yourself, women love power. So, eventually, you're going to find a women you love as much as she primally needs you. You're going to get married, maybe settle down a bit. Wild sex for the first two years, but after a while, she'll get ansy. She'll grow tired of the novelty of the Alpha Male. Your relationship will become the dull forced marriage that is seen constantly in America. You'll likely divorce her and move on, getting a younger wife that'll need you as much as your old wife did when you first married. Seems swell, doesn't it? I can assure you, it isn't. By now, we have risen to power. While you live the life of the swingers, we are the Senators, the Chairmen, we are the rulers of life as you know it. We have transcended your pitiful existence, and control every aspect of your very fate, without you even so much as noticing. By now, we have the money and the power, and as Scarface once said (We know you love him, and have his poster on your bedroom wall,'cause you're cool like that) next we get the women. And guess who it is that loves power, as you said women do? That's right, it's your little skank of a wife! Now, most of us will likely have settled down with a wife, but I'm sure there are plenty that would be glad to take your wife when she dumps your sorry ass to go to the people she knows have the real power. And, as we get older, our fortunes and power will grow. We'll eventually get a few trophy wives, settle down a bit, and live in the lap of luxury. Meanwhile, you, the "Alpha Male" will be left alone. By the time you hit thirty, your primal attraction, your ONLY asset, will begin to fade. Your third wife in ten years will grow tired of your old, pitiful body, and will leave you. Stuck in a dead-end job as one of our pawns, you will grow old and even less appealing. Eventually you will die an old and unloved man, either by taking your own life, drowning yourself in booze, or perhaps merely out of your own misery. So go ahead. Brag about how many women you are ***ing. Call us losers. We may seem to be upset, and you may mock our pain, but I assure you, we know your fate. And we are smiling inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer their 8 string stuff much more. It gets you like lost in a trance with the low tones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I never really got that vibe from it. Very interesting though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was fantastic but not their best (although close). "Nothing" would be my number 1, then "Violent Sleep" and then "Catch 33". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are all already enlightened as there is no one to be enlightened nor any enlightenment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found Some Dharma in Meshuggah Lyrics (Metal Band) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This band is pretty praised for their very well crafted lyrics, so I decided to actually look into the lyrics and found a lot of explicitly dharmic ideas in their album "Catch ThirtyThree". The band is heavy metal (and very strange heavy metal at that) so it will probably not be enjoyable to everyone. Anyway here's the album that I found a lot of the content from  
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b7HHEWsWKZU list=PLZnw-eYMBLSw4oET4L1v30DFzlftiOEhb  
  
Some notable lyrics:  
  
From "Inprint of the Un-Saved"  
The scattered jigsaw of my redemption laid out before my eyes  
Each piece as amorphous as the other - Each piece in its lack of shape a lie  
  
From "Disenchantment"
I stay my breath to escape this slavery  
I stay my breath to re-awake and face it encore  
The struggle to free myself of restraints, becomes my very shackles  
  
From "Re-Inanimate"  
My ignorance cast in the mold of all things absolute  
I sustain forever my gaze. A stare fixed on the distant oblivion  
Resting in the inverted state of being dead, non-sensory matter  
As all the earth, the wind, the fire, the sea behold and learn to pity me  
  
From "Entrapment"  
Mutiny of self. Insurrection games convincingly performed  
Incapacitated by physical thoughts acting out the will of tendon and bone  
  
From "Mind's Mirrors"  
The feeding frenzy of my starving soul, gnawing voraciously at the bones,  
the exo-skeletal patchwork protecting my own reflection within;  
The twin-and-same engaged in the mirrored act of chewing away  
at the shell of my attacking self. The paradox unseen  
  
Treacherous this deceit to make no choice matter  
To have and yet lose yourself, until finally all reasons why are forgotten  
To live through ones own shadow. Mute and blinded, is to really see  
Eclipse the golden mirror and the reflection is set free  
  
From "Shed"  
I float through physical thoughts. I stare down the abyss of organic dreams  
All bets off, I plunge - Only to find that self is shed   
  
From "Dehumanization"
A new level reached, where the absence of air lets me breathe  
I'm inverted electrical impulses. A malfunctioning death-code incomplete  
All things before me, at first unliving glimpse undeciphered  
Its semantics rid of logic. Nothing is all. All is contradiction  
  
From "Sum"  
Vision will blind. Severance ties. Median am I. True are all lies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ankle Pain During Sitting Meditation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been sitting regularly for about a year and a half now and I still haven't found a way to sit that is completely comfortable and doesn't result in some kind of worsening pain (usually in my ankles). For whatever reason, my ankles really do not like getting forcibly extended. I've tried sitting Burmese, quarter lotus, half lotus, and kneeling with a cushion under me. The kneeling seems to provide the least pain to my ankles but more pain elsewhere, particularly my inner thigh. The rest of the positions I feel I'm most mentally sable in but my ankles getting extended becomes unbearable and I'm not sure if they're becoming damaged or not. I have very minor scoliosis (like 10% or something like that) and I have a condition called squinted knee where my knees sort of face each other at 45 degree ankles, causing me to walk with my feet pointed away from each other if I want my legs to be straight, just in case either of these may be the cause of this ankle pain.  
So anyone have any suggestions? inb4 using a chair I cannot focus nearly as well sitting in a chair as I can in some kind of cross legged position. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like that's some sort of new design language for Moto. Hope it wears off soon (although it won't for the Moto Z because they need to fit the mods).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nowhere, and it still isn't anywhere now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, other than being called Laughing Buddha, more eastern names for him include Budai and Hotei (the latter meaning "cloth-sack" due to the sack he carries around). In some cultures he's depicted as sort of a santa-like figure, as in he goes around with a bag and delivers gifts to children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the camera noticeably worse than the Note 4? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've studied Christianity, Taoism, Hinduism, New Age, Judaism, and more occult religions somewhat (Thelema, Anti-Cosmic Satanism, etc.) and Buddhism. I feel that they all offer really good moral lessons, however Buddhism and Taoism are the ones that feel almost foolish to deny when it comes to practice and learning. For example with Christianity, if you don't believe in heaven, the whole thing sort of just falls apart and you're left with trying to figure out realistic answers to *why* to do good things, which just brings you to Buddhist understandings. The outcome of the practice still requires faith yes, but the core teachings and understandings of Buddhism are much more rational and easier to find proof in in everyday life.  
  
Hinduism I also feel somewhat similar too (especially Advaita Vedanta) but it seems to be focused too much on ritual and less on how to actually arrive at the Truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says it's already off. The images when viewed are fine, it's just when they're downloaded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Images Get Compressed When Downloaded From Chrome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed that whenever I download an image from Chrome the image quality of the downloaded image is terrible. There's compression marks all over the place and unsmooth color gradients etc. Is there a way to fix this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rats and roaches are thriving though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Icon Pack: Glasklart  
Clock: Analog Clock Widget  
Launcher: Nova  
Phone wallpaper is just black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! Fooled again, Bot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luxury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Filed My Acoustic Saddle Too Far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was trying to lower the action on my acoustic and accidentally filed the saddle too far on the high e side and now the e string just buzzes and has no sustain. Is there any way to fix this or do i just need a new saddle?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Filed My Acoustic Saddle Too Far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 06:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they're both God and in thinking about how they can both be the same God we get an idea of an ultimate reality far beyond our understanding or ability to imagine that we can still experience or interact with, even if in a limited and small way. This idea is different from the God of Abraham who has a clear identity, desires, dislikes, et cetera.  
  
Read up on Kabbalah studies. Judaism believes God to be the same as how you described Brahman.  
  
According to Wikipedia:  
The nature of the divine prompted kabbalists to envision two aspects to God: (a) God in essence, absolutely transcendent, unknowable, limitless Divine simplicity, and (b) God in manifestation, the revealed persona of God through which he creates and sustains and relates to mankind. Kabbalists speak of the first as Ein/Ayn Sof (  "the infinite/endless", literally "that which has no limits"). Of the impersonal Ein Sof nothing can be grasped. The second aspect of divine emanations, however, are accessible to human perception, dynamically interacting throughout spiritual and physical existence, reveal the divine immanently, and are bound up in the life of man. Kabbalists believe that these two aspects are not contradictory but complement one another, emanations revealing the concealed mystery from within the Godhead.  
  
Also according to my friend who is looking into Judaic spirituality, nothing can truly be said to exist nor not exist, somewhat similar to Buddhism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never read the Dalai Lama's book but I really liked The Tibetan Book of Living and Dying. Some if it seemed a little too faith-based for me but all of it seems to be beneficial in practice. I would recommend to continue reading them but at the same time study general Buddhist concepts, or else some of the concepts you've been reading about may be misunderstood. For example, when Sogyal Rinpoche says how the Ground Luminosity is the "true Self", he does not mean this in the sense of a soul. Buddhists do not believe that there is Self, so take away everything we believe to be real and all you're left with is the way things actually are and the way "you" actually are, what Sogyal Rinpoche is referring to as the Self. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be John McDonald? I know he only uses the "she" pronoun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't get Rick and Morty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read What the Buddha Taught by Walpola Rahula, it's an incredibly good book on the core understandings and practices of Buddhism. Keep in mind that it will seem very different than The Tibetan Book of Living and Dying, as that book is based in Vajrayana Buddhism (a more esoteric form of Buddhism based on teachings believed to be taught by the Buddha later in his life). Don't expect to find anything about the Bardo of Dharmata or the Ground Luminosity from Dr. Rahula, but it is a great start if you want to learn about Buddhism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 04:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading somewhere that the hair knots are actually snails  that covered his head while he was meditating so he wouldn't get sunburn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But even the Mahayana Sutras recognize the Theravadin accounts as being legitimate but just not the full teachings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, how very big of you. You're an alpha male, are you? Well, let me clue you in on something: Alpha Males haven't been in charge for a good couple of decades. Obviously, this tirade is directed on a High School level. Once you get out of high school, and begin working at your dead-end office job, you know who your boss is going to be? That's right, that pasty nerd you made fun of. It's funny, you see. The majority of the women you are talking about, despite the blatant lies you've slipped in, and the generalizations which remain moderately untrue, are frankly, idiotic sluts. The fact that you're trying to taunt us with them is inane, because while they sound appealing in text, in reality, we wouldn't want anything to do with the ****ing skanks. And furthermore, thank you for "****ing every girl in the school (I bet you can bench 2000 pounds too, amirite?)." Honestly, thank you. Why, you may ask? Because, by taking away the easy route, you have brought pain upon us. You have brought us misery, you have forced us to adapt to that misery, and to grow as people. Luxury doesn't incite growth, pain does. So while you're busy sticking it in your AIDS-ridden skanks, we're studying, learning, gaining skills that are necessary for life. You may scoff at this, call us stupid nerds for not getting the pussy while it's hot, but guess what? We're going to get it eventually. You said so yourself, women love power. So, eventually, you're going to find a women you love as much as she primally needs you. You're going to get married, maybe settle down a bit. Wild sex for the first two years, but after a while, she'll get ansy. She'll grow tired of the novelty of the Alpha Male. Your relationship will become the dull forced marriage that is seen constantly in America. You'll likely divorce her and move on, getting a younger wife that'll need you as much as your old wife did when you first married. Seems swell, doesn't it? I can assure you, it isn't. By now, we have risen to power. While you live the life of the swingers, we are the Senators, the Chairmen, we are the rulers of life as you know it. We have transcended your pitiful existence, and control every aspect of your very fate, without you even so much as noticing. By now, we have the money and the power, and as Scarface once said (We know you love him, and have his poster on your bedroom wall,'cause you're cool like that) next we get the women. And guess who it is that loves power, as you said women do? That's right, it's your little skank of a wife! Now, most of us will likely have settled down with a wife, but I'm sure there are plenty that would be glad to take your wife when she dumps your sorry ass to go to the people she knows have the real power. And, as we get older, our fortunes and power will grow. We'll eventually get a few trophy wives, settle down a bit, and live in the lap of luxury. Meanwhile, you, the "Alpha Male" will be left alone. By the time you hit thirty, your primal attraction, your ONLY asset, will begin to fade. Your third wife in ten years will grow tired of your old, pitiful body, and will leave you. Stuck in a dead-end job as one of our pawns, you will grow old and even less appealing. Eventually you will die an old and unloved man, either by taking your own life, drowning yourself in booze, or perhaps merely out of your own misery. So go ahead. Brag about how many women you are ****ing. Call us losers. We may seem to be upset, and you may mock our pain, but I assure you, we know your fate. And we are smiling inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I get gold so I can see what r/lounge is and then I'll give it back? I promise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mahaparinirvana Sutra vs. Mahaparinibbana Sutta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't the fact that these two sutras describe the Buddha's parinirvana in two different ways mean that one of them must not be true? And if one of them isn't true, what does that say about the lineage to which said text is ascribed? Not trying to point to different sects and say "your stuff isn't true" but how is the "elephant in the room" here usually addressed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kindle readers have them and their pretty good. The e-ink display isn't practical for regular use but the touch is fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where's All the Hearing Damage From Listening to Loud Music? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.technobuzz.net/unlock-bootloader-verizon-samsung-galaxy-note-4-sm-n910v/  
  
I found this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions About Rooting N910V </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty new to rooting, and while I've researched it a bit I'm still confused about the process I would have to go through to root my Verizon Note 4.  
  
1) Does the bootloader need to be unlocked for this phone before rooting?  
  
2) Where are the risks in rooting?  
  
3) Is installing something like Xposed as risky as installing something like Cyanogenmod? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else's GPM acting especially slow lately? Like more than usual? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the songs I have downloaded are from when I used to download from YouTube so I don't think any DAC can save that quality haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More megapixels means worse low light photos unless they increase the sensor size as well which they don't really have room for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He specifies in the Mahaparinirvana Sutra that we went into Parinirvana for the sake of expediancy, basically so people won't get overly attached and to teach about the idea of Parinirvana by example. However he also specifies that he did not go extinct and that the Buddha is eternal being one with the Dharmakaya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We described it to my friend who hadn't seen the movie yet,  
"You know Darth Vader in the video games? Yeah...that"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on previous leaks I've seen, the height is about that of a Galaxy Note 4/5/7 etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got into New Age spirituality from listening to Tool at age 18, then later moved on to Advaita Vedanta Hinduism before turning 19. My Asian Philosophy professor taught me Buddhism around then as well. I initially hated it but I couldn't figure out why at the time. A few months later I realized that it made me uncomfortable by flat out telling me that everything I believed to be true wasn't. So then once I finally let go of everything I believed to be true I quickly realized that Buddhism is the correct way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not anymore, I simply realize that I drifted off and bring my attention back, only to find that I drift off again very quickly. I meditate every morning after I wake up for 20-40 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
