<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8864</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to make money and get a job with my applied math MS. Any thoughts/experiences? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PAAAAAAAAAAAAAAR-TAAAAY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a nasty words.  Lol.  Some words just sound nasty, not by definition, like "tinny." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FOR-YAY? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right!  I really hate the pronunciation on this one.  It should have been spelled "La Tech." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GAH-LOW-ISS ?  Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What terms/names do you have a hard time pronouncing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have trouble with "Cauchy."  I keep pronouncing it COO-CHEE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grades really suck the fun out of math, or school in general for that matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 04:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember talking to a colleague in my physics lab from Germany.  He said that for his undergrad career, he didn't take a single test.  Rather, after two years of self study he was required to take a qualification exam and defend in front of a committee.  

Another professor of mine told me  that most of the students at my undergraduate institution were bright students, and the difference between an A and B were like splitting hairs.  I see so many intelligent, bright students leave STEM because of grading politics like this.

I prefer a project based education, where you demonstrate your knowledge of what you've learned in terms of real life applications.

I find grades to be incredibly petty and arbitrary in how it evaluates students.  Most students study to the test, and big picture ideas about how it connects to other subjects is seen as trivia.  This mentality of working towards a grade discourages creativity and critical thinking.  So long as you think like the professor, you'll have a good grade, but is that really learning?

For myself during my masters degree program, the teachers dock points from students on very trivial details.  I remember for one class if you didn't label a certain subscript a certain way, you were docked a whole midterm grade.  

What's even more annoying is my current topology class, I could be off my a word or proof miss a couple steps to the end, and half the points for that test are gone.  It's taking a huge psychological toll on me.  I feel like I can't be a professional mathematician.

I wish I could be in some sort educational institution where the way to graduate is to create something instead of taking a test, like building some sort of machine or presenting a thesis or teaching a class.  

If I don't get into a relatively good PhD program, I'm simply going to give up on STEM.  I don't feel like teaching either because our education system is so messed up.  If the worst happens, my life's work in STEM will be completely meaningless.  I sort of wished I was a hedonistic, greedy child that enjoyed my youth instead of walling myself up in a hole learning trivia like a trained circus animal.  I'd rather be a pompous, greedy wall street douchebag that rips off everyone.  At least I'd be rich living in bliss.  This idea of "working hard" and "studying your passion" feels more and more like BS.  It's propaganda to keep the lower class to work for the rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 02:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like industry doesn't really hire guys with just master's degrees.  I would have to learn how to program.  Actually, I'd rather get a job in industry than get a PhD.  A professor convinced me to try for grad school just to keep options open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 20:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, what examples did you have in  mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 18:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my experience, most people sitting in a math class feel like what they're learning is irrelevant to their lives.  I don't believe an "well-rounded education" because it imposes values onto the student.  If you really wanted a practical, well rounded person, I think standards should teach students civics, money management, and logic.  These three classes are way more practical than geometry, trig, and calculus to the average student.

I find it strange that once people leave high school, students who enter community college start to really get serious about their education and choose only the best teachers.  The bad ones get low enrollment and eventually get fired if they aren't tenured. 

In public education, there's no real way to let the free market push out the bad teachers.  Once they've tenured, it takes a lot to pry them out, and even then they just get shuffled into another school district.

If I can go into a high school where students, staff, and my fellow teachers are passionate to teach and willing to learn from their mistakes, I'd be more than happy to teach.  Instead, we treat students like inmates.  Some students come from unstructured homes and come from poverty.  Teachers have little to no support in terms of improving, and just a few teachers who slack off impose a huge burden on other teachers, so you create a culture of apathy and stagnation.  Teachers have no ownership of classrooms for various reasons.  Common core makes no sense, and students expect their teachers to be grade mills for doing the bare minimum.    And parents pressure teachers for grade inflation.

I can go on and on, but I don't want to teach in public schools.  Nor does the idea of working for a Big Data company to generate ad revenue excite me either.    Or maybe I should sell-out?  Get tenure as a public school teacher and coast for the rest of my life, and get full pension.  Or sell out at a big data company, make big bucks, and retire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like that's my backup career.  But I would rather teach community college than public education.  At least in America, it's mostly useless to the students.  Basic arithmetic is mostly what everyone needs.   I believe since public school teachers are tenured, most don't care a slip into a state of perpetual laziness.  There's no future in teaching in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what they can realistically say.  "Try harder?"  My current topology professor is giving me that line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update:  Regardless of what happens to this class, I'm going into an applied math or stats PhD program.  I have no intention of entering a pure maths program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first C in grad school math, I feel miserable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 05:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to apply to a PhD program.  I'm currently a masters student.  I'm taking topology, and I just can't get those damn proofs down.  A "C" on the transcript is really bad for grad school.

I've gone to every single office hours, felt like I've engaged with the material, but I just can't seem to perform when tests come!

What's worse is that I'm doing all this studying, and I don't see the joy in what I'm doing. I feel like if I didn't have to take tests, and can study the material at my leisure, things would feel much better.  Not only that, I have some personal goals and needs that I'm not attending to, and I feel like I'm sacrificing my life's work for something that isn't providing me happiness.

I'm not exactly too thrilled about a PhD program either because I feel the same thing might happen.  Nor am I too thrilled about getting a desk job that isn't engaging.

Ironically, I went to the library to borrow a book on the history of math.  It's really exciting to read!  And see how people have invented and challenged themselves with math.  They didn't have to worry about grades either.

What should I be looking forward to?  Should I start taking anti-depressants?  Worst case scenario is that I don't get into a PhD program, wind up unemployed or in a job that has nothing to do with my life's work, only to see myself slowly waste away into nothingness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feymann method? Studying habits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious if you guys have any studying habits/techniques you swear by that works? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the tip.  Are you familiar with the Feynmann method?  Sounds very similar to what you are proposing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I feel like I might get stuck staring at the same resources over and over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I'm not doing well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
