<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2866</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will say that I was also one who internalized my issues, and it backfired to the point where I was hospitalized in my 20s because I just shut. down. and. couldn't. deal. I would really recommend talking to your therapist about coping skills. You cannot change your mother, but you can make it easier for yourself. 3

Does your therapist have you in dialectic behavioral therapy? It is super helpful for people with borderline. If not, I would try to find one that does. 3 to you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does having BPD and depression affect my relationship with my children? I can only give it from my side, obviously, and my kids are still fairly young (8 and 11). I think that I am not my diagnosis, nor am I my disease. My BPD causes me to act out in ways that can be harmful to others around me, so I am always vigilante about a few things: my surroundings, the people I have to interact with, and I always have a plan in case I have a triggering event.

I apologize a lot to my kids, because I think it helps them realize that parents can screw up, and I tell them I love them **a lot**. We also talk a lot about actions having consequences, whether we mean for them to have negative or positive consequences, as people we have to own up to it when there are negative consequences.

I also tell my kids that forgiveness is within their power, and no one has to make them forgive someone else. We talk a lot about taking ownership of our actions, and something my therapist told me to do about things is something I do a lot with my kids. We imagine things as a ball that we hold in front of us - whether that thing is something we perceive as a slight, or something bad that happened, etc., we hold it outside our bodies. Then it's our choice whether we accept the ball inside us, or acknowledge it and drop it. (I made a drawing to help my kids conceptualize it). 

i think because I have BPD and depression, I'm hyper aware of how they are doing emotionally, and check in with them a lot. I am also a HUGE fan of personal time, and I actually make them have separate "alone time" during the day to recharge. 

I hope that helps answer your question?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
