<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2924</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Marty McFly made many different timelines in the Back to the Future movies, maybe Terminator could be the result of another one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be VERY convuluted, is the thing. Because then there's the whole war of machines and whatnot. Unless if one of the movies it's all actually prevented and never happens, and I've only seen Terminator and Terminator Genisys so I dunno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When do they take place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooooh! The thing is, this would be a universe where people are all aware that there are bees who can talk. Do you think that would change the future? And oh my god, if we add Bee Movie, then we should add The Wicker Man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen it lol. When does it take place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Well then awesome, I'll add it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robocop takes place in like the middle of the 21st century I think, about 30 years after Blade Runner. It would be a bit of a stretch to have Robocop take place after Blade Runner, when replicants are much more advanced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, that was in here at first, but it doesn't line up with the timeline at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I accidentally put in two movies called Predators when one is meant to be Predator 2. Whoops.

And cool, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah cool. I'm pretty sure it'd line up well, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Why do you say that? Does it line up perfectly with all the other movies? Also, when do they take place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What other movies could take place within the Alien/Predator/Blade Runner/Ghost in the Shell universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey so for some time now I've been trying to get a timeline together of a possible shared universe between movies. Now, obviously Alien, Predator, and Blade Runner are set in the same mythos, but when I watched the 1996 version of Ghost in the Shell, I realized that it could totally take place within the same universe as Blade Runner, being that Major is a replicant, and then therefore it would be tied to the other films as well.

I want this timeline to grow and have so many other movies in it, so do you guys think any other movies would work? Here's what I got so far:

1. Predator  
2. Predators  
3. Alien vs. Predator  
4. Alien vs. Predator: Requiem  
5. Predators  
6. Blade Runner  
7. Ghost in the Shell (1996)  
8. Blade Runner 2049  
9. Prometheus  
10. Alien: Covenant  
12. 11. Alien  
13. Aliens  
14. Alien 3  
15. Alien: Ressurrection  

I did originally have Ex Machina set in here, which would have been the film that shows the creation of the replicants and how they became unleashed to the world, but sadly I found out that I guess the film takes place in the 2020s, which wouldn't line up as replicants were created in the mid-2010s.


EDIT 1: I'm actually now thinking that Back to the Future could fit in this universe. It all fits together, right? There are flying cars in 2015 in Back to the Future Part II, and they also exist in 2019 in Blade Runner.

EDIT 2: Also, I'm thinking 2001: A Space Odyssey could also make sense in this timeline. Replicants wouldn't be created until the mid-2010s, but the first computer AI could have been created beforehand. I mean, replicants are clearly more sophisticated than Hal 9000.

EDIT 3: I'm adding in Seinfeld. Why? Well, it's amazing, and it also doesn't contradict anything considering it's a show about nothing, so I'm putting it in god dammit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's your favorite film director and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> World's Greatest Dad is a really good dark comedy about a Dad whose son kills himself. You should watch it, it's really funny actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, so without spoilers, can someone who has scene Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2 tell me how the post credit scenes are? Don't say exactly what happens, but if they're good or not, and of any of them set up future movies. I repeat, no spoilers or else I will find you, and I will kill you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nein </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
