<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3404</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please read [this thread](https://np.reddit.com/r/indonesia/comments/645nx0/one_of_marvel_comics_is_being_used_as_a_tool_to/) by OP. It is kinda long but you'll understand what is happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw some of the Facebook Comments and some of them are rationals and some of them hope Marvel do not fire him. I am understand Bahasa Indonesia.

I wished he apologized for what he did because it may offended some of the X-Men readers but sadly he got more defensive.

I think Marvel has every right to fire him and I understand that Marvel do not want to associate their brand with an artist that has intolerant views.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 07:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Duh, kuota nya mau habis nih." 

I heard this when I was in Fushimi Inari Shrine, Kyoto, Japan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Champion Weapons, Savage Lynel Bow, Royal Bow, Savage Lynel Shield, and Savage Lynel Bow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is just the lightning not electrical attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched this movie few months ago after I visited Tokyo for vacation. So some of the place are really familiar to me like Yoyogi station.

I like the movie but what impressed me the most is how they did the big reveal after several build-up moments. It was really well executed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where to farm Swift Violet easily?

I need 90 Swift Violet in total to upgrades my stuffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parent said that Do not marry someone from Padang/West Sumatra, because most of them are pelit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 05:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This video](https://youtu.be/7IUPHWJuzC0) is for you. I learned a lot from this video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah me too, initially I paid because I do not like the advertisement but I am glad that I paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What do you think of this?](https://www.engadget.com/2017/04/04/spotify-keeping-new-music-from-free-users/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Topple the Patriarchy!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, it is primarily about three mothers with different backgrounds who live in California and they got involved in a mystery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 05:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone here like [Big Little Lies \(2017\)](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt3920596/)? 

It is one of my favorite shows that debuted this year. I really like that most of the characters are relatable and likable but they are not saint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember that She mentioned to Ed that she has baggage. Maybe that was foreshadowing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please check [this map](http://www.zeldadungeon.net/breath-of-the-wild-interactive-map/) and turn the legends off except Shrines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corned Beef, Cheese, or sometimes Vegetables to add some crunch and freshness to the my Indomie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Russell Crowe who did the voice over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in Jurassic World and I am glad that he branched into blockbuster movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to share [this video](https://youtu.be/7IUPHWJuzC0) about Lynel attack patterns and how to handle them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to share [this video](https://youtu.be/7IUPHWJuzC0) about Lynel Attack patterns and how to handle those things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think [this video](https://youtu.be/7IUPHWJuzC0) is good one about Lynel Attack Pattern and how you counter them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 06:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am upset because there is no collaboration with Ed Sheeran </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spotify link.](https://open.spotify.com/album/56mWuvukxl5ylhGoa0OBzw)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pernah waktu tinggal di luar negeri, lagi di bus, ngelihat orang duduk di sebelah saya main Tinder, waktu itu belum banyak yang pakai Tinder. Saya lihat dia banyak swipe left tapi ada 2-3 kali swipe right. 

Sampai rumah saya langsung coba Tinder dan sejam kemudian langsung uninstall gara gara gak ada yang bisa di-swipe right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this movie was okay but I enjoyed it as a stand alone movie. Scarlett Johansson was good as Major.  I gave it around 6 out of 10. I wish Togusa had more prominent role in this adaptation

About the whitewashing, I can get behind the reason but yeah that does not mean that every adaptation should do the white washing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colin Trevorrows The Book of Henry - Official Trailer - Naomi Watts, Jacob Tremblay, Maddie Ziegler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you the reason but it is spoiler. They still call her Major but not Major Kusanagi

[Her name in this one is Major Mira Killian. In the two third of the movie, it is revealed that her real identity is Motoko Kusanagi, HANKA stole her life and her brain and people may not care about her because she is a missing person. They re-brand her as Major Mira Killian along with her fake memories.](#spoiler)

[Like the other person said, I think this movie explained well enough why she is not an Asian woman but a Caucasian woman.](#spoiler)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie surprised me, it was not as good as the original but as the stand alone movie, I really enjoyed it. 

The plot and how the story goes could have been better but The special effects was really gorgeous to look at and I think Scarlett Johansson is a good fit for Major. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your opinion, what is the best one-handed weapon, two-handed weapon, spear, and shield besides hylian shield?

Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not mind if the trailer gave too much. After all, it is for broader demographic, not just /r/movies readers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought boikot Inul Daratista is a thing in 2003. Then, she is successful in her karaoke business and she does not need to ngebor anymore.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His twitter is not good for your blood pressure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes, Chris Pratt jerked harder than /r/movies, /r/moviescirclejerk, and /r/marvelstudios. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good drop for Beauty and the Beast and fantastic number for Power Rangers. I am glad that both of those movies have a good number for Box Office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anggap saja gambar tersebut sebagai ilustrasi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother just sent me [this picture](http://i.imgur.com/ThOMo8G.jpg) few hours ago. If you want to post it on a separate thread, you have my permission to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is Wonder Woman, actually they just released these things when I read your message.

* [Wonder Woman Teaser](https://streamable.com/cvmod)

* [Wonder Woman Poster](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C7sSce9VsAAzmiR.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I am not sure because after I watched the movie, all I can think about is Krispy Kreme. I think it works on their part.

[It shows on their donut box too.](https://i0.wp.com/www.powerrangersnow.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/02/Photo-Feb-20-9-54-17-PM.jpg?resize=338%2C450 ssl=1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie reminds me of Alien, Gravity, and the Thing. Life was not as good as those movies but if you are looking for a thriller to watch on movie theater this week, this movie is a good choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a fine line between a good and bad product placement and Krispy Kreme  placement is on that line. I am not sure if it is good or bad product placement.

But I enjoyed the characters in this movie. Especially when Trini and Kimberly played with their donuts and the campfire scene. Those scene show this movie does not neglect character moments and I appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just a teaser poster and a new trailer will debut this Saturday. 

ICYMI

* [Flash poster](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C7o9W1KVYAEfPGI.jpg)

* [Flash teaser](https://streamable.com/43iuh)

* [Batman Poster](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C7oQOS2X0AI3I5u.jpg)

* [Batman teaser](https://streamable.com/798lb)

* [Aquaman Poster](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C7nzTmwV4AANCGh.jpg)

* [Aquaman teaser](https://streamable.com/4fxal)

* [Wonder Woman Teaser](https://streamable.com/cvmod)

* [Wonder Woman Poster](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C7sSce9VsAAzmiR.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why Lynel hunting is so addictive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because some people like him as Superman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Lionsgate try to find a new franchise after Divergent and Hunger Games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Aly and AJ changed back their name and they will released a new song in couple weeks.](https://twitter.com/alyandaj/status/830266813795561472).

I know this from this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brandon Routh, I expect him to have bigger career after Superman Returns. Well, at least he is pretty good on Arrowverse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the movie and I think it was okay. I think the movie got better ehen the first person died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the movie and it was the same case with the Beauty and the Beast. People just blow this out of proportions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am glad that Beauty and the Beast got that OW number and I hope that Disney know what to do with their live action remakes.

I realized that this March has so many tentpoles compared to the other Mach in past years like Logan, Kong: Skull Island, Life, Power Ranger, and Ghost in the Shell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try this place called [Gelato Secrets,](https://www.zomato.com/jakarta/gelato-secrets-menteng) near Menteng Jakarta Eye Center, it is near my place. They also have some unique flavors like dark Chocolate Chili and many different flavors of Sorbet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not think Beauty and the Beast will be front loaded. Family Movie has some legs, especially when they got decent reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one should I do first? Vah Medoh or Vah Naboris? I already did Vah Ruta and Vah Rudania. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant to show only movie that distributed by Disney. 

But the comment said that 6 out 7 highest OW number belong to movie distributed Disney so the one who hold 7th position could be change between Beauty and Harry Potter Deathly Hallows Part 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Star Wars: The Force Awakens $247,966,675	

1. Marvel's The Avengers $208,806,270	

1. Avengers: Age of Ultron $191,271,109	

1. Captain America: Civil War $179,139,142

1. Iron Man 3 $174,144,585	

1. Beauty and the Beast Estimated number $170,000,000 

Although the number could be interchangeable with Harry Potter Deathly Hallows Part 2 which has $169,189,427. Now we have to wait actual OW number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, good job Disney. I think that they have a good direction what to do with their live-action remakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that this movie has more moments of Belle and The Prince and I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any tips on how to beat Lynel in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Cobie Smulders works better on tv (Jack Reacher 2 didn't do so great as one of her first leading roles in film)

The movie is meh in my opinion but Cobie Smulders is really good as an action star. She got a bright future as an action movie star </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Cobie Smulders works better on tv (Jack Reacher 2 didn't do so great as one of her first leading roles in film)

The movie is meh in my opinion but Cobie Smulders is really good as an action star. She got a bright future as an action movie star </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah surprisingly Book of Life was pretty decent on many aspects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people will say this reminds them of Book of Life but I think the only similarity is both of these movies is about Da de Muertos. I think the approach will be different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 05:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the Wii U version and yes there are some noticeable frame drops. Especially when you enter a village. But fortunately, that did not reduce an my enjoyment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thank you, I thought it was one time thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 02:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got The Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild few days ago and this game is so addictive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to get Epona back? I used my Smash Link Amiibo and forgot to register my Epona.

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read some reviews that imply Luke Evans is really good as Gaston </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Disney, the name itself sell like kacang rebus in here. That includes some of the properties that distributed by Disney like Star Wars and MCU. It would be a huge mistake if they delayed the release.

Although, general public did not notice that Star Wars and Marvel in general owned by Disney. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Franco, meanwhile, makes for a terrific double threat. While hes clearly having a blast in the role of his career, hes also a generous director who gives his all-star ensemble, also including the likes of Judd Apatow, Megan Mullally, Zac Efron, Zoey Deutch, Bryan Cranston and Jacki Weaver, ample opportunity to shine.

I am afraid that James Franco would screw this up but I am glad that he for once did a good job in this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Franco's 'The Disaster Artist': SXSW Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 09:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it looks promising. I think this is the first time that Ava Duvernay tackle a blockbuster movie and I cannot wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a wedding last night and I saw Anies and Sandi on a close distance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BABY DRIVER (1994 ) DP: Bill Pope | Dir: Edgar Wright </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 09:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some Twitter reactions

[Baby Driver is exactly what you'd imagine an Edgar Wright Fast   Furious to be. A pure blast - Devindra Hardawar](https://twitter.com/Devindra/status/840792994638888961)

[BABY DRIVER: Let's call this HEAT remade as a jukebox musical. Very different from Wright's previous movies and a total blast. - Jacob Hall](https://twitter.com/JacobSHall/status/840793400840450048)


[BABY DRIVER is Edgar Wright's LA LA LAND: Every bit of its soundtrack is choreographed \(by Ryan Heffington\) to action and dialogue - Jen Yamato](https://twitter.com/jenyamato/status/840796114072801280)


[BABY DRIVER: A really fun, kick-ass, wild ride! #EdgarWright fans will go crazy! Awesome cast, amazing soundtrack, great car chases! - Scott Mantz](https://twitter.com/MovieMantz/status/840794007122903040) 

From these reactions, I think the movie is going to be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so, they do not want to screw this. If they screwed this and JL, then they will done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neutral though, I used to live in canada and most of canadian people are nice enough to me. I can expect the same thing for you.

Plus Jakarta is a good place for expats to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trailer sounds fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed the movie, The dialogues and the characterization are not really good but at least it is better in this movie than Godzilla 2014. John C. Reilly's character is the only characterization that I feel they done something right in this movie

The monsters fight were awesome and brutal. Especially when Kong pulled the organs from the Skull Crawler.

Is MONARCH going to be act like SHIELD in this universe?

I cannot wait for other kaijus, especially Mothra and King Ghidorah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Trek, Mission Impossible, and Transformers are the only franchises that I think have good prospects for Paramount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wet Hot American Summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This and Guardans of the Galaxy Vol. 2 are most anticipated movies from Marvel Studios.

I just read this and it feels reassuring about how the movie is going to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a feeling that Charlize Theron and Jason Statham are siblings and Hellen Mirren is their mother in this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah me too, actually Spiderman: Homecoming is the least anticipated property this year from MCU for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the movie though, it is not perfect. The humans character got uneven development and the only character that well executed is John C. Reilly's character. But, the monsters fights in this movie were awesome. I think it is worth if you just want to watch monsters beat out each other.

P.S. I like the after credit scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 07:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * IGN: Irham
* Deposit: Pancham, level 27, male, nest ball
* Request: Landorus-Therian
* Request #1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amy Poehler, I want her to do more Drama in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the International trailer](https://youtu.be/vaVR9-rTUTI).

I prefer international trailer though, it seems more fitting for this movie because it is more comedic than red band trailer that seems filled with plot points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say it is combinations of Hangover and Very Bad Things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the International trailer](https://youtu.be/vaVR9-rTUTI).

Anyway Scarlett Johansson, Kate McKinnon, Ilana Glazer, Jillian Bell, and Zoe Kravitz are solid enough for me to convince me to watch the movie.

I prefer international trailer though, it seems more fitting for this movie because it is more comedic than red band trailer that seems filled with plot points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sisters, Finding Dory, Angry Birds movie, and Office Christmas Party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a dedication </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gerard Butler will beat Natural Disaster after he beat terrorists from Fuckheadistan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mel Gibson

Olivia Munn

Nicolas Cage

Cara Delevigne

Emma Watson

Hugh Jackman

Tom Cruise

Chris Pratt

Chris Evans

Iko Uwais

Anna Kendrick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thanks, I messed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually the original title was 'Rock That Body', but yeah, I prefer the original title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is the moderator right now](https://media.giphy.com/media/fJPsqicaMZaZW/giphy.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/movies in a nutshell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was for Kinography </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not sure if she is going to be an Aussie or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Character Posters](http://imgur.com/a/xxPFV)

Info about the movie from [People.com](http://people.com/movies/scarlett-johansson-kate-mckinnon-rough-night-photo/?xid=socialflow_twitter_peoplemag)

 Scarlett Johansson leads the cast of Rough Night  an R-rated comedy about a bachelorette party gone way wrong  and PEOPLE has the exclusive first look at the film, due in theaters June 16.

 Joined by Zo Kravitz, Jillian Bell, Ilana Glazer and Kate McKinnon, Johansson confidently struts ahead of the group wearing a sash that marks her as the bride to be while the rest wear one that says friend of the bride. The ladies all seem excited for the epic night to come as McKinnon pushes a suitcase printed with international flags.

 The stars play five best friends from college who reunite in Miami 10 years later for a wild bachelorette weekend. But when the partying ends up taking a dark turn and they accidentally kill a male stripper, the longtime friends are forced to put their heads together and cover up the accident.

 Its hilarious, McKinnon tells PEOPLE of the script, penned by Broad Citys Paul W. Downs and Lucia Aniello. (Colton Haynes, Demi Moore and Ty Burrell round out the films cast.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zo Kravitz, Jillian Bell, Scarlett Johansson, Ilana Glazer and Kate McKinnon in 'Rough Night' (June 16, 2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be Fair Pitch Perfect was PG 13 and Mad Max Fury Road was R. So Obviouslt, Pitch Perfect 2 was making more revenue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with all of your points. I think some of the people just blindly want R-Rated superhero movie and I disagree with that.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I remembered that both of them made[ this song for The Big Bang Theory](https://youtu.be/ZUh_a2R6c9g).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney just beat themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was comedy-musical show by two women. They are similar to Flight of the Conchords

[Here is the trailer
](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RKkwnzVtCF0).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am good, I just watched a Garfunkel and Oates trying to be special on Netflix and it cheered me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your favorite dessert? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IMDb introduces M rating for Mindfuck Kinos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have some examples of these Indonesian YouTubers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is also alumni from SMU 8 Jakarta because some people in my social circle know him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Sunlight is an Indonesian Kino, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not sure, I think it is more like Wajah Femina or Gadis Sampul things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former Cleo Indonesia Bachelor

Actually just checked my path and three of my friends on Path are friends with him.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 10:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please Read These, thank you

[Part 1](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C6ExLgnUwAA-qq1.jpg)

[Part 2](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C6ExLcoUYAAO3KF.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nolan (1994) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * IGN: Irham
* Deposited: Spearow//Level 19
* Requested: Gothita </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FRESH VIDEO] Ariana Grande   John Legend - Beauty and the Beast (From "Beauty and the Beast") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A plea to EVERY Movie Theatres: PLEASE stop showing the Movie Trailers before EVERY movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else hate [THIS](https://youtu.be/F-eMt3SrfFU)?

I'm hoping this gets some traction now that pitchforks are out.

I have already purchased the tickets. We're already sitting in the seats waiting for the movie. Is it too much to ask to not tell me anything more about the Upcoming movies at this point? Just show me the movie. I want to see the movies blind.

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been to Gay Parade on overseas before just to see the crowd but I like that the people was so energetic and I saw a lot of rainbow in there.

Also, yeah I took some picture with the protesters who have memorable signs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are thinking that Reddit crowd is smarter than your average internet crowd, you are going to have a bad time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this from Sydney's Gay Parade? How was the crowd OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't explain it like you are five years old but I will explain it as simple as I can.

I do not think it was to follow the trend. I think it just to follow the momentum that Women's March already happened around the world. 

I think it is also raise awareness to some of the issues that they have in their demands

Plus, March 8 is also International Women's day so it think they can also use that momentum to conduct the protest.

[This is also a good opinion why the protest is happening.](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C6ExLcoUYAAO3KF.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wade and the other girls from the Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants plan a trip to Cabot Cove.

I thought we are going to get the cameo from the other girls including his wife.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wade and the other girls from the Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants plan a trip to Cabot Cove.

I think his wife is one of the other girls.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [These are their demands.](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C54IbAYU4AAE1TB.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah me too, I had family matters this morning. But I am glad that this protest was high energy and crowd size are big enough for me.

This means that some people care about these matters in Jakarta or maybe our country.

[This is one of my favorite signs.](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C6C3G85UwAQr4Xj.jpg)

[For more photos, you can check their twitter @womensmarchjkt](https://twitter.com/womensmarchjkt) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Keduanya keluar dari ruangan dan sempat diteriaki oleh pendukung Anies-Sandi.
 
 "OK Oce, OK Oce, OK Oce," teriak pendukung pasangan calon nomor urut tiga itu.

What????

I guess I would do the same thing if I were Ahok and Djarot
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FOTO: Aksi Womens March di Jakarta, 4 Maret 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far, Daredevil, Luke Cage, and Jessica Jones are pretty decent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 10:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * IGN: Irham

* Deposited: Drowzee, Lv. 8, Male

* Requesting: Physical Mewtwo (Jolly) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah there was a moment like that but it happened so fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lah bukannya Star Trek Beyond ada ya?

Tadi cek LSF, Beauty and the Beast udah lulus sensor kok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/GetFreeCash 

* [Angie Han - Slash Film](http://www.slashfilm.com/beauty-and-the-beast-review-reactions/)

* [Matt Mytum - Games Radar/Total Film
](http://www.gamesradar.com/beauty-and-the-beast-2017-review/?utm_content=buffer832a2 utm_medium=social utm_source=twitter.com utm_campaign=buffer_tftw)

* [Roth Cornet and Andy Signore - ScreenJunkies video review](https://youtu.be/CTuhOHoUehw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Good luck for those of you who are going to Jakarta's Women's March](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C5wGAGGVAAA-9vN.jpg), this morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###FILM CATEGORIES:

**Best Comic-to-Motion Picture Release**:

* Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice
* Captain America: Civil War
* Deadpool
* Doctor Strange
* Suicide Squad
* X-Men: Apocalypse

**Best Science Fiction Film Release:**

* Arrival
* Independence Day: Resurgence
* Midnight Special
* Passengers
* Rogue One: A Star Wars Story
* Star Trek Beyond
 
**Best Fantasy Film Release**:

* The BFG
* Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them
* Ghostbusters
* The Jungle Book
* Miss Peregrine's Home for Peculiar Children
* A Monster Calls
* Pete's Dragon

**Best Horror Film Release**:

* The Autopsy of Jane Doe
* The Conjuring 2
* Demon
* Don't Breathe
* Ouija: Origin of Evil
* Train to Busan
* The Witch

**Best Action / Adventure Film Release:**

* Allied
* Gold
* Hacksaw Ridge
* Hidden Figures
* The Legend of Tarzan
* The Magnificent Seven
* The Nice Guys

**Best Thriller Film Release**:

* 10 Cloverfield Lane
* The Accountant
* The Girl on the Train
* Jason Bourne
* Hell or High Water
* The Shallows
* Split

**Best Actor in a Film:**

* Chris Evans (Captain America: Civil War)
* Benedict Cumberbatch (Doctor Strange)
* Chris Pratt (Passengers)
* Ryan Reynolds (Deadpool)
* Mark Rylance (The BFG)
* Chris Pine (Star Trek Beyond)
* Matthew McConaughey (Gold)

**Best Actress in a Film**:

* Amy Adams (Arrival)
* Emily Blunt (The Girl on the Train)
* Taraji P. Henson (Hidden Figures)
* Jennifer Lawrence (Passengers)
* Felicity Jones (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)
* Narges Rashidi (Under the Shadow)
* Mary Elizabeth Winstead (10 Cloverfield Lane)

**Best Supporting Actor in a Film**:

* Chadwick  Boseman (Captain America: Civil War)
* Dan Fogler (Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them)
* John Goodman (10  Cloverfield Lane)
* Diego Luna (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)
* Zachary Quinto (Star Trek Beyond)
* Christopher Walken (The Jungle Book)

**Best Supporting Actress in a Film**:

* Scarlett Johansson (Captain America: Civil War)
* Tilda Swinton (Doctor Strange)
* Margot Robbie (Suicide Squad)
* Kate McKinnon (Ghostbusters)
* Betty Buckley (Split)
* Bryce Dallas Howard (Gold)

**Best Performance by a Younger Actor**:

* Ruby Barnhill (The BFG)
* Julian Dennison (Hunt for the Wilderpeople)
* Tom Holland (Captain America: Civil War)
* Lewis MacDougall (A Monster Calls)
* Neel Sethi (The Jungle Book)
* Anya Taylor-Joy (The Witch)

**Best Film Direction:**

* Scott Derrickson (Doctor Strange)
* Gareth Edwards (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)
* Jon Favreau (The Jungle Book)
* Anthony Russo, Joe Russo (Captain America: Civil War)
* Bryan Singer (X-Men: Apocalypse)
* Steven Spielberg (The BFG)
* Denis Villeneuve (Arrival)

**Best Film Screenplay:**

* Melissa Mathison (The BFG)
* Eric Heisserer (Arrival)
* Rhett Reese, Paul Wernick (Deadpool)
* Jon Spaihts, Scott Derrickson, C. Robert Cargill (Doctor Strange)
* Taylor Sheridan (Hell or High Water)
* Chris Weitz, Tony Gilroy (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)

**Best Film Editing:**

* Jeffrey Ford, Matthew Schmidt (Captain America: Civil War)
* John Gilroy, Colin Goudie, Jabez Olssen (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)
* Stefan Grube (10 Cloverfield Lane)
* Michael Kahn (The BFG)
* Mark Livolsi (The Jungle Book)
* Joe Walker (Arrival)

**Best Film Production Design:**

* Rick Carter, Robert Stromberg (The BFG)
* Doug Chiang, Neil Lamont (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)
* Stuart Craig (Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them)
* Guy Hendrix Dyas (Passengers)
* Owen Paterson (Captain America: Civil War)
* Charles Wood (Doctor Strange)

**Best Film Music:**

* Michael Giacchino (Doctor Strange)
* Michael Giacchino (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)
* James Newton Howard (Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them)
* Justin Hurwitz (La La Land)
* Thomas Newman (Passengers)
* John Willians (The BFG)

**Best Film Costume Designer**:

* Colleen Atwood (Alice Through the Looking Glass)
* Colleen Atwood (Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them)
* Alexandra Byrne (Doctor Strange)
* David Crossman, Glyn Dilloin (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)
* Sang-gyeong Jo (The Handmaiden)
* Joanna Johnston (The BFG)

**Best Film Make-Up**:

* Jeremy Whitewood (Doctor Strange)
* Nicky Knowles (Fanatastic Beasts and Where to Find Them)
* Amy Byrne (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)
* Monica Huppert, Joel Harlow (Star Trek Beyond)
* Allan Apone, Jo-Ann MacNeil, Marta Roggero (Suicide Squad)
* Charles Carter, Rita Ciccozzi, Rosalina Da Silva (X-Men: Apocalypse)

**Best Film Special / Visual Effects**:

* Louis Morin, Ryal Cosgrove (Arrival)
* Joe Letteri, Joel Whist (The BFG)
* Stephane Ceretti, Richard  Bluff, Vincent Cirelli, Paul Corbould (Doctor Strange)
* Tim Burke, Christian Manz, David Watkins (Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find Them)
* Robert Legato, Adam Valdez, Andrew R. Jones, Dan Lemmon (The Jungle Book)
* John Knoll, Mohen Leo, Hal Hickel, Neil Corbould (Rogue One: A Star Wars Story)

**Best Independent Film Release**:

* Eye in the Sky
* Hunt for the Wilderpeople
* La La Land
* Lion
* The Ones Below
* Remember

**Best  International Film Release**:

* Elle
* The Handmaiden
* In Order of Disappearance
* The Mermaid
* Shin Godzilla
* Under the Shadow

**Best Animated Film Release**:

* Finding Dory
* Kingsglaive: Final Fantasy XV
* Moana
* Sing
* Trolls
* Zootopia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Rogue One,' 'Walking Dead' Lead Saturn Awards Nominations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Other Fast   Furious 8 Teaser Poster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jaden Smith   Cara Delevingne To Star In Life In A Year Movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got this rumor from my highschool teacher couple years ago. One of the alumni told my teacher that there was a weird recruitment process. There was this pengajian group but it kinda close knitted. 

Every time you attend that pengajian, they asked you a sum of money as routine payment. After the pengajian, there was someone who indoctrinate you about various subject, especially about anti-government movement. My teacher said the alumni's became more anti social after he attended those pengajian. My teacher also mentioned that this pengajian is closely related to PK or DI/TII.

What I just told you is not entirely true, but I am pretty sure there are people who heard these stories in this way or another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 11:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think PKS is like a cult though, especially their recruitment process in some universities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard this the first time from Sing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 05:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wait for Christmas this year. For now, I will play Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild on Wii U.

I think there is not much difference between Switch and Wii U Version.

Besides, I hope they released some bundle versions in near future like Wii U </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw [Christopher Bradley's name](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chris_Bradley) on the document and I think one of the kids got his power </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the best movies in X-Men franchise and the best Wolverine movie in my opinion. 

I like that this movie really explored Wolverine on a personal level and his Relationships between Charles Xavier and Laura. Violence level are high in this one because you'll see a lot of head stabbing. I see this movie is kinda standalone movie on its own but at the same time it respects its source materials such as Old Man Logan or some X-23 arcs.

I think the only criticism I have is that there are some parts that little bit dragging in the middle and I wished it could be faster on those parts. Other than that this movie was really good and you'll have a good time.

I gave it 8 out of 10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope they will hire someone who is competent in script-writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That Lorde new song, Green Light was so good.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dMK_npDG12Q) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 02:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are more reviews

[Collider John Campea's Video Review](https://youtu.be/e4LHpX91p9I)

[Chris Nashwaty - Entertainment Weekly Review](http://ew.com/movies/2017/03/02/kong-skull-island-ew-review/)

/u/mi-16evil  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The market opportunities are too substantial to ignore

I agree that the producers cannot ignore these opportunities but at the same time they just cannot rely only on luck to find a perfect formula. They just have to make it work by themselves like make a strong script and marketing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghostbusters (2016). I enjoyed Kate McKinnon and Chris Hemsworth in that movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk about representation on Reddit is rarely end well. I've seen it many times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sand Castle | Official Trailer [HD] | Netflix | Nicholas Hoult and Henry Cavill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was strange to see Kristen Bell in the shootout with Michael Pena and Dax Shepard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trailer is just an okay for me. Anyway, I think Javier Bardem is the first reason why I am interested in this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basura is kinda new though, I heard about it for the  first time about couple months ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basura bukannya mall di Jakarta Timur ya? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In short, No.

I do not think you need to see other X-men movies because the story was self-contained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 11:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some changes about where this March is going to happen.

 Womens March Jakarta

 Saturday, March 4, 2017

 **Starting at Sarinah at 9 am, followed by a march to the National Palace where speeches and performances will take place starting at 10 am**


[The details about this event](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C5wGAGGVAAA-9vN.jpg)

[These are their demands.](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C54IbAYU4AAE1TB.jpg)

[Here is the previous thread about this announcement](https://np.reddit.com/r/indonesia/comments/5vwrah/jakartas_womens_march_march_4_2017_bundaran_hi/).

If you want to join this Women's March please just come to Sarinah on March 4, 2017 at 9:00 AM Western Indonesian Tim. If Possible, please wear something Purple or Pink. 

For your information, all gender, culture, religion and race is welcome to join. So please come if you have a chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you support equality and justice for all, hit the streets this Saturday for Womens March Jakarta (March 4, 2017) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 11:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, I gave Godzilla 7 out of 10 if you are into spectacle of Kaiju Movie. Can I expect the same with this movie?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you rate this movie on a scale 1 to 10? OP gave 7 out of 10.

What are your thoughts about the movie? 

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the animations and the simplicity in this video but at the same time I was expecting more glamorous video though. 



All in all, This video is still one of my favorite videos from him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time will tell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicholas Hoult Joins Emma Stone And Rachel Weisz In The Favourite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you mean about that censorship, hmm...

I am not sure about that. If there was that kind of censorship, I do not think LSF did that blatantly. I need to watch the movie for second time.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not think it was censored because I checked LSF website and they have the same run time at Logan page at Berlin Film Festival where this movie was premiered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enough to fill a bottled water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it was one of the best westerns I've ever seen.

It is better than The Good, The Bad and The Ugly and Shane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Captain America: Civil War
2. The Dark Knight
3. Captain America: The Winter Soldier
4. The Avengers
5. Guardians of the Galaxy
1. Spiderman 2
1. Iron Man
1. X-men First Class
1. Scott Pilgrim vs The World
1. Kick-ass


Honorable mentions:

* Iron Man 3
* Superman II
* Superman Return
* X2
* Logan
* The Dark Knight Rises </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 13:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None, I watched it at Ayy Lmao Drafthaus. 

They also served latest craft beer and they checked your ID before you enter the theater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the movie and there was not any post/mid credit scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
