<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 10:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do agree. Between worlds is just a better game in every sense, and more enjoyable to new players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you say that Jon was taking PEDs, then everyone he fought against was also taking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clear penalty and Mandzukic in... uefalona! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually it is better to play between worlds first, because it is an amazing game, and you dont want to go through it already burning out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Franco is smiling at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, he already beat him, there are no what ifs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with DC. He needs JJ more than JJ needs him. Why? Because JJ beat him clearly (49-46) when they fought. There's nothing to win for JJ in a rematch, while there's a lot to win for DC.

DC knows that if he doesn't beat JJ before he retires, there will be an * in this career. Especially if JJ comes back, gets the belt, and continues undefeated. This won't be like "Conor vs Khabib" in terms of "is Conor the best 55 or not?" because DC and JJ already fought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Spain, I couldnt find much.

The Hadrian wall, which more or less separates England and Scotland, was built by a "spanish" roman emperor. Hadrian was born in Spain.

There are strong celtic connections between Scotland and north west of Spain.

The Panama scottish disaster was partly also caused by Spain, which was the country mostly disputing those lands.

The house of Fitzjames, which is from scottish origin, now based in Spain: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/House_of_FitzJames </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Certainly, I think very few British people really subscribe to the European project of the EU.

Most countries in Europe subscribe it just because it is convenient for them.

If you think a random bloke in Spain and another one in Denmark both want a "federal Europe" "we are brothers", then you are very wrong.

People in the UK thinks that people in the EU believes in the "project" same way americans believe in USA. The EU is just a convenient platform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's within living memory Franco ruled in Spain

You know Spain was a republic before Franco? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Just that I think even Europhiles are more likely to feel British (or English, Scottish, Welsh, N.Irish) first.

Do you think that more than 50% of germans would feel more european than german? or anywhere else in Europe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that color. Pacifica's are amazing guitars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah but he was winning, and mostly everyone agreed the fight was going to be a TKO or a UD for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life skills, such as persistence, conscientiousness and control, are as critical to resources and wellbeing in after life as they are when people are most younger, according to new investigate led by UCL. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/04/04/1614912114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at the University of Zurich have identified the brain mechanism that governs decisions between honesty and self-interest. Using non-invasive brain stimulation, they could even increase honest behavior. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/04/06/1615504114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ability to distinguish objects in peripheral vision varies significantly between individuals, finds new research from UCL. The research shows that on average we are worse at spotting objects in crowded environments when they are above or below eye level. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "no takebacks, no replays, no changes" mentality of say...soccer 

in soccer the main ref can ask to any of the other 3 refs. Many times one of the other refs has changed a call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he won though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers manage to form RNA nucleobases in a MillerUrey reducing atmosphere containing NH3 + CO, strongly supporting the possibility of the emergence of biologically relevant molecules in a reducing atmosphere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 11:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isnt Eddie Gordon in TUF25? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, now that he is retired we cannot do a "with Henri" Rumble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They claimed to be the party of the NHS. They can say anything you want to hear. Another very different thing is what they will actually implement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the biggest problems in football nowadays are fights between parents during kids games, like the one that happen this weekend in Spain. Is this that common anywhere else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO 3 people commenting a fight are too many. They know this, and they try a lot to not step into one another, which means there are a lot of blank moments. It is way easier to narrate when there's only 2 people, which is the perfect formula.

Before or after the fight 3 are fine, but while it happens, 2 is the perfect number. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how did you get the background like that because it is amazing. I guess you were super far away and used a big zoom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people posts here a lot of pictures, most of them are just your standard picture that anyone can take with a phone.

But your picture is really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the cover of the Science magazine of this week, and the only picture that appears in the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the cover of the Science magazine of this week, and the only picture that appears in the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japanese culture has always been amazing when mixing contemporary (or urban) stuff with some sort of fantasy. The idea of a random bloke living with his parents, watching anime in his bedroom and suddenly being transformed into some sort of hero is very common. Persona 5 is nothing new. FF8 especially was pure urban, to the point that you start in some sort of college. Or even before Chrono Trigger was set-up in some sort of urban place. These 2 games were huge and instant hits.

Japenese artists are very good doing this because it is was the readers want to see. They want to imagine themselves in that scenario. They want to think they can train boxing and become Hajime no Ippo, or get the Death Note, or go to Gantz, or time travel like in Erased, or be a super chef like in Food wars, or just make 100 push up a day and be One Punch Man.

In western culture it is rare, but not that strange. Harry Potter, for example, follows the same idea. Or even Spiderman. But the reality is that in western culture medieval fantasy stuff or sci fi are way more popular.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is that when using my laptop (Linux - Transmission - openvpn) it fails as explained in my house, but exactly the same setup without touching anything works perfectly well in a friends house.

So I dont think the problem is related to any of my software or configuration. It has to be the router somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, then it has to be a problem with my router or something. crap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The link goes directly to the paper. The title I used is from here: http://www.popsci.com/these-monkeys-avoid-sick-friends-by-sniffing-their-poo?dom=rss-default src=syn

Which is easier to read, and I think free of access </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To avoid spreading parasites through the group, mandrill monkeys avoid grooming someonean otherwise common social activityif their poop smells off. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you use torrent ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to know if someone with BT is having similar problems </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  HIV risk reduction is the biggest benefit for sure.

it is not really a benefit. If you are circumcised and you have unprottected sex because you think your risk is low, then you are as dumb as people who thinks that aids and hiv are unrelated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone using PIA VPN and BT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wants to go to Miami. Vancouver is like the opposite. Plus the most expensive city in the world to live.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Bara wins everything, we win the league  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, they do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> potentially super easy. you dont need to recalibrate the balance or anything, just remove 1.2 to whatever shows the display, except if it is 0, in which case just show 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is small because he is super thing. In terms of height and reach he is even bigger than Conor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  bandwagon.

I guess you don't watch many Real Madrid games. Don't let the final score fool you.

let's ignore the game against Leganes because their stars were not playing. Against Alaves they won 3-0, but they played a horrible game. They scored in the 30min mark without really deserving it, then they were dominated by Alaves for like 50 minutes, and Alaves almost scored 2 goals. Madrid was playing horribly bad, to the point that their fans were booing. Then at the very end they just scored 2 goals very fast.

Real Madrid really plays to nothing. It is impossible to define their style. Without their big stars they would drop a lot of points.

And by the way, before anyway saying I am a blind FCB fan, I think the same about Luis Enrique. We play to nothing. Suarez and Messi just saved so many games of nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zidane: "Next season? I am not preparing anything, I am not sure about continuing" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 11:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is better to make a direct translation, than an "interpretation". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was clear in my original comment that I was saying that even Microsoft Windows is fragmented, because for X or Y reasons some people cannot update. Where I work there's people with XP, 7 and 10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only think I said is that even the Microsoft Windows market is fragmented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am spanish btw
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not illegal. I work for a public institution with thousand of people, and my key is validated against Microsoft server every few days. Sometimes after a new installation if you forget to run the validation script, after a few days you get the "you are using illegal stuff".

The license the place I work in only works for W7. If I try to update it to W10, it says my license only covers W7. People with pirated W7 could update to W10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Without fragmentation we'd all be stuck on Windows XP because it worked and Microsoft would've had no incentive to improve upon what they had.

Not really, because what Microsoft wants to do is to sell you a new OS every few years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James after being subtituted: "The pu### of his mum, he never puts me for a whole game" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 12:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  fragmentation argument has always been overblown by people who participate in OS Wars

Especially because it also occurs in Windows, for example, when I am using W7 and I cannot update to 10 (some sort of enterprise license thing, I don't really care). Or now with Vulcan, DirectX (and its many versions), OpenGL,...

It also occurs with browsers, which is the piece of software most used nowadays: Firefox, Chrome, Safari, IE,...

Fragmentation is good. The idea of "converge" is bollocks. The reason why Linux market share is under 1% is not because "people is confused between gnome, KDE and the several distros". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature21686.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monounsaturated fats, like olive oil, help roundworms live longer. Because many species share similar patterns of fat metabolism, its possible that the findings could extend to other animals, including humans, the researchers believe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you divide 550k by 145 it gives 4k. which means, in order to get their money back they only would need 4k per flat (plus costs)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey I also have a 2i2, I have a few questions. First the sound out of the 2i2 sounds very flat, the integrated card sounds much better.

Second, did you install Jack? or how did you configure it? I want to play the guitar through it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prenatal loss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they say they will make 145 flats. each one will go for at least 200k (new flats in B listed building, and Dennistoun is going up). That is around 29m. so like 60 times more than initial cost.

yes I know theres the cost of materials, builders,.... but in order to make profit, after all cost, they only would need an extra 4k per flat. and they will get way more than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dennistoun school building sold to 'fraudster' property tycoon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Edgar beats Holloway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. People forgot very fast that Aldo is the best  FW ever. Remember he just won easy against a monster like Frankie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprising how many underrates Aldo, who is the best FW ever. I think this one will be easy for Aldo. Max doesn't have anything for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dock, connections, joy sticks, smaller screen... Every bit you cut down by cents is a good cut  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handheld is the big market for Nintendo. I doubt they will go full home only, while I can see them going only handheld. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about that. The UK has been invaded (I mean mass invasion) as many times as most places in the EU.

If you mean it like "if we were connected, the Nazis would have invaded the UK", those kind of invasion don't have any long term effect. The Nazi invasion in France, for example, didnt have any long time effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how different the UK would be if it was still connected to mainland Europe by some bit of land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope Nintendo releases soon a Switch without dock, just handheld. Maybe a smaler screen (3DS XL size), and fixed game pad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prenatal loss of father during World War One is predictive of a reduced lifespan in adulthood. Researchers. These results support the notion that intrauterine exposure to a major psychological maternal stress can affect human longevity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suarez is actually kind of slow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The headline I used is the first paragraph here: https://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2017-04/uos-fca040317.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research suggests that over the next 100 to 200 years CO2 concentrations in the Earth's atmosphere will head towards values not seen since the Triassic period, 200 million years ago. Furthermore, by the 23rd century, the climate could reach a warmth not seen in 420 million years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neymar is the fastest Barcelona player, with 34.83kmh, while Rakitic is the slowerst one with 30.66khm. Messi is in the bottom pack with 32.27khm (infography) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evidence of ancient 'geological Brexit' revealed. Researchers have worked out how a thin strip of land that once connected ancient Britain to Europe was destroyed. They believe a large lake overflowed 450k years ago, damaging the land link, then a later flood fully opened the Dover Strait. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like doing this kind of podcasts / videos, I suggest you ignore most of the feedback and / or comments, and just keep going, refining your formula.

I also think you need to find your target audience, which is not this subreddit. Think people here loves Limmy, and you are like opposite. I am not saying this in a bad way.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philippines was the last spanish colony. Is this related to Gibraltar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eldense's coach (this weekend they lost 12-0 against Bara "B") recognises the game was rigged. There might be many other rigged games involving them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should a Focusrite Scarlett 2i2 produce better output than my integrated sound card? (it isn't at the moment) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a computer with an integrated sound card and a Focusrite Scarlett 2i2.

Yesterday I was doing some basic testing, connecting my speakers to either the desktop output or the Focusrite headphones output. In both cases using a mini jack, which was going directly to my desktop, or through a converter to the focusrite.

I was getting stereo sound in the focusrite, but the sound quality from my desktop was much higher. The focusrite sounded flat, almost no bass, very crappy, while the desktop output sounded OK.

I wonder what I am doing wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you didn't even bother clicking the link, because you'd see that the title here is the same title as used in the paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you click the link, you will see that the title is the title of the paper, and what I pasted here is a part of the abstract.

If you have any problem with that, you should contact PNAS' editorial board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you see all the pictures she took from Melania, I think a lot of them are good, such as:

http://www.reginemahaux.com/images.php?category=4 id=6

http://www.reginemahaux.com/images.php?category=4 id=5

http://www.reginemahaux.com/images.php?category=4 id=2

This picture from Donald is amazing:

http://www.reginemahaux.com/images.php?category=4 id=3

I think people is critisizing this just because it is related to Trump. You don't get this row of AAA stars by doing crappy pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that picture too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what the criticism would be if this was unrelated to Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. He was not able to make weight. Also, he is a much better fighter at LHW than under LHW. His record under LHW was 11-4, losing against some no names. His record as LHW is 12-1, only losing against DC.

A more interesting question would be if he could be a champ at MW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like 52 hours. I didn't rush, and I tried to capture as many pokemon as possible through my way (I think I got like 50% of the pokedex) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to make it clear, I am completely unrelated to this research, so I cannot answer your questions. For some reasons, also, I cannot read the full paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We examine the short-term effects of the largest-scale policy shift, Californias Assembly Bill 60 (AB60), under which more than 600,000 licenses were issued in the first year of implementation in 2015 alone. We find that, contrary to concerns voiced by opponents of the law, AB60 has had no discernible short-term effect on the number of accidents. The law primarily allowed existing unlicensed drivers to legalize their driving. We also find that, although AB60 had no effect on the rate of fatal accidents, it did decrease the rate of hit and run accidents, suggesting that the policy reduced fears of deportation and vehicle impoundment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Providing drivers licenses to unauthorized immigrants in California improves traffic safety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police arrests Eldense's coach (who lost this weekend against Bara "B" 12-0) accused of rigging the game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gibraltar will remain part of the UK, I am sure 100%. An agreement between the UK and Spain is more complicated. The UK basically wants Spain to bend over. In a agreement both sides must win something.

It is important to remember that it is the UK who is starting all this with Brexit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said the opposite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you understand how borders work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every member will be able to veto the agreement between the UK and the EU. It needs to be approved by all of them.

Some of the things that you say, such as energy, renewables, housing and labour, are unrelated to the EU now that the UK has left it. What's the point on having an agreement about those points with the EU if you are leaving it? It defeats the point of Brexit. The UK will only care about getting trade, and as long as you comply with the EU trading rules, everything else is fine.

The only important thing for Gibraltar in regards to the EU is the border and freedom of movement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a good fight for RDA. He will fight against one of the smallest WW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ...implying that Gibraltar is not sovereign.

Gibraltar land, water and air borders are surrounded by Spain.

When the UK was part of the EU, the EU forced Spain to open the border, and so they did. Now Gibraltar is not part of the EU (or it won't in 2 years). The EU cannot say how the Gibraltar - Spain border will be. This is something that only Spain, the UK and Gibraltar can decide.

Imagine that the UK remained in the EU, but that Ireland left, and the EU contacts the UK "We have decided that your border with Ireland will be open, so open it now". Do you think that the UK will take that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the UK was part of the EU, and Ireland was leaving the EU, any decision about the border would run through the UK. Imagine that the EU arrived with an agreement with Ireland saying that the border would be open, without consulting the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People are over reacting but Spain are getting close to the line.

how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The final term in the EU's negotiating position is basically Spain asserting a limited form of sovereignty over Gibraltar.

False. The only thing said is that Spain will be allowed to veto any agreement the EU might do with Gibraltar. Meaning the UK and Gibraltar will need to deal directly with Spain.

The only thing said so far is that the UK won't be able to circumvent Spain when negotiating Gibraltar with the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lets bang bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This weekend Bara B won 12 - 0 against Eldense. Now a player from Eldense accuses some of his teammates for fixing the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. So many times we hear "he looks so good at a higher division", and then the figher saying "I have never felt this good before".

And then while in LW Cowboy is a title contender, with only loses against champs or Nate Diaz (who won against the current champ), in WW he lost against Masvidal, who is a top5 yo 10 at most in WW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the point of MMA though. There are more impactful martial arts than boxing, like wrestling or BJJ or muay thai.

In a fight to death get the best boxer and the best MMA fighter, and you know the MMA fighter wins.

Conor vs Floyd, you know if it was MMA Conor would win in 10 seconds. In boxing, floyd will win, but will be more competitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say that in general our foreign ministers are quite good (probably the best minister we usually have). As you said, this one is a legit person. I also remember "Moratinos" a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we have the PP, which is like the Tories, but more corrupted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It might help though if Spain employed more than a single customs officer to do the checks though ;)

Why should we?

Borders are always slow. In Edinburgh airport I usually wait from 30 minutes to 1 hour, depending on how busy the border is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are over hyping our (spanish) diplomats. The only thing they care about is expensive food, alcohol, whores, and envelopes with money.

This all started with the comment from Tusk, saying that Spain will be able to veto any agreement with Gibraltar, which is just a way of saying that the UK must reach an agreement directly with Spain. Whatever agreement the UK reaches with the EU, it probably won't work with Gibraltar, unless the UK wants to close Gibraltar to the rest of the EU and sink millions every year just to keep it alive. The EU cannot force any other EU member to open its borders with a non EU country. It is as simple as that. When the UK was part of the EU, the EU forced Spain to open the order, and we did it.

This WAS NEVER ABOUT "as part of Brexit, Spain will take control of Gibraltar". British politicians need to be more pragmatic, more serious, more "realpolitik". Every stupid discrepancy cannot make headlines in the newspaper 2 days in a row, with almost war declarations. The UK always said "no agreement is better than a bad agreement", but the EU cannot also walk away from the agreement whenever they want.

That said, I hope Gibraltar remains part of the UK (because that is what Gibraltar wants), and I hope the UK and Spain reach an agreement regarding the border. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am spanish, btw, and I am in favour of Gibraltar being part of the UK, if that's what the Gibraltar wants.

I am also in favour of an open border between Gibraltar and Spain.

The only thing I don't like about Gibraltar is about it being a tax haven. So if I were the spanish person negotiating with the UK, I would ask them as part of the open border agreement, to tax Gibraltar the same way it taxes the rest of the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK will need to reach an agreement with Spain about the border, it is as simple as that. Tusk said that the UK-EU negotiations for Gibraltar cannot circumvent Spain. I think that's pretty obvious. The EU cannot force Spain to open the border with a non EU country. When the UK was part of the EU, Spain was forced to open the border against its will, and Spain did open it. Now that the UK is out, there's nothing the EU can force Spain to do in this matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and death penalty

http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/politics/brexit-poll-leave-voters-death-penalty-yougov-results-light-bulbs-a7656791.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was like 70 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spain won't get "arsy".

People here are ignoring the original comment from Dusk, and just going into war scenarios.

The fact is that, whatever deal the UK does with the EU it won't involve freedom of movement, and as you said, freedom of movement is needed between Gibraltar and Spain, and that's why Tusk said that Spain will be able to veto it. This freedom of movement is very likely to be limited to Spain, not to the whole EU, because otherwise Gibraltar would be a buffer area for the UK in the EU. Same way, Spanish freedom of movement will be limited to Gibraltar, and not the whole UK.

You cannot force a EU country to have freedom of movement with a non-eu country just because "I want it". Spain and the UK will need to reach an agreement about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is part of the negotiation.

Gibraltar and the UK will need different agreements. Gibraltar NEEDS freedom of movement. That's why Spain has the right to veto it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're lying. Most comments there say something on the lines: "there won't be a war, just isolate them and don't let them use anything from Spain".

Also, there's nothing there about any Spanish minister saying he is going to plant a flag.

Source: I'm Spanish and can read Spanish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany is supporting another EU member. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK is using a few million EU citizens as bargaining chip. Isn't that despicable ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spanish here, Spain won't veto, why:

* I know it might surprise to some here, but Spain has bigger problems than Scotland joining the EU.

* In terms of our nationalist movements (I am catalan myself), the fact that the UK gave Scotland Indyref1 is way worse than Scotland joining the EU, because the UK legitimised independent movements.

* As every government in Europe except the UK, our government is fragmentated. Our government won't be able to veto it directly, it would go through our parliment, and get the approval of 3-4 parties. It is not going to happen. it is just unnecesary wear and tear for something very unrelated to us.

* Spain will do whatever EU tells us to do. We will fake grunt and hope to get something in exchange.

* Finally, the idea of blocking Scotland from the EU "just because" doesnt make any democratic sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what i have now. Global  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot unlock my Xiaomi . Followed many guides. Classic 50% stuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barcelona B just won 12-0 against Eldense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game was in the 2B category, which is the third one after 1 and 2a. It's the biggest win in this category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jinxed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok then they can stay inside the UK but outside the EU  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 11:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fortunately there is lineageos

if you can unlock your phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then they can stay in the UK and outside the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would need a 66% of the mps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Referendum. If they want to leave Spain and join Morocco so let it be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spanish here. Don't give a shit about Gibraltar.

Best thing for Gibraltar would be to be an independent state and join the EU, like Andorra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with that? I have only played Y and Moon, but both games are amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And lol at ALBW still at #1.

I do agree with that. I think it is the best 3DS game. Not only that, I think it is one of the best games of "this generation", and by "this generation" I meant PS4, XBone, 3DS and PS Vita. ALBW is in my top 5. The only game I have played in ages that when I finished I was like "fuck, I want more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 12:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah I like it, but I am just a fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  March Madness. 

I don't even know what is that. Sounds like some sort of WWE event.

Who the fuck cares, though?

IMO MMA fans are mostly a divergent group to most "sport fans". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a simple question. which % of Glasgow population do you think these people represent?

Don't be fooled by your echochamber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a studio. I don't have gas, so everything is electric. I have one of those meters I need to top-up. I spend around 40-50 pounds a month. During the cold months I have an electric heater full blast for 5-6 hours every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 11:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a guy, 1.70, sort of thin. I have been assaulted 3-4 times during my life. I don't even remember. Maybe I have been unlucky.

It is true I have never been sexually assaulted, but the second time it happened I was scared about leaving my house alone for like 2 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey we can swap our residence permit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its been like 3 weeks, 1 fight, and 3 weeks. what the hell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is what you get with 3 weeks without UFC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you think if Andreas Agnelli asks a journalist to ask to Allegri about a sub who is not playing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  as much as this sub loves Cody now, he's a meathead.

This sub loves Cody because he is the champ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to push an agenda against his own coach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing is having a "club newspaper", that's ok. The other one is using it to push the coaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The president asked a journalist to ask Ancelotti about Bale. Is that really a "who gives a fuck?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you can see some of the messages between Florentino and Alejandro de Pedro: http://www.eldiario.es/politica/conseguidor-Punica-falso-diario-digital-servicio-Florentino-Perez-Real-Madrid_0_627138361.html#mensajes

That newspaper "Diario Bernabeu" was paid by Real Madrid.

Some of the stuff, for example, Florentino asked to remove that "all Europe was following Isco". Or he asked to question why Bale did not play with Ancelotti. He also pushed to talk about referees, and show when Busquets stepped over Pepe's head. or he complained that they were talking too much about Di Maria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  men face pressure to be powerful and successful

This is a false generalisation. I never felt pressure to be powerful and succesful. That's really a thing in a western society.

The reality is that noone expected anything from me. I was never athletic, had good looks, or have good grades. A school counselor when I was 14 (she was meeting with everyone), advised me to just have a technical job (such as being a plumber) as my career option. I applied for some stuff but was always rejected.

Most of my friends are or were in a similar situation. Maybe we are just a bunch of losers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am jealous. I would like to had beene coding games when I was 13.

That is why instead of saying "hey look the cool thing I did when I was 13" he is like "hey look the crappy thing I did when I was 13", knowing that 99% of people here didnt code anything at that age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking the same until I arrived to the section where he speaks about his last game.

First you watch the trailer, which is amazing. Really good stuff. You know that in order to do a game like that he is good coding, designing,... way above the average. Many of us have dreamed about doing games, and this guy just did an amazing indie one. Then he writes:

"Despite all I had learned up to this point, this game featured some of my biggest blunders."

This is an extreme "humblebrag". Especially because he says "some of my biggest blunders". "I just did this amazing indie game which many reviewers loved, but hey guys, it contains some of my biggest blunders humblebrag".

Then I re-read the article, and I realised everything is pure humblebrag. When he described his first game, when he was just 12... that game is brutal for someone who is 12. When I was 12 I had no idea how to code, and this guy was already doing games! he was probably a better coder than many people nowadays, but hey "his code was patently atrocious".

Then when he was 15 he did a freaking game engine, only being 15!, but hey, his code contained "monstrosities".

TLDR I am sure this guy is super proud of the things he did and the code he wrote. I know that if when I was 15 I coded a engine using directx I would be super proud, but hey, it is better to humblebrag, get some click, and say it was "atrocious" "I should delete it from my hard disk". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not statistically, but they can be considered a minority in terms of power and privilege.

I am not a woman, so I cannot speak for them, but being a guy sucks. Or maybe I am a total loser. Maybe both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can natively install AAA games via Steam. My hardware is recognized."

Steam and AAA, not really. Game library for Linux is minimal. If you want to play games you need windows. Yeah you can play Valve games and some other stuff, but the number of AAA games is really really small. Linux is not really taking off as a gaming platform. Valve is pushing for it, but it is not really working.

About the hardware, it really depends on what you have. if your hardware is well established and like 1 year old at least, then no problems. If you have an AMD card you may need to sweat blood to get it working. Some peripherical stuff might be a total nightmare, like a printer or a scanner. if you have an Intel i5 4440 with integrated card, then it will be perfect out of the box, same for nvidia.

And by the way, Linux has been my main OS for the last 15 years. But even today when installing new stuff in new computers (especially in laptops, it might be impossible) it can get very tricky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a extreme case of "humblebrag".

All the games look very good considering when he did the first one he was like 12 or 13, and the last game shown is really really good. As an indie game it looks amazing, and I could see a lot of people paying for it.

The code is also "decent". He is learning new technologies and using new styles. By no means I would say it is "bad code" or "horror code". I could read through it and understand it.

Just by watching the last video you know he is an excellent programmer and game designer but it is better to say "what an horror I did", bait for some clicks, and humblebrag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ph.D. students read at 700-800wpm

I have a phd myself, and I doubt about any relation with having a phd and reading faster (I am myself probably a slow reader btw). Reading papers is a very slow process. It is very different to reading a novel. Most papers are written in a very obfuscated way. I spend 2 or 3 hours (at least) every day of my life just reading papers. Today for example, I was reading the Nature feed, and that's how I shared this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the article and the sources it uses.

EDIT: The above comment was just posted 2 minutes after I shared the link. Impossible to read the article that fast, and check the sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Babies who share their homes with a dog are much less likely to grow up into adults with allergies than those who don't. It also lessens their likelihood of developing everything from obesity to asthma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some more info if you cannot access the journal: https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2017/mar/29/western-consumers-fuelling-tens-of-thousands-of-air-pollution-related-deaths </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transboundary health impacts of transported global air pollution and international trade: consumption in western Europe and the USA is linked to more than 108,600 premature deaths in China. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Brexit is changing the lives of eight researchers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My problem with MM is the "no idea what should I do now" which happened constantly, to the point of being annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no idea about that glitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played MM 3D difficult, and the game was very difficult.

I remember playing MM as a kid, and it was impossible. I don't know anyone who finished it on the 64. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think german people does something like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It cannot be right that someone signing a work contract in the UK on Tuesday has more rights than someone signing a contract on Thursday.

I wonder if they will say It cannot be right that someone signing a work contract in the UK on the 29th M 2019 has more rights than someone signing a contract on 31st M 2019.

I am against Brexit, but that logic of "2 days of difference" makes no sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Youtube's audio quality good enough good enough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering. I mostly listen music at work, and I mostly use youtube to do so. The other day I was considering buying new headphones, at the moment I am using cheap sennheiser hd202, but then I thought, is it worth it if I am going to mostly use Youtube?

Google says that: "The audio you hear during a YouTube video will usually be 126 kbps AAC in an MP4 container or anywhere from 50-165 kbps Opus in a WebM container. Changing video resolution (360p, 720p, etc) in the video settings will probably not impact the audio stream, but it is likely that your connection performance will. "

Which is kind of low, considering that before it seems they used 192. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hendricks also tapped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I am the only one who did not enjoy KH1 back in the day. Maybe because I expected a completely different game. I was told it was a Disney meets Final Fantasy with touches of RPG.

In reality the Final Fantasy component is near 0. The RPG is non existant. The game is more like a arcade - platform where you just moved around known Disney environments.

I never understood why it was so loved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milk and honey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Will the US try to undermine Eu with transatlantic deal with UK.

Unlikely when the EU is worth 14 trillions, while the UK is worth 2.6 trillions. EU represents roughly a 85%. EU shrinking is bad for USA.

This is like the EU trying to undermine the UK by offering a better deal to Scotland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did Nate say to him once they hugged? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin also wanted Brexit and Trump.

Putin loves anything that would create instability, because that is good for Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I have been through your link and it is quite interesting.

I wonder if I can get a copy of chess_piece_presence.npz so that I can run your examples.

It doesn't need to be the full dataset, just something I can put through </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the third one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way Masvidal beats Tyron Woodley. People overhypes Masvidal because he won against Cowboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an excellent fight, one of the best belt fights we have seen in a long time. Good technique, and good athletic fighters with a similar skill.

We need a rematch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one do you recommend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 48% of the UK is "little" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4.6 unemployment rate. Lowest in the UK and one of the lowest in EU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 12:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 1/50 surprised me. Where I live (Glasgow) I think there are 2 of them which I visit often, and I would say people serving me are always locals (based on their accent). Same in Costa, Gregg's, McDonalds, Tesco, Iceland or Pizza Hut or the cleaners where I work.

It is strange in Glasgow seeing non local people working in any of these services job. I guess immigration is very low here. And let me tell you something, salaries are shite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a new 3ds, but I will never pay full price for a digital game. Even more when the game was released 8 years ago, which is a version of a 12 years old game.

If the game was a PC game, it would be on Steam for peanuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think ALBW hits a perfect spot in terms of difficulty. Oldest Zeldas have a lot of moment where you have no idea about what to do, and there are literally no hints.

I remember when I was a kid playing a link to the past, and then Ocarina. Without help from friends and Nintendo helpline, it would have been impossible for me to finish those games. Its like in a link to the past, when you need to run against the books with your pegasus boots, that's something that people will rarely think about, and there are no hints at all. Majoras Mask was brutal. I dont know anyone who was able to finish it back in the day. I finished it during christmas this time, and I had to use a guide constantly. The game is very poorly designed. Some of the old games were very annoying.

ALBW has a lot of "eureka" moments. For example, to access the first 2 dungeons, you need to do some work to do obtain the required object. It is not difficult, but some exploration is required.

Also, I think that Zelda games, are games where every one you play, the next one becomes easier. Like you know that if a dungeon is surrounded by water you need zora swimmers, and you know to check every watterfall for hidden passages, and you know that if a wall has 2 objects near each other leaving a gap, you better place a bomb there.

The season games had a lot of moments where the action required to moved forward made no sense. Like go to this exact spot and play an instrument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where to buy it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'd love to see some of the GameBoy ones remade instead.

I tried to play them not long ago (last summer), and I didn't enjoy them at all.

There were a lot of "what do to know" moments, which never happened in aLBW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible? My impression was that the 3DS was a bit better than the N64, and that's why they ported OoT and MM.

Wind Waker for Switch though. There are a lot of amazing games in the NGC which would be amazing in the Switch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I only need to follow the TWLoader wiki? and that's it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 11:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I install TWLoader, do I also need to install nds-bootstrap?

I don't really know what I am supposed to do with nds-bootstrap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(17)30246-5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A drug that can reverse aspects of ageing has been successfully trialled in animals, say scientists. They have rejuvenated old mice to restore their stamina, coat of fur and even some organ function. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iPhone 5's have a screen size of only 4", and it is not even 720p, and a tiny battery of 1,440 mAh.

I cannot imagine watching Netflix, Twitch or Youtube there. Can you do for example do face projections in snapchat? Or because we are speaking about games, play any of the newest games with cool 3D graphics?

When I say "unusable" I don't mean that the phone doesn't work. My old xperia still "works". What I mean is that the phone fails to deliver with new technologies. For me, nowadays, HD stream of stuff like Netflix, Twitch or UFC is a must.

I guess it really depends on the use you give to your smartphone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They want bums for peanuts. Duffy was on a 20/20 contract, which is super low for a guy was headlining a card, with a 4-1 in the UFC. I guess he wants now something like 50/50, which makes more sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If it's out of necessity people wouldn't upgrade every year or two en masse.

False. After 2 years batteries go to 50% of capacity, hardly lasting a day, and software updates makes the phone almost unusable.

My smartphone of 5 years ago had a 3.5" screen which made it almost impossible to use as video player. It could barely play youtube videos, and it would fail completely with Netflix, Twitch or other streaming services as UFC. It was almost impossible to use it to browse the net. I didn't upgrade it because "why not", I upgrade it because it was almost impossible to read a newspaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comparison with the iphone makes no sense. An iphone is primarly a phone, and it is primarly used to communicate (calls, texts, whatsapp, facebook,...). Most people who have a smartphone don't play game. Hell, I don't play games on mines.

Remove the communication side of a phone and tell me how many people would buy it. Apple tried it with the "ipod touch", and it was a total disaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the "gamer" demographic is too small and fickle for any major company to care about anymore. 

??

There are on average, at any given moment, 1.5 million playing Dota2 and CS, which are "gamer" games, excluding China.

There are around 7 million players concurrent at any given time playing LoL.

Gamers are what kept this industry alive for more than 30 years, and gamers are still the ones spending big money, buying the consoles, pre-ordering,...

The day this industry runs away from gamers, then it is dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Female brain size affects the assessment of male attractiveness during mate choice. Large-brained and wild-type guppy females showed strong preference for males with color traits that predict attractiveness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "viral"

check google hits, near 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FS1 will probably be TJ against Cody </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Careful though, you can't use something like how much a company makes to justify your own actions, as that is a very slippery slope.

I agree. My point is that nowadays piracy is almost a meaningless problem for companies, as opposed to I dont know, the late 90s, when people were burning CDs like no tomorrow (PSX or PC, it was crazy).

I don't know a single person who pirates game nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  referendum

There's a reason why Germany doesn't allow referendums anymore.

Referendums seem like "true democraphy", but they are very easily controlled by populistic agendas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what I am doing is not 100% legal, but I am not going to pay for the same game twice.

There's an easy solution to this, when you buy a physical game, they should also let you get the digital version. This is how it works in Steam, you buy the game, get the code, put it in Steam, and now it is available in every computer you own.

The videogame industry is generating billions of money every year. I think piracy is a tiny problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that most ends are either an early call, or a late call. There's rarely a middle ground. Brad Picket this weekend for example, most people said it was an early call. Was it really? The "are you defending yourself" is such a grey statement.

I just think that the rules should be changed, and that there shouldn't be anything like an "early call". Refs should be stopping fights earlier, and that's it. Yeah, fighters go through camps, spend money,... but if you got dropped and the other guy hammerfists your face, then it's done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a FF8 (original), but I was away and I didn't have the console with me, so I went through the ending using an emulator.

I also have some NDS games which I bought, like FF4, that now I want to play in my 3DS, but my NDS games are in my parents house far away... and I am not buying the same game again.

I like buying games (physical games, I am not going to pay $50 for a digital copy), but it is more convenient having them digital in your system so you can carry more of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's a demo you can try. I really liked Pokemon XY, which is also "fake 3D". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using a satnav to get to your destination 'switches off' parts of the brain that would otherwise be used to simulate different routes, reveals new UCL research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
