<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop fucking commenting about p2w on everyone's post. No one likes a petty looser.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo I'm sorry you don't like my server but other people might. Can you please fucking stop? Also I know it was you on my server, I checked your ip. That's really sad and petty. Just drop it and go fuck someone else's shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HuntFactions [PvP]{Factions}{Simple}{Competitive}{New}{Crates}{1.11.2} </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 01:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About HF:
        HuntFactions, founded by spiffyFox, is a new and ambitious factions server, with a small yet dedicated player base. HuntFactions operates as a subsidiary of the AerisGaming Community, with the MC division being run by the owner of Hunt. While creating Hunt, we aimed to bring back the clean, simple, and bloody factions experience that has become so hard to find. The team is devoted to introducing and developing new, clean, and balanced features over time. For example, we plan on adding a custom end map, spleef with rewards, and custom items soon! HF Is an extremely new server, so as expected, we have a small player base. Most people who play on the server are also active on discord. Its a really great group! We yearned for a refined factions experience, a flashback to factions servers of a few years ago. We built it.

We are currently developing our Hub Expansion. This will include prison, skyblock, OP factions, survival, modified survival, and more!

Players who join during our current beta will be given a [Supporter] rank, with access to special permanent features.

***We are looking forward to new faces! Please post comments/concerns/questions below.***
        
Server Information:
Plugins and Features of Note:
* Factions (ECON Enabled)
* Crates
* Crazy Auctions
* Voting
* Donor Ranks
* Parkour
* Competitive
* PvP Arena
* PvP Log
* Expendable Obsidian
* Vast Spawn Shop
* Fun and Dedicated Playerbase
* Discord

* Server Address/IP: **HuntFactions.mc-srv.com**
* Server Locale: East Coast (USA)
* Game Play Type: *Classic Competitive Factions Experience*
* Version: 1.11.2
* Website: [Here](www.AerisGaming.enjin.com/huntfactions)
* Discord: [Here](https://discord.gg/548S5n)

*Rules-*
* No Racism
* No Hacking
* No Abuse
* No Spamming
* No Advertising
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 08:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the founder of a half beta/half in-dev network. We are looking for some creative staff teams/servers to join us. We provide hosting, professional IT support, website, etc. Would you maybe be interested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you understand how kids work. They enjoy and respond to small rewards. Some people like this mechanic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your a twat. Please get off my thread now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your saying it's unfair because it's p2w. It is neither unfair nor can you pay to win. No matter how much money you spend on my donor shop you will never gain anything you need in order to win. Thus, it is not pay-to-win. And yea I'm mentioning your karma. At a certain point you have to understand that you might in fact be the ignorant one, not all the others who call you ignorant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have negetive 50 something comment karma. You are blatantly the ignorant one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you fucking kidding me? First off, I ain't rich. I'm putting a lot of money into making a genuinely fun server for kids of all ages. I myself am a huge fan of factions and I fully intend on playing myself. Secondly, if you spend two seconds on my server you will soon realize that those ranks really won't help you for shit. If your not good at factions those ranks sure won't help you, and if you are good at factions then you really could get everything in those ranks in one day. The singular feature that could maybe be considered cheaty in those ranks is the ability to change spawners for $20. However, we have an SS plugin so you really don't need it, and you know what? Fuck it. I'm allowed to sell out a tiny bit. I'm providing hours and hours of fun out of my own fucking pocket. If it was a balancing issue I would understand but it's not, so before you go shitting on people's work at least really check out the gameplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think it's p2w? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here good with bungee and interested in setting up/ helping me set on up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so please add me on discord at Fox#2227. Thankses! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HuntFactions [PvP]{Factions}{Crates}{1.11.2} </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About HF:
        HuntFactions, founded by spiffyFox, is a new and ambitious factions server, with a small yet dedicated player base. HuntFactions operates as a subsidiary of the AerisGaming Community, with the MC division being run by the owner of Hunt. While creating Hunt, we aimed to bring back the clean, simple, and bloody factions experience that has become so hard to find. The team is devoted to introducing and developing new, clean, and balanced features over time. For example, we plan on adding a custom end map, spleef with rewards, and custom items soon! HF Is an extremely new server, so as expected, we have a small player base. Most people who play on the server are also active on discord. Its a really great group! We yearned for a refined factions experience, a flashback to factions servers of a few years ago. We built it.

We are currently developing our Hub Expansion. This will include prison, skyblock, OP factions, survival, modified survival, and more!

Players who join during our current beta will be given a [Supporter] rank, with access to special permanent features.

***We are looking forward to new faces! Please post comments/concerns/questions below.***
        
Server Information:
Plugins and Features of Note:
* Factions (ECON Enabled)
* Crates
* Crazy Auctions
* Voting
* Donor Ranks
* Parkour
* Competitive
* PvP Arena
* PvP Log
* Expendable Obsidian
* Vast Spawn Shop
* Fun and Dedicated Playerbase
* Discord

* Server Address/IP: **HuntFactions.mc-srv.com**
* Server Locale: East Coast (USA)
* Game Play Type: *Classic Competitive Factions Experience*
* Version: 1.11.2
* Website: [Here](www.AerisGaming.enjin.com/huntfactions)
* Discord: [Here](https://discord.gg/548S5n)

*Rules-*
* No Racism
* No Hacking
* No Abuse
* No Spamming
* No Advertising
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HuntFactions [PvP]{Factions}{Crates}{1.11.2} </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 07:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking for a serious manager for my network. Please add me on discord at fox#2227 if your still for hire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should make a simplicity pack based on one of the graphics in the new launcher, the one with the small rollercoaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend Request Sent :) ~Fox#2227 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of server? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello. I am the owner of Hunt Factions, soon to be Hunt Network. We are looking to acquire a survival server. If you are interested in become partners, please PM or MSG me on discord at Fox#2227  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there. I think I have some connections that might interest you, but the discord link wont work for me. Please add me at Fox#2227 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly wtf is wrong with you guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunt Factions | A New Unique And Ambitious Factions Server On The Rise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright I'll type out my shitty draft :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I would have an easyer time going through cards I plan to use if I could see them infront of me. I'm just trying to get an idea of other people's processes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making my first EDH deck and I feel a bit lost. It's hard for me to find my smaller creatures and cards. I haven't found a good way to be able to visually plan my deck. I have looked through EDHrec. Any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a youtuber join my unique and competetive factions server! Please contact me if your interested or want more info :) OFFERING $ FOR GOOD WORK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contact on discord at fox#2227 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not free to play but saints row really helped me cope with depression. Very funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great! Could you add me on discord at fox#2227? Or if you have Skype that works too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunt Factions, an ambitious and unique in-dev server, is looking to add more plugin developers and a builder to its staff team! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there! Hunt factions is looking for more plugin developers and a builder to join us on the server. If your interested, please pm on reddit or contact me at fox#2227 on discord! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 14:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great build! Would you be interested in joining my staff team as a builder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a "Awesome" game with a sick soundtrack and a shit ton of fun. Kind of like saints row the third. I like the free roam, and the levels are great. The second or third level, epic af, to kanye west Power, is great. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a free roam game with a great soundtrack, thats just, a ton of fun. I love saints row, fallout 4, GTA is meh but it gets boring playing alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying very hard to differentiate my server. We have a lot of custom plugins on the way and some are here already. One big mechanic we have that has never been done as far as I know, is the shrine system I have created. Faction leaders, and leaders only, are given perms based on their factions stance. If the faction is in the top 15 on the leaderboards, the leader may go to the shrine and buy special equipment based on the rank (if the leaders faction is ranked first, they can buy any of the 15 items). This would allow him to equip his army with lightningbolts, rockets, and more. This also gives the leader a reason to use the faction economy, to raise money for the equipment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please let me know if you would be intereted in joining my team of staff as a builder for a unique ambitious New factions server. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bushier! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 07:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey y'all! I'm selling my r1 i3 alpha. Price is negotiable. It has 16GB Ram, and a 850 evo 250gb ssd that I may or may not decide to sell depending on price offers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey there! Im looking for talented builders to join my team for a new unique and ambitious factions server! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HuntFactions, a unique and ambitious factions server, is looking for Devs and Builders! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello fellow redditor! HuntFactions, a in-dev factions server focused on faction diplomacy and full scale battles, is recruiting Devs and Builders to finish up our early-development staff team. If your at all interested, have questions, or want more information, please contact me @ Fox#2227 on discord. 

Thank you!
~Fox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks man
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 03:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how to I get it to output a log?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I do have the loading screen mod. Where can I find the log? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question... I have 131 missing props. What's the best way to go about obtaining said props? Thanks yall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would really like something like that incorporated into my factions server-in progress. Please message me if your interested :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well ive already started early development.Please contact me at Fox#2227 on discord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiring Partners, Administrators, Builders, and Devs for a new competitive Factions server, giving other servers a run for their money! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiring anyone interested for any position to help set up, and run a Factions server. Based on a server that I played on a few years ago, this server will entice strategy and large scale battles. Please PM me if interested, or add me on discord at Fox#2227. 

This is going to be a fairly new kind of Factions server, and ide like to hear and share new fresh ideas. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
