<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4010</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, really appreciate the help ^^ I tried playing the mod a while back but there's almost only hackers and bandits playing anymore, plus the only maps available are Chernarus cause the others are empty :P I've been checking up on SA from time to time but this time I just got tired of the same bugs happening even after months/maybe even years of being in the game. That's why I made this post :L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, you're about the 20th asshole who didn't get what I posted about this. Kindly fuck off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game feels really random though, I was checking out an old factory building and fell down from the second floor. I instantly got the message "you are dead" when i hit the ground. Also no, I didn't notice the stick automatically going into my inventory where my axe should be and none of my friends + any players I've asked have noticed that. I don't have a problem with zombies being strong, but when their hits are so extremely random and can hit from 2 meters away it's really annoying. When a pristine item on you can go to ruined state in one hit it's really annoying. Don't tell me this is bullshit like the other people on here because it's happened to me three. fucking. times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you... Was getting tired getting shut down every time :P Some people pointing out that the stuff I posted is wrong is really irritating since this stuff has happened from experience.. This was meant to shed some lights on these bugs/glitches that's currently in the game and have been for a while and I just want the game to get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, ok. I'l just forget everything that happened to me and my friends during the last 2 weeks plying the game then cause clearly it didn't happen according to you. -.-' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SA has always been shit. Not saying it's worse and unsure how you got that from my post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way it's rn? Nah. The way it used to be? Yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know its still in development, but this is just bringing lights to bugs and glitches that CAN be fixed. Alot of these things have been like this for ages, I know because I've had the game since launch. Also thanks for telling me to go play the mod, maybe I should do that with the 4 other players that are playing? I was just talking about my preferences and how the game could improve from its current state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't. I don't like playing a broken game that's been broken for months/years now. This post will change nothing at all anyway but atleast I wrote what's wrong with the game down in hopes that it MAY change something... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks for ruining the game dev team! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I recently started playing again with some friends thinking-- scratch that, HOPE, that we were going to have some fun. That didn't happen. Except we encountered bugs at every corner and glitches that makes you say "Why tf is this still in a game that has been out this long?"

Let me list up several things that's wrong and game breaking for players:

1. A 1 - 2m fall will kill you. Instantly. No unconscious, no leg breaking, no screaming out in pain, just death.

2. Military tents are about as hard to put down as throwing a ball into a bucket while driving a car on top of a bridge 5000 feet up in the air. It is literally impossible to put it down where you want to put it down. Unless you want to put it in the middle of an open field where everyone can see it is impossible.

3. Thanks for changing my axe with a long stick without my consent after cutting down a tree, really appreciate that.

4. Cars won't even start and there's absolutely no reason they shouldn't. Got the battery? Check. Got the sparkplug? Check. Got 4 pristine wheels? Check. Refueled that bad boy up completely? Check. Start the car? No f*cking chance. Even if the frame is somehow not pristine it should at least START. Or even better, let us fix the damn thing and even see if it's damaged. Like we did in the fkn mod? And while we're on about cars..

5. Thanks for adding the teleportation device inside vehicles, really love the sci-fi take on the post apocalyptic doom that we're all playing in. Even with ping as low as 20 on a server the car/truck/bus you're driving will teleport 4 meters to the left or right without warning. We've lost about 4 cars because of this so far...

6. If you're carrying two guns at you and change into your axe because a zombie attacks you, say goodbye to the one you had in your hands. Cause that one has either despawned or somehow got dropped beneath the ground. 

7. Zombies, ahh zombies. I remember a time when they weren't such a pain in the ass. Like when they didn't follow you through 4 towns without showing signs of stopping. Or when they couldn't hit you from 2 meters away. Or when their hits wasn't ruining your pristine jacket in one punch or made you bleed with one hit.

8. Oh boy how I love eating food. I wish I could spend half the time playing this game looking for it and eating it! Well now you can. Even if you somehow manage to scrap yourself up to a light green hydrated and energized you just go half an hour and you're back at starving again. Only in DayZ can you be stuffed and starve at the same time.

9. Hypothermia. This is just the best addon you guys could come up with, cause this game just HAVE to be as realistic as humanly possible doesn't it Rocket? Me and my friends have died multiple times of this bullshit we quit playing if it starts to rain on the server. Run in the rain for 1 minute? Hypothermia.

10. Last of probably many to come. After finding me and my friend's base got raided during the night we decided to switch location and find a more suitable area for our utopia. And when I finally found the best of spots, I took my military tent out of my car and tried to put it down. (Read 2 for more info on how that went) Alas, as I pressed the letter G on my electronical board of keys my character decided to throw this 100 pound tent like it was a tennisball into the unknown. I spent half an hour looking for my tent in the shiny outer doors of chernarus but had no luck finding my dearest. It had either despawned, thrown deep underground, or somehow landed in Elektro confusing a freshspawn wondering why it's raining tents.

Last thing and this is directly to the devs. Change back to the format the mod had, not 100% copy paste but get back the most important shit. Don't make it so impossibly hard to have fun in this game. Loot is almost nonexistent anymore and fixing up cars feel much more like a chore than it did in the mod. You only needed a motor, wheels, fuel tank and some scrap metal to fix it up and THAT is all you should need in a GAME. I loved the health bar hud from the mod, it's much easier to keep up with rather than getting a pop up message. Just, don't make the game so extremely realistic and bring it back to the good old DayZ it USED to be.

Tl;Dr Dayz is broken.

EDIT: Alright, I get it, you guys hate criticism and love to bitch to people when they point out flaws in an early access/in development game. about 90% of you people said that what I've listed is wrong and is bullshit while I'm saying this is from experience. YOU can't fucking say otherwise. If we can't call out the flaws of this game NOW in this format how the hell are we supposed to? How are the devs going to fix it if no one is calling out the bugs and everyone is praising it for the garbage it currently is?
Also for you people telling me this is not my type of game or "go play the mod", kindly fuck off. I've played the mod, I loved the mod, I played SA since fucking launch and I've enjoyed most of it. But simply wanting this game to be BETTER isn't bitching, or whining, or ranting, or any of the bullshit you guys call it. I wasn't pissed, or angry when I wrote this, I was neutral and tired of bugs still not being fixed and decided to make a post on the hope that some of this may get fixed. Fucking grow up man.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get what you mean, been spoiled by trailers for a long time so i usually don't see any more trailers of a movie other than the very first then void it like the plague. Only to have something spoiled through a thumbnail or a screenshot :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highway to hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really glad that Assassin's Creed isn't on this list. Both me and 2 of my friends that have played through all of the games thought this was an awesome movie. That's my opinion tho :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youtube turns RGB if you type awesome in any video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a preference I guess, passwords feels more natural to access a pc in my mind and it's just irritating that I can't use the password I've had for ages without adding numbers and extra letters or having to use a pin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's not possible to have two separate passwords? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to remove the strict rules of password login? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I linked my windows 10 to my microsoft account yesterday, after that I couldn't use the password I always used to log into my pc. Only the password to my microsoft account worked. Problem is I hate the strict rules where you **need** one upper case and a number for it to be a "strong" password. Ffs microsoft just let me use my normal password without all this bullshit.

Is it possible to have one password for login and another one for your microsoft account or do they **have** to be the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit sherlock, I thought that it somehow could with the water and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that [the eels they force fed him with the water regrew his teeth? Since the water apparently had healing properties.](#spoiler)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes dad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Norwegian Royal Family waving </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend can't access his account because he doesn't know the secret answer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been helping my friend on Daybreak's site, made a ticket and everything. They asked if we could guess the answer to the secret question and we did. We even added proof that we are the real people trying to access his account and not some hacker. We cave them the account name and a picture of him accessing his email connected to the account. After all of this they say that HE should make an account and basically do all of this over again for some stupid reason and that they can't do shit without the secret answer.

How fucking stupid are these people, we've done everything we can, given them EVERYTHING they need to fix this, all they have to do is just reset the secret question/answer or change the answer to what we want. Ffs Daybreak we just wanna play h1z1 but you guys make it so damn fucking hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The current system destroys teens and children's motivations to even finish school. I graduated High school last year but didn't get my diploma because I failed one class, aka German. It was because of several reasons, mainly lack of any motivation to learn the language because I deemed it completely unecessary, having three different teachers throughout High School that didn't care/got angry too easily/or did too little too late. I wouldn't say I'm a bad student, I'm more on the middle on the grading cane. I excelled in some classes and not so much in others. The fact that this one class I failed could decide that I can't choose the education I want/excel in infuriates me and makes me feel like a failure. On my very last exam(Architecture   Design) I got a 5+ (B+ for you Americans) and good grades in these type of classes. Next year I'm going to college for Architecture but after that I don't even know if I can continue on this path that I, some of my teachers and family think I should go. The fact that this class was not optional and I had no choice is also, very demotivating. If it was something else like english I would've made it without question. FYI I'm Norwegian and I'm about as good in english as norwegian.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not surprised about John Wick, my town apparently doesn't show it at all. It even has posters of it up and everything, movies like these SHOULD go here too. Think this happens to other towns too which may explain the lack of money being made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Troy Bakers joker was one of my favourite characters of this series, think he nailed it tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start with the way they came out, Asylum, City, Origins and Knight. Origins wasn't made by the same team but is still great in my eyes. Plus the story isn't that connected to the other games so you won't have to worry about that. Plus the maps gets larger and larger for each game, in Asylum you're on an island, in City it's a walled of part of Gotham, in Origins it's the same as City but years earlier plus a similar sized island connected with a bridge and in Knight it's the biggest one with three new islands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no button that says show system applications, the app is just called "weather", it shows up under "all", and at the top right corner the button that says "more"  only have 2 options which are sort by size or reset app preferences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I unhide/access apps not in the app menu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to figure out how to access some apps that I know is on the phone but isn't showing up in the app menu. Like the already installed weather app. Can't find it anywhere but I can see it in settings. This is starting to irritate since there is no solution online at all, every solution I've found is either "do this thing that won't work on that phone you have" or "download this unnecessary program". Htf do I un-hide apps?
Phone is Samsung Galaxy J3 btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I unhide/access apps not in the app menu? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er ikke s veldig mange forskjeller mellom ABS og PBT da, s det spiller ikke s veldig stor rolle:p Poker har en aluminium ramme, tenker at det tler litt mere da ^^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 13:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Viste ikke om Anne pro engang x) De er jvlig like men jeg digger Pok3r rgb bedre egentlig :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too be honest yeah, I write to both english and scandinavian friends so it would be much better to have nordic than the regular one :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit thanks man! Don't know why I didn't check Amazon at all, but I'l keep this in mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [help] Pok3r RGB with Nordic ISO layout and RED switches? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking for this keyboard for some hours now and the closest I've found is [this](https://www.maxgaming.no/gaming-tastatur/vortex/pok3r-rgb-mechanical-keyboard-mx-brown). This one got brown switches but I'd rather get red ones, anyone know where to get it WITH the nordic ISO layout? I thought about maybe buying this then changing the switches to red but I'm not sure how that would work with this keyboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 13:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read up on it and found that program yesterday, after using that the videos worked perfectly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My audio and video is not in sync </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recorded a video but when I put in in Premiere Pro the audio and the video don't add up, the audio is always slightly behind and I have no idea why. The original recording is 100% in sync but it gets unsynced when adding it. Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm not mistaken I think Avatar was MADE to be watched in 3D, unlike other movies after that that was made for 2D which then just got a 3D overhaul. Like having a great product that cost a lot of money only to have bad clones afterwards because it's cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We do, unless that solo tries to kill us multiple times or raid us we'd rather just let them do what they do. As I said most of the time it's just me and maybe another friend, at most we're three people sometimes but not so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any servers that ban big clans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only play solo or with a couple of friends, so we're 3 people at most. Every time we've played on a server our base has always been destroyed by a group that's about 7-10 people, and tbh I'm getting kind of sick of the unfairness of that. So does anyone know of any servers that ban big clans? Preferably an European server.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episode IX will probably go with "The Return of The Sith" or something like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm aight, guess I just have to wait then. If this doesn't work I think I gotta purchase another version of windows... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did I not give any more info? I've even sent a message through rust to give them feedback on this and it's not like I know everything about why it's crashing, I only know that it is. As for the link you posted, thats a problem I've had for months. I can't get the latest update for Win7 normally OR manually (I've tried, alot) which means I can't update my desktop nor any other program currently installed for some reason. Just to add that when I wrote this I actually did crash every 5 minutes which caused both me and some friends alot of items and a ton of irritation. So yeah, I was a irritated when I wrote this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 18:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **[BUG]** Game crashes every 5 minutes now, ffs facepunch it's been 3 days since the update and nothing has happened. Now I can kindly say f*ck off to the game because you either die by crashing while crossing a lake or crashing at the beginning of a gunfight. The game is literally unplayable for a ton of people now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
