<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol...Yeah after rereading that it does sort of sound like I shouldn't be allowed to own pets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. No. Not at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, my girlfriend says I should clarify that by adding that the "last guy in a mask" was NOT me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last guy in a mask did unspeakable things to her lady parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol.. Not kidding..this dog is "passionate" about the frisbee. I DO have scars. Just not on my face. Yet. http://m.imgur.com/8siKgJH
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discovered too late that my dog does NOT like surgical masks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well-written and great advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the exact same case and phone. That case was just made to show wear and dirt. Mine is the same age and looks just as bad...and I have tried to take care of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, wow. Very interesting/fascinating. I suffer from sleep paralysis and night terrors, but have never seen anything interact with my wife. I have seen tall, dark monsters approaching the bed from my wife's side, but I could always wake her in time to turn on the lamp, which is on her side of the bed. I feel like she somehow protects me from these things. Please post more info if this happens again. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you have physical access to the phone install cerberus. I use it daily on several different phones. I believe there is a one-time fee, but its only a couple of dollars. It lets you do anything remotely that the user can do. You can take pics with front and back cam, screenshots, view texts, record audio and video, track in real time, open up a shell, everything. It also lets you hide the app from the app drawer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My rescue-pup, Lex, showing off her great form. We rescued her on what was supposed to be her execution day. She has been the most amazing and impressive dog ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was pleasantly surprised by Googles stylized version of my photo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.manmadediy.com/users/chris/posts/63-how-to-tailor-a-button-down-shirt-for-a-perfect-fit
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found this, but I dont think its something I could do myself. It would take some practice....and a sewing machine. https://www.bespokepost.com/the-post/how-to-tailor-your-own-clothes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I was talking about "pinning the slack" https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=srzdpcRA4-g

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. I wouldnt pay more than 10-12 bucks to get a five dollar Goodwill shirt fitted. As someone who gets most of his clothes fitted, I would like to learn this also, but I feel like its complicated and time-consuming for the layperson (me). I dont know if you have ever had a shirt fitted by a tailor, but they have you try it on and button it. Then they pull it tight on each side around your body by taking up the slack under your arms. They then use pins to keep that "slack" tight while you remove the shirt. I assume they cut out that pinned slack and sew it back up....but I dont really know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> every town I have lived in has had a tailor shop. Some were also dry cleaners. Tailoring isnt expensive and can make an off-the-rack shirt look like a million bucks. I buy some of my "dress clothes" from the local Goodwill or YMCA for very cheap, and then have them fitted at the tailor. Makes a huge difference. To have a long-sleeve shirt fitted is around ten bucks. I believe pants are cheaper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Place tape over your TV's mic..cam....uh..remote..umm "spy parts" to reduce what the CIA can monitor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have physical access to the router? If so try the 30/30/30 hard reset. Maybe that will work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hit the eject button. Thats the best way I've heard it said.  Hit the eject button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know what the status of that is yet. I THINK the driver stayed on the scene, but I'm not sure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mom got out of surgery at 3am this morning. Her right tibia and fibula were broken, but were set with rods and a plate. She'll have physical therapy, but we dont know the long term damage yet. She will most-likely be somewhat affected by it for the rest of her life. Her sister had some lumbar spinal fractures and some small pelvic fractures, but because of her pre-existing condition the doctors arent sure about treatment yet. Thanks for asking! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Witnesses are saying that, at the last second, my mother saw the oncoming car and pushed my aunt (her sister) out of its direct path.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My aunt (my mothers sister) has cerebral palsy, is in a wheelchair, and lives in a nursing home. My sixty-nine-year-old mother visits her three to four times per week. Yesterday, while sitting in the sun during their visit, an out-of-control car jumped the sidewalk, slammed into them both, and ran over my mothers legs. Witnesses are saying that, at the last second, my mother saw the oncoming car and pushed my aunt (her sister) out of its direct path. Here is a picture of them in the hospital together before being sent out to different hospitals for treatment/surgery http://imgur.com/sLVcVJS . The paramedics wheeled mom's bed into her sisters room so they could say goodbye. Here are pics of moms xray. http://imgur.com/zyxSmBU  http://imgur.com/5xVhwfJ  http://imgur.com/9gTaDvW

vague local news article http://wsls.com/2017/02/25/vehicle-hits-two-people-in-front-of-giles-nursing-home/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is out of control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typed password into username field. Oh well, fuck it. New password is now iheartreddit69 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping for a graph. No graph. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once found a typed letter of recommendation for employment from 1949. It was on company letterhead. Very nice. I also found a copy of Lone Survivor with Marcus Luttrell's autograph inside.  It was autographed "to Dave..." My name isnt Dave, but it was still a neat find.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roy Orbison has lost a LOT of weight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats right. Pardon my forgetfulness. I got kicked in the head by a chicken (long story). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reading the top gazillion comments to find out what these things are and ending up instead reading about shit and toilets...now I have to ask WHAT ARE THOSE CLEAR STONE-LIKE STONEY THINGS??! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone malfunction captured my dogs spirit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here. After constant surveys, sometimes two or three per day for months, it suddenly stopped. I was completely honest and never tried to con them. Their scam algorithm needs some work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.imdb.com/title/tt4695012/?ref_=fn_al_tt_1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this! Will test and report back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Military Reading List </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response and for that info (which says a lot about you). I have downloaded and extracted the file, but havent had the chance to toy around with it yet. Would it be ok to PM you a question or two? I dont usually do this. Feel free to ignore this message or respond openly or in a PM...or like I said, not at all. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a late-to-the-party jackass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks SharpieInThePooper! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are we talking about the EQGROUP auction files?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> something something barking up the wrong tree.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is exactly what I came here to learn. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitten by a dog one day after it was vaccinated for rabies. Should I be worried about rabies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 17:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitten by a dog one day after rabies vaccination. Could I have been infected with rabies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitten by a dog one day after rabies vaccination.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 12:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...was this a regular threesome (MFF) or a Devils threesome (MMF)? Because, that might make a difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common parlor trick....magnets in their shoes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legal liability nightmare.....? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shout-out to Zach.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here...and the thumbnail even looked like Screech... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see how being airgapped would hinder the benefits of such a system.  This is fascinating to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes sense. I know literally nothing at all about these systems, but this doesnt sound unreasonable. Thanks for the insight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Why not have it isolated?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this FOR SURE. I just finished reading Glimpses of the Devil and Hostage to the Devil. Threes...NOT GOOD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 20:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider myself very skeptical, but I have had similar experiences with this app very often.  Its unbelievable at times. I wonder what pact with the devil the developers made....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "..will definitely take action"  Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS. VERY IMPORTANT. I took over the role after my predecessor left with zero notice. I had nothing: no passwords, no idea what servers did what, nothing. The place was a mess, but I learned a lot and had fun doing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you get into it and start doing it a system for documentation may work itself out. That is, once you begin to become familiar with your duties/procedures/responsibilities, you may find it easier to document. And dont be afraid to change. If you start out with something, but an easier or better method/technique comes forward, then dont be afraid to change. It could be continuously evolving. I started out in a new job and began documenting using notepad. That evolved to multiple text files, which evolved to a spreadsheet, and so on. Good luck! Documentation can save your ass in many different ways!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 14:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok..I didnt see that. THanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I followed this guide: http://android.gadgethacks.com/how-to/tip-speed-up-gboard-performance-android-by-disabling-these-two-settings-0175748/

edit: here https://www.reddit.com/r/Android/comments/5l38v0/found_a_fix_for_gboard_on_android_for_being_slow/



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...I'm not a builder, but isnt that plastic sheet on the ground a vapor barrier for radon gas and other harmful vapors and moisture? Is it ok to remove that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was totally thinking sex-dungeon...but..yeah..this is ok, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 14:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What version of Android are you running? Did you update gboard? The gboard update slowed my n6 to a crawl. I almost uninstalled it, but Googled it instead. Changed some gboard settings and am now back to normal. Thats just one of the recent issues I have had.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did something similar, but very simple and less technical, a few years ago using YAWCAM, the open source cam software. Using motion detection to alert me of motion in a certain area...my boss was very tall, more than a foot taller than anyone in the office. I set YAWCAM to alert me when it detected motion  in the hallway at a certain height....saved me more than once.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are welcome. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 01:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw this on TV. If your defroster sucks or if your AC doesnt work...fill a sock with silicon-based kitty litter and leave it in the car. It will absorb all moisture and your windows will never fog up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good story! Thanks for sharing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well said! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crying right now...reading reddit through tears... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We both had a laugh at that. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I being salted here or is the correct term still 'peppered'? (link to pic in text) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was hilarious at the time. Recently, while driving with my young son in snowy weather, I became stuck behind a working snowplow that was treating the road with salt pellets. Unable to pass because of other traffic, but wanting to keep up my speed, I was following the truck very closely and being pelted with salt pellets. Not realizing the irony, I turned to my young son who was riding shotgun, and exclaimed "I'm being peppered by this maniac!!" Without missing a beat he immediately said, "I think the term is...salted."  Again, this was hilarious at the time, but it doesnt really seem so now that I have written it out. Here is a pic for reference (pic found online, not actual pic) http://imgur.com/a/9Nqao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 13:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animal-lover upvote. Sleeping in bed with 2 dogs and 3 cats right now. My best friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 10:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goosebumps. Well told. Thanks for sharing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip! Worked for me! I have been very frustrated lately with the slowness of this app and the overall slowness of my phone since installing it. This seems to have helped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here...every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for taking the time to post this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Namecheap for years. Absolutely no problems. GoDaddy for two months. Ninety-nine problems, but a working domain wasn't one.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> commenting on my own post. The more I watch it the more I think its nothing really. When I first noticed it I really thought it was odd, but not I cant be sure. I dont know what it was, dont know if its abnormal or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video in text. This could be nothing, but while filming a cat playing upstairs in our house something smoke-like appears in video at 14 seconds bottom right. More info and link inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 04:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We do not smoke. There was no dust and this does not act like dust. There are no HVAC vents near that area. There are no bugs in the house.  The camera operator did notice the smoke on the camera screen while filming, but did not see anything unusual on the other side of the camera. Some strange things have happened to me/us in this house recently, things that terrified me that I cant explain. This could be easily explainable. I dont know yet.

LINK:  https://youtu.be/thn5Y3eiuG8

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Prior to the 1960's welfare recipients in the United States were prohibited from owning a television and, more surprising, gardening/owning a garden. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 15:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate. Thanks for posting. You are not alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Return of the popups...I love KAT, their popups are annoying. Even TPB's popups are manageable. KAT popups are persistent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone notice the other deer to the left, just exiting the water and entering the treeline?...laughing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reflection checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murica! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, this cat was like Mission Impossible going after that food! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When she made these she'd been at it for about 3 months. I think they're pretty great, too. Thanks for the compliment! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girlfriend crocheted some Christmas tree ornaments this year.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Up-armored Catfeeder...for the persistent, creative, overeating cat who wont stay out of the food... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/DarkNetMarkets/comments/2ri9sd/how_to_create_a_new_identity_peaches_guide/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What difference does a label make? The point is you did it...it worked. You may have used off-the-shelf tools, but so what? Not everyone knows how to do that.  Good work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're both on git. I followed this tutorial when I installed Fluxion. Once installed you will have to install 3 additional dependencies, but they're all easy apt-get install ***.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rQdlT4HsOyU

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 13:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you interested in just cracking wpa networks or are you specifically looking to crack wpa with aircrack? The reason I ask is there are some automated tools for Kali that work GREAT. I have had unbelievable success with LINSET and FLUXION. They're both CLI, work on Kali, and offer multiple options for cracking wpa in different ways. Both of them use tools that are mostly already on Kali including the air* tools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound strange, but I promise you its true. I have narrowed this issue down to a toilet issue (we have two). Occasionally we hear a long, loud "foghorn-like" sound coming from all around us. Its everywhere and nowhere at the same time, but it only happens when I flush either of the toilets and just after the tank finishes filling up. Does this make sense? Originally, and I am not kidding you here, my wife suspected demonic possession/poltergeist.  Any ideas?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! YOU SEE IT! I got some neg replies to this, but that was the first thing I noticed...something didnt look right. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really needed to hear this. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 13:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its mindset. I love reading, but I also work 50 hours per week, have a family, several hobbies, and a house and lawn to care for. I still manage to read several times per week...and that doesnt include audiobooks when I am traveling. I dont think I am anymore organized than the next guy..and I dont think I have more time on my hands than anyone else. I just....I dont know...I love my job and my life. Things just seem to fall into place. 

EDIT: I just read my original response "make reading a priority"..like I'm some sort of public service announcement. I take that back. Bad response.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just have to make reading a priority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 11:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O..M...G.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
