<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3445</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds military service boosts well-being for transgender vets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study: People who want police to use body cameras also think law enforcement officers are doing a good job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police video shows officer press gun to unarmed man's head, threaten to kill him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indicted police officer among several arrested in drug ring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mostly People Who Trust Police Say They Support Body Cameras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Californias kindergarten vaccination rates hit new high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State vaccination rates up sharply in wake of new law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State vaccination rates up sharply in wake of new law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State vaccination rates up sharply in wake of new law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State vaccination rates up sharply in wake of new law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Affordable Care Act increased health insurance coverage, volunteering rose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Affordable Care Act increased health insurance coverage, volunteering rose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student Disciplined As School Splits Hairs About What Kind Of Red Dye Is OK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student banned from class over hair color </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antarctica is melting faster than originally thought, new study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good morning; thank you for letting me know, Professor. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mostly People Who Trust Police Say They Support Body Cameras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Clears Way for Police Body Cameras in New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge Clears Way for Police Body Cameras in New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your line of thinking. Probably the same way we should approach drug abuse. 

One of the hardest problems I encounter when trying to eat clean, dramatically limiting to completely erasing my consumption of sugar, high density carbs, junk food, etc., is that there aren't many options for me to eat right outdoors in most neighborhoods, malls, and other places. Even a place like Panera, has great salads, but they only go great with the delicious breads, pastries, and lattes they serve. So you negate a lot of the benefits of the salad. To top it off, my favorite soup there is the turkey chili, and they take it off the menu every summer.

I can travel to Manhattan where there are a lot of options for me to go to a place like Chop't and pick up a hearty salad with low-fat grilled chicken; and drink a unsweetened green tea; but it's always a headache to get parking out there and everything is also more expensive. 

How about creating tax incentives, government subsidies, grants etc. to start restaurants that focus on eating whole non-processed foods? Perhaps that could get places like Chop't opening locations in the suburbs and maybe the inner-city and road trip stops. 

I know eating home is the best option, and I have no problem with cooking from Monday to Friday. But I don't want to cook, nor does my wife on the weekends, and that's where we struggle to keep a good diet. And we are in fairly good shape with probably more will power than a lot of other people. Yet we still love our cheat days; that said, I know there are people whose struggle with sugar addiction is far worse. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually going to ask the same thing; for my family, and I flew to a country where people have been found to have Zika back in December and January. Are there any symptoms to watch out for even after several months of potential exposure? Should every one who flew to a place with [risk of Zika](https://wwwnc.cdc.gov/travel/page/world-map-areas-with-zika) be specifically tested for it upon return? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also love to read how promising your work can be to potentially correct the genetic link to alzheimer's - the most common cause of dementia.  The [National Library of Medicine](https://ghr.nlm.nih.gov/condition/alzheimer-disease#genes) reads it is an inherited gene mutation passed from parent to child. How likely can it pass to grandchildren? My grandfather died of alzheimer's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also like to know what their research is finding to be the best preventive measures for this. The WHO defines it as getting [lost in familiar places](http://www.who.int/mediacentre/factsheets/fs362/en/), as my grandfather used to get lost in our neighborhood where he spent most of his life in the U.S. It is definitely one of the scariest situations in which a family member could be involved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alamo officer held in connection with aggravated assault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First U.S. sugar tax cuts soft drink sales by 10% - while sales in surrounding areas, where no tax was imposed, rose by 6.9%. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newly discovered 'super-Earth' may be the 'most exciting exoplanet' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police officer helps boy tie his tie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservative Student Barred From Own Graduation After Wearing 'ICE' Hat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JSerra student scores perfect on ACT only months after paralyzing injury </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Miami Officer Is Arrested Over Shooting Of Therapist During Standoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you want to be the fishes of the sea?? or the shark the ocean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you want to be the fishes of the sea?? or the shark the ocean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marine who lost a leg in Afghanistan carries American flag while completing Boston Marathon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Marine tries to teach reporter how to make a military-style bed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Portugal, Drug Use Is Treated As A Medical Issue, Not A Crime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Portugal, Drug Use Is Treated As A Medical Issue, Not A Crime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laboratory has served 5,000 Premature babies 1.5 million ounces of donated, processed human breast milk to give them the best chance to survive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ONLY ON FOX: Woman says she finds uninvited man inside home, frying her chicken, drinking vodka </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 police officers arrested for drunk driving in 1 night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children who own pets less likely to suffer anxiety while building cognitive health benefits, study shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children who own pets less likely to suffer anxiety while building cognitive health benefits, study shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Older gentlemen dances salsa with class. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds Pokemon Go players are happier, friendlier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pokemon Go players are happier, friendlier, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Navy SEAL explains what to do if you're attacked by a dog. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama Ends Death Penalty by Judicial Override </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sacramento police officer suspended after video shows him punching jaywalking suspect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to be a Better Phony Navy SEAL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of luck, man. Perhaps there are legal aid organizations that can help with something like that. But sometimes as long as you dot all of your i's, I have heard people get around some tough bureaucracy pretty efficiently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to news reports he's a [licensed engineer](http://www.cnn.com/2017/04/04/us/nyc-subway-rescue/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore cop accused of sexting teen acquitted on Md. charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11 year old twin sister DJs Amira   Kayla practicing to Biggie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously? sorry to hear that. Any chance of getting that expunged from your record?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without exaggeration, that's less than $1 USD in Colombia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> son of a cop and son n law of another cop, here; sadly, from my experience, you are right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dashcam video from 2015 shows Denton sticking the shotgun in and punching it on the suspect who had just been Tased. Another officer appears to stop Denton, but when the suspect  who had a knife  was pulled out, video shows Denton hit him with the gun multiple times. Denton has been acquitted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Owasso Officer Found Not Guilty Of Excessive Force </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Exit Drug: Hospitalizations Caused by Opioid Abuse Drop In States With Legal Cannabis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Con Edison engineer rescues unconscious boy from subway tracks before train roars by. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5-year-old Hoke County student suspended for using stick as gun during recess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Jersey teen gets accepted by all 8 Ivy League schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5-year-old Hoke County student suspended for using stick as gun during recess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Benton elementary teacher suspended after video shows her grabbing, pushing student </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever feel like punching your wife?
Hit the comedy club tonight 
to get some reasons to start a fight
and do it right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The House tentatively approved legislation Tuesday that would ensure Texans have equal insurance coverage for mental and physical health care. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House OKs bill on mental health insurance benefits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miami-Dade police officer accused of beating wife after attending comedy show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miami-Dade police officer accused of beating wife after attending comedy show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Miami-Dade police officer accused of beating wife after attending comedy show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't ten years worth of data, but [beer sales are dropping](http://time.com/money/4592317/legal-marijuana-beer-sales/) somewhat in states where cannabis is legal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 14-year-old Juneau high school student was honored by the governors office today for rescuing a 5-year-old boy he saw fall into a fast-running creek. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about posting a glossary of terms and phrases that can allow people to better understand systems and jargon used by the scientific community? 

I think that would allow people to better consume and learn from the information shared in the AMA's and other postings on the sub. 

I would love to help on something like that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Oliver goes off on Americas most absurd marijuana laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roselle Catholic teacher charged with having sex with student </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roselle Catholic teacher charged with having sex with student </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually; an exit drug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Student Suspended for Challenging Muslim Prof Who Said Jesus Crucifixion Never Happened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Less people get hospitalized for opioid abuse in states where medical cannabis is legal, according to a recent study, published in the journal Drug and Alcohol Dependence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time ever, an American badger is seen burying a whole cow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police acquitted in beating of mail worker who unknowingly gave cop killer directions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers on Thursday filed a bill that would make Delaware the ninth state to legalize marijuana. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers on Thursday filed a bill that would make Delaware the ninth state to legalize marijuana. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former police officer charged with sex assault faces more counts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he's got one of those tiny ant-made cameras, I would feel like rinsing my foot off after stepping on him. 

However, if he's big enough to hold a man-made camera, I would probably feel like hiring him as my nutritionist to find out what made him grow so big.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's for [science](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BKKa_OlSXgQ)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ant trapped in a tiny perfect sphere of water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spinach Leaf Transformed Into Beating Human Heart Tissue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WV Senate committee passes medical marijuana bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WV Senate committee passes medical marijuana bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WV Senate committee passes medical marijuana bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cop fires. A teen dies. Yet six police body cameras somehow miss what happens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cop fires. A teen dies. Yet six police body cameras somehow miss what happens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucky Marine Survives Sniper Headshot By Inches In Afghanistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philadelphia Officer Arrested Over Dog Found in Trash Bag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philadelphia Officer Arrested Over Dog Found in Trash Bag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Take a Selfie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Shocking Truth About Wealth Inequality (MR. FORTHRIGHT Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Springfield Police Department Releases Video of Officer Fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Gay Connecticut Lawmaker Just Introduced a Bill to Ban Gay Conversion Therapy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: 83-year-old man checks out of hospital, steals ambulance - Authorities say Donald Winkler was upset with the quality of care at the hospital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient, 83, Checks Himself Out Of Hospital Then Steals Ambulance To Get Home: Cops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Health Insurance Plan Hits Older People Hardest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Health Insurance Plan Hits Older People Hardest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is how fast it can go from 0-100 when stopping a car. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The videos, taken from the body cameras of Samuel A. Rosario and a second officer, shows the 32-year-old Rosario punching a 19-year-old man at least 11 times while they're on the ground. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The videos, taken from the body cameras of Samuel A. Rosario and a second officer, shows the 32-year-old Rosario punching a 19-year-old man at least 11 times while they're on the ground. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For The First Time Ever The Federal Government Calls Cannabis Medicine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OCC student suspended after filming teacher saying Trump's election was 'an act of terrorism' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OCC student suspended after filming teacher saying Trump's election was 'an act of terrorism' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orange Coast College Teacher Calls Trump's Election "An Act Of Terrorism" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man makes a homemade rolling log mouse trap and catches 11 mice in one night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby Kangaroo Rescued From Dead Mother's Pouch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, that lady is new. I shop at that Rite Aid regularly and know the pharmacists well. I fill my children's prescriptions in that store. It's also located in one of the better suburbish neighborhoods of Queens - Howard Beach; we're mostly all homeowners, and, in comparison to the rest of the city, you don't get a lot of crime in our area. 

Secondly, by her accent, I could tell she is from a non-Hispanic Caribbean island (I grew up with a lot of them). And even if I am wrong, and she is Hispanic that doesn't mean she can't be racist against her own ethnic group. I know a lot of Latinos, blacks, and whites who are racist among each other. 

Thirdly, I am not the victim in this case. She is. She is probably underpaid hence undertrained and has to resort to preconceived notions that she has to follow some one because of his her ethnicity like it's 1970. As a business owner, if she really thought I was suspicious, she could simply watch me through the surveillance cameras; she could proactively prevent me from coming back with a better plan to really shoplift something - potentially when she's not around. This company's headquarters has also contacted me to correct the situation; and as a loyal customer, I doubt this will end favorably for her. 

Sincerely, I wish her the best, and I hope she doesn't get fired, but better trained. As a society, it is truly sad that racism has to reduce our workforce to behave so unproductively. We are a lot better than this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bridgeport cop charged with assault after collison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CT officer accused of dragging man from van, beating him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CT officer accused of dragging man from van, beating him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As humans we have something called peripheral vision, and the ability to notice things to which we're not paying direct attention. I wanted to give her the benefit of the doubt because frankly I don't like playing the race card, but there were other people with hoodies and coats on in the store with lighter skin, yet they weren't profiled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was 30 F outside; I had a cold; hence the hoodie. You could see everybody else had coats in the store. My wife and I were the only dark-skinned people.

Thanks for watching, but take note: Trayvon Martin was identified by his killer as being suspicious, describing him in a hoodie.

EDIT: Being a business owner, I would have preferred she focused on watching me in through the surveillance cameras if I looked suspicious. If I was really shoplifting, I would not do it with her on my back. I would just come back when she's not hawking me. Her racist preconceptions turn her into an inefficient security guard. She is very under trained.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was following me before I even pulled out my camera. All I was doing was picking out items to buy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Tulsi Gabbard Calls for Federal Decriminalization of Marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prison inmates were put in a room with nothing but a camera. I didn't expect them to be so real </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racist Security Guard Follows Latino Around Store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk says 100 of Tesla's Gigafactories will allow the whole world to transition to sustainable energy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Tyson tells Larry Merchant how to knock your opponent out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look under the sofa cushions; it botanically goes by the name of genus loose changus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spring is coming. The trees already have buds in them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up and take my money for whatever the f you're trying to sell me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had me at "daily is not the worst thing." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racist Security Guard Follows Latino Around Store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paging [John McClane](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pyGh6S41EGQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 20:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to kung-fu movies that I would watch after Saturday morning cartoons, the television networks used to also broadcast a Clint Eastwood or other type of western-type movie that I would watch when it was too cold to go outside. I had no problem watching these before-my-time yet great movies. The casting, storyline, videography and other elements broken down in this analysis make movies like these timeless. 

And Clint Eastwood is still kicking ass. Million Dollar Baby, American Sniper; both classics in their own rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chuck Berry does the "duck walk" on Johnny Carson's "The Tonight Show" in 1987 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Tyson presents Boxing's Greatest Knockouts (1988) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Artist Sells Snapchat Nudes As Fine Art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Floyd Mayweather struggles to read a two sentence radio drop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chuck Berry performs "Johnny B Goode" live in 1964 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "great artists steal." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP, Chuck! Its crazy how they suggested that Mr. Berry got the idea for the song through that phone call. Probably one of the little fun fictions that had me watching this movie dozens of times. 

TIL: The anniversary of the release date of Johnny B. Goode is in about two weeks: March 31, 1958.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Michael Jordan says he is NOT the GOAT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fate of the Furious trailer stars an army of autonomous cars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure whether this is an authentic claim; but if its fake, its sad that he would attempt to secure fame at the expense of the memory of one of America's worst tragedies. I am from New York City, and although I didn't know anybody personally who died in the towers, I know people who knew people that died. 

It was a direct attack on our city and country. Although I was not allowed to enter Ground Zero, I never felt more compelled to help out in the rescue efforts as an utterly selfless act than I did on that day, and when I returned a couple of days later. 

My uncle is a firefighter that was assigned to Ground Zero, and he told me he saw body parts; he told me it was the worst thing he had ever seen when I interviewed him for a school writing assignment a couple of years later. There are still first responders who are suffering from severe ailments. 

Thousands of peoples of lives were lost and irreparably damaged as a result. And it was not in retaliation to something that they directly did to anybody. Innocent lives were lost, and it's disgusting if any one should ever seek to fraudulently profit from this mass murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 23:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You can](https://i.imgur.com/qZLeIU8.jpg)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For people who have Windows 10, he dropped a video showing you how to remove the [telemetry](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u1kGMCfb2xw).

Collecting personal data is every tech giant and government's evil master plan. If they don't get you one way, they'll figure out another way. It's great we have outlets like this, so we could all collaborate to maintain privacy.  

Sadly enough, (I may be wrong) I think that our never-ending quest to get the most out of apps, the web, tech for the lowest cost possible has opened the competitive landscape so much that companies are not forced but have been steered into exploring data collection as a monetization play. The human mind is capable of so much, however, so I am sure there are other ways that companies and the government can be sustainable without knowing the width of every ridge along the ring of our buttholes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
