<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 09:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really the knots and where to.  
I have Dyspraxia so I have big trouble with knots anyway, can't even tie laces. 
My main methods would be train or bridge usally but it's a bit indimating.
Things do always get worse, and I'm very self-destructive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's not really a lot I enjoy.  
And it's same shit different day, I'm a joke already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I'm very desperate so I'm considering everything.  
I was going to take 4 times the fatal amount for someone my weight, and I cant get the hang of hanging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 07:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish it was easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 23:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure where I could do that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 23:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what fancy device, and I can't tie knots that well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 23:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna go with a liquid, foul tasting but I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone provide me with links on how ligature strangulation works? (Non-suspension) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can NEVER get it tight enough, it's VERY frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard a small amount is deadly.  
And I'm in the UK, luckily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really know how it works yet, can't really find that much info but according to Wiki it's 0.5ml to every kg of body weight, takes effect within an hour but it takes a while to kill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it feel like to OD on essential oils? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 06:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 06:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or any essential oils. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got a weird method. Whst do you guys think of using Eucalyptus oil to OD on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the fatal amount and I'm planning to take double that, possibly even more then that because I might throw it up. 
I hate vomiting but I'm really desperate. 
Thoughts?
I also want to try to find more info before I try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long do people throw up for after taking an overdose for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we talking hours or untill it kills them!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Effect of Eucalyptus Oil poisoning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What household products can cause chemical burns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 150 feet onto concrete and 250 feet onto water with a 95 percent fatailty rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is has been me the last few days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What song? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2meirl4meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 20:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have BPD.  
Mood swings are getting worse, I wanna cut but parents found out, I wanna pour bleach on my arms and I'm now getting so depressed at times I can't function for a while daily. I'm getting more paranoid in public, and I'm thinking of suicide daily, not just how nice it would be to escape, but how to do it, effectiveness, when ect.  
I can't see my boyfriend for 10 days, last saw him Thursday, going to see him next Sunday, because apparantly he's too ill but he went to work on Friday and he sounded ok-ish, I could go see him but I'm not welcome at his because his Nan is old-fashioned.  
But he's hardly been replying to my texts, but he's still quite active on Facebook?  
So I'm a bit lonely and scared he's cheating.  
I just wanna fucking kill myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys do when your too depressed to do anything, even move and just want to lie in bed for ages? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, Its been like a year I think since I got like this depressed. I have BPD, but this is happening again 
I literlly can't function, I just have to lie there. I give myself a limit of half an hour but it's hell, so was looking for ideas, it's been happening near-daily since Thursday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do any of you know how to get antiemetics in the UK without a prescription? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 15:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can delete if against the rules,I'm just desperate and I can't go on like this.
I don't have any I'D either but I can get one if I need to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't care about anything anymore. Sat on train with short sleeves, haven't done it since Monday but oh well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 12:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 10:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. 
When it comes to in person I hate it.
I haven't texted my boyfriend back in a while,  he knows that I text back within a few minutes. 
I keep splitting on him and this is how our last texting went.
I sent him 5 texts, one of them being this. 
Ok 2 things then I'll actually leave you alone lol suprised you went to work if your this ill 
And ik I'm being a massive bitch atm I'm being difficult af ik I am I'm not meaning to be I wish I wasnt acting like this idk how else to explain it I'm sorry o love you   
Then like 10 mins later he sent this.  
I love you so much you don't have to leave me alone I like talking to you and tbh the only reason I went work is coz is l so I would have money to see you   
It's been a couple hours and I haven't replied.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 09:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to find out how to buy antiemetics in the UK without a prescription </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 08:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. But I also can't sleep due to stress and terrible nightmares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cases of Eucalyptus Oil being used for suicide? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 15:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus if effects, fatally,  how long,  how much ect.
Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 13:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Mum had it untreated untill I was 15, she's in treatment now.  
My childhood from 0-5 was very unstable untill she met my Dad. (Step)  
Got way more stable, very loving but because it was untreated her behaviors got passed down to me, while I got bullied at school, various other trauma, and I think that her running away has put the extreme fear of abandoment on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 13:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True for me. I'm a lazy fuckall who needs to die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 13:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thought this was /r/MadeOfStyrofoam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quite a few. My jeans look baggy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 12:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they should.  
Depends how long, severity, how effective treatment is ect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 12:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was actually meant to be a throwaway, but I just decided to use it for stuff like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 10:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What symptoms?  
As long as it's not throwing up, I think I will be fine.
Also if it's not against the rules, where could I buy them from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you buy the seeds online still? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So how come if humans got low welfare including mental health it's still a life "worth" living? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been a while </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 06:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It happened again last week with the same guy that used to do it to me before. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 09:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same guy I posted about a few weeks ago.
He did it, he fucking did it I can't handle it.
I was trying to ignore the fact it happened.
My boyfriend figured out something was wrong on Tuesday as I was shaking after sex, and got so annoyed over something he usally jokes about, and for the first time I walked out on him. I only walked into the bathroom and came back like 10 mins later after he commented on something I posted on Facebook.    
He kept on asking what was up, untill he went to the bathroom I texted him to tell him I kept running into him and my ex, I know my ex wouldn't do anything physical,  but he does make me regress.
My boyfriend kept asking if anything happened,  I wouldn't give him a straight answer but he wanted to know.  
He said he felt sick, sad and angry.
We can't do some stuff we used to sexually,  I'm finding it really hard looking people in the eye for that long and talking to strangers,  I can't even talk about what happened without completey shutting down, can't talk that easily, cant stop shaking.  
He tried asking some yes and no questions and said I could nod or shake my head, but I can't even do that.  
He wants me to go to College, but it's his word against mine, no proof.  
The thing is, I've been more moody since it happened, untill I told my boyfriend I just feel empty and very apathetic and I don't wanna be here at all, I'm hardly talking, I can't eat that much I'm hardly sleeping cant focus at all and truth be told I feel so sorry for my boyfriend.  
We were talking on the phone about it, I've never heard him get so upset, I felt terrible, I feel terrible that it's affecting him, I'm just so sorry, I'm so fucking sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah ok thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok, what's the ordering like from online?  
What do ask for when they deliver it. as in any ID and is it in inconspicuous packaging? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most harmful thing a person can do to the body that isn't drugs or smoking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How harmful is it?  
Regular or non-regular?  
Effects and will it decrease life span?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My outer arm, when the palm is facing down.  
It just feels better there, inner arm can be a bit sensitive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't get a response here try /r/morbidquestions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 11:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much compared to superficial? 
How did you get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 07:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does, but in the UK only certain documents count, and I might be at College on the day it could arrive when I order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do have my College ID and my bus pass. I don't go to bars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I never cut thst deep. 
How much does it bleed? 
What did you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not using a knife for murder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am haha,  haven't ordered yet but I know it is going to be a craft knife set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw and commented.  
That it is a very unhealthy subreddit and that we have all given up and are hopeless and that we encourage this behavior.  
I commented to clear things up.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't sure what happened when ordering anything that's meant to be over 18, that is what I was asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean why?  
Sorry, bit confused </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely going to be a set of Craft Knives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 18:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would be more satisfying, I'm more about the bleeding then the pain. I'll keep that in mind, I think my moods are getting worse and my thoughts are getting more bad and raced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens when ordering an age-restricted product from eBay? As in, do the postman needs to be shown ID? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 18:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm 21, got my own bank card and still live with my parents.  
I need to order something from eBay, and it's an age-restricted (over 18) but I don't have any ID.  
And how to make it so my parents won't find out what is it?  
I know they'll find out, but it's near Christmas so I'm going to pass it off as that, but I do not want the postman telling them, and I'm at College 5 days a week. Any help is appreciated, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to go deeper.
I usally do some every few days, and on the day I do its usally a couple of times. Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 15:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait really?
How are they compared to deep cuts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New over old. 2 weeks I think vs over a year. Made sure to avoid any recent SH in this pic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 14:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New scars over old scars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 14:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bit blurry before shower with my small amount per usual </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 13:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 12:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Neo, but he left :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 12:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I saw this before I'm very active atm D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I did some more colouring on the page I uploaded a while ago to stop my thoughts from going round and round. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 22:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 21:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would degrading the blood vessels do and how painful would it be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 21:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to go through stages of thinking about stuff like this and I like to know this stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be the effects of injecting bleach into the bloodstream? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also how much would be fatal and what would happen in your body and how long will it take? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would I be able to find a list of self-induced illnesses online?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks awesome haha, I was looking at them and it just came to me :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the anyway someone could cause in themselves a disease or illness? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything really, fatal or non, I'm just interested if there's any way someone could make themselves like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily I didn't have to as my Mum had it but she got treatment for it and is now mostly stable,  but I'm the Quiet type where she wasn't. 
The don't understand some of the stuff is different to her as it is to me, and my sister doesn't understand it at all 
My boyfriend tries to and he is very supportive,  but he does get fed up of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I has tiger stripes :3 (Pic of day old cuts but I thought it looked cool haha sorry if not allowed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My arms look like tiger stripes :3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 10:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm part of that subreddit.  
It's a safe place to discuss suicide and stuff relating to it without being judged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could do but my arm is already cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same! I like the way it looks the most, hence the pictures. I love the blood the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could, and I've been tempted to not put the plaster wrappers in the bin too, but I would hate to get caught, I don't tend to bleed a lot anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 22:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's groupme?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 19:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what forums and that's what I meant by random stuff :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I need people to talk to when I'm feeling like I don't matter to anyone or when I feel a bit lonely. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing is I have no idea where to find these, and I prefer to be via messages anyway.  
Like people to talk to about random stuff, or when I'm not feeling right. I just don't matter enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of course I did it again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found that, I prefer it when it rubs but I don't tend to drink that much and my blade tends to get dull quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 14:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just use sharpners blades.
I would like to get a different sort, so I'm tempted to order some to my house as it's near Christmas,  but I would not want my family to find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 14:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, got terrible memory and organisational skills and it can make me jumpy and nervous, combined with BPD, makes it seem like I'm just being difficult for the sake of it and just being moody over nothing but I have real trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My arm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I should smear my blood on the bathroom walls at College to freak everyone out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 12:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bit blurry and I want to go deeper so it will bleed more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 12:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 07:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to ask, Mastodon fan? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was but I started on my arms again, but of a hassle. Luckily it's winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've considered getting a tatoo before, but I always come back to cutting, so I ain't sure if it's a good idea for me, but if your confident in you abilty not to do it again, go for it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it's cold here again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm only doing them small at the moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True this. I am not equipped for life, I can't do anything right, all I do is fuck up. This is who I am until I die, no hope left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a small amount </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 13:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 12:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it really funny, I joke about all sorts. 
I joke about being raped and stuff I've actually been through because it makes them less painful and normalizes them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21, and I do not know what will happen if I do or don't go through with my refeerrel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diagrams of places where not to cut?
Do you mean don't cut deep there or not at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am an idiot, I'm scared the Doctor will see my cuts and I can't avoid it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to go to the Doctors tommorow, to get the Implant. I have some cuts in my arms ranging from a couple weeks old to around 3-4 days.
Except I did it today without thinking but they are superficial. FUCK.
I dont wanna go back to therapy  and I have no idea what they are going to say, not looking forward to this one bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only light scratches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 12:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like documenting them and looking back on them I suppose, they look nice to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 11:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the only one is actually /r/selfharmpics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 11:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty much everything haa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GUYS I MIGHT HAVE TO DELETE THIS ACCOUNT BECAUSE MY BF KNOWS MY ACC BUT I DON'T WANT TO IT'S A MASSIVE URGENCE I'VE HAD THIS 3 YEARS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 10:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically me and my boyfriend was messing around but he decided to go onto my reddit app and he "accidently" saw my reddit account name and he said that he's not going to look cause he knows he won't like what he sees but GUYS my post history is fucked i'm fucked it makes me look more fucked then I am what the fuck do i dooooo D:
I don't wanna start over and there's a couple of subreddits that are suscriber only so how the fuck am i gonna get back   
he's said he's been curious about this before but he knows the sorta stuff i post and he said it would really upset him but when he's curios he usally won't stop wondering but I like to think that i can trust him but I''m complety FUCKED.  
apparently he forgot it too but he has good memory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few before I returned home from College </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 09:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to do to the Doctors to get the Implant, with fresh cuts on my arm.
I'm really not looking forward to it because I'm not sure what's going to be said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So have I, I was wondering how.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 21:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh really? 
They seemed like they would be really hard to break open, how'd you do it?
You do for stuff like scapels or craft knives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 14:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is mine:  
subreddit	post	comment  
morbidquestions	268	65  
SanctionedSuicide	173	143  
selfharmpics	198	11  
BPD	137	36  
MadeOfStyrofoam	86	75  
AskReddit	3	68  
SuicideWatch	1	48  
ptsd	19	27  
selfharm	7	33  
depression	2	24  
mentalhealth	1	21  
raisedbynarcissists	1	11  
electricians	4	3  
dpdr	1	3  
offmychest	1	2  
satanism	1	2  
AskDocs	2	0  
HorriblyDepressing	1	2  
bodymods	3	-1
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do self-harmers cut deeper then superfical? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 11:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like how, what tools they use?  
And if they don't have any ID how do they get them?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 11:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same! My boyfriend says I need to grow a backbone and stand up for myself. I hardly ever argue, unless I'm extremely annoyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 11:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usally if I'm angry or frustrated I'd do it if I can't cut at that moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've hidden my diagnosis.
The only people which know is the immediate family I live with, my sister's boyfriend and mine. The only one that knows how much it's really affecting me is my boyfriend, but it's obvious I get mood swings at College.
They just ask if everything's alright and tend to talk about random stuff to get me distracted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am posting more frequently these days. Thank you, hope you feel better soon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 14:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first 3 I like, only heard a couple of Obituary and Judas Priest I ain't too fond off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure to be honest, I'm just fed up with life and stress and thus is how I deal with it, I am posting in this sub near-daily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 07:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://lostallhope.com/suicide-methods/statistics-most-lethal-methods
This has each method ranked by lethality, time and agony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 11:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mental health is so bad again. My family has realised something is up, and they want me to go Doctors, something my boyfriend has been saying to me for months.
I can't handle this, I'm cutting myself again and all I want to do is kill myself. I hate this so fucking much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a few </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 11:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 11:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's /r/MadeOfStyrofoam which I'm a frequent at, but it is sometimes memes but I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best way to fatally stab someone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in position, knife, force ect.
Bonus points if self-inflicted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck it's not a competition 
Not gonna lie I do wish I had some of the cuts on /r/selfharmpics just because they look awesome and fun to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alrighty :3   
Eletrical plug/socket   
Batteries  
Lava Lamp   
Rubber bands  
I don't see why you have to omit stuff :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
