<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6651</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [When you realize you bought the NBA equivalent of RadioShack in 2012](http://m.imgur.com/gallery/kCllp) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you realize you bought the NBA equivalent of RadioShack in 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Jerami Grant is "Massage Room." Dude has excellent hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And that, kids, is the story of how the Clippers remained mediocre and never made it past the second round." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still triggered by purple/gold because 81?

let it go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *sauces </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to go to bed, CP3 pissing me tf off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, should say "in the NBA" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I hate the tactic, wouldn't Hack-a-Jordan make sense for the next couple minutes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when the weed hits you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.landofbasketball.com/all_time_leaders/points_per_game_single_playoffs.htm

doesn't compute FG% for us but lists FGM and FGA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just drafted by the Jazz in 2k as a PG, so I'm fucking scouting tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West at 46.3  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Westbrook's 37.4 ppg is the 7th highest playoff scoring average of All-Time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but Billy Donovan just is not cut out for this job. How do you spend your second to last TO with over 7 minutes left in the 4th?!?

EDIT: Even if Russ was the one that called it, the guy has been completely inept. Poor clock management, poor rotations, trying to build Roberson's "confidence" in the playoffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jimmy Neutron Syndrome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it just me or is Harlan referring to Harden as "James" more often of late? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished O'Rourke's "On the Wealth of Nations," and the point that I've gleaned and researched is that Adam Smith -- a much smarter man than I (or Trump, for that matter) -- was emphatically opposed to Mercantilism, which is exactly what isolated spending and production means. This isn't anything new, either. Smith published "The Wealth of Nations" over 200 years ago, and it still has merit today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and the driest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then why not say the '90s too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want the Thunder to dominate for 47 minutes and walk off the floor a minute early just to spite Reggie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...the Celtics and Lakers never met in the '70s fam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And her hairdresser's name? Sharon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respect the hell out of Russell, but you put any of the other four guys on the '60s Celtics and tell them to focus on defense and rebounds, they still win most of those titles.

Conversely, there's no way the '67 Sixers, '94-'95 Rockets, or three-peat Lakers win their titles relying on Bill to dominate in the post offensively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the WORST lineup you can make out of former or current All-Stars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are all at their All-Star level of talent, so no 2004/2013 Lakers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they'll let Julius clone himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't even bother. According to r/NBA we're going to be bad for the next decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andy crawled to freedom through five-hundred yards of shit smelling foulness I can't even imagine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg yes, just saw Neverender in Hollywood and died during every song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like a pearl-clutching Victorian fainting on a couch. "How ever could one say such a thing?"

I'm weak, lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol Coheed   Cambria is my favorite band and all the music is part of the same story...but listening to them in order still doesn't make it any more coherent, especially not with lyrics like:

Librarian find me the pole
The one that kicks your head in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If there were an unwholesome trinity that included Bill Cosby and Jared Fogle, who would complete the trinity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually curious now...if each season represented a different LeBron, what would be the ideal 5 seasons of LeBron to play together? 

I'm thinking something along the lines of 2006, 2009, 2010, 2012, 2013. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pat Riley is definitely a tits guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7:30 

50 SHOTS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now go to your room and don't come out until you think about what I'VE done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read that first as Indians and I was like yeah 3-1 kinda sucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The salsa is pathetic but I like the way they cook the chicken. As for donuts, they just brought Krispy Kreme back to my hometown! Haven't been by yet, though, because it's always packed...even at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assuming the W's hang on in the 4th, it'll only be their second series sweep since Curry was drafted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately I stopped drinking soda years ago, and the fries need to be perfect for me to consider ordering because I normally won't finish them. Green Burrito is my weakness; Big Carl + Southwest Chicken Soft Taco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE think Calderon kinda looks like a Spanish Dominic Monaghan from LOTR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say they're great, but 50 wins is nothing to sneeze at. Pretty far from "awful" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is that Hakeem doesn't get to play the Spurs or Magic if Elie misses that shot, so you shouldn't be dissing such an integral supporting cast that played their asses off for him.

If the Finals is all you care about then how can you say MJ doesn't come close? 1993 he averaged 41 FUCKING POINTS A GAME. You're completely contradicting yourself as to what makes a "run" impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lakers were also awful

lmao, such a bad team that they won 50 games...scrubs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost as if this is a team sport and his fellow Rockets deserve some credit for winning (and if you actually cared to research your beloved run you would have mentioned Mario Elie's GW in the WCSF game 7, without which Hakeem would have gone home with nothing). 

Furthermore, Hakeem didn't have a HoF center guarding him every round, which is why the Suns and Jazz didn't have an answer for him. Who cares if Stockton or Johnson were on the other team, those guys weren't guarding Hakeem.

And if we're going based on opponent record, Kobe and Shaq in 2001 are more impressive than LeBron last year since the Cavs played garbage opponents all three rounds before the Finals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wilt Chamberlain - the league didn't track blocks or steals so pick any year

Rick Barry - 1967

Michael Jordan - pick any year 1991-1993

Kareem - 1971

Larry Bird - 1986

Shaq - 2001

Duncan -  2003

Bill Walton - 1977

Magic - 1987

Dirk - 2011

EDIT: I would also say LeBron - 2013 was more impressive considering the Pacers were way tougher to beat than the Raptors in 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only one who comes close

This makes you sound really ignorant considering that's over 60 years of basketball to be dismissing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You couldn't be more incorrect. Seasons are ALWAYS referred to based on the year the Finals occurred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely disagree. Look at baseball. Babe Ruth played almost 100 years ago but people still worship him because the stuff he did was mythical, just like Jordan. And it's not like MJ is glorified by rumors or legends like Wilt's 100. We still have video evidence for MJ's accomplishments which are mind-boggling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still says "rookie year" in the body, and you won't be able to edit the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked my dad recently and he still thinks the Bulls would have beaten the Rockets regardless of regular season meetings. Obviously Hakeem would have given Longley fits, but Maxwell and Horry had their hands full with Jordan and Pippen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was disappointed and disgusted, but I remember thinking "he's taking that jersey off for the last time" when he was leaving the floor in game 6 against the C's, so I wasn't entirely surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to recycle it for r/WritingPrompts! If you're gilded though I demand due recompense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're stranded alone in the middle of the desert, YOU are the largest body of water in your immediate vicinity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found Slender Man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you combine John Donne's "For Whom the Bell Tolls" with "The Polar Express," the narrator's story becomes a lot more grim and sinister. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Never send to know for whom the bells tolls; it tolls for thee."

"Though I've grown old the bell still rings for me, as it does for all who truly believe." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The force will be with you...always. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing on earth was going to stop Kobe and the Lakers from making the Finals in 2009 after losing to the Celtics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about in ice skates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the best stories behind how players chose their jersey #'s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E.g. MJ and his brother, Kobe adding his ABCD camp numbers together, Arenas and 0 minutes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nash/Stoudemire was way more comparable to Stockton/Malone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Brick Anderson](http://ballislife.com/revisiting-nick-andersons-4-missed-free-throws-at-the-end-of-gm1-of-the-95-finals/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much fun do you have in a blue oyster cult? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mahcus aint gonna be rooked. Maybe knighted but not rooked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ~~This guy coached his~~ **Durant and Westbrook carried their** team past Pop and the Spurs. Smdh.

FTFY

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will gladly contribute to a Kickstarter to reimburse someone like Russ if he goes off on the refs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone tell which ref that is on the right sideline? He's looking right at Harden the entire time. There has GOT to be some accountability or some sort of reprimand from the league. This is blatant incompetence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **APPLES AND ORANGES** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billy Donovan is overrated. Won 2 chips in college because he had three future lottery picks in Horford, Noah, and Brewer. Blew a 3-1 lead last year, and squandered any chance of winning this game by leaving Roberson in to brick FT's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billy Donovan is making D'Antoni look like Red Auerbach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apples and oranges </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practicing incorrect technique and fundamentals isn't going to make you better. He has an NBA pedigree and access to top-tier coaching that the average person doesn't. Not to mention, he gets paid millions of dollars to shoot hundreds of shots every single day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D-Rose playing for the Bulls could be pretty good. They might even make it to the ECF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kyrie's GW on Christmas is the difference between Cavs being .500 and .500 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Through four games in the playoffs, Manu Ginobili is scoreless on 0-15 shooting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck it. If Russ can get a triple-double in one half, he might as well go for a triple-double in the second half too. 40/20/20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We **don't** assume

Reading is hard. 

And btw, the Crusades were a real thing. Christians have committed just as many atrocities over the centuries as any other religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 1995 Magic were ranked 1st in the league offensively. The 2017 Pacers were ranked 15th offensively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It bothers me how people associate "Christian" with a positive connotation that assumes goodwill and benevolence. We don't assume that all Muslims, Jewish, and Catholic people are good people just because of the specific sect of religion they prescribe to. Seems really self-righteous to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has always amazed me how well Russ finishes despite going a million miles an hour in transition. Impeccable body control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three things:

1. BRef has playoff assists stats pre-1984 so this is just plain incorrect.

2. Kobe was a SG and pretty damn good at passing anyways, unlike Kyrie.

3. Who the fuck is Kurtenbach? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Mike Bibby was still in the league </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why did you put quotes around I'm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2013 ECF feels like a long time ago now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to see a clip of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But did he play in sandals while eating a potato and reciting the Magna Carta in Spanish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol casual fans are his biggest supporters. I'm talking the pre-teens who only know the names LeBron and Curry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inb4 4-D chess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely you mean top-three pick? I don't think it'll be the end of the world if we have to settle for someone like Monk or Jackson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming we traded D'Lo in scenario 1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOAT em LeGet

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see it now. Game 4 of the NBA Finals, W's getting ready to sweep the Bulls. Dray already has 11pts/4reb/5ass/6blks/5stls. Chicago is down by 27 and Carter-Williams puts up a desperation three with three seconds left. The ball caroms of the rim right towards Green, who raises his hands to the sky. As the ball flies right towards him, he drops eight fingers and flips off the nearest camera with both hands. The ball flies right between his outstretched arms like Vinatieri in the SuperBowl as the buzzer sounds, and r/NBA collectively implodes out of frustration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off with the "exceptional defense." Shumpert was guarding PG 90% of the last few games. There's no one else on the Pacers to worry about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Warriors are the best team in the NBA. I'm not surprised in the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trick question. Always go with Emerald because dragon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That bread is so white it looks like snow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy eats lettuce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consensus best pg in east. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to slow this video down? He's moving so fast all I see is a red/blue blur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was literally the fastest basketball play I've ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If John Wall played bass for Led Zeppelin...he'd be John Wall Jones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Perry Jones and Quincy Miller were going to be All-Stars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spooky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I never had a problem with that hype party...Miami was stoked and wanted to celebrate. But once he made that comment it came off as really obnoxious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
