<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     *holds up spork* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gets really annoying in certain moments

"Oh, shoot, how annoying! This person is legitimately upset with me because I broke their personal space and fucking bit them. How annoying for me, personally, and not at all annoying for the person **I fucking bit**"

 but its still done as affectionate

Learn to be affectionate in other ways. Jesus Christ.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, bullshit. Just don't bite people.

Reminds me of The Office, where Michael has to figure out which of his employees is gay so he doesn't make any gay jokes towards them. Dwight says "Well why don't you treat everyone like they're gay?"

Other people can playfully punch each other and everyone is fine

No, actually. Most people don't like being punched.

but if I do it I ~~accidentally~~ **intentionally** hurt someone.

Stop minimalizing your bad behavior.

A bite is my version of a kiss on the cheek. 

Doesn't a kiss, or a bite, or any physical interaction require an idea of consent? 

Don't be a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 17:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actual test is a couple hours at most. Days or weeks happen because of backlog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She is happy and giggly, or fuming and talking about divorce.

So she's a wonderful human being, until the intentional ignorance you have towards your mother comes up. She's a saint, and you're a dick. What are the huge majority of these 150 comments siding with your wife?

Pull your head out of your ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it does. Just once, but still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 19:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used it last Friday: I love it. Very user friendly, cuts down on the analysis time considerably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 12:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 17:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like one please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 14:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spooky dishes! 

Doot doot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 14:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be nice if you included this in your OP. 

^but ^thanks ^for ^playing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 14:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Best case* scenario, what do you want out of this? To hurt your ex? To help your daughter? Whats the end game?

Because if I were your daughter, this entire fucking episode would irreparably harm our relationship. Court orders be damned, I'd want nothing to do with you. 

So best of luck to you, alienating your entire fucking family because you're caught up with a doctor helping your child. You're disgusting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Wouldn't something like that be covered by health insurance?

YES, absolutely. My sister has to have daily enemas, and one of the ingredients is corn syrup. My mom bulk-buys corn syrup (3-figure amount of bottles) every fall when it's cheapest, and she uses their flex-spending card for it.

You could probably get a lot covered by insurance; the special deoderant, the fiber you take every day, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 22:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We use SOFT, I like it.

We have middleware for our Sysmex called WAM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 03:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They posted [2k retweets then blizzard is back up](https://twitter.com/PoodleCorp/status/777656533156896768), literally the minute after it did, I could log in to WoW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 12:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been here 3.5 years, no car yet. Bus every morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't see how we can jump to her being "scared" because she wrote a letter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 22:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the best way to farm invasions? Right now I'll complete one and fly to the next closest, its faster than quests, but not super fast.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time playing, I have a lvl 72 paladin. Should I use my lvl 100 boost on her, or grind up to 100 and use it on another character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 22:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can connect to my 5ghz wifi network, but not my 2.4ghz </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 01:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello!

I have a Belkin N600DB Wireless Router. I've just moved it one floor below my computer, but proximity wise it's maybe 15 feet away. My computer can see both networks, but will not connect to the 2.4ghz. The 2.4 appears to have full bars on Windows 10 Network Settings, but as soon as I attempt to connect it fails or has no bars.

If I walk into a room on the other side of the router (computer - router/wall - room) I have a fantastic 2.4ghz signal.

Thoughts? I don't know that it really matters, since the 5ghz is giving me 30Mbps (exactly what I pay for).

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What bug eggs are these? Found on a stove top. Fruit flies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 01:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 23:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just here to get banned from shitty subreddits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 21:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. It also doesn't play .gifv from imgur. Stock Nexus 5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 04:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is getting more off-topic, but I'd like to chime in as an exmormon:

Mormons don't believe that they are forcing their beliefs on anyone. Yes, the do baptisms and other religious ordinances for dead people, but Mormons believe that the dead person has the *choice* to accept the ordinance in the afterlife. They believe that without the soul of the person making the conscious choice, then the ordinance counts for nothing. Mormons think they're just giving dead people more options in the afterlife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [House centipede larvae?](https://www.google.com/search?q=house+centipede safe=off biw=1920 bih=905 source=lnms sa=X ved=0ahUKEwid8qnX7fbNAhVD7yYKHdnSCPoQ_AUIBygA dpr=1)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't have a magnifying glass, but it looked hairy? Hard to see. It also seemed like it had more than six legs, but it might have just been the hairiness of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MD] On a piece of luggage in a plastic bag in a cardboard box. Very small, ~4mm maybe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 03:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, given that I only took half a day off work based on the old plan, and at this point have 0 opportunity to change that, I can't possibly drive for 4 hours round trip and spend any time with my daughter.

Plus two hours for a movie. Did you read the actual post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are you just going to insult anyone who doesn't agree with your ideals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your reason was valid but hers wasn't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 16:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then, no, prophets don't have power over what they teach.

Like we don't have power over how the Sun operates?

But we can avoid the Sun. We can mitigate it's effects. 

Also, the Sun is, you know, **real**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 16:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand your argument.

Yes, sunlight can cause skin cancer. We actively take steps to help mitigate skin cancer. We should wear long sleeves, apply sunscreen, and avoid the sun during the peak part of the day. You seem to advocate for protection from the sun.

Yes, of course suicide is a mental health problem. However, mental health problems can be exacerbated by outside influences. One of these outside influences appears to be the teachings of the LDS church.

How should we go about helping to mitigate potential causes of suicide? In particular, the teachings of the LDS church?

Simple: We should avoid the LDS church. We should ignore it's teachings, avoid peak LDS teaching times (Conferences, church on Sunday, etc.) We should actively seek to support and love all fellow human beings.

You should be advocating for protection from the Gospel, /u/bhroberts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 18:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can't blame your parents after this for not knowing how much it you want them there.

Right, because the parents will be *so surprised* that their **15** year old son needs support when he's been in the hospital for **+3** days.

They are shit parents, and it's shitty of you to shift the blame on to OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 17:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Showing my house" doesn't mean I'm showing my house interesting things. Reread who you replied to, this time looking at the context clues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 16:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh, that makes more sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 15:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a treatsie?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 14:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ETA

Estimated time of arrival? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't even need a urologist. Any doctor can order that test. Go to your GP, or to a clinic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who tests semen, this is correct. Spin down, put under scope, then yes/no. Super easy, takes 10 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do sperm tests. That's some crazy-ass turn around time. From the time I get a semen sample, I can give results in ~45 minutes. Two hours if it's a poor sample (low sperm count, super viscous, etc). Since you are just looking for the *presence* of sperm, literally all they have to do is centrifuge it and place it on a scope. "Sperm = yes or no". 

Call around. Your current healthcare place sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 15:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going on my honeymoon for 2.5 weeks, won't be able to do any lifting. I'll still do mobility. I've been on a -500 Cal cut. My plan is to eat a little above maintenance (+150) to preserve muscle.

Good plan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 16:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, -4 is the Reddit default to hide comments. You can change it in your preferences setting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 18:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and handle myself thanks.

Oh, but by all means, get your current SO to argue with your ex on speakerphone.

Yep, you got it, OP. You handle yourself super well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 16:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe I find the extrapolation of 30lbs to "morbidly" obese idiotic?

So you wouldn't, then. Man, that's awfully shallow of you. Why wouldn't you date someone fat? They have a lovely personality, and they're so kind and loving! You're super shallow.

You wouldn't date someone significantly shorter than you? That's even more shallow than not wanting to date someone who's fat! At least the fat person can control their weight. The short guy has no control. You're super shallow. If you could just get past the height, you'd see he's a really great guy!

If you need to take your point to extremes to make it, you don't have one.

If you don't understand [hyperbole](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hyperbole), maybe read up a bit before getting in petty arguments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 16:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't answer my question. Can I take your avoidance as admitting that you wouldn't date someone who was morbidly obese or 8 inches shorter than you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, he's totally an asshole. That doesn't mean she has to propagate the drama, though. It's possible to politely and succinctly answer people who ask why they broke up. She didn't do that, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two inches isn't significant. What about 8 inches?

Would you date someone morbidly obese? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you date someone significantly shorter than you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I just blocked him and moved on.

No you didn't. You kept him on facebook and kept his number in your phone. You got in a yelling match with him, months after breaking up! 

How much do you think Shane bad mouthed me after the breakup.

**It doesn't matter**. You should not care. Him doing that makes him look like an ass. Anyone who is your friend would see through whatever bullshit he is spouting. Anyone who believes him isn't your friend, and so why do you care?

Also Tom told me to put him on speakerphone and he had my back. 

So Tom also likes drama! Congratulations on finding a compatible partner.

I don't have to stay mum on the subject.

You also don't have to rant to one of Tom's friends. You can be the mature one here, although from your interactions here, obviously that will be difficult for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I didn't go around telling other people what he said about Shane did I?

JFC, how do you think that any information leaks out ever? If you actually wanted to avoid the drama, you wouldn't have ranted for 5 minutes. If you really wanted to avoid the drama, you wouldn't put your current SO on the phone with your **ex**. If I was dating someone who was so obviously still hung up on what her ex thought of her, I'd break up with them.

If you didn't want drama, you wouldn't have gotten involved at all on facebook. If you didn't want drama, you wouldn't be here, arguing with everyone who dares to not see things your way.

Tom won't break up with you because you're fat, Tom will break up with you because you cause and seek drama.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't see that as a legitimate reason to dump someone.

There's literally no such thing as a "legitimate" reason to dump someone. If they don't make you happy and fulfilled, for *whatever* reason, then break up!

Would you date someone a foot shorter than you? What if they were not intelligent? What if they were living below the poverty line?

Everyone has things they're looking for in a partner. If you don't fit it for whatever reason, then that's reason enough to break up. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, the drama from your OP and life are definitely of your own making. Reassess how you interact with other people, even if you don't like them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's shallow to dump someone over their weight.

Why? If you're not compatible with someone on an emotional or *physical* level, then break it off! Sex is a huge part of any healthy relationship, and if someone isn't attracted to their SO because of weight, then they should break it off.

I had no idea the the acquaintance would go run his mouth like that

Like when you ran your mouth for 5 minutes?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 18:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting married in 8 days!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 21:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which station? X96? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 20:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your first paragraph has a lot of clich filler. OP had a specific question that's been completely dodged, what is the *X* that only the prophet can do?

He leads it through a prophet.

How has Monson lead the church recently? What revelations have come out recently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 14:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish the rules were numbered so I didn't have to count down to #10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 16:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M E T A

E

T

A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 15:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> judging people's children based on a couple of comments.

You're in **/r/relationships.** What do you think every post is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
