<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1156</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cummings, the ranking member of the House Oversight Committee, noted that Trump fired his former national security adviser, retired Lt. Gen. Michael Flynn, weeks after he learned that Flynn had misled Vice President Pence about phone conversations with the Russian ambassador over U.S. sanctions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cummings: Russia probe a fight for the soul of our democracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey has become an almost equally divisive figure for Republicans and Democrats for his impact on the 2016 elections. His revelation that the FBI was examining additional emails from Hillary Clinton that were discovered on disgraced former Rep. Anthony Weiner's computer, has led Democrats -- including Clinton herself -- to say it cost them the White House.
"I was on the way to winning until a combination of Jim Comey's letter on October 28 and Russian WikiLeaks raised doubts in the minds of people who were inclined to vote for me and got scared off," the 2016 Democratic presidential nominee said Tuesday in an interview conducted by CNN's Christiane Amanpour at the Women for Women International summit in New York.
Senate Democrats say the plan to grill the FBI chief about his decision and his timing.
"The most important investigation the FBI is currently conducting is into Russia's interference in our last presidential election," Sen. Chris Coons, a Delaware Democrat on the Senate judiciary committee, told CNN Tuesday. "This isn't just about understanding Russian interference and potential coordination of some kind with the Trump campaign. This is about defending our next election as well."
But Comey's public announcement during the March House Intelligence Committee hearing that the FBI has been investigating possible coordination between the Trump campaign and Russian operatives since last July sparked the anger of Trump and his allies.
Sen. Richard Blumenthal, a Connecticut Democrat on the judiciary committee, said he and others also plan to grill Comey on why he announced that the FBI was looking again at Clinton's emails -- just days before the election.
"The American people really deserve answers about why he did release his comments and letter, and I think he may want to be more forthcoming and he may want to use this forum as an opportunity to tell the American people his side of the story."
Meanwhile, Sen. Lindsey Graham, who is leading his own investigation into Russia's interference in the election, said he still wants Comey to answer whether the FBI issued any warrants against the Trump campaign -- a question he asked months ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FBI Director James Comey will testify today on Capitol Hill in a Senate oversight committee hearing on what the FBI knows about a 2015 terrorist attack in Garland, Texas. However, the hearing is expected to turn to the topic of Russia's involvement in the 2016 election and Hillary Clinton.

Comey has become an almost equally divisive figure for Republicans and Democrats for his impact on the 2016 elections
Clinton yesterday blamed Comey's letter on Oct. 28 about her emails for her loss in the 2016 election, saying "If the election had been on Oct. 27, I would be your president."
Senate Democrats say the plan to grill the FBI chief about his decision and his timing of that letter.
GOP Sen. Lindsey Graham said he still wants Comey to answer whether the FBI issued any warrants against the Trump campaign.
And don't forget: Last time Comey was on the stand, he revealed big news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The room is already packed for the Comey testimony
Packed house waiting on #ComeyHearing pic.twitter.com/DwqAJo2Rim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey testifies at Senate hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said the result of the election interference was now influencing, I would say, legislative process today. Thats wildly successful.

Rogers spoke alongside former Director of National Intelligence James Clapper, who is scheduled to testify before Congress about Russias meddling next week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former House intel chairman: Russian election interference was 'wildly successful' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I unintentionally, incorrectly said the vehicle was backing down the road," Haber said Monday. "According to the video, the vehicle was moving forward as the officer approached."

Haber added, "After reviewing the video, I dont believe that [the shooting] met our core values."

In an updated press release this evening, police clarified that the vehicle was initially backing down the street, "and despite multiple verbal commands from the officer, the vehicle continued to reverse, backing into the main roadway."

The press release continued: "The vehicle then pulled forward as the officer continued to approach the vehicle giving verbal commands. The vehicle continued on the main roadway driving away from the officer." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I was on the way to winning until a combination of Jim Comey's letter on October 28 and Russian WikiLeaks raised doubts in the minds of people who were inclined to vote for me and got scared off," the 2016 Democratic presidential nominee said Tuesday in an interview conducted by CNN's Christiane Amanpour at the Women for Women International summit in New York. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Comey is scheduled to testify at a Senate panel on Wednesday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least four congressional committees are investigating Russian meddling into the election </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FBI Director Comey was the best thing that ever happened to Hillary Clinton in that he gave her a free pass for many bad deeds! The phony......Trump/Russia story was an excuse used by the Democrats as justification for losing the election. Perhaps Trump just ran a great campaign?" President Donald Trump said in a pair of tweets Tuesday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Democrats ready Clinton inquiry, Russia questions for Comey hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While Trump defenders argue that there is nothing unusual about a new president of one party moving in a sharply different direction from his predecessor, voices within the Obama camp characterize the Trump approach as petty, especially in relation to the Let Girls Learn initiative and the school meal standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THE MEMO: Trump seeks to wipe away the Obama brand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hamas leader says new document has provided conditions for change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hamas leader issues direct plea to Trump to seize 'historic opportunity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those comments from one of the Democrats most powerful and high-profile women come at a moment of opportunity and struggle within the party. It has been shut out of power in Washington, controlling neither house of Congress or the White House, and whose ranks have been decimated at the state and local level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pelosi: Democratic candidates should not be forced to toe party line on abortion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's stance on the procedure has shifted over the years. While he once identified as pro-abortion rights, he vehemently opposed abortion during his presidential campaign and said he would defund Planned Parenthood if elected.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Planned Parenthood cuts will come 'at the appropriate time' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama wrote on Twitter.

Well said, Jimmy. That's exactly why we fought so hard for the ACA, and why we need to protect it for kids like Billy. And congratulations! https://t.co/77F8rZrD3P

 Barack Obama (@BarackObama) May 2, 2017 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama responds to Jimmy Kimmel's healthcare plea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 54-year-old man, identified only as Daniel M., was arrested on Friday. His lawyer told a Swiss newspaper he was suspected of trying to find out how German states have obtained CDs containing details of secret Swiss bank accounts set up by Germans to evade tax.

The man was detained in Frankfurt, and officers from Germany's federal criminal police carried out searches at several addresses in the region. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swiss spy agency defends practices after German arrest in tax case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Best Goals Ever Scored In Champions League || Episode No.1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kelly, 46, left Fox News in January after being the highest-rated female host in cable news in prime time for three years. She turned down a $100 million offer to stay with the network.
 
The wife and mother of three young children cited a preference to be home with her family after school and in the evening. Kelly reportedly took millions less to go to NBC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBC's Megyn Kelly to interview Putin in Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK PM May plays up 'bloody difficult woman' image after Juncker dinner reports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kimmel noted on his Monday show that before ObamaCare went into effect, people born with a congenital heart condition like his son might have been turned away from getting health insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem highlights emotional Kimmel monologue on House floor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Kremlin has dismissed the claim as "strange", while an independent expert referred to it as an act of "political warfare".

Viktor Baranetz, a former colonel and defence ministry spokesman, toldKomsomolskaya PravdaRussia was quietly 'seeding' the US shoreline with nuclear 'mole' missiles".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia has hidden nuclear bombs ready to detonate along US coastline, says former Kremlin spokesman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the video, an unmasked young militant warns that the Hisba will punish dissenters according to its interpretation of Islam. Enforcers are shown hitting one man with plastic tubing and beheading two elderly adherents of Sufi Islam, accusing them of sorcery and apostasy. Reuters could not verify the authenticity of the video, which has since been removed from the internet.

Egypts military spokesman declined to comment on the incidents in North Sinai, the thinly populated but strategic peninsula between the Suez Canal, Israel and Gaza where a legacy of government neglect has created fertile ground for radicalisation among disenfranchised locals. A security source downplayed concerns that the militants were capable of spreading the kind of sectarian violence that has torn apart Iraq.

They are trying to have an impact, and we are not saying we have completely eradicated them, but they are weak, he said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State seeks to impose religious rules in Egypt's North Sinai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ABCs Jimmy Kimmel has, in the past, been willing to engage in politics in a sincere way. But its exceptionally rare for a late-night host to offer the depth of emotion that Kimmel displayed Monday night, a natural function of how deeply the issue affects him. There are few more sympathetic characters in the human imagination than sick children; Kimmels personal story makes this exploration of the idea even more affecting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The simplified choice for moderate Republicans: Jimmy Kimmel or Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ossoff, Handel in dead heat in Ga. race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue of sanctions is likely to be high on the agenda. Merkel has openly backed the European Union's decision to place sanctions on Russia following Moscow's annexation of the Crimean Peninsula from Ukraine in 2014. She has been the lead mediator in talks with Russia over Crimea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Merkel to meet Putin amid tensions over Syrian war, Ukraine crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far, much of the effort to sell Trumps tax plan is being done by members of his economic team. Camp said it will be beneficial for Trump to sell the plan himself, when the time comes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House tax-reform push is game changer, says ex-chairman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea says U.S. bomber flights push peninsula to brink of nuclear war </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fastest goal of Damien Mori is placed at no.4 in the top 10 ranking list. He scored a goal for Australia in just 3.6 seconds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fastest goal of Damien Mori is placed at no.4 in the top 10 ranking list. He scored a goal for Australia in just 3.6 seconds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA head visited South Korea amid nuclear tensions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal court lets net neutrality regulations stand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Siding with Venezuela, the justices ruled 8-0, with Justice Neil Gorsuch not participating, to throw out a 2015 decision by the U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit that allowed one of the claims made by Oklahoma-based Helmerich   Payne International Drilling Company to move forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Supreme Court sides with Venezuela over oil rigs claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American Technology Council is part of Trump senior adviser Jared Kushners White House Office of Innovation. That office was established in March to try to streamline government operations.
We should have excellence in government, Kushner told The Washington Post in March. The government should be run like a great American company. Our hope is that we can achieve successes and efficiencies for our customers, who are the citizens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump creates tech advisory council </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The revised Hamas political document, to be announced later on Monday, will still reject Israel's right to exist and back "armed struggle" against it, the Gulf Arab sources told Reuters.

Hamas has fought three wars with Israel since 2007 and has carried out hundreds of armed attacks in Israel and in Israeli-occupied territories since it was founded three decades ago.

It remains unclear whether the document replaces or changes in any way Hamas's 1988 charter, which calls for Israels destruction and is the Islamist group's covenant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Palestinian Islamist group Hamas will remove a call for Israel's destruction and drop its association with the Muslim Brotherhood in a new policy document to be issued </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2.5K visas for Afghans who helped US troops included in spending bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hijazi was detained in Egypt in 2014 on charges of human trafficking that were widely dismissed by the international community. The Obama administration had previously lobbied Egypt for her release without success. The news of her release came after Trumps meeting with the Egyptian leader in early April.
Trump told the newspaper that el-Sissi is a good man and that the gesture was fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: It took '10 minutes' with Egyptian president to secure prisoner's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, if this is the deal we're going to get, it seems to be we should have just did the bill for the whole year," he said.
"But we specifically held a vote-- we did a short term spending bill for this time, so that when Republicans control the government, we could actually do the things we campaigned on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jordan predicts a lot of conservatives will oppose spending bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cohn also touted the administration's tax plan.
"We're very excited about our tax plan as well," he said. "We're going to continue to drive President Trump's agenda forward."

Republicans this week are looking for a path forward on their healthcare bill after failing to win enough votes to pass it last week.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cohn: I think we have the votes for healthcare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rather than cutting needed programs like those at the Environmental Protection Agency, whose budget is targeted for a 31 percent reduction under President Trumps spending plan, he should focus on implementing GAO suggestions to make government more cost-effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump could save big bucks following reports recommendations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pocahontas is the racially charged term that Trump used on the campaign trail to dismiss Warren, who has claimed Native American heritage. Clearly, she had got under his skin. The Massachusetts senator was a self-declared nasty woman with a message for Trump: Women have had it with guys like you. She went to toe to toe with him on his favourite medium, Twitter, hammering him for delivering a one-two punch of bigotry and economic lie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Run against Trump? Elizabeth Warren will certainly stand and fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The agreement will move the needle forward on conservative priorities and will ensure that the essential functions of the federal government are maintained, said Jennifer Hing, a spokeswoman for Republicans on the House Appropriations Committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Congress negotiators set spending plan to avert shutdown, bolster defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter partners with Bloomberg for streaming TV news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congress is expected to vote on the roughly $1 trillion package early this week. The bipartisan agreement includes policy victories for Democrats, whose votes will be necessary to pass the measure in the Senate, as well as $12.5billion in new military spending and $1.5billion more for border security requested by Republican leaders in Congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Trump is relying on a host of officials to carry out hard-line immigration policies that include building a permanent wall on the Mexican border. 

The officials include both long-time proponents of reduced immigration who in Trump see an opportunity to push forward policies that were set aside by previous administrations, and decorated national security professionals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seven key players for Trump on immigration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nawaf Al Abed scored the fastest goal in football history (3 seconds) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Really unfairly," he said. "She's a high-quality person. She's been amazing for the country."
 
He added his wife has been a "great representative."
 
"In fact, her polls: She went up 29 points, did you see that?" he said. "But shes been very highly abused by the press, which was very unfair. And now people are starting to know her.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Being president a 'big burden on the family' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biden, who will be 77 when the Iowa caucuses roll around in 2020, will also helm the University of Pennsylvanias Penn Biden Center for Diplomacy and Global Engagement in Washington, D.C.

Biden heads to Manchester, N.H. Sunday for a dinner with the state Democratic Party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biden schedule sets off 2020 speculation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ros-Lehtinen, 64, declined to endorse Trump during the White House race and differed with him on issues such as immigration. She balked at supporting the proposed Obamacare replacement legislation that the president backed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican lawmaker Ros-Lehtinen, a Trump critic, to retire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says China could have hacked Democratic emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is stepping up outreach to allies in Asia to discuss the North Korean nuclear threat and make sure all are "on the same page" if action was needed, a top White House official said. The U.S. president will discuss North Korea with the leaders of Thailand and Singapore on Sunday after speaking with the Philippines' president on Saturday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korea says U.S. reaffirms it will pay THAAD costs; Trump calls Asia allies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama got $400K to speak at A E event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NY lawmakers hatch plan to release Trump's state taxes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to talk with Singapore, Thailand on North Korea nuclear threat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schumer: The country doesn't work 'my way or the highway' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue on the table is North Korea, Priebus told ABCs This Week when asked about a phone call between President Trump and Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Priebus: No bigger threat than N. Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump must work to stop Iran's secret nuclear program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump blasts 'dead' ObamaCare: New healthcare plan 'on its way' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump previously has suggested he could end the payments, or use them as leverage in talks aimed at getting Democrats to agree to changes to ObamaCare.

But this week, Trump sought to defuse threats by Democrats to withhold support for a spending bill over the issue by saying that he would continue to make the payments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems, not trusting Trump, want permanent ObamaCare fix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope calls for end to violence, respect for human rights, in Venezuela </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CNN senior political analyst David Gergen late Saturday said President Trump delivered the most divisive speech Ive ever heard from a sitting American president at a campaign-style rally in Pennsylvania.

"To bring your campaign speech into the presidency is something presidents rarely do," Gergen said on CNN.

"He played to his base and he treated his other listeners, the rest of the people who have been disturbed about him or oppose him, he treated them basically as 'I don't care, I don't give a damn what you think, because you're frankly like the enemy.'" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gergen slams divisive Trump speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blumenthal said that outside contractors are not qualified to handle the veterans crisis line. The Democratic senator called for real action over rhetoric, noting there is a bipartisan effort in Congress to address the issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem senator blasts VA for outsourcing veterans suicide line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you guide me to build gaming pc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 11:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a threat to national security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 11:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iran's Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei has criticized President Hassan Rouhani for saying his detente policy with the West had caused the threat of war to fade as tensions intensify in Tehran before May election.

Rouhani, a pragmatist whose election in 2013 led to a diplomatic thaw between Iran and the West, championed in 2015 a landmark deal in which Tehran agreed to curb its nuclear activities in return for lifting of international sanctions.

A standoff between Rouhani, who is seeking a second term, and Khamenei's allies, who opposed the nuclear deal, has intensified in recent months ahead of the May 19 vote.

"Some say since we took office the shadow of war has been faded away. This is not correct," Khamenei was quoted as saying by the state media on Sunday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran's leader dismisses Rouhani's detente policy ahead of vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 11:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IMF team in Cairo to review second installment of $12-billion loan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 10:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few Republicans also showed up, including James Gaines of Chantilly. He held a sign that sought to needle Perriello for opposing two oil and natural gas pipelines planned for rural Virginia. Tom Perriello says this isnt a real job, read the sign, which bore a photo of a man working on a pipeline. Northam has not come out against the pipelines  which McAuliffe backs as a big source of jobs  but says they must be subjected to strict environmental review.

Asked who he supports in the GOPs three-way primary, Gaines drew a blank. I dont even know whos in it to tell you the truth, he said. On the Republican side, Gillespie, Prince William County Supervisors Chairman Corey Stewart and state Sen. Frank Wagner (Virginia Beach) are vying for their partys nomination. That contest also will be decided in a June 13 primary. The general election takes place Nov. 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what Melania Trump has been doing since becoming first lady? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finding the Easter Bunny in the white house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Northam and Perriello generally agreed on policy and exchanged only a few, gentle jabs during the hourlong forum moderated by NBC4 reporter Tom Sherwood. The debate, the first of five, was held in Fairfax County - important territory in voter-rich northern Virginia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Northam and Perriello hold their fire in first Democratic debate for Va gov </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This weeks shows come after Trump held a rally Saturday in Harrisburg, Pa., to mark his 100th day in office, an event organized to contrast an annual star-studded dinner held in Washington that Trump skipped this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunday shows preview: Trump plans next steps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Navy strike group arrives in Sea of Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Democratic lawmakers sounded off against the Trump administration's climate change and environmental policies on Saturday, as tens of thousands of protesters assembled in Washington for the People's Climate March.

Democrats in Congress have not hesitated to attack the administration for what many have deemed a blatant disregard for climate science and environmental regulations aimed at stemming the effects of global warming and climate change.

But the rally on Saturday, marked by potentially record-setting high temperatures in the nation's capital, offered Democrats an opportunity once again to take aim at President Trump. 

"It shows you that we have a mobilized and organized effort to push back and fight President Trump's really hardline, extremist agenda," Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz (D-Fla.) said on CNN.


The march came a day after the Environmental Protection Agency announced that it would pull the plug on its websites containing information on climate change, in order to "reflect the views of the leadership of the agency."

EPA Administrator Scott Pruitt has voiced skepticism that human activity has caused shifts in the earth's climate, despite arguments to the contrary by an overwhelming majority of climate scientists.

Rep. Don Beyer (D-Va.) on Saturday denounced the EPA's decision to remove the climate change sites, calling it "a slap in the face to the world."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems blast Trump's policies at Climate March </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of hundreds shepherded into a queue behind metal barriers by police before handing over their petitions one-by- one, Anna, a 16-year-old Moscow schoolgirl, said she hoped Putin would get the message and not run again.

"Nothing positive has happened in our country on his watch and I have the sense that things are getting worse, and that the main problem is the fact that those in power are the same," she told Reuters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He now faces serious competition from hardliners, some of whom are close to Iran's supreme leader, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, who has criticized Rouhani's economic record, saying his detente with the West and concessions on Iran's nuclear work had yet to yield economic benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rouhani warns voters to prevent 'extremism' returning to Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marching is wonderful. But marching doesn't win elections or run the government. The country needs a unified opposition.. March and shout your lungs out, but it will do not good against Trump and his Republican backers. Find candidates. Find good candidates who bridge the issues gaps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DiCaprio marches with climate protesters
Actor Leonardo DiCaprio marches toward the White House with climate change protesters who are upset about President Trump's climate policies.
http://us.cnn.com/videos/politics/2017/04/29/leonardo-dicaprio-climate-change-protest-nr.cnn/video/playlists/climate-change/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The motivation for the current climate march is clear: The young Trump administration already has moved to roll back former president Barack Obamas signature climate initiative, the Clean Power Plan, and Trump and his team have taken many other actions to weaken environmental protections of air and water, and to enable fossil fuel exploitation on public lands and waters.

The administration is grappling with a major climate policy decision: whether to remain in the Paris climate agreement. Several of Trumps Cabinet picks are advising against following through on his campaign pledge to cancel the accord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The climate event differs from last weeks March for Science in its focus and also its participants  only 1 out of 8 contingents of Saturdays protest featured scientific researchers. The rest included labor activists, indigenous people already facing severe effects from climate change, and children and young people who will live with the effects of climate change longest as the Earth continues to warm.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of the signs at Saturdays climate march were dark and ominous, warning of climate catastrophe, dying oceans, crop destruction and planet degradation. But the mood of the marchers was anything but somber. Tens of thousands gathered all morning in the lush green National Mall in front of the US Capitol carrying signs, singing and chanting as they prepared to march to the White House. It was a racially diverse crowd with marchers of all ages.

The marchers came prepared with water bottles, hats and sun screen. They also arrived with sunny dispositions. Its beautiful, said Allison Dale, a geologist from Conshohocken, Pa. its so well organized and everyone is really friendly and in a really good mood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate March draws huge crowd to DC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
