<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2522</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Retaliate doesn't mean war. Absolutely, no one thinks it does. Not the US, not Russia, not any government anywhere. MADD is still very much a real doctrine in the US. It didn't go away with the Soviet Union. 

Obama has a large variety of tools at his disposal to retaliate. War would be the least beneficial and least effectual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you quoting that from? Made up land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recognizing written sarcasm requires the reader to have a similar mind set as the writer. There is a reason people use a tonal change to differentiate spoken sarcasm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how this type of journalism works. The journalists foster insider contacts that will tell them what is really going on. Usually, the source is kept anonymous to keep open the line of communication. If the source is revealed, they will not be in a place to provide information for very long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we didn't go to war with the Soviet Union, what makes you think going to war with Russia is any more likely?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TheCounterintelligenceDivision (CD) is a division of the National Security Branch of the Federal Bureau of Investigation. The Division protects the United States against foreign intelligence operations and espionage.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FBI_Counterintelligence_Division </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 15:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, the DNC WAS alerted to the hack. Their people blew it off. That's on the DNC, not the FBI.

[An IT employee at the DNC help desk was called by the FBI and the employee had no way to verify the identity of the agent.](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/12/13/us/politics/russia-hack-election-dnc.html?_r=0) The IT staffer ran the tools at his disposal and found nothing. The FBI should have SENT an agent the half mile to the DNC headquarters. They put no resources into alerting the DNC leadership. They did however send two agents to Colorado to look into the company Clinton hired to handle her server. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 14:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There might be a difference between legal and ethical, but for an office like the Director of the FBI there should be equal outrage for unethical and illegal acts. Interjecting himself into the election 11 days before the vote, spending an enormous amount of resources investigating Clinton's emails while not even alerting top DNC members of the Russian hack, and not alerting the public to an investigation into Trump's ties with Russia all promote a perception of partisan action. Please tell me how this all displays integrity on Comey's part. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 14:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There might be a difference between legal and ethical, but for an office like the Director of the FBI there should be equal outrage for unethical and illegal acts. Interjecting himself into the election 11 days before the vote, spending an enormous amount of resources investigating Clinton's emails while not even alerting top DNC members of the Russian hack, and not alerting the public to an investigation into Trump's ties with Russia all promote a perception of partisan action. Please tell me how this all displays integrity on Comey's part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they going to ban trolling next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We made a tool to show how Trumps offshoring tariff might affect your shopping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More people support Clinton than Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are wrong. A majority of the people in this country did support Clinton. It is a straw-man logical fallacy to call something a straw-man logical fallacy. You got yourself stuck in a loop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very relevant. Trump's supporters represent a minority of the country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Record highs for Trump is still historically record lows for a President-elect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 18:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if they aren't below the age of 64 they don't count in the statistics. See the problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem I have with this statistic is that it neglects the fact the millennial generation is currently the largest age group in the country which also coincides with record high higher education enrollment rates. So of course the participation rate will seem low because students aren't counted as participating in the labor force but are counted as part of the adult population. Also, a lot of people under 64 retired early because of the recession. Once these effects get watered down over the next 5 - 10 years, I think you will see a rise in the participation rate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Missing the point but that's not my problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like your one of the people that is part of the problem. Bully for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 22:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the T_D troll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can tell you right now that study is garbage. It's being thrown around an excessive amount right now so I looked into the data a little bit. Turns out there are people that just checked the wrong box because they mark themselves as citizens then mark themselves as non-citizens during follow ups. Pretty sloppy work if you ask me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do tell. Because I work as a precinct official every year and I can tell you that is not true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh they were taught the difference between fact and opinion. The problem is that opinions where always led with easily recognizable qualifier such as "I believe" or "I think." So all Trump and his ilk have to do is start their lies with I believe and their followers let him off scott free when it turns out he was just lying. 

Edit: Here is a great source talking about this problem. http://opinionator.blogs.nytimes.com/2015/03/02/why-our-children-dont-think-there-are-moral-facts/?_r=0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously you have no idea how the voting system works. People do get caught trying to commit voter fraud. The system is just very good at catching it so no one really tries it anymore except for the idiot here and there that doesn't know how easily they will be caught. Stop trying to push your idiocy on others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, you are wrong in so many ways. 

We are a democracy...more specifically a subset of democracy called a constitutional republic. 

Those are not the same Republicans or did you forget about the big switch in the late 1960s with Nixon? Racial integration was Democrats bubbaroo pushed top down by LBJ...shocker here...a Democrat!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know the foundation of democracy is one person one vote? Number of counties doesn't mean jack bub when the popular vote shows something else. The electoral college is meant to balance big states vs. small states as is the senate. Counties never have and never will mean anything other than a way to organize election boards. You need to brush up on US constitutional theory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the T_D troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really looking forward to the shit show that will be the confirmation hearings for the fools Trump has nominated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 14:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is from the English version official website for the Ayatollah of Iran. Not sure anyone should be trusting it or even following the link. The Iranians are known for their cyberattacks and sneaking malware into their official websites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess you don't know what pejorative means.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not social justice but you don't seem to care. \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A blind trust involves selling all of your assets and having a fund manager buy new ones you dont know about. He should sell *all* of his businesses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to stop feeding the T_D trolls. That's the only way they'll go away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the T_D troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do enlighten as to what the "extreme side of equality". You are the only person here spreading misinformation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note also the organization has denied it's investing in Taoyuan. 

Note also Nixon denied all involvement in Watergate. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, it's because you are saying something different. Well, it's really because what you are saying is dumb. The 77c to the dollar issue isn't wrong it just lacks proper context. It has more to do with the difference in jobs than pay differences for the same job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, both are pejorative terms used by people to discredit social justice and feminism. But hey keep on being a prejudiced malcontent. Seems to have served your life well so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I think it has more to do with your personality than your looks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, you're just wrong buddy. What you said isn't about social justice. But hey, if you don't know what social justice actually means then it's an easy enough mistake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow aren't you just a steaming pile of shit masquerading as a person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're cool with objectifying people? The whole argument here is that you should judge people on their character alone not their looks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also treat those dirtballs like the shit they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like your feelings were hurt. Best go back to your safe space.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 19:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is bullshit. If your opinion shows you to be a shitty person you should be treated as such. People have every right to treat you poorly for being a terrible person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, you should get your electrolyte levels checked. You're saltier than the Dead Sea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would but you ate it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the only person here calling you racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you have to be with something to defect from it. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the T_D troll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would be very easy for the Republicans to demonize. If you actually look at Republican campaign strategy, it purely focuses on demonizing Democratic leadership, e.g. Debbie Wasserman-Schultz, Hillary Clinton, Barack Obama, Nancy Pelosi, etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love that. Free markets and social progressivism is a winning strategy for the future. I'm hoping they become European style liberals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I'm working through some comments and I'll reply to some here.

**On the topic of abortion** I agree with you on the viability part but that is not in dispute, it is actually the foundation of the limitations on Roe v. Wade. The argument anti-abortion advocates and especially activists use is that life begins at conception which is a belief founded in the Christian faith not medical science. This is a religious debate not a political conservative debate. The reason being that the states that have legislation restricting abortions or adding steps to the process are stepping into and dictating the patient-doctor relationship. This goes against one of the very core tenants of what it means to be a conservative and a Republican...the support of a small non-intrusive government. 
Once an honest man could go from sunrise to its set 
Without encountering agents of his state or government 
But a sorry cloud of tyranny has fallen across the land 
Brought on by hollow men, who did not understand 
That for centuries our forefather have fought and often died 
To keep themselves unto themselves, to fight the rising tide 
And that if in the smallest battles we surrender to the state 
We enter in a darkness whence we never shall escape

One of my favorite quotes on this point from the song Sons of Liberty.          

I also find it very hypocritical of the Republican Party to push legislation of this type. Legislation regulating admitting privelages are also completely trumped up. Abortions are *incredibly* safe for the woman. These restrictions are very obviously made to limit access to legal abortions. The only way to claim otherwise would have been to add these same regulations to a whole host of *actually* dangerous outpatient procedures like [hysterectomies.](http://www.consumerreports.org/cro/magazine/2014/11/is-outpatient-surgery-safe/index.htm) Recently and currently, Republicans have been pushing moral restrictions on a whole host of women's medical issues, mostly centered around family planning. But, when it comes to corporations they say (1) corporations are people and (2) corporations can be trusted to act morally and responsibly so the need for regulations is purely onerous bureaucracy. What I don't get is why religious Republicans can't trust women to act morally while they believe they can trust corporations to do the same. Regardless of my stance on the issue of abortion any further restrictions are purely moral that must be fought for in the civic sphere not by using the government to force a belief on to others. 

If you don't want abortions provide *real* sex education not abstinence only bullshit. That's how teenagers get pregnant. Provide more funding to Planned Parenthood to provide cheap or free contraceptives and education to poor and underprivileged woman. If you don't like PP because they also happen to provide abortion services as well fund an organization that does everything PP does minus that. 

**Freedom of Speech** Based on what I saw you saying I wanted to discuss this a little bit. The 1st Amendment states 
 Congress shall make no law...abridging the freedom of speech...

This right is purely in the context of the government. Civil society may react to what you say however people please. They may disagree with you, private citizens and companies have the right to suppress your voice, and also say whatever they want back to you. It is your right to say something. It is not your right to make people listen to you or give you a platform for you speech.  It is just as much someones right to tell you to shut up as it is for you to say whatever you want.

**LGBT Issues**
This is another issue that is purely religious founded in Abrahamic beliefs. Anti-LGBT views are in no way those of the political conservative. This is another example of the Republicans pushing big government. The true conservative recognizes that the potential of a nation can only be reached when all of its citizens have the equal opportunity to achieve success. It promotes the most efficient economy by promoting an efficient workforce. Many of these religious liberty laws are just the institutionalization of discrimination. Now I'm not saying you can't discriminate  against someone, it is your right to do so. You just have to discriminate against a person because of who they are not what they are. Who describes an individual, what describes a group membership inherent from birth. Trump himself isn't anti-LGBT because he recognizes that position is also anti-business. However, *every single* nominee to his cabinet (including his VP, CoS, and Chief Strategist) hold some degree of anti-LGBT views. Every single LGBT friend I have is scared for their future now because of it. 


That's all I really had time to get through, but I hope to hear your thoughts!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ann Coulter is a provocateur...she has no ideologies. She just found the easiest way to make herself money.

What I am saying is that I am also a conservative and I don't get downvoted like you described when I share my opinion. You just have to (a) have a solid, logical, fact-based argument...not one based on emotions or belief and (b) not be an asshole about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a difference between being dumb while calling your ideas conservative and actually being a conservative. If what you say is true, I believe you fall into the former category.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won't disagree with you, all of the Abrahamic faiths are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah for now, but he will firmly be the establishment by 2020. His campaign was literally founded as a anti-establishment movement and he won't be able to do that again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 14:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article also neglects to mention that the most difficult and expensive part of manufacturing small molecules isn't making it, it is purifying it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, lets take a look and unpack the slander you have unleashed on me personally, gussied up in the guise of "sources."

Absolute numbers are a piss poor way to analyze data between two extremely different groups. It needs normalized to make apples to apples comparison. Any competent scientist can tell you that. So once you can support your claims in terms of lobbying expenditures as a percentage of revenue there is no solid conclusions that can be drawn. Obviously those with the most money have a greater capacity to fund lobbying. Why wouldn't they? What's better for you as an individual a class-action lawsuit or an individual lawsuit? 

Your second point has nothing to do with equality. You are losing yourself in your own biases. Corporations seek to protect their interests. Why shouldn't they? Business do not have representation in Congress. Businesses do not get to vote. The only way a business can serve its interests in the public sphere is by lobbying.

 the government (controlled by lobbyists of the rich)

It is truly rich that you still do not understand the problem of this statement. I'm not going to argue with you that lobbyists influence the government. That is the entire point of the industry! No one group **controls** the government. So like I said before. None of your sources back up your claims like you think they do. They just reaffirm your biases. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they really wanted to fight for increased wages they would organize sit-ins and slow downs. Actually start bleeding the profits of McDonald's and its franchises. Protests only serve as PR. They put very little real pressure on the employers, at least in the short term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 14:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of the articles support your point like you think they do. The book is a tad one dimensional and elementary in its analysis.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the government (controlled by lobbyists of the rich)

Okay, you need to step off of your conspiracy horse in neutral politics if you want me or anyone else here to take you seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the Economist has always been a liberal political paper. There are a few things that go with that perspective you need to keep in mind with a couple of the biggest being a strong disdain for populism and nationalism. If you look at their coverage through that lens it makes a lot more sense. They also generally support the status quo and gradual change in the tradition of English conservatism. I don't think anyone has ever tried to claim the Economist was unbiased. It is just that the biases it does express are very much in line with Western values and globalism. 

Now to claim they lack facts in their coverage is an insult to their integrity if you do not have evidence to back it up. Regardless of their political bent, they will not make things up. Their reputation is far too important for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are interested here are a few sources discussing trust in society.

https://www.russellsage.org/sites/all/files/cook_society_chapter1_pdf_0.pdf

http://www.pewglobal.org/2008/04/15/where-trust-is-high-crime-and-corruption-are-low/

http://poland.pl/social-issues/social/strong-civil-society-built-trust/

http://www.global-economic-symposium.org/knowledgebase/the-global-society/ethics-and-trust-in-society-and-business </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's not about intentions - it's about possibilities.

I think people have a tendency to forget this. Intentions change much more rapidly than possibilities. Intentions are good enough when countries share values or when one has a history of being a satellite state. The Russian-American relationship does not fit into either of these categories. Couple this with the history of Russia being absolutely pummeled in multiple wars and Russian actions make a lot of sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wasn't a focus of this discussion nor is it needed for this discussion. All of the countries involved have horrific human rights records. The only time the human rights record of a country matters geopolitically is when dealing with the West.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please elaborate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really think it is an excess of the system or even a problem the system itself. The world is going through a technological revolution that is fundamentally altering the way the global economy functions and how it produces wealth. We cannot expect our leaders and policy makers to make informed decisions when no one really knows what is going on. 

That is also the source of the extreme partisanship in the United States. Prior to Reagan, Republicans and Democrats generally agreed to what the economic problems were, but disagreed on how to approach them. What we have now is two parties that cannot even agree on what the problem is to be able to reach a compromise solution. 

When we cannot be certain of what action to take it comes down to political preference which can be arbitrary. 

Once the digital revolution starts to slow down and we understand better only then is it possible to make informed choices on economic and labor management.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a flaw with every single aspect of your argument. The very fundamental way in which you think and process information is flawed. Declaring something so does not make it true. Facts are provable. Opinions are not. Saying a lie is your opinion does not make it less of a lie. It does not remove your responsibility for the words you say or write. If anything it is an act of cowardice and subversion intended to confuse and misdirect. In a society based on trust and civility, your arguments and OP's statements are just false, not an opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 13:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One, that is a false comparison and, two, that is a terrible argument. It relies on the other person believing in religion as well. Fact and opinion can always be separated regardless of modifiers like "I believe" in front of demonstratively false information. A better comparison is like saying I believe the sky is yellow. Well, no, it's not. There is proof to the contrary. The point being that the sky being yellow is not an opinion, it's just called being wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 12:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just plain dumb. It is false regardless of his belief. Something doesn't become a matter of opinion just because you or he says it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you forgot your /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This perspective is a tad one-sided. Rather than resisting free trade and globalism outright, it is possible to use the net economic benefit to the government to help the displaced workers. The increased tax revenue can be used to help retrain the displaced workforce and improve efficiency in the labor market.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: anti-capitalism circlejerk because no one understands that pure economic models never work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just have to be willing to take a risk. One awkward night is worth it if you find a good group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope that money will go towards political campaigning to reduce education spending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not how this works at all. There are a few different routes a company can take. (1) Don't give your current employees a raise, but hire more staff to prevent employees from needing to work overtime [great for improving employment rate] (2) Don't hire more staff, allow overtime for your employees [increases worker wages but gives company more payroll flexibility] (3) increase the salary of midlevel employees to the new minimum and shift some of the low level work load to them [increase of payroll but easier logistics] (4) some combination of the above. As a scientist this raise would be great because now all post-doc position will be required to pay a minimum of $47,476 which should result in more high quality candidates pursuing a post-doc instead of going straight to industry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 18:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty dangerous to stop caring about your opponents considering they are your fellow citizens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know that was Trump's entire platform? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol Did the Obama protesters ever go away? So, don't expect the Trump ones to go away either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 03:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it affect voice recognition at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal Impact: 0.31

Looks like the field doesn't really respect the only journal that would publish this study. 

https://www.researchgate.net/journal/1556-5068_SSRN_Electronic_Journal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 18:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't show anything. She could just be reading something someone pulled up for her. My grandmother could manage that much too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly didn't read the article because it repeatedly reports from interviews of Clinton's staff that she did not know how to use a desktop computer. She only knew how to check her email on her phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I find funny about this whole argument is it makes it out to be some vast conspiracy from Hillary like she was hiding a shadow government or something. That is a total load of poppycock. She is just an old woman that had absolutely no idea how to use a desktop computer and didn't want to put in the effort to learn how. It was incompetence and nothing more. We all know now the right has absolutely no qualms with incompetence as evidenced by the election of Trump. 

http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2016/09/hillary-clinton-emails-2016-server-state-department-fbi-214307 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The estate tax main purpose is to prevent entrenched rich families from getting richer and richer every generation. It slows the concentration of wealth inherent to our economic system. Too high of a concentration of wealth and the economy will become less efficient and grow more slowly. It has nothing to do with feelings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's also a little off his rocker. He frequently drops off baskets of oranges at the house of my friend's parents. Not bring it in to them mind you, but he just leaves it on their porch. Kind of like anti-scurvy ding dong ditching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes you can just be wrong too. Disdain for incompetency spans the political spectrum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 13:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is literally the epitome of sexist hiring practice. Women still deal with less qualified males being hired over them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 23:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, brother. What you are saying completely agrees with what I said, but your tone is an opposition. What I said is that while the Dems lost substantially, it would be unwise to ignore their interests completely. That's kind of the point of the filibuster. They are in the mood to work with the Trump administration and willing to compromise to get at least some of the bipartisan agenda moving and moderating the Republican party policies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your blindness! Keep on keeping on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always funny to see pompous people. You do you, brother, but you completely missed my point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that makes it okay to it ignore the interests of over half the country?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's rhetoric struck fear in the hearts of many minorities. Imagine being on the other side and taking everything Trump has said literally. Only then you will understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a terrible sentiment. Especially considering there are more Clinton supporters than Trump supporters. It seems the tyranny of the minority has begun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a conspiracy. The DNC *always* helps its preferred candidate in the primary at every level of the ballot. That's kinda how political parties work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, you live a sorry life if this is what you do for "fun".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead the Republican Party will continue to make a mockery of our institutions. They have lost all respect for our Republic in their attempt to cling onto power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty rich considering literally everything Trump has ever said is pandering. He literally sends out campaign emails asking what he should say and do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No she's not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's wife modeled in US prior to getting work visa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
