<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4941</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://img.washingtonpost.com/rf/image_960w/2010-2019/Wires/Images/2017-03-22/AP/APTOPIX_Congress_Health_Overhaul_81434-94991.jpg w=1484 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remember where I saw it but aren't a large number of Republicans completely new to legislation writing? Like a lot only had their first term under Obama so they've never crafted anything as complicated or far reaching as this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/meirl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And absolutely no one commenting on any of the posts saying it was postponed as far as I can see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I've been in Congress, I can't recall a more universally detested piece of legislation than this GOP health care bill," Amash tweeted on March 20.

Ouch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  pre-existing conditions

Side effects from a few lobotomies?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it doesn't pass maybe they're just going to pretend it did and go full steam ahead with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RTFA. . .Ukraine is mentioned loads of times and Manafort is directly linked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If an upcoming story is as bad as some people are speculating, he might intensionally hang himself soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a way is it good that Donald Trump got elected? Like if Hillary got elected would there be anywhere near the amount of investigation into Russian meddling in other countries business and the ties of high profile people to the Kremlin like Manafort here? This way everything is coming is coming to the fore, Russian bribery, influence over people, their information war, hacking etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what you're reading or where but it's likely the opposite. There's evidence long term and heavy use could result in short term memory problems or cognitive functions (although the subjects were still within the normal range), but that's about the height of it.

It's a fucking disaster of a drug.

Guna need a source on that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok? Not all addictions are the same though. Alcohol and cigarettes will almost certainly kill you if you're addicted to them, so why shouldn't they be banned as well?. The likes of weed and MDMA have such a low potential for addiction it's hardly worth mentioning. The health side affects are also hardly worth mentioning unless you're severely abusing them, which is unlikely because of said addictiveness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about instead of making it easier for **addicts to stay addicted**. . .

They're talking about recreational drugs aren't they, not heroin? So that makes no sense.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only one is a stupid argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So go a step further and legalise recreational drugs completely, have them government controlled? The government could produce and sell MDMA and weed to licensed premises and everyone's safer since both are multitudes of times safer than alcohol and cigarettes and the majority of gang's income evaporates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you see 16+? and why is it 18:0023:00? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not, it's been absolutely awful for ages now. I've completely stopped reading it because of how bad it's got. Some articles, like this one, will contradict the headline of the article.

First paragraph:

Donald Trump is going to get himself out of office soon, a leading Democratic senator has claimed

How could any reasonable person take that to mean he's going to resign?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? What specifically is wrong with this article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Others have it worse so stop complaining!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 19:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleted lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read your comment and then went back and read the original comment then read yours again and then the original comment again and I can't for the life of me understand where you're getting that from. When did ShockRampage ever say Arsenal shouldn't buy better players because Arsenal are worse with them? or even imply it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Not a Trump supporter at all and I completely agree with you. Europe has been saved time and time again by the US and they've done nothing but take it for granted." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See ye all in the Premier League next year! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got no seats the last election AFAIK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ireland has no relevant extremes at all, just completely middle of the road. . .like the weather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  for other areas, though, it can often feel like a real roll of the dice finding one to rely on.

FYI, this is a problem the Rust designers know about. There's been a few debates about exactly this  but unfortunately there's no easy solutions :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Servo screenshots, March 15th, 2017 (from /r/Rust) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup praise Allah (or whatever God) this happened in France and not in America or else dozens would've been killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does Islam have to do with a student targeting a headmaster because he held a grudge against him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post: Germany needs to do more to tackle shrinking population

Comments: Fuck refugees

Never change /r/europe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well, I guess continental Europe knows how to deal with their elections.

It's a lot easier to avoid that non-sense without First Past the Post voting, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 22:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're saying it was rigged because turnout was so high, how you rig an election with a paper trail I haven't seen explained yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fillon children funneled salaries to parents bank account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there was no gun control then they wouldn't have to resort to reactivating deactivated guns though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll find lots here /r/bodyweightfitness/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're in europe GP care is free!!. . .except Ireland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I'm most worried about when campaigning actually starts, that the campaigners and debaters will have very extreme views like abortion being allowed even a week before birth.

Specifically on the video though, this idiot clearly has an agenda. He must have gone through hundreds of people just to get this not even 3 minute clip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Deciding to levy a  fine is perfectly within the realm of the possible within the law. 

If this passed and, say, the Catholic church brought a case against it to the Supreme court for being too lenient. Do you really think the justices would entertain any other idea than this legislation making an absolute mockery of the constitution? Why not make torture a 1 euro fine? or give the guards that searched your house without a warrant an hour community service? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unconstitutional, I'd imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully the organisers of the repeal campaign don't think the same, because they'll most likely lose if they only attack the religious aspect. One of the most anti-abortion people I know (still thinks it should be legalised for exceptionally cases) also happens to be one of the most anti-religion people I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried searching the url before posting and there was no results. . .weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not directly related to the SCW but still thought people here might want to see it since it's about major players in the war and the abuses were very near Syria.

Edit: In hindsight I probably should've said this didn't happen in Syria in the title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse again if a government doesn't form in Northern Ireland it could be direct rule from Westminster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve McClaren: Derby County sack manager for a second time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why do Assad supporters always use false equivalence and whataboutism.

Because they've nothing else to go on. Even the most delusional Assad supporters can't justify his and the armies actions so they just resort to everyone does it or Assad is bad but others are worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think most teams would be happy with a draw away to Leeds. The good form continues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he doesn't disclose his party's finances).

Gee, that's not suspicious at all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. . .at least our free healthcare/education is saving us from a life endless debt or bankruptcy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judicial review on Warren Farm decision finds in favour of Ealing Council and QPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Originally from here](https://www.reddit.com/r/soccer/comments/5yb3pj/distance_covered_by_sanchez_ozil_and_giroud/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Distance covered by Sanchez, Ozil and Giroud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably the worst Barcelona midfield in a decade, one of the biggest complaints Barca fans have against Enrique is the state of the midfield. They didn't even have to press around Barca's box like the first leg just the midfield, put them under some kind of pressure and it would have completely thrown them off, instead they got free reign completely to do what they wanted with the ball, I couldn't believe what I was watching in the first half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They pressed Barcelona around Barca's own box the first leg and put 4 past them so obviously the best plan of action for the second leg is to surrender Barca's third, surrender the midfield and defend around their own box giving Barcelona of all teams complete control of the ball. It's criminal tactics, absolutely no excuse for it. When Di Maria finally came on and they finally started pressing like the last game they had a goal in less than 10 minutes.

Even considering all that most of the goals were down to PSG's own mistakes rather than Barca brilliance.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Otherwise, it's the risk you have to take to have sex.

So should abortion be banned only in the most exceptional circumstances as well (rape, incest etc)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally worse than neo-nazis. . .This is why I'm absolutely dreading the campain because there'll be no debates anywhere just screaming matches from both extremes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of any good reason why that would be put in there, like who even cares?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I'm gonna cum"

What's this actually from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 11:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicare is what I've seen people call it, rolls of the tongue a bit easier as well imho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 10:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. . .someone that only supports their team from a bar stool and when they (Arsenal) start losing they'll just start supporting another team from their bar stool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> QPR 2-1 Barnsley | Video | Watch TV Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even joking I actually think the Championship is one of the best leagues in the world, obviously not quality wise but just because of how unpredictable it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For the last 9 years as obvious as it is for a pool fan to say it, its not like English teams have been fucking blazzing up europe taking names and raping ass.

Liverpool won it in 2005, Man United 2008 and Chelsea 2012. That's not even mentioning which of them were runner up or got knocked out in the semi-final the last decade.

I swear reddit is just american kids playing FIFA all day or something

Looks like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barstoolers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you have to do is compare this game to the other one. The difference between Arsenal and Bayern is about the same as Madrid and Napoli but Napoli can actually walk off the pitch with some dignity. Took the game to Madrid in both legs and even took the lead in both, Madrid were much better over the 2 legs but Napoli had plenty of chances and could easily have gone through. Arsenal on the other hand. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Callejn had a massive chance near the end of the first leg as well, but was narrowly offside, it was a lot closer than the scoreline made it out to be. Don't know what the other person is on about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing they lost pretty bad on aggregate but at least they can go out with their heads held high (unlike some other team), not many teams take the lead in both legs against Real Madrid but in the end Madrid just had more quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck sake, can't throw this away. Hall badly at fault? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Football might as well be re-labeled a non contact sport if this is a definite foul. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the flat Earth subs a lot are Seventh Day Adventists to be exact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reads like a Sunday Independent article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They rarely rock the boat taking stands. 

They at least explicitly stated they're in favour of an abortion referndum. Fine Gael and Fianna Fail are still dodging questions on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally 2 of us read the study, yey. Not only were the samples small, but they were different. Like with such small numbers could this not easily be explained by randomness?

Why do I also have the feeling that if the researchers found no increase in aggressive negotiation tactics by men towards women that they'd "mysteriously" come up with another click-baity conclusion like "Even after the election women are less likely to back down from men" or something equally laughable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should of asked first time round, but exactly what behavior should be called out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reading through the paper I'm putting this one in [the novel pile](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=42QuXLucH3Q). It just seems like it was done for easy exposure. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Behavior that happens in a lab? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 13:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comments with the words insane, crazy etc will automatically be deleted as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The London Mayor's name is Sadiq Khan? I'm surprised how progressive UK is sometimes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 12:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also this https://i.imgur.com/uIalauM.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [/r/PussypassIRL](https://i.imgur.com/CstapGM.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a good PR move to me tbh. Solidarity sounds a lot less. . .extreme or radical than Anti Austerity Alliance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be a dick, but could you not? At least not comment in both threads because it looks bad (and is against the rules?)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I hear one more European consider themselves an international traveler because they took a train from Spain to France and then lecture Americans on how they don't travel enough, I am going to lose it.

The culture difference between New York City and rural appalachia is probably greater than the cultural difference between Spain and France.

+107 :L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also the similar belief in amd that sony is the big evil corporation and ms are the caring and loving company. 

But. . .Sony are tiny compared to Microsoft, it isn't even close. Microsoft is one of the biggest corporations in the world full stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you're probably not ~~french~~ European, why do you care about ~~Marine Le Pen~~ the EU anyway ?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going into fantasy land for a second and pretending Fillon and Le Pen drop out, who'd win between Macron and Hamon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tasks tagged with any `easy` tag might sound impossibly hard when you first read them but if you get someone to explain it simply (which they always do) it'll turn out to be *very* easy like adding a couple of lines of code or removing code that doesn't do anything anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an absolutely, outrageous comment. Do you honestly think that people can't *constructively* criticize something unless they have a superior, alternative way of doing it? Is no one allowed to criticize certain things about a car unless they can design a better car? Can no one criticize aspects of a house unless they can design a better house?

The original comment is a perfectly legitimate criticism (among a litany of others) maybe instead of making snarky comments you make a reasonable counter point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to assume you're a complete beginner like I was. 

I've done more tasks with Servo so I'm going to be biased towards that (although imho Servo is a bit more accessible to complete beginners without any opensource experience or even git experience like me)

You can make a comment here saying you're looking for a task and say what (if any) experience you have. https://github.com/servo/servo/issues/15162

Then if you get a task go here [Github-workflow](https://github.com/servo/servo/wiki/Github-workflow) and follow the instructions and also [this](https://stackoverflow.com/questions/20956154/whats-the-workflow-to-contribute-to-an-open-source-project-using-git-pull-reque/20956155#20956155) stackoverflow answer is *extremely* helpful, I wish I found it when I started out.

That's about it tbh. Nearly the hardest thing is finding a task because the easy ones get taken pretty quick :-). Contributing to the Rust project is basically the same but AFAIK there's no equivalent to the github workflow so you'll be going back and forth to the Servo project to the workflow which is one reason why I just stayed with Servo and I don't think there's a place to comment if you want to put you're name down for a task either. Each [This week in Rust](https://this-week-in-rust.org/) blog post has a section for tasks up for grabs though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  abundance 

Vast majority I'd say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I love about contributing to Rust / Servo. The first few easy tasks I took I had problems just "getting" what to do. The people running both projects bend over backwards to help you get it finished which is why I'm always looking to do more now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  if they leave a project due to attitude.

If you had a manager scream in your face at work would you stay there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia works with the SDF and the Syrian government works very closely with them as well. Just today it was announced that the SDF would give the Syrian government a lot of [land they control to the west of Manbij](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C56MKmHWMAAb6Iw.jpg) to the government so Turkey and Turkish backed rebels wouldn't attack manbij (which they were shaping up to do). 

There's no conspiracy here, it was friendly fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 09:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MightierThanThou posts a never ending stream of pro US shit. Statistics and facts are purposefully twisted or left out to prove the US is the best country ever in every metric. He even has his own specific tag (MTT) on /r/ShitAmericansSay. Don't feed the troll, he's more dedicated than you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If you can't explain it simply, you don't understand it well enough." - Albert Einstein. . .(no meme, he maybe actually did say it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 12:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Travellers, kind of the same, but different.

Side note. In case anyone doesn't know "The joy" is mount joy a prison in Ireland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird how these gangs never go to like southside Chicago to show black people what's what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   64 million people? 

Germany has ~81 million and healthcare is essentially free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the witch king of Angmar, the leader of the 9 (and yes most powerful). It was him that brought about the destruction of the Kingdom of Arnor. 

Fun fact that people get wrong a lot. The witch king could be killed by a man it's just that Glorfindel prophesied that it wouldn't be a man that killed him which, by process of elimination, was a prediction that a woman would kill him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Golum actually describes seeing Sauron briefly and said he had only 4 fingers on one hand I think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actual rural people don't ask for fibre to their homes, it's more they're asking for internet *at all* or speeds above 1Mb, you don't need fibre for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "He guided us with his eloquence!. . .to 2 wars that killed thousands of soldiers, countless Iraqis/Afghans and put the US Economy in the toilet in the process"

Fixed that for him.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  These people really are children, aren't they?

I remember a post from there where someone took a photo of their chocolate milk in school and thanking everyone for getting it back into schools because Michelle Obama got it banned or something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emmanuel Macron splits baby with campaign platform  POLITICO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't be long until we see reports of Al-bab being captured in a counter attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guessing because the Indo is as balanced as a see-saw with an elephant one side and a mouse the other, especially when it comes to Sinn Fein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really like what more do you need apart from the likes of NoScript and avoiding dodgy websites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also believe Intel is in communication with the head of an IT department to only buy Intel chips and not the actual hardware vendors that put the chips into pre made hardware like IBM or HP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  At least it is proof that there is no moral boundary hindering them, just laws (which they tried and COULD try again to disobey)

Congratulations on describing every corporation ever, if you think AMD is for some reason paragons of virtue and would never engage in anti competitive practices just like Intel then you're delusional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the things that never happened, this never happened the most. It reads like a typical AMD fanatic trying to get people to buy AMD. . .for some reason. I'd love to call them shills but I know they're not even getting paid which makes these posts all the stranger and sadder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can Intel even compete when AMD has such dedicated cultists spamming endless shit about them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you keep spamming this exact same comment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So economic disaster. . .which doesn't agree with the person I replied to that said. . .

it has resulted in awful atrocities

. . . . . . .

Don't worry, i doubt you fall under that category.

Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, the comment I replied to, to me anyway, implied totalitarianism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would they try and wipe out and why? and how, use the unarmed guards? Essentially non existent army? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I find them autocratic, secretive and utterly populist. They are liars. 

So going by this I presume you don't support any major party in Ireland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How anyone could type this shite out, read it and think "yes, this comment is a good comment and one worthy of sharing" is beyond me. Do honestly think AAA/PBP are actual communists on the level of Stalin or something? If they got into power do you think they would set up gulags? Who would be rounded up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do badly written executive orders that he doesn't read count as creating policy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw something about him being unfit like he's hardly featured in any game in a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trade grows  without the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every traveller funeral / wedding in my local town will have **armed** guards watching it. If there is a funeral or wedding all the pubs will be called by the guards and warned about it so they can close their doors for the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In his decision, Mr Justice Kearns said it was suggested the hotel should have geared up for trouble **because a security consultant, who gave evidence for the Connors side, had described fracas as being part and parcel of Traveller weddings**.

https://www.irishtimes.com/news/crime-and-law/courts/high-court/man-injured-at-traveller-wedding-reception-loses-damages-claim-1.2218528

Security consultants know a thing or 2 about security and if they say fights are part and parcel of Traveller weddings then hotels should have every right to deny marriage services to Travellers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does this answer either of the other dude's questions?

What has Trump done that is universally good and favored across both major political parties?

. . .

what has he done that aligns with the vast majority of Americans' belief? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 72 seconds exactly, crazy stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "they stole all the children at Sandy Hook. everybody knows this and it is highly disturbing." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another assist as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything better than the daily mail saying this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another 4 - 1 inbound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-lexical lifetimes using liveness and location </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "In Sweden one can be arrested for speaking about immigrant related crimes. They don't have free speech like we do here. " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.bookdepository.com/ always seems to have them discounted. . .still pricey though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it not peace keepers or reserves or something though, like Georgia battered them until the actual Russian army showed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like he should be the host of a shitty game show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're out of contract in football you're out of contract you can sign with any team anywhere in the world of they want you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socialist. Teams would be owned by the players (workers) not everyone like communism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Botswana has been a stable democracy for decades and is also one of the more developed countries in Africa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you really are busy today with pro Le Pen and anti immigrant rubbish. . .maybe look for job? or at least a hobby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIGHLIGHTS | BIRMINGHAM CITY 1, QPR 4 - 18/02/17 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://github.com/rust-lang/rfcs/pull/1598 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly all the pollsters had Mrs Clinton ahead of Mr Trump, with NBC for example giving the former First Lady enjoying a five-point lead as Americans went to the polls.

Clinton entered polling day leading by five points nationally in the latest CNN/ORC poll, and by three points in CNN's most recent poll of polls. 

From your first link. . .this is bang on, she won the popular vote by around that margin. It doesn't mention Brexit in the article either but Brexit polls were always neck and neck with Leave taking the lead a few times.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was wrong with Brexit polls? The US national polls were mostly right as well. In the days leading up to the election they were around 60 - 40 or 55 - 45 or something which was right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fianna Fail has jumped six points to 33pc

Fuck sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was under a different name but essentially the same bank. It was renamed CIT Bank (who started the proceedings) after a merger and Mnuchin is still on the board. So technically wrong I suppose? Not sure why CNN should retract they're story since they weren't wrong and Politico and Huffington Post corrected their article to reflect the truth so not sure why they should either. 

This was fake news. 

. . .

Fake news has been defined as news which is "completely made up and designed to deceive readers to maximize traffic and profit"

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fake_news#Definition

Politico and Huffington Post were wrong on a technicality how this qualifies as fake news, going by the above definition, is beyond me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
