<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject873</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One evening, when I was around 8 years old, my dad took my brother and me to a store in Toronto called The Silver Snail. It was basically the coolest place on earth as far as I could tell. Lots of comic books, Transformers, obscure action figures, etc. I went out front to look at the awesome window display. A few minutes later I hear "Do you want me to buy something for you?" I turn around and there's a man, mid to late 60s, leaning in to talk to me. Instant gut tremor. "No thanks" and I immediately go back inside the store. A minute later, as I'm looking at something in the store, I hear "Are you sure you don't want me to buy you something?" Same guy. I noped the fuck away from that guy pretty fast and back to my dad. Pretty sure my gut reaction saved me from a lifetime of therapy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wasn't even wearing black velvet but, in her defense, I didn't please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met him at a stuffy Juno Awards party at a hotel in Toronto like 15 years ago. It was a room mostly filled with people in black tie, passed hors d'oeuvres and general fanciness. I was just sitting there when I smelled pot. I stood up and looked around to see who the fuck is smoking pot at a party like this. He just laughed, made a witty comment about my sudden smell-pot-stand-up motion and passed me the joint. Suddenly I was in a smoking circle with him and Alannah Myles. Good times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your first memory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thankfully, most of my eyeshadow and mascara is on my wife's eyes, so i don't really have to do much to get it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i do. i just don't specifically rub soap on my eyelids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
