<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8479</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's some ("cheap") services I have used in the past:


- Splice.com does have a small but increasing amount of vocal packs that you can use for your commercial releases.They're the cheapest and easiest way to get high quality vocals i've found yet.


- Looperman.com, where you have to deal with the vocalists for licensing. There's some very nice and straight forward people, but most of them will charge more than 100$ per release (after what i've experienced).

- beatport, there are some nice and "for commercial usage" vocal packs of many genres which I've made use of. The quality depends very much and the price per pack is between 20-50$.


- fiverr.com, where I had a vocalist sing some original lyrics for me. In most cases you have to write them yourself though. Also, it's a fair amout of work to have the vocalist sing the lyrcis how you imagine them (which included singing the bit myself first, and several rerecordings on the vocalists side). Pricing is about 30 up to 200 bucks (I paid 105$).

Sorry for my not so good english. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 10:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use fruity compressor almost every time on my snare and sometimes on the whole drum bus to make it sound bouncyer. It helps to stick all the drum layers together.
I also have a slight compression in my mastering chain (about 1:1.4-1.6) to fit in the loudest parts of the track.
Edit: Also on Vocals, always. Makes a huge difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't mention where you're from... This is actually a very weird question, as the copyright law in most countries applies on any intellectual property in the moment you create it. There shouldn't be any need to register your work. The task of providing evidence to prove that work was originally made by you in a lawsuit is another chapter.

edit: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 12:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucerne, Switzerland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I always thought it's so far away... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 10:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 10:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL I have tripohobia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It always seemed so far away... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 10:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 17:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool. Followed and added a track too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
