<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2022</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 00:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is such fucking bullshit. What the fuck, am I not fucking free to fucking do whatever I fucking want? Who fucking are they to fucking track what I fucking and SEND ME A FUCKING CEASE AND EXIST LETTER. I they send that shit imma fucking cancel my hbo contract. Fuck this shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *unzips*

Story time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 01:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked this character but IMO Erikson shouldn't have brought him back in the most WTF manner later in the series. Coming out of Kruppe's asshole? The hell Steven Erikson...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 21:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I...Am I the only one who would let Cotillion....do naughty things to me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, he probably even came in her ass a couple of times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 21:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad this show is getting the recognition it deserves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are looking at a screen right now.. I'll wait for my upvotes thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His huge cock slid into her wet fucking pussy. She immediately started screaming. 

"FUUUCK. FUUUCK. FUCK ME
 FUCK ME FUCK ME FUCK ME FUCK ME FUCK ME FUCK ME EEE AWWWW...AAAAAAAAAAAAH!"

He went crazy with her tight little pussy. He started wheezing like a man-pig. "MMMMMRPHH," he groaned, pounding her like the good cum-whore that she was. 


                           

                        


              ***





Some time later, he reached into her gaping asshole and started rummaging inside.

She started screaming again. "Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!"


She squirted all over his fucking arm. 



        
                            

              
            
           
               ***







He slipped his cock out of her throat and unplugged her nose. 

"Shit..."

James checked her pulse. Nothing...it happened again. 

James stepped back, unperturbed, and pulled his iPhone out. He dialed and waited. 

"Hello? This is James. It happened again." 


               </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malazan Book of The Fallen. 

Mistborn. 

The First Law  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly Hannibal made the notion of cannibalism seem so...tempting. 

At least in my perspective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just gonna have to trust me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And disclose certain confidential information? No thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any Nickelodeon actresses that recently turned 18? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 23:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you're thinking and IT'S NOT that I swear. I'm looking for any young Nickelodeon actresses that recently turned 18. The most recent the better. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 05:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion a spin-off of Robert's Rebellion would be much, much better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 23:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 06:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading TTH myself. A little slow on the first half, but now it's really freaking good. So much stuff going on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 06:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yeah DG is way darker than GoTM. 

I think the prologue sets the tone perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 04:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but what about that Witness dude? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 03:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope Donald Trump gets fucked in the ass by orangutan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 03:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would rather we stop focusing on ourselves and pay attention to you. What a selfish person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My theory. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 10:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've heard in various interviews about how some rappers apparently had a falling out with Tupac before the time of his death. Among the rappers apparently Snoop Dog, Ice Cube, Dre, Suge Knight, Biggie, and some other were involved in some falling out ot another with Tupac. Now, what if, all these rappers conspired to have Tupac taken care of?

Maybe they saw him as a threat to their careers. Maybe they thought that as long as Tupac lived, there would be no other king of Rap. What do you guys think? ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 09:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if blowjobs existed back then  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 09:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because God made cock to fit in pussy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesus Christ probably had sex. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 09:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I fucking hate The Walking Dead. I can't wait to see the new episodes so I can hate them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 05:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hit the head against the nail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doran Martell sitting there thinking "these fucking sluts" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username suck mu dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 04:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not superior 

Jesus Christ sucking a popsicle. Did I say I was superior? Did I say that? Are you assuming I'm some guy who thinks of himself as extremely intelligent? Fuck no. In fact, I'm pretty ignorant and my knowledge is probably below average at best.

My friend, however, is pretty dumb and even he admits it. Last week we spent looking for a pair of keys that were in his pockets all along. He even thought Obama was Puerto Rican for fucks sake. I'm just saying people like that will probably have a hard time understanding Malazan. That's all. No need to get Triggered.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It hurts me because I was this close to discussing my fav book ever with someone I know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What pisses me off is that this person is the only person I've got to try the series for the first time in my life and they quit right before my favorite book?!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets keep in mind that I'm talking about someone who read 5 *books* in the series. I mean, dragons and philosophical monologes is something that's apparent in the first 2-4 books. This person *knew* what they were getting into.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I can see, but I bet those pebbles don't even bother in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be honest here, yes, the series can be confusing, but the average person won't have any problems if they just read it with interest like they would a harry potter or asoiaf book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 00:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, if you read the series and concentrate when you do so I don't see why people would have problems with it? 

It just seems to me that every person that tried and didn't stick made a half-ass attempt on something that honestly just requires you to fucking read </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rust only quickscopes?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where there any serial killers that started killing because that fucking bitch said he had a small penis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 10:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AFFC Spoilers] I just came upon this speech. Amazing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ser? My lady? said Podrick. Is a broken man an outlaw?

More or less, Brienne answered.

Septon Meribald disagreed. More less than more. There are many sorts of outlaws, just as there are many sorts of birds. A sandpiper and a sea eagle both have wings, but they are not the same. The singers love to sing of good men forced to go outside the law to fight some wicked lord, but most outlaws are more like this ravening Hound than they are the lightning lord. They are evil men, driven by greed, soured by malice, despising the gods and caring only for themselves. Broken men are more deserving of our pity, though they may be just as dangerous. Almost all are common-born, simple folk who had never been more than a mile from the house where they were born until the day some lord came round to take them off to war. Poorly shod and poorly clad, they march away beneath his banners, ofttimes with no better arms than a sickle or a sharpened hoe, or a maul they made themselves by lashing a stone to a stick with strips of hide. Brothers march with brothers, sons with fathers, friends with friends. Theyve heard the songs and stories, so they go off with eager hearts, dreaming of the wonders they will see, of the wealth and glory they will win. War seems a fine adventure, the greatest most of them will ever know.

Then they get a taste of battle.

For some, that one taste is enough to break them. Others go on for years, until they lose count of all the battles they have fought in, but even a man who has survived a hundred fights can break in his hundred-and-first. Brothers watch their brothers die, fathers lose their sons, friends see their friends trying to hold their entrails in after theyve been gutted by an axe.

They see the lord who led them there cut down, and some other lord shouts that they are his now. They take a wound, and when thats still half-healed they take another. There is never enough to eat, their shoes fall to pieces from the marching, their clothes are torn and rotting, and half of them are shitting in their breeches from drinking bad water.

If they want new boots or a warmer cloak or maybe a rusted iron halfhelm, they need to take them from a corpse, and before long they are stealing from the living too, from the smallfolk whose lands theyre fighting in, men very like the men they used to be. They slaughter their sheep and steal their chickens, and from there its just a short step to carrying off their daughters too. And one day they look around and realize all their friends and kin are gone, that they are fighting beside strangers beneath a banner that they hardly recognize. They dont know where they are or how to get back home and the lord theyre fighting for does not know their names, yet here he comes, shouting for them to form up, to make a line with their spears and scythes and sharpened hoes, to stand their ground. And the knights come down on them, faceless men clad all in steel, and the iron thunder of their charge seems to fill the world

And the man breaks.

He turns and runs, or crawls off afterward over the corpses of the slain, or steals away in the black of night, and he finds someplace to hide. All thought of home is gone by then, and kings and lords and gods mean less to him than a haunch of spoiled meat that will let him live another day, or a skin of bad wine that might drown his fear for a few hours. The broken man lives from day to day, from meal to meal, more beast than man. Lady Brienne is not wrong. In times like these, the traveler must beware of broken men, and fear thembut he should pity them as well.

When Meribald was finished a profound silence fell upon their little band. Brienne could hear the wind rustling through a clump of pussywillows, and farther off the faint cry of a loon. She could hear Dog panting softly as he loped along beside the septon and his donkey, tongue lolling from his mouth. The quiet stretched and stretched, until finally she said, How old were you when they marched you off to war?

Why, no older than your boy, Meribald replied. Too young for such, in truth, but my brothers were all going, and I would not be left behind. Willam said I could be his squire, though Will was no knight, only a potboy armed with a kitchen knife hed stolen from the inn. He died upon the Stepstones, and never struck a blow. It was fever did for him, and for my brother Robin. Owen died from a mace that split his head apart, and his friend Jon Pox was hanged for rape.

The War of the Ninepenny Kings? asked Hyle Hunt.

So they called it, though I never saw a king, nor earned a penny. It was a war, though. That it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck is wrong with you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gomorra  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 09:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snorlax cuz he's slippin through TWOW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this book worth reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 09:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 09:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. I need this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does nobody feel a little bad about the actual fans who wanted to meet Khaled?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those of you who read the main series as it came out, how was it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 02:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you reread the previous book before the next one? Was the a lot of online discussion and speculation between releases? How was the general experience of following the series like that as it came out? Do you wish you'd waited until it was finished?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 21:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we can't have nice things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 06:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad the man is a nutty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 01:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can't even </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a load of cum on his face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/nottheonion would have a field day with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I have to believe Spider-Man actually exists to go to Universal and get on the ride?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. So much this. The thing about Daniel Radcliffe is that he's already starred in a franchise that will keep him in a stable financial position  for the rest of his life. Now he does roles that help him grow as an artist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me of "We Have Always Lived in the Castle" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 04:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you get downbernied so hard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Troll harder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> finally. 

finally. 

finally. 

finally. 

finally. 

finally. 

finally. 

finally.

finally. 

finally. 

finally. 

finally.

finally. 

finally. 

finally. 

finally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 08:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no, that one's on Pornhub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 22:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 11:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is torturing yourself in your bucket list?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 03:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bonus track: Duiker ft. Toc the Younger and Fisher Kel Tath- O' this Sorrowful life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I contact Eminem and ask him for a creampie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 23:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daredevil vs. The Mountain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 22:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: the Arena where Oberyn fought. Daredevil (show) in his latest suit and the zombified version of The Mountain in full armour. The Mountain has his sword and Daredevil has all his gadgets that he's acquired as of s2. 

Round 2: the streets of Hells Kitchen. Daredevil is in his season 1 beggingers outfit (the one with the black mask) and the Mountain (normal version) is in civilians clothes. Both are unarmed. 

Round 3: Mat Murdock in lawyers clothes must survive in the Arena against two armed versions of The Mountain for 5 minutes (like IP man vs Myke Tyson). After 5 minutes, if Murdock is alive, he wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 15:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt so uncomfortable during that whole Lysa Arryn/LF/Sansa plotline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 15:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope she stabs him right then and there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 21:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boltons have huge horses, I bet a lot of them were under those little mountains  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 21:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what's scarier, watching Dothraki cavalry charge you or Bolton's cavalry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 22:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Louis CK? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 23:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I give you permission to masturbate but only tonight ok? Go ahead honey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This got me rock hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayy le fucking mao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite lyric from Em and why is the one about the gerbil up an ass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 01:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
