<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1236</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In summer the newsreaders do rotate around. Sometimes at the beach, in parks, near forests etc. Sometimes they just greenscreen though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not take this picture  
All credit to Michael Huang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not take this picture  

All credit to [Michael Huang](https://www.facebook.com/michael.huang.9085790?pnref=story) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old Town in Tallinn currently </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 19:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have never watched another sport, haven't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 22:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Friend had a talk with a scammer's mom aswell  
  
My friend made money from selling shit in growtopia. He didn't even play it, he just found some kind of a site that double's your world locks if you gave these to them for a week and they are worth good money so he made some business. I remember I was with him when he was about to sell something, literally 11 year olds handed him 150 for fucking growtopia locks.  
  
  
Well once there was a kid who scammed him, because they made the trade online. But since it was on facebook. we had the kids name and all, my friend searched through the kid's facebook friend list and founder her mother. Gave her a call, mother apologized and payed the money.  

Just in case you wonder, my friend told me that selling the world locks for IRL money isn't even allowed, and they ban accounts where you can see stacked up world locks waiting to be sold. He had an account ban literally worth of 3000. Dude is 15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nocturne main streamers/youtubers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 23:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if there was any? Ninjaken doesn't play league anymore basically, streamers overwatch, do you folks know any? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 22:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jack sparrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can some1 explain i dont get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 01:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Holocaust </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KhDV4FmUAoI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't they make cigarettes with some other herb that doesn't contain as much harmful chemicals as tobacco does? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 18:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering, why aren't cigs made up of any other herb other than tobacco, which has less harmful chemicals in it and that doesn't give "high". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why don't they make cigarettes with some other herb that doesn't contain as much harmful chemicals as tobacco does? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 14:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 12:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Reddit Amrchair historians know only about the 20th century and american civil war, WW1 and WW2 that's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a buddhist school so what were you expecting? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 00:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.ee/maps/place/P%C3%A4rnu+Keskus/@58.391886,24.500829,3a,75y,132.95h,91.66t/data=!3m7!1e1!3m5!1s9pJshExlnnbUAEaFl1Vtyw!2e0!6s%2F%2Fgeo0.ggpht.com%2Fcbk%3Fpanoid%3D9pJshExlnnbUAEaFl1Vtyw%26output%3Dthumbnail%26cb_client%3Dmaps_sv.tactile.gps%26thumb%3D2%26w%3D203%26h%3D100%26yaw%3D17.419155%26pitch%3D0%26thumbfov%3D100!7i13312!8i6656!4m5!3m4!1s0x46ecfd3d2a185db3:0x720287523796e5d8!8m2!3d58.3868776!4d24.5019931?hl=en

https://www.google.ee/maps/@58.3919055,24.5025009,3a,39.5y,220.88h,90.97t/data=!3m6!1e1!3m4!1sViXKkbSKbshEXmoxszlxsA!2e0!7i13312!8i6656!6m1!1e1?hl=en
  
Some abandoned factories i believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally collect lighters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that you collect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some broken windows you could climb to and hop. I will give you a little warning and advice - don't break the windows, some of them are indeed alarmed and cops will respond and arrive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] This possible recorder? spongebob song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.facebook.com/unexpectedMemes/videos/1658818897773737/

is there a source for this "song" on the background </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A movie which has something to do with mexico where there was one scene where 2 guys went into a early teens kids house and he took pictures of him to make a fake id. His mom then comes down and they run to their car and it goes forward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 19:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cant describe more. It was definitely very fucking funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiddle had good AoE clear with E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You always have to pay for the visitation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. On the top there is a cafe. You literally just go to the lift's and ride one up. If you want to be nice buy something from the cafe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enter*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need to design a bench back that is 120 cm * 14,5 cm. However, the resolution value in photoshop fucks my shit up. What resolution value do I need to ender so that the imagine zoomed in 100% will be 1:1 with what I want it to be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a rush, but basically I need an imagine exactly 140 cm by 14,5 cm. When the resolution is 72, its too small, 150 its too big etc. What do I need to do so when it is zoomed in to 100% it would be those lengths when I measure it with a ruler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hakuna matata </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't Riot use their iconic fist glass breaking intro/outro on their videos anymore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the little things that make me sad. Clicked on 10 videos from last 4 months didn't seen a single use of it ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 18:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks more like ELiGE's dad lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folks you havent seen CSGO then, everything is misplaced by a few pixels. There was 2 days where /r/globaloffensive 's frontpage was full of stuff like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] The song they are playing in this video (a very popular one, can't remember the name) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qWfyipcTyPo
please :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 18:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is most internationally famous Estonian musician. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man! Thats it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some remix of that ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tr13F8H-pI8  
0:15 to 0:30 was the iconic part, it was some kind of remix of this or smth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a remix of this then. It was more popular than the original i think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A popular song, heard it a ton, cant remember the name. Vocaroo inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://vocaroo.com/i/s1efKmK6emMv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> History has been made. Friend put primary fill, got jungle! Sick proof also! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL  
In Estonia there was once a security firm showing some sites to help people secure their computers or something similar, he types www.re and redtube pops up first. Sadly the video has been removed from YouTube, haven't seen it since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks folks Walk The Line it is I believe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] The song/beat he is playing on the guitar from 0:30 to 2:30 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I certainly have heard it before, some kind of a country riff but i cant think of a name and couldnt find it either. Video from 0:30 https://youtu.be/SDaqqOL_VVY?t=30s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but surely ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought I'd share my spotify reggae playlist, 376 song and updating it slowly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pick happy sounding songs, sad sounding reggae is what i don't listen to. Also newer reggae sucks ass, the vocalist just seems to scream the lyrics somehow, and the music suck too.

For clarity, a happy song: Junior Byles - A Place Called Africa
  
Joe Higgs - Come On Home
 
Culture - Why Am I A Rastaman 

sound really sad to me, both of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tyty man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a new one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roland model psb 1u.  
And yes, I am powering it with the same supply, using a snake.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought i'd share you this gif of when it is exactly occurring when the adapter literally turns itself off. Whenever I plug something in the input audio jack in the pedal or in the amp (if the other end is in the output jack in the pedal ofcourse :D) the light turns off and power is lost. If I just have the power block connected to the amp and pedal everything's fine, adapter light is on. If i put the cable to pedal output, it still is green. If I plug the output cable to amp input, it turns off. When let's say I have put the output in the pedal, not in the amp input yet, but i put another audio cable to the input, without even the other end being connected to my guitar, it turns off. Horrible explanation, I can't explain it better, ain't a native speaker. 

TLDR; Input = no power

https://gfycat.com/ElectricBestAlbatross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will probably try to find another power supply or something with 9V output, will try it again. Sometimes works, sometimes doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pedal doesnt work
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Why doesn't my BOSS DS1 pedal work when I plug in the exact power, 9V with the same pos/neg shit. The red light doesn't light up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 20:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 9V Roland adapter power cable thing. I use a cable snake so I can plug it into the pedal and Roland cube amp. Sometimes it works, most of the times it doesn't.

https://gfycat.com/TautFortunateAsiaticgreaterfreshwaterclam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 00:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estonia - our slavic influences and our nordic influences, also most grandparents living in countryside, where grandchildren and children will help do stuff. Countryside is awesome, there are so little big cities anyways. 90% of people love to be in the countryside i'm quite sure. Our love of nature basically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 19:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/childfree would hate on me, shoot me, hang me, harass me etc. cause im a 15 year old kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering where are you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Africa rest's on a seperate tetonic plate than the Eurasia content, and since it was connected to Asia with such a small land piece, I would be better to call Africa an independent continent. Can't believe I am explaining geography in /r/trees lol.  
North and South America and on different large tetonic plates, therefore they are considered independent continents, also because their connector-land is so tiny etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Continent is such a horrible term tbh. How large is that "large" piece of landmass to get recognized as a independent continent etc. Some argue that a continent is a landmass that is resting on one tetonic plate, but that is arguable, since there are some 10+ tetonic plates, some are just holding the sea with few islands, and we don't define it as a fucking continent. India is on a seperate plate than Eurasia's plate, we don't say that India is a continent, since it is also connected to the landmass of the giant Eurasia content. There is the carribean plate with islands, we don't define those as continents either.   
TL;DR: The term continent is fucking horrible and confusing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A continent is a large piece of landmass from others. Europe and Asia "areas" are on the giant Eurasia continent, divided into two "areas": Europe and Asia.  
I'm just a random 15 year old 4(B or C something i guess?) grade student from Estonia, some people may argue with me, but that's what I learned, i'm quite sure geographists agree with me, and it all makes sense to me myself. If you take an image of the [image of the Eurasia continent](https://thestateofthecentury.files.wordpress.com/2013/02/eurasia-map1.jpg), you can clearly see that Europe and Asia are on this one giant landmass. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredible video quality, production, simple and such a easy but beautiful video desings, incredible information. Love him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 22:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fji is indeed part of Oceania </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 22:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i take fucking hours if i cant alternate pick fast enough sometimes :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia is a continent, Oceania is an area with imaginary borders which contains multiple islands, continent australia etc etc. We have marked areas, which contain continents, which contain countries, islands etc etc.
  
Continents: Australia, Antarctica, Eurasia, Africa, North America, South America.
  
"Areas" (I dont know the English translation, in Estonia we have a word for it ,,maailmajagu"):
Oceania, Europe, Asia, Africa, America, Antarctic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Estonia though, searched through the biggest 2 musical groups and forums for used pedals, effects, and there are like 7. Lot of were new for a price like 30
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 01:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought about getting a Boss DS-1 Distortion, not entirely sure tho, read some reviews and listened to demos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Can you get a good distortion pedal under 60? Could you suggest me some? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for my first pedal, a distortion one. I'm dumb as hell though and my friend aint such an expert either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 03:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only people who call us Viro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 20:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wayyy too big map </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easiest setup ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope their video intros remain the same, fucking love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estonia :)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 20:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stickholder took 2 hits to destroy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't you destroy the rock holder? Shit seems like invincible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colorizebot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 01:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ddosing website is the easiest thing ever, literally get the site's ip and then stress it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just got to Silver 2 with the 31st win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 02:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women ain't expected to be the first to ask a man out. Generally it seems as a girl it is much easier to get into a relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has happened to Azingy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 00:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody know what he does now, if he plays league even anymore etc..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 00:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Josey Wales, Junior Byles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who still cant connect to chat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 22:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 22:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, will there be a next one? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Bayonet | Damascus Steel FT [W] Flip Knife Slaughter MW or Bayonet Blue Steel MW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 19:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B/O: Flip Knife Slaughter MW or Bayonet Blue Steel MW
Sent trade offers here: http://steamcommunity.com/linkfilter/https://steamcommunity.com/tradeoffer/new/?partner=77409314 token=-KhR1cCv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 17:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Witnessing another meme birth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 14:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wish he made the javelin an asiimov or smth :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 13:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Blackjack C1 is beautiful! Awesome guitar you bought mate. Sadly, I believe there is only 1 music shop in Estonia that sells Schecter and that's where I bought mine, there were no Schecter instruments with the sustainiac pickups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 12:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He cheated, but also served his ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 03:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OnePlus 2 :d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 01:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/centaur </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck is there a ban on !knife and !ws plugin? Why did they, what's the point on limiting community servers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GEAR] My week old Schecter Lady Luck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it for 400 at one of the few music shops the capital of Estonia has. Love the sound and the look!  
It already went to a guitar technician for cleaning of the frets, neck etc.

http://imgur.com/a/YJlLd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have opposite opinion, Muay Thai usually sucks, Acolyte are gods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 16:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never seen a good Project Yasou and Primetime Draven. All of them are bad eventually, even if they have a good start. Never seen a Primetime Draven with a positive KDA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What skin users usually suck at their champion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 16:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example: Most Primetime Draven users are horrible at draven etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love how pistols and smg's sound the same now. Also, p250 is supressed and five seven is a fucking machine gun. They remove all the iconic fucking soundings and replace it with the same sound modified for each weapon a bit. SMG's all sound the same...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love how pistols and smg's sound the same now. Also, p250 is supressed and five seven is a fucking machine gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mees sa eestlane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 12:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still read it even though I dont know a single narcissist, but the thing I have noticed is that some of posters think that being punished even once = max level narcissism. I dont know, but you  cant really raise a kid by letting him do everything he she wants, never punishing and telling what might be wrong. Some just cry there for 1 incident in their younger years and are going no contact now, years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colorizebot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 18:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colorizebot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estonia :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 01:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well first time I drunk alcohol was at like 4 when I asked to try beer from my uncle, disliked it. But I suppose you are looking for the first drunk experience. At a friends birthday, freshly turned 15 myself aswell, 1L rum and I had 2g of weed. Drank 4 glasses of 50/50 rum and cola mix, then went to smoke weed in the woods. Worst. Fucking. Idea. Ever. Such a fucking headrush and instant horrible feeling, I leaned onto my friend and somehow got inside, there I went and lied on a couch, swimmed on the floor and did the most random things ever. No big hangover though, so lucky me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make a config files that when I type "exec ezaim" it loads up a certain map? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically I modified a workshop aim practice map for it's lack of armor trigger, I want an easy way to start the map. I thought about making a cfg file that when i execute it, it loads up the map, but couldn't find anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 20:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I know they wont do shit about GOTV demo ticks, however, I would love it to record voice chat. Sometimes in MM funny shit happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 02:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gold record is in /r/leagueoflegends and it is 400-450 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 21:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They shared a girl in the movie basically. While Dean (dude whos driving on the right) was sleeping in the back he woke up told the girl and the dude that he has an genius idea and that you are gonna like it. That was the idea. They were threesoming in the movie before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 19:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The laws ain't that different. Basics are the same everywhere. Since they have an ukrainian license it if safe to assume that they can handle the vehicle and know the basic and fundemental laws in ukraine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you personally believe that flusha was hacking some time ago with his wierd flicks to people's heads through walls etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he got kicked from Titan for ScreaM, he fragged more and consistently more than others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the moment that your game of Truth or Dare had to do something with sex and dicksucking pussylicking fucking gangbang orgy HIV AIDS hERPES </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OnePlus 2 Double tap to open screen and double-pushed home button to open camera don't work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 01:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got the phone a week ago. I have both of the settings on, none of them work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 04:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> E-boyfriend LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 19:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oui's Lollipops were really fun ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 19:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? I was talking about phantomlord. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 19:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 years ago, in 2013, he was playing League. He was a good streamer back then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 15:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happens so often only in CSGO, in LoL it happens like once in 10 games and when browsing the net, it happens even more rarely. Btw, I shaked the mouse on intention to see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse gets stuck very often in CSGO. You can see it at the end, it even gets me killed. What's the problem? It happens this often only in CSGO. (Dont hate on the video, quality and sound aint that important :D) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 15:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my uncle taught me that too, the best i have made so far. It is basically as OP's expect the locker holder is smaller
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 01:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SmitZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZBOTZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 13:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/9om-H064Bxk?t=6m35s

also here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 80 difference, didnt have the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just ordered a onePlus 2, what should i know about the phone? Bugs, glitches, features etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 21:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope it will be delivered in 13 days as promised :D A friend has it, he likes it. He doesn't know anything but that it is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 20:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's through :D but the comment said that saving any kind lf animal poop. It aint right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 18:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicken and cow shit can be used as  natural fertilizers for greenhouses, strawberry bushes etc, often better than the chemical shit you buy in the store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 09:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you are like 75 if it was your grandpa :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a fan of barter system, dont know how we could make it work this late, tbh I would like a modified communism/marxism or anarchism. Money just seems seperate us all and makes people materialistic. Consumption is huge. Some people care about nothing than money and power, since more and more money nowadays seems to rise one's power over other individuals. It seperates us.  
Then again, im 15, so it might just be my retarded logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Op, how old are you currently, was your grandpa born in 1878..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money and capitalism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiat Multipla </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kama, dont even know the translation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eastern european countries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/popping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4chan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see films in dreams, like american pie sometimes. But probably the dream where I skateboard on walls doing penta kickflip backflips on walls in order to impress a girl and fuck her. Was 9. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> School shooters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estonians politics LOL, if you understood what goes on here, its like a fucking circus lol. Not presidental elections though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Estonia, theres Mardipev. Children dress up as Mardisandid, looking like old men, singing, questioning in order to get stuff from house to house. A long tradition, sadly disappearing slowly because kids run halloween cuz easier to get free stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In estonia a bottle of water is 50 or 60 cents, also in sunday shops are always open </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 00:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is the Zaza you see guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 00:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see, where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Bringing multiple lighters on my way home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 15:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, me and one of my friend collect lighters. I'm going to Italy the day after tomorrow. I thought about buying the cool lighters I see in shops, but then I thought how and can I even bring them on the plane back? Let's say about 5 lighters I would like to buy atleast. I read that I gotta put them in hand luggage not the checked luggage  

I know that I can buy them after the security check if there are some souvenir shops etc, when I went to barcelona I just bought 3 after the security check and later just walked onto the plane with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 03:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf is america really that expensive that a lunch meal is 10 bucks or you just go into restaurant to get that medium rare steak with a potato or smth? In estonia, a good tasting, healthy, lunch type meal is like 6 euros  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
