<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8145</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I double tapped a book bc I was trying to find a definition for the word  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second Desert Dwellers! I like some DJ Drez. I like Cosmopole by Cantoma and most of the Mantras in Motion album. Sombience by EarthRise SoundSystem. Bonobo - Shadowtricks and Ketto. Maybe ODESZA. Man o to by Nu. You can try DJ Hyfi on soundcloud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can unbutton your pants and close the door, I would suggest some seated poses where you're not doing splits (risking tearing your work pants apart) - so like a wide legged forward fold, a low lunge (but not pigeon ...), reclining twist. 

You can also stay seated in your office chair and just lean onto your thighs in like a seated forward fold. 

And you can do great neck stretches. Bring your left arm behind your back and grab the wrist with your right hand. Then work on slowly moving your head around and explore the area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> move along, nothing to see here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my night time audible book that I dont ever listen to during the day. It's one I'm not super interested in. And when I start the book, I tend to doze off within 5-10 minutes, retaining nothing of what I listened. I actually got it free off this sub and it's an Irish ghost story. I've been at the same part of the story for about 3 weeks now. 

If you want something kind of interesting and light, I would go with a YA book. Like To all the boys I've loved before or Eleanor and Parks. I wouldnt want something super exciting that I dont want to turn off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Billy Collins. I own maybe 7 books of poetry and his is one of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Honor of World Poetry Day, What's your favorite poem or line from a poem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poetry reaffirms our common humanity by revealing to us that individuals, everywhere in the world, share the same questions and feelings. Poetry is the mainstay of oral tradition and, over centuries, can communicate the innermost values of diverse cultures.

One of the main objectives of the Day is to support linguistic diversity through poetic expression and to offer endangered languages the opportunity to be heard within their communities.

The observance of World Poetry Day is also meant to encourage a return to the oral tradition of poetry recitals, to promote the teaching of poetry, to restore a dialogue between poetry and the other arts such as theatre, dance, music and painting, and to support small publishers and create an attractive image of poetry in the media, so that the art of poetry will no longer be considered an outdated form of art, but one which enables society as a whole to regain and assert its identity.

[via](http://www.un.org/en/events/poetryday/)

I'm a huge fan of Mary Oliver! 

*When it's over, I want to say: all my life I was a bride married to amazement. I was the bridegroom, taking the world into my arms.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was one of the people who really liked it. The writing style and story makes it a fairly fast read. 

Noah Hawley is a writer/producer for Fargo too. I think that's one of the reasons the book was very easy for me to visualize. 

If you don't get too attached to the people but are okay with just hearing a good story, you should like the book!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thelma and Louise going on between Rosita and Sasha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rosita's scar is healing but Maggie still doesn't look pregnant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna roll with Negan's crew. Hilltop is all skinny twerps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rosasha or Sashito?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did love Emma Watsons squeak when Beast left  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read both Grady Hendrix books - Horrorstor and My Best Friend's Exorcism. Horrorstor is about employees trapped in a haunted IKEA-like store. My Best Friend's Exorcism is about two friends in high school and their relationship as one of them becomes possessed. I liked My Best Friend's Exorcism better bc the 80s references had me laughing early on. These are less horror and more humor. 

The Troop by Nick Cutter is more body/gore horror. But it's a fun horror read. Not much humor but the kids are unique personalities and the setting is easy to picture. I imagined the author had a sense of humor when writing the book. 

I don't know too much about sci-fi horror ... but I think the Grady Hendrix ones are pretty fun comedy-horror books. They're silly though! Don't expect horror Shakespeare  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Book Thief for the following reasons: boring (most books set in this era are interesting and exciting), characters that didn't change, self-important prose that didnt make sense or was overwritten. And the choice of Death narrating added almost nothing significant to the story (which is why you often hear other people who don't like the book say Death as the narrator is merely a gimmick). 

I've heard the author intended this book to be adult fiction, but it's marketed as teen fiction bc it does well in that category. I read this before a lot of the hype started coming out. And the more people started raving, I kept thinking "did I miss something?" And my dislike for the book over the years has turned into hatred ... 

Also hated The Curious Dog in the Nighttime. I really liked Rosie Project though .... 

Not a fan of Kingkiller Chronicles and RPO but those are talked about on this sub quite a bit. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that could have gone a lil worse :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/childrenfallingover  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have about a 1:58 500m row and it took me about 3 minutes and some change (less than 10 sec) to do the row. It sucks bc I saw 22 cals and the math on that is less than half the distance to 55 cals; it was very demoralizing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have an in-gym competition and want to "beat" the scaled people, just do a few deadlifts and get on the scoreboard as Rx. If you wanna do a workout though, I would do scaled. The last workout isn't going to be much better! It always irks me when people do Rx and get 1 rep and beat all the scaled people, but you're allowed to do it, so it's part of the game. 

It comes down to if you want to move through the workout or if you just want to spend the 13 (or whatever) minutes looking at the barbell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 03:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If 65# goes up easy, maybe just try one or two reps and get on the board! You don't have to do all 55. Then next year, see where you're at  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> baking soda works wonders for whitening my teeth. i just add a touch of it on top of my toothpaste. 

i have no proof of this. but anecdotally ... i have gone to the dentist to get the trays and the whitening product you put on your teeth for 30 minutes before bed (that stuff you syringe into the trays) and then you rinse with some mouthwash afterwards ... but i think the baking soda honestly works just as good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you lie, boaty mcboatface </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A coworker of mine is very mild-mannered and humble. He loves vegetation and hiking; like he is the type of guy you want on a zombie apocalypse bc he can tell you what to eat during that first month of foraging through the forest. He was showing me some pics of plants that he had taken me on a hike (not colorful flowers ... just green plants that all look the same to me). And I was like "Ohhh, cute," and he had his arms crossed, very pleased with himself and then motioned for me to keep scrolling. And then all of a sudden it's a picture of him in nothing but black briefs and white crew socks. He has his hand on his hip and his other foot resting on a couch. I still dont know if he know I saw it and I dont think he was trying to get me (a female) to check him out (he's a gay male). I just thought it was kind of sweet and innocent that it wasnt a dick pic ... but a pretty tame "sexy" shot. Where he's wearing terry cloth socks that hit low to mid calf.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I won a ride on the Zamboni during a hockey game and an all expense trip to Florence Italy for doing a Dating on Demand video for Comcast. 

It's why I don't 100% hate Comcast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw thirteen reasons why on the scroll up top so that's how i found your comment. 

I liked thirteen reasons why but i think it might portray suicide among teens in an unrealistic way. but im not too well versed on the topic ... but i found it a little disingenuous for that reason. 

but if you're in that YA mood, i would really suggest Love Letters to the Dead for a more somber serious read. And then I would also suggest To All the Boys I've Loved Before for a fun, light-hearted  read (even though you totally didnt ask!).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Rosie Project scroll up top so that's how I found your comment. I thought the book read like a romantic comedy/mystery and I adored it. I laughed and thought it was so fun. It was one of Bill Gates best books of whatever year on his Gates Notes blog. It's definitely worth a read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there's a gym (in Woodstock GA of all places) that makes you do 1-on-1 fundamentals sessions. Ranging from 10-20 sessions depending on your physical abilities. And I think it runs at least 60 per lesson. It's almost cheaper to show up with an L1 certification! 


I felt like when I was looking for my 2nd gym, the going rate was around 160-250 for my area (Im in the suburbs of Atlanta). And the fundamentals classes last about 2 weeks. Typically 3-6 classes and you have about 2-4 people in the class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, so many people are awful when they begin. Set your ego aside in the beginning and work on the basics. Do manageable weights (dont grab what the guy next to you is grabbing). When doing skill work, grab a coach that's just hanging out and ask them to check out your next practice lift so you can get that coaching that crossfit offers. Coaches are people too and sometimes they get glamoured by the bigger lifts and their "friends" in the class, so you have to sometimes fight for that attention if you're new. It sucks but it's a reality. With you being tall, any weird thing youre doing with your body is probably super visible. You have longer levers and you just want to start off with a good base so when you start adding weight, it's not arms and limbs flying everywhere and torquing and twisting things that dont need to be torquing and twisting in those directions! 

Good luck you're not alone in this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is super interesting, thank you for sharing! I remember growing up in the late 80s, in health class we learned about both type of diabetes (and plus Stacey from the Babysitters Club had the genetic diabetes), so it's weird/culturally interesting that nowadays people automatically assume you have the adult onset type. 

They just found out my friend's child has type 1. It was a huge adjustment for them. Neither parents had diabetes, and I never heard my friend really talk about diabetes in her family. So it felt like it came out of nowhere. She was about 4 when she was diagnosed. My mom would babysit her and she would always talk about her head feeling funny. Then one day they had to rush her to the hospital bc she had some type of fainting spell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started crossfit in 2008 and the gym I started at would let you slide in without taking the fundamentals class bc they were just trying to get new members. Now, that same gym wouldnt dream of it. 

If the gym is older and/or they already program some type of Rx and scaled version, I woudlnt automatically assume it's an unsafe gym if they dont mandate a fundamentals class. 

If a member can make a time slot for regular class time but cant make the limited time options for the specific fundamentals class, are you going to just turn away all those potential members?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my gym does it and I can only say what I observe ... but they set up a later time slot. And it looks like it was a crossfit elements class with a short workout at the end, using what they just learned. 

They also had a facebook group (just for the new you) where they talked about nutrition and food. That seemed to be a big part of the work! 

I think New You helps with getting new members. And they're not necessarily the groupon types who are just looking for a deal. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read how to read literature like a professor ... and that book might be a good starting point for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://basketballpredictions.blogspot.com

You have to wait a bit bc he typically posts a quarter of the bracket like once a day. I don't see anything up yet. 

I use his commentary combined with 538 from the New York Times. 

I won my office pool one time this way! Once out of 7 times buttttt I'll take it. 

If you're in a big pool, choose a lower seed to go all the way!! Good luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spine first so the book's pages point straight up to the sky if the book were open  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will remove this announcement after Thursday bc I know we have a LOT of people not in the USA (and even inside the USA) who really dgaf about college basketball! 

Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I signed up r/curlyhair for the Annual r/CollegeBasketball bracket challenge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you never know if the bookmark is gonna fall out. People who don't place the spine down are living on the edge as far as I'm concerned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like most of the Rx people at my gym didnt really get past 8 minutes of 17.3. The video that CrossFit HQ put out [by Nicole Carroll](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GDQyzlp-HuU) included tips for this workout. She suggested it was a pulling workout. And I think for most Rx people, it IS. 

I did scaled. And most people, doing scaled, are going to make it out of 8 minutes. So after watching this video, I tried to not use a lot of my arms with the jumping pullups. But my legs were jelly when I got to the later rounds of scaled. I didnt trust them when I did my snatches! Jumping pullups seem like such a joke but I had to break mine up when I got to the 3rd round! 

Next time I think I won't use Rx strategy videos going into a scaled Open workout ... thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Team of Rivals on audiobook. That's a good 3 months listening for me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a bag with two compartments, so I always put the book in a compartment by itself with the spine down. The edges get rubbed down a little bit but I expect that to happen with books I throw in my purse so it doesnt bother me. 

And this is definitely one of those times where I found a kindle or ereader solved all my problems. Now I can have 100 books in my purse, no problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if they'll touch on some of the women's issues that the creator was very supportive of, or show some of the, uhhhh, bondage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaderboard Issues and people waiting til the last minute to input scores - Why doesn't HQ just hide the scores until the workout is closed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like that would remove the incentive to delay entering your score ... and then it would be exciting to see where everyone stood.  You could have 2-3 days to dispute scores then the leaderboard would be locked for that workout once the next workout started?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crap I actually haven't seen that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I'm the one on back not getting what's going on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a good musical that's out of the theater ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends and I are having a musical movie night. 

I know La La Land is out there but we're looking for something already available. Preferably Prime or Netflix, but we'd rent too. 

My friend is making Korean pork but the movie doesn't have to match! I'd like something newer and not Singing in the Rain. My friend wants to see Julie Andrews. Soooo as you can see we are not super focused so all suggestions are welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone doing Rx, I'm going to ask them to show me their squat snatch. If they're catching it high and I see that pause above parallel, I'm going to tell them that's a no rep beforehand - so they don't get surprised during the workout. Like you chose to do Rx, so do Rx. But if they catch at parallel and then get the depth with the bounce, I'm not gonna split hairs. No ones going to regionals that I'm judging. 

It's really the scaled people busting out their jumping pull-ups and not starting at extension that will be more difficult for me to call bc they typically go fast ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I judged a scaled person tonight! It's not that bad. But Id suggest using something very similar to the scorecard HQ put out so you know the reps and when to write the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mein fist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, it's okay to read some 200-300 page books just to get a sense of "completion" and moving through books. I know when I read some long books back to back, I feel like I'm not getting anywhere sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a lot of luck with ebay. Here's a listing of their [groove shorts](http://www.ebay.com/sch/i.html?_from=R40 _trksid=p2050601.m570.l1313.TR3.TRC0.A0.H0.Xlululemon+groove+shorts.TRS0 _nkw=lululemon+groove+shorts _sacat=0).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are those amazon ones see through? That's a good price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 14:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to be such a basic b but I love the lululemon groove shorts. they're a teensy bit longer. I wouldnt call them compression by any means but they look cute on and stay put during a workout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://games.crossfit.com/athlete/127253

There's Jen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, on his ig he said he can only do like brisk walking 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I heard him say during last years Games that he already had this years planned out. So if that's the case, they're way ahead. But I wonder how much of that is true. It would be silly to hear feedback from 2016 Games and not apply that towards 2017 even if you already have it planned out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definite Fikowski fan and then Khan Porter for other reasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sellout was a good find for the thrift store bc I feel like it's relatively new and was reviewed well but not, like, Gone Girl popular  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just joined my first league. Im like a 2.5 with the USTA rating, I think. I have a tennis court in my condo area but no one to practice with but we do have a small wall to hit the ball against. Do you have any good drills to just get all around better?! Youtubes would be nice. If I hit a ball over the fence it goes into a creek and I only have like 4 tennis balls and I seem to lose one ball every half hour if I'm practicing far away from the wall, so I'm looking for advice and tips and maybe other drills to do against the wall. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gene Simmons played a radio DJ and Ozzy Osbourne played the preacher in Trick or Treat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Piranha? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CrossFit Scaled Life

Im glad I came here to see that Castro impression :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only read the caption but it reminds me of Han Kang's *The Vegetarian* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Vampires in the Lemon Grove by Karen Russell
 I feel like an extremely unimaginative writer in comparison.

I know! I dont love her books but she is a fantastic writer. Her ideas are interesting and her writing is pretty unique to the standard stuff I end up reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Better shape up ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look Richonne, no one likes your happiness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has a book ever inspired you to take a journey? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this question on Goodreads ([here](https://www.goodreads.com/book_movie_challenges/show/6172), if you're interested) to promote the movie The Shack ... I searched for reddit's thoughts and didnt find a thread on the subject! 

For me, it was Burial Rites by Hannah Kent. The author described this dreary, stark version of Iceland in the 19th century. So unfortunately I'd have to time travel! But I could feel the ice in the air and hear the ocean. Even though the book was a sad journey, I've never had as much wanderlust as I had reading that book. 

Even though I didnt go anywhere, that was one book where I *really* felt the setting. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andrea Ager </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an L4/L5 herniation. And that seems fairly common. What is the deal with C6 and C7? What movement causes that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the tip of one of this fingers got cut off. I dont think it was crossfit related though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found out Nike is selling plus size. How late am I to this party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you done any bodyweight stuff or exercising since?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had powerlifters turn off the dubstep and change it to Rent every time they walked into the door.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if it's quite a bit cheaper?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the problems can be the judging. It's REALLY hard to no rep someone who is maybe half an inch above parallel and you're not SURE if they're low enough and they're stronger than you so they're PROBABLY doing it right it doesnt matter anyways bc they've done 10 other wall balls while you've been debating this in your head. 

The best way to get better at judging is to actually do it. I have judged competitions before and messing up and knowing how to quickly and effectively tell someone they've no repped ... knowing what are the most likely ways someone will no rep a rep ... exactly knowing the standards ... and then using it in real world application and not the video standard,  it's made a world of difference. 

So in regards to the cheating ... if you're an athlete you might not even realize you were doing shitty reps bc you had a shitty judge. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scale scale scale! 30# for you is a LOT different than 30# for someone who is 180# and has been relatively fit and strong their whole life. 

When I started, I was at 2 days a week. But my mistake was that I would not really do anything on my days off. So I just stayed sore between my crossfit visits. I upped it to 3 days a week and I actually starting seeing results in that I wouldnt be so sore ALL the time. 

And I would choose much lighter weights than a lot of the people at the gym. You're new, you're smaller, you're learning. It's YOUR body, you have to deal with the consequences of the workout. Write down the weights you use and smiley face or a frowny face next to it, depending on how you felt afterwards. Was it manageable or too much? If you're finishing after everyone or hitting the time caps a lot, go lighter or do less reps. 

If your gym has an issue with that, you can find another one that understands how to help people who are new to this type of exercise. 

Good luck! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old are you? 

Great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know why but I'm a sucker for these videos when people from other fitnesses try crossfit out and vice versa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 21:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 95! But I've also started to search for the shorter ones (like less than 9 hours) on Overdrive using my library. I have a fairly short commute so it's difficult to get through more than one book a month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in the hospital for at least a week. A friend of a friend of a friend was much older and was only in there for 3 days. Do you think they kept him that long bc of actual damage or what? 

This is all rumor but that same friend told me he was working out and there happened to be a doctor there and an AED. If that's the case, lucky guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can we adopt him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so I was totally thinking of Lumiere before I read the article but maybe the candles are stored in the closet at the Beast's castle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this has already been asked, but how do you choose which books, how many, and whether or not to do audiobook/ebook? What is the title of the person that does this job? What are their other job duties?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the most rare or interesting book that you guys have?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WAT you can borrow a musical instrument?? I love that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really a jump scare movie. Just a lot of close ups of faces. There's one part where they're driving to her parent's house and they hit a deer. And then when he goes out for a smoke, you see one of the house workers running towards him and then he veers away last minute ... and that popped up in a trailer and it's not really a jump scare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont understand why the crossfit site sucks so bad. Crossfit seems to make oodles of $$$$, they have the bulk of the Games ran by volunteers. They don't pay the athletes ... at least have an awesome website that functions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, im a huge falcons fan and didnt want to disrespect the sub but i was like OK U GOT ME NY DAILY NEWS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a little Oscars humor from the New York Daily News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your reply! I herniated a disc (like over a year ago) and I think that finding a good treatment plan after (and going to a gym that understands injury and how to design and scale for you) is essential to getting back moving. 

I had a lot of luck with active release and was very glad when a chiro I tried out implemented it. I had been going to someone just cracking my back. I'd go in and out in 15 minutes. My new person sees me for 30-40 and seems to do little to no bone adjustment and does a lot of the active release techniques. And the neurosurgeon was able to diagnose me ... but the treatment plan from those guys is surgery, shots, wait it out, pain meds, etc. So it's nice to have someone be like ... oh, you have a tight psoas - try these exercises. 

I did 17.1 scaled and my back is sore but I definitely don't feel injured! But would I do it again to get a better time? Hell no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it also helps when someone else is counting your reps for you. Like you can just turn off your mind and go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Shave and a Haircut*

"What's up my Neegs?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negan is married to the pretty little liars  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eugene is as serious as sepsis y'all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the wives are wearing LBDs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! That's totally it. Thank you. 

Are the characters gay on the show? Do you know?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of the Loop: what is the fandom with the asian cartoon ice skaters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see them on tumblr a lot and it seems to have like the two ice skater cartoon asian dudes smooching. What do people like about this fandom so much and why is it always on my dash?! What is it based off of? I've tried to google ice skating cartoon and I dont see anything pop up. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone read The End of Dieting? Does it just rehash his other works? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Eat to Live and Fasting   Eating for Health. And I also have two cookbooks (ETL). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go to games.crossfit and go to your affiliate and click the team icon, it should bring up just your gym's leaderboard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed! But then you realize you havent even done half the reps at that point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an RX rope and they're not like the traditional speed ropes. I like it bc once you cut the rope, you dont have to worry about the handle sliding up and down the rope (like the spealler one I have from Rogue will sometimes do). 

But they're heavier ... the heavier, thicker rope helps me with my double unders personally ... but if you're used to a speed rope, this might be a difficult rope for you to use. But it's the only rope I use now. I have a hard time going with the thinner Spealler rope from Rogue now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Born a Crime, by Trevor Noah, narrated by Trevor Noah**

It won an Audie award and it was fantastic. He talks in the language, the accents, mimicing his mother .... you cant really get that with the book. And there's really nothing like hearing an author reading their own book. I typically enjoy them like that. 

I have also bought LaRose by Erdrich. She also narrates her own work and that has received a lot of high praise!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate when I get book shaming from people who dont read in the first place. Like, cool, it took you two years to read Steve Jobs biography but you're going to make fun of me for reading twilight over 7 years ago and it was like 3 books out of 30 I read that year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I have a full time job and sometimes I have a part time fitness instructor gig, then I work out. And then I need to clean and wash clothes and make food and talk to people and drink alcohol and then it's like UGH how do people find time to write daily! But then this might work for me. INstead of me not writing at all (bc I cant seem to make it happen every day so I dont do it AT ALL, makes sense ...) a good alternative might be to just dedicate a less busy day to writing. WHY DIDNT I THINK OF THIS BEFORE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really admire that you set up a daily writing habit, that's definitely my goal!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished Born A Crime by Trevor Noah. I am not that familiar with him and I dont watch the Daily Show. But it won an Audie Award so I gave it a shot. No regrets! He was a little shit growing up in South Africa. He didnt quite fit in but he has a great, interesting life story. And I didnt know anything about apartheid and I learned so much while laughing. 

I also have Shoe Dog by Knight on my to-read list! 

Broken by Laura Hillenbrand has a great narrator and the story of this guy's life is AMAZING. But it's WWII, so that might not be your cup of tea. It's a serious read, and Zamperini was a POW, an Olympian, a pilot, and lost at sea for a month. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have a daily writing habit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to write daily but I feel like it takes me at least an hour to get into a "writing flow". But it might just take me that long bc I dont have a good daily writing habit. 

For those who write every day, or thereabouts, do you allot time for it? How long?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mainly read books and hardly read fanfiction. 
 
I just finished Trevor Noah's Born a Crime and I started Homegoing by Yaa Gyasi. Both these books are super illuminating about Africa and the African experience!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] 07x10 Question about Daryl's intentions at the end of the episode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When that guy was talking to Daryl (I forgot his name), it seemed like he was going to attack Negan's group, lead a trail of weapons back to Carol's place, and then have Negan exact revenge on Carol to inspire Ezekiel to join in officially against Negan.

Then Daryl was like "No." 

But then Daryl seemed to want to keep Carol in her house, by herself, by not telling her that Glenn died? 

My group watching the show made it seem like Daryl was like ... leaving Carol out there to fend for herself. He wasn't protecting her from pain, like he was leaving her there bc she's given up essentially and like he cut her off. 

Because what's going to stop that guy from going with his plan alone? He seems pretty determined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt have an ACL tear but I did have a back injury (disc herniation) that really threw me for a loop over a year ago. 

I talked to the gym owners I taught at and explained I wouldnt be able to demo poses, but I asked if I could use some of the students to demo if the class needed demos. And so we found subs for classes where it just was not feasible for me to teach. Lucky for me, I have never really done yoga when I teach it, I can talk through most of the class (we had a thread about this awhile back). So it actually wasnt a huge change for my students. The gym people in charge have taken a few of my classes so they knew my style of teaching fairly well, so they ok'ed me to teach, using students to demo if I needed to. I explained what was going on to the class (and they were awesome about it). 

And teaching yoga happened to be the easiest part of that journey! The gym and the students were all great about the whole thing! 


And, going through an injury like that, it can make you a more sympathetic yoga instructor for sure. Good luck with your journey! You might have tough parts but I've seen plenty of people make it through with grace!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to be a movie, so just know that after you read it, you'll be ahead of the curve! 

I have a hard time with Erik Larson as well at times. I actually prefer like Laura Hillenbrand bc I think she makes the stories read more like fiction than Larson. But Larson does some great research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading I Am Legend (book) and I find it more depressing than The Road by Cormac McCarthy. I'm only a few chapters in, but I find it hard to pick up bc it really bums me out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed some key things apparently  like I saw the doctor trying to rape Hannah and I barely remember seeing the burnt face but never made the barron connection  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no! I didn't know she had another book out, running to amazon brb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Visit by Shyamalan ... I saw them around the same time and they're not super similar but I remember liking them both a lot! I think I went into them not expecting much. They're both Found footage. 

You might like The Den - it might be a netflix thing. It's not half bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed Burial Rites! It was rumored to be a movie starring Jennifer Lawrence but I think that got scrapped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nic pizzolatto! he was one of the exec producers of hbo's true detective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard Lincoln in the Bardo is excellent. I bought it but have yet to listen to it. George Saunders was on Dinner Party Download this weekend so I think I'm going to listen to it after I finish Alien out of the shadows!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didnt Daryl tell Carol about Glenn croaking?! 

My friends were all like ... Daryl is setting up Carol by not telling her (because that guy with the kneepads was going to lead Negan's people to Carol bc she's living solo).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read On Such a Full Sea? I had it from the library but I never cracked it open.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this the book that the movie leonardo dicaprio was based on? the movie was really good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **A Monster Calls, by Patrick Ness**

Got this from the library bc they had it and I remembered being like, "Isnt this a movie?" I knew where the book was heading but I ended up bawling like a baby during the last part anyways. 

I also cried during my previous book, Born a Crime by Trevor Noah. It was all shits and giggles and then I get to one part and just bawling during that too. It was on an audiobook so I was driving at the time, looking a hot mess on my commute. 
 
**Homegoing, by Yaa Gyasi**

Started this one last week but I'm not very far in. This African chick's mom is trying to marry her off to a white guy. She wanted to marry the warrior chief so Im kind of bummed for her.  


**The Doll-Master and Other Tales of Terror, by Joyce Carol Oates**

I havent cracked this one open yet but I'm starting it during lunch. Hopefully it won't make me cry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I started the movie at 10:10pm and by midnight, I still had 40 minutes left and I fell asleep. 

Can someone point out a good blog post that can tell me what the hell happened. I woke up and that doctor was trying to have sex with hannah. And then again, I flittered in and out of consciousness when they put a feeding tube of eels into that guy's throat. Does it all connect or just arbitrary weird things?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand to-be-read lists, but I honestly don't get those arbitrary book challenges lists. Like who cares if you read a book by "an author whose name starts with the letter P" when there's actual valid reasons to read other books. The books I want to read far outweigh any likes I get by crossing out some spot on social media hasta/bingo bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually have an audiobook going on and then a book on my cellphone (typically an Overdrive book from the library). This gives me something to read or listen to during my commute or during lunch at work. 

Then I have one (rarely two) going on in book format. One is typically a "fun" read and the other is a nonfiction or more literary fiction. 

Such a fan of technology though! I don't have to lug books in my purse like I used to before I figured out how to read books on my Overdrive/Kindle app  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Alien: Out of the Shadows, by Audible Studios**

It won an Audie award so I'm checking it out. I'm not super familiar with the Alien universe, but I'm actually following along fairly easy. 

Next, I think I'll check out that Fred the Vampire Accountant book  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know! Something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know why they don't include a t-shirt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was reading Night Film, I kept hearing about books by Lauren Beukes - Broken Monsters, Shining Girls ... 

have you read any of them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I actually came looking for a movie discussion thread, hoping to hear something good about the movie. I haven't heard much (even on Reddit) and was kinda bummed to see the RT rating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to see this movie in the theater but it's not looking so good with Rotten Tomatoes so now I'm talking myself out of it  ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive actually listened to The Troop by Nick Cutter, that was fun. It's about a scoutmaster who takes his boyscouts on a camping trip to a Nova Scotia (?) island. This frail dude walks onto their camp and shit gets weird. The kids all had different personalities so it was very easy to follow along. More body gore. 

I saw "Alien: Out of the Shadows: An Audible Original Drama" on the Audie awards and so I got that recently. Havent listened to it yet, though! It's about 4.5 hours. 

I have Certain Dark Things on my wish list (the one by Pack) too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the 2 and 4 ratings. I dont trust people who LOVED or HATED books that strongly, the 1s and 5s. And I feel like 3s dont have an opinion either way. 2s and 4s are my go-tos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Born a Crime, by Trevor Noah, narrated by Trevor Noah**

I JUST finished this one today. I laughed and learned and then in one part, I cried. And I listen to audiobooks on my commute so I was crying in my car. 

edit: i just downloaed the utterly uninteresting and unadventurous tales of fred the vampire accountant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in r/Atlanta and someone had posted a picture of a car on 75N pointing south (no one died, just a car causing a shit-ton of traffic and pointing in the wrong direction on a major freeway), and I said something along the lines of "I bet it's a woman" and immediate downvotes. 

ANNNNND, come find out, it was totally a woman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love having a denser book and then a more "fun" book going on at the same time. 

Sometimes it's a nonfiction with a fluffy fiction read. But other times, I will read a 'heavy' thematic fiction book and then have some nonfiction like Mary Roach, Bill Bryson or an SNL memoir as my "fluff" read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this going as a listen? I had the library book but i dont think I could read it all in under 3 weeks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it dumber fun than ready player one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone talks about Cormac McCarthy's the Road as being very sad and devastating. But after one or two chapters into I Am Legend, I find it really hard to pick up because the character is so isolated. It's harder for me to read than The Road! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always see Prey at library book sales.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Hillbilly Elegy on my audible list! I think it was up for an Audie award if I'm not mistaken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Daryl's in the shelf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew some people liked SJ Watson's before i go to sleep (which actually became a movie starring Nicole Kidman ... but I dont think many people saw it). It got a lot of comparisons to Gone Girl (before GIrl on the Train came out). I read it though and the plot kind of  reminded me of Memento. But the characters were kind of meh to me. I enjoyed reading the book though. 

Good Girl by Mary Kubica was another book I put on my to-read list after Gone Girl, but I've never read it. 

I really liked the unique characters in Gone Girl. And I really found that in Descent by Tim Johnston. He writes great characters and the story is a bit dark. 

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I get towards the end of my commute, there's typically a good stopping point in the story where I can stop the audiobook and where I'm also at a red light or something. Then I'm not losing my place in the story as I'm paying less and less attention bc IM ALMOST HOME.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love audiobooks narrated by the author, especially comedians and memoir type books. 

Currently listening to Born a Crime by Trevor Noah. 

have also listened to: 
- Bill Bryson, basically a nonfiction writer. He doesnt have a great narrator voice but by the end, I really liked him narrating. 

- Billy Crystal, I am not a true Crystal fan. Growing up I'd always be like "ugh, this guy again?" when he'd host the Oscars. I tolerated him bc he was in Princess Bride. But his audiobook was fantastic! Very sentimental and actually funny man. He does his Muhammid Ali impressions and you CANT just get that experience reading the book. 

- Aziz Ansari Modern Romance. Great listen. Laughing like an idiot in my car. 

- Amy Poehler, she's very nice and I found her sweet. But she doesnt really have any PUNCH to the audiobook. 

- Jenny Lawson - her voice actually was very distracting and off-putting. This book was the one with the squirrel or rodent reaching it's arms out and it got a lot of high praise within the audiobook community. But I didnt like the book at all. 

-  George Carlin, which I've read his books and it's just not the same

- Chris Hadfeld (the astronaut, I loved this one!)


Those are the ones that I've either listened to recently or they stick out for various reasons. I'd love to listen to Neil DeGrasse Tyson. I feel like his would be a wonderful listen too bc he's such a great host and tv interview.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. 

I actually have a kind of awful, but kind of enjoyable audiobook (that I  actually got on reddit from a free code giveaway) just for this purpose. I was wide awake at 1:11 last night. Turned on that audiobook, 45 minute sleep timer, put aside my phone, and was out in 5 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author has a new book called Human Acts! I read Vegetarian too. I dont think I completely got it, but I definitely recognize Han Kang's boldness in her writing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can just tell you my experience ...

I paid like $4000 for a 200 hour course. It included books and free attendance to the studio's yoga classes. And we had Saturday and Sunday all day training for, god, what felt like months. 

At the end, we did a demonstration that we could talk through sun salutations (basically), we had a ceremony, got our certificate and that was that. My point is - my studio wasnt that picky about the TYPE of yoga you taught, but could you demonstrate teaching poses safely. 

Are you trying to get certified through a Yoga Alliance place? Or some special certification that is like YogaFit or DDP Yoga? Or are you doing like a Mysore thing? If your goal is to teach at a typical studio ... wouldnt said studio want you to mention "traditional" yoga? 


I'd ask them to be more specific about why you're not passing. Would they like to see more alignment cueing? Different class setup? What do they NEED to see from you? You paid them, so they can give you better feedback. 


Is the organization asking you to go to more training and workshops that THEY run (like, are they just trying to get your money)? Are other people in the class going through the same thing?  

As for the teaching skills, the way to get that is through teaching. You might can teach at gyms, or at churches, places like that. It just really depends on the owner and what they'll accept in terms of certification.  Maybe say you'd like to be put on a sub list. You can, last resort, post on facebook and see if anyone wants to help you out by taking a FREE yoga class! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [cant ... see ...](http://i.imgur.com/NyKI8Qc.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With regard to the sensation in the upper back ... I would let go of your toes, shins, calves or whatever your grabbing and just relax the upper body. USE gravity. 

If you're seated and you feel like you're rolling backwards into the tailbone, adjust from your base and roll toward the front of your crotch. If that doesnt help, prop up your hips with a blanket [LIKE THIS](http://media.yogajournal.com/wp-content/uploads/BAS_260_02_fnl.jpg) (ignore her hands). Use gravity to help you with your seated forward folds (like it helps you with your standing). 

Use your arms to lift you up [like this](http://www.yogabasics.com/YB-NEW/wp-content/uploads/2013/11/Paschimottanasana8826.jpg) not pulling [like this](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/originals/0a/53/8f/0a538fad13a89d2a6fb9a2c469e4d316.jpg) and not reaching [like this](http://yogakillarney.ie/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/Zackforwardbend2.jpg) (you can also see how he's rolled towards the tailbone here. he's NOT using gravity to his benefit. if you look like this, you should roll your hips forward so you are not on your tailbone but towards the bone in "front" ... or use a blanket to prop the hips up.)

You can also try a rolled up blanket under the knees if your hamstrings are the thing tightening up on you. Like this: [Pic](https://sleepysantosha.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/IMG_5314-768x523.jpg)

Experiment, go in without judgement (ie, like you already know what the answer is) and see which one stretches the hamstrings FOR YOU ... and not pull on your lower back or upper back. You should feel a nice stretching sensation in the hamstrings, not like a cord is about to pop. 

edit: you do get a stretch in the spine area but Im not trying to split hairs here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's happened two times for me. Once at a yoga retreat. And once during my 200 hour yoga teacher training. Both times during savasana. 

I was probably stressed during my yoga teacher training. And at the yoga retreat I was having a fun time, so IDK where that one came from. 

But I remember feeling energy in my chest and it traveled up to my head region and the next thing I knew I was bursting out crying. I mean, it came out of nowhere! 

I felt fine after! and I wasnt sad. I tried to google why it happened (and aside from reading "release of emotions" which didnt really tell me anything I already didnt know) and after not finding anything further on the subject, I just appreciated the moment and let go of trying to figure out wtf had just happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I typically read a nonfiction book every now and then between my fiction and memoir reads. 

I think with Mary Roach and Laura Hillenbrand, people are getting really good at writing interesting, jaw-dropping nonfiction (bc truth is odder than reality sometimes). I love Bill Bryson as well. They're just really engaging authors. 

There's a book I want to read called Endurance by Alfred Lansing - about people on a boat for something like 30 days bc the boat was stuck in ice. 

These books have a gravitas about them because THEY REALLY HAPPENED. And I typically will pick up one or two things from them and spout off random trivia at parties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *really* liked the characters. And that made the book interesting for me. I found myself interested from the get-go. The books characters and situations were easy for me to visualize (bc I like movies and celebrity culture at times). 

There are some "fun" things coming up. But are they creepy? Did I feel like anyone's life was in danger? No. I think the book was a lot more light-hearted than the reviews made it seem. There's an air of mystery and weird things going on ... but I wouldnt call it creepy. 

And I can kind of understand why you're feeling this way about the book. The expectations and reviews pumped the book up quite a bit ... 

It reminds me of the movie The Village (by Shyamalan). It got pegged as "horror" so when people saw this gothic romance, creepy movie, they were like WTF .... I think if they went into the movie knowing what it was going to be, the movie would have been better liked. 

Im rambling. 

I personally enjoyed the book. But I didnt go into it with expectations of something it's not. The scariness and pace stays about the same (for the most part). There are fun plot things coming up! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not the type of person who had a need for the reread bookshelf. I have so many to-read books and I feel like I want to move forward.

Are there any other people who don't reread books? Who's with me?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a fair comparison. 

And Litsy would be like the instagram for books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regarding Selfies + Generic State of the Sub </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! 

**A QUICK HISTORY OF THE SUB AS I, NIKIVERSE, REMEMBER IT**

I was on reddit 5 years ago, flipping through /r/FancyFollicles and *oohing* and *aahing* over all the great hair there. Seemed like I saw a lot of pixie cuts, ombre, etc but I hardly EVER saw curly hair. And I was AGHAST that there wasn't a curly hair sub. So I made it. 

And 5 years later, here we are. 

My main goal was to have this sub a reflection of r/fancyfollicles. I personally love seeing the pictures of beautiful hair. And, if you hop on over to fancy follicles, you'll probably see more than half of their front page with picture content and not text content. So this sub was never intended to be picture-less. 

But it does seem like every few months we get complaints about the excessive, "karma-whoring" of the selfie posts. And I GET THAT. 

In fact, /u/ImaCheeseMonkey and I definitely saw that as an ongoing issue. So we had a suggestion to post your routine along with your selfie. We have tried to enforce this in the past, and it takes a lot of time to do it effectively. 

So we got mods! And /u/dragonfox helped set up the flair so people could just view the "help" posts and see less of the "hair victories". 

But since then, hardly anyone tags their posts with the flair (and this might be a mobile issue ... I understand that is going on as well). So we were going in and tagging posts with flair ourselves. So that got tiring, obviously. 

And then recently, [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/curlyhair/comments/5qhyky/meta_do_we_need_to_have_the_vanity_discussion/) came about. And here we are again. 

I would like to make one comment about a mod here. /u/ImaCheeseMonkey told me she was going on a break. And I fully support her as a moderator because she has done SO MUCH for years on this sub! 

I created the sub, but I do not have the CSS or modding skillz to really properly manage the sub on my own. (like, if you see me comment here, I dont even know how to comment as a moderator and I'll be doing that the first time with this post). 

So this brings me to my next point. 

**MODERATOR HELP**

I NEED someone who can configure automoderator. Mainly, I would like automoderator to police the selfies by verifying the submitter has posted their routine (ie, a comment).  (Can automod even do that? I feel like it can.)

Otherwise, to fully police that rule, it's a person sending messages out to the offenders and deleting their posts if they don't comply, which can be a soul-sucking, never ending, daily task). 




**IN THE MEANTIME**

if you post your beautiful hair, post your routine WITHIN AN HOUR in the comments. I will add this to the sidebar. If not, your post may be removed. This will eventually become a RULE, but policing the sub without additional mod help is not feasible. 

Also, Flair your post. Especially if you're on desktop. 


**Thank you guys so much for your feedback and involvement.** We're not going to make everyone happy. But I feel this community has been created by all of you. I really enjoy learning about how to manage my own hair and seeing all of your gorgeous curls. 


I will keep this thread up for a week. Feel free to comment with what you want to see in the sub, what you like/don't like, a funny comment, and we'll see where we end up. 

edit: changed a 4 to 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live in Georgia. The sun still rose ... so I guess we got that going for us, which is nice. 

But seriously, I feel like the Falcons always do that. They lay off the accelerator at the end of the game (bc they're typically ahead by so many points). And the team will catch up a little bit ... but the Pats caught up too much.

Julio and Freeman did great. Matty Ice went down the field really fast so that probably didnt help the defense catch their breath. 

Next year the stadium will have like ... $2 hot dogs and drinks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **We Are Never Meeting in Real Life, by Samantha Irby**

I laughed out loud a lot reading New Year, Same Trash. So I got an ARC with this one and it started off hilarious! Now she's touching on her family (grew up poor, alcoholic father, disabled mother) and her depression and her physical ailments and it's getting serious. She's angry, but she's hilarious. I will definitely try out Meaty ... her other book!

**Based on a True Story, by Norm Macdonald**

I had paused reading this book to finish another yoga book I was reading. So I'm returning to to finish it off! Still have about halfway to go. It's hard to separate truth, twinges of truth, and outlandishness but I knew that going in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening to Born a Crime as well. I'm only like 20 minutes into it though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like if I write anything longer than 3 sentences, it doesnt get read ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know why you got downvoted. I've taken many classes at studios where the instructor is walking around and adjusting. That's what you pay for as a student sometimes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my teacher training, I was taught to do mainly verbal. 

Because I've always taught that way, my verbal cueing is pretty decent ... I mainly say that because most of the students dont look confused. I teach a lot of beginners too. Because I'm not a studio, but a regular gym, I try to use words that make sense and not *just* the sanskrit - like high runners lunge. If they're going into a yoga pose, I talk them into the pose, then I will say the name of the pose once they get in. So when they go into it the next few times, I just start saying the name of the pose. 

I think it helps to have a few established people there ... they're usually in the front row. 

BENEFITS: For me, as a teacher, I can see if people arent doing a pose right. They arent craning their neck in down dog to see what's next, getting out of alignment. Also, integrity of the pose be damned, some students will do WHATEVER the instructor does, even if it's probably not the safest, most alignment friendly version of the pose. I think "verbal only" can help students bring their practice to a little more internal space. I can also look around and see if they're bored or maybe I'm working them too hard. 

So I teach in a large studio where people in the back row cant see me anyways. Bc I mainly do verbal cueing, I can walk to the back of the class and see what the "hiders" look like. Then I can demo right next to them pretty easy if they are totally lost. 

I will say, my first times teaching were mainly showing ... so it took me awhile to get here. And I dont "verbal only" so I demo when I need to. But I'm not doing my own yoga practice up front. 

I have done some of the online yoga video things ... bc I use my phone and dont broadcast it to my tv, I also like when I can hear what the instructor can verbally cue me into the pose. When I have to go to my phone to see what's going on, I typically have to pause the video ... 

But Im in NO way trashing on people who do it mainly by show. When Im learning a new pose, I want to see it too! I think people learn different ways and you might prefer one or the other depending on where you're at in your yoga journey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since each semester brings a new group of students to the practice (new freshmen, leaving seniors), most campus yoga classes are going to be geared towards beginners.  

You'd probably be okay with starting with either one, honestly.

The vinyasa class might move a little faster, but after a few classes of confusion, you'll catch onto more and more movement cues and you'll get better! I personally wouldnt suggest people take restorative yoga to "train" them to get into vinyasa yoga. The classes are different. Vinyasa is moving with the breath and a mainly standing/moving class. Most restorative classes are prop heavy and like taking a long, awesome nap! You're not going to be able to take too much away from a restorative class to get you "prepped" for vinyasa. 

Thats my 2 cents anyways. 

Also, I teach yoga at a 4 year university.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a few trainers at my gym doing this, though Ive never tried it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was INSANE  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does it feel to be Ryan and have it in the hands of your D right now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure that feels great on his turf toe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Falcons clearly dominating the whole game and here we are  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right back atcha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kids don't even remember Spud #budweiser  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So impress with our D rn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gabriel has had a fantastic game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking his nose!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #sisterhood  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I KNOW  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not my halftime show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did Gaga post the ?!

cuz I don't see beyonce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's so weird I love it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they told us the moon landing was fake earlier  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> finish him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freeman is the X factor in this game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game got really fast and now the commercials are ramping up. I'm so excited  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do these mobile games afford super bowl ads?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are the points?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rhythm be damned, I'm trying it tonight!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Restorative yoga typically has a lot of props. When you "flow" instead of doing chatarungas and the like, you might just do cat/cow instead of up dog and down dog. 

But Yin is a little more "active" even while being still; the classes typically are not as restful/restorative but more meditative. You do hold the poses for 3-5 minutes. Because you're holding these poses, many of them are seated and close to the mat. Yin is intended to get more into the structure of the body (ie, the connective tissue) and that's another reason you're seated and not moving (for safety). You won't do any sun salutations. The yin poses are similar in style to the "traditional" yoga poses, but they're called something different in yin - so instead of plow pose, the yin name is snail .... 

When teaching yin, I pretty much get them into the pose and say one or two cues, then stop talking. My music wont have words, if you have it at all. 

I think this is a common question so don't let the haters get you down! 

It seems like you're teaching more of a restorative, gentle yoga class, so I would watch a few of those on youtube and see what those classes are like. For most of my restorative, gentle yoga classes I've had a lot of props (like Im talking bolster, 2 blankets, a block ....) so you might be limited in how truly restorative and relaxing you can get them depending on the clientele and the studio/gym's offerings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten legit manduka towels from ebay. $40

edit: here's [one](http://www.ebay.com/itm/Manduka-PROlite-Mat-71-/401060081947?var= hash=item5d610b311b:m:mmmk3FAwvUdrDiSBvzpbW2Q) for $80; there's only one left. free shipping! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're in the middle of writing something, what is your daily routine like? Do you have a set schedule, a set writing place, set breaks, etc? Let me hear about your work day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun NYTimes article about Atlanta

[An Evolving Sports City, Atlanta Chases a Championship](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/02/03/sports/football/atlanta-falcons-braves-hawks.html)


This city has been teased before, by those Braves behemoths of the 90s, by the Falcons in 1998, even by the Hawks, who went 60-22 two seasons ago before losing in the conference finals. Counting the futility of its two departed N.H.L. franchises, the Flames and Thrashers, Atlanta can claim only one championship  Braves, 1995  across a combined 167 completed seasons.

Yeah, so I'm ready for a Superbowl win!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This city has been teased before, by those Braves behemoths of the 90s, by the Falcons in 1998, even by the Hawks, who went 60-22 two seasons ago before losing in the conference finals. Counting the futility of its two departed N.H.L. franchises, the Flames and Thrashers, Atlanta can claim only one championship  Braves, 1995  across a combined 167 completed seasons.

Yeah, so a superbowl win would be tits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Evolving Sports City, Atlanta Chases a Championship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
