<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fetishisation of work is making us miserable. Lets learn to live again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an article that makes an important point and is something I have been thinking about for a long time. Our culture hero worships the workaholic without regard to the sacrifices in life that are made by people who over work. This article explores this and I think it's something we as a society need to think about and discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fetishisation of work is making us miserable. Lets learn to live again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill to ban fracking looks set to be voted through in the Dil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 18:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report calls on Irish government to tackle Denis O'Brien's media control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fitzgerald let slip names of whistleblowers to senior Gardai during meeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 17:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God it wasn't suicide. I got a bit paranoid when no reason was given. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like something out of Star Wars. Fantastic picture, well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 04:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also 'have a nice day', 'happy holidays' so many American greetings and goodbyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 00:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and the social Darwinism of American capitalist culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 00:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting article by a British lady living in California about how Americans' obsession with happiness is counter productive and making them less happy and more anxious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America is obsessed with happiness  and its making us miserable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 00:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 15:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like your friendly, neighbourhood cult leader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember Jason MacAteer used put in excellent deep crosses consistently when he was used as a wingback for a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland at risk of another banking disaster according to Central Bank director of credit institutions supervision Ed Sibley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 19:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 21:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To Dennis O'Brien, perchance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The congressional approval and re election rate you mention is due to gerrymandering, which is a perversion of democracy where politicians get to pick their voters. This leads to uncompetitive races, nothing breeds apathy more than knowing your vote doesn't count. Legalized corruption in the form of campaign donations also feed the feeling of impotence in the electorate. The truth is they are not represented in Washington. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pope is heavy on the mdma every weekend, I hear! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but 'crystal' puts its potency on a par with crystal meth as opposed to less powerful amphetamines such as speed, adderall etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cultural critic and theorist Henry Giroux talks about his new book 'America at War with Itself' and how he believes the mentality of war is being applied to every facet of American life. From the War on Poverty and the War on Drugs becoming a war on the poor, to debtors prisons, the incarceration state and the militarization of police forces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "We No Longer Live in a Democracy": Henry Giroux on a United States at War With Itself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 01:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an interesting article about a book that highlights the role drug use played in the Third Reich. I've often thought the image of Hitler ranting and raving hysterical is best explained by his reliance on crystal meth (injected in an early liquid form). It is news to me that he was also addicted to injections of an early form of oxycodene. It's explains a lot about his delusions and bad decision making in the later years of the war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High Hitler: how Nazi drug abuse steered the course of history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 17:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High Hitler: how Nazi drug abuse steered the course of history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 17:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to hear, you wouldn't know it from the comments on this subreddit sometimes. When did reddit:Ireland get so rightwing and hateful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asylum seekers' protest extends to fifth centre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 00:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 00:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so are you saying mass deportations should be racially driven? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 23:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you feel if Trump got elected and began mass deportation of the undocumented Irish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opinion: Ireland warehouses asylum-seekers, institutionalises them and leaves them in limbo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said it was about an economist, not by an economist, but no harm. It's all a bit beyond me to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting article about the about turn of a major economist against the reigning economic models of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time to junk the flawed economic models that make the world a dangerous place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time to junk the flawed economic models that make the world a dangerous place </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Afghan boy killed in Calais in attempt to climb on to lorry to UK 14-year-old said to have had legal right to travel to Britain, but despair at application delays led him to try stowaway route </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 20:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Afghan boy killed in Calais in attempt to climb on to lorry to UK 14-year-old said to have had legal right to travel to Britain, but despair at application delays led him to try stowaway route </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 20:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France bans plastic cups, plates and cutlery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Rebecca Ryan - the girl who has learned to beat her OCD demons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 01:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Rebecca Ryan - the girl who has learned to beat her OCD demons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 01:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple pays $118m tax penalty for underreporting income in Japan (x-post from /r/worldnews) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 13:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing to see here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Starbucks keep opening stores without planning permission? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland's Dementia Village modelled on The Netherlands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 02:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traditionally dressed Muslim woman set on fire in NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 23:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 17:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, it's great when you're under pressure or stress to remind yourself you only have to have live one moment at a time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 04:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is weasel words just something you say when someone makes a better argument than you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 03:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Surrender is the only escape.' I read it in a guy's poem on Myspace years ago, I was just after giving up drinking and didn't know how to deal with my emotions without it. It became my mantra for a few years and started me down the path of absorbing Buddhist wisdom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 02:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe if SF got rid of Gerry Adams I'd vote for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on 400,000 a year. That would go a long way supporting clubs in the league of Ireland and youth development. I don't know how he has done it, but he has soccer in Ireland locked down as his own little fiefdom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corruption is rife at the top tiers of Irish society. Sports organisations today, Charities yesterday, banks and developers the days before. Politicians all day long. Who are we supposed to vote for to change things? Fianna Fail will probably get back in power after the next election. It's a stagnant, rotten stasis and it's depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 21:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He practically burned the Dail down speaking the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relative of Clodagh Hawe issues powerful plea to people to remember Clodagh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 02:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The transatlantic trade deal TTIP may be dead, but something even worse is coming | George Monbiot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The transatlantic trade deal TTIP may be dead, but something even worse is coming | George Monbiot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The transatlantic trade deal TTIP may be dead, but something even worse is coming | George Monbiot | Opinion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 21:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporting of man who killed his family too sympathetic, say women's groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 00:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 01:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who did he sign for again? I can't keep up. Looks class, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WATCH: Local schoolchildren singing for the ODonovan brothers is sweetest thing ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 01:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a murdered woman became invisible in the coverage of her death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 01:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 03:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez Luiz! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'I don't think we can solve the crisis without interfering with private property' Fr Peter McVerry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 03:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was great, a real enjoyable movie with great music and good characterisation and fun 80's nostalgia. It's a real shame it wasn't a bigger hit. The only complaint I would have is the actor playing the lead is too meek. To do the things that character does in the movie, he would have to have a streak of hurt and anger in him, but he doesn't have it. Jack Reynor is brilliant as the older brother though, as is the girl who plays the love interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author hasn't even considered the possibility that the Irish government could accept the money it's owed. That is poor journalism, he can explain his feelings about what could happen if we did, but he cannot pretend the option doesn't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were wrong the first time so why bother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 22:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The EU rules are telling us to take the money, it's tax we're owed. The judgement is against Ireland, apple can't appeal. Ireland is appealing, Michael Noonan was on rte this evening announcing he was going to appeal. Does Michael Noonan work for Apple? Don't answer that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ireland is appealing, not Apple. He does have the option to accept the ruling and keep the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All sales throughout the world (apart from America) are put through an Apple company in Ireland. Apple declared 50 million through this company. The rest, 13.95 billion, they said went to a head-quarters. But this head-quarters only exists on paper, it has no employees and is stateless, so apple paid 0 tax on this money. RTE did a good explanation on in the 6.01 news, but that was effectively it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 21:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's his point, their employees pay tax so they shouldn't have to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 20:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they paid 0.005% tax in 2014. I'm sure they're nice guys in other ways, but why should any of us pay tax if the richest corporation in the world doesn't have to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petition to pressure Michael Noonan to take the apple tax payment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 20:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 18:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok, sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 18:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok, sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eimear McBride: Writing is painful  but its the closest you can get to joy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 13:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eimear McBride: Writing is painful  but its the closest you can get to joy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 13:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 19:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fascinating though. In a sense you are living in two dimensions, even if one isn't what we would call 'real'.  I was watching 'Stranger Things' and it made me realise we all live in many different dimensions, but apart from the exterior world, they are all within us. It reminds of a quote 'when someone dies, a whole universe dies with him'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 16:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking wow! I don't know whether to envy you or pity you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 01:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> victim blaming... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, it's easy for people to demonise these people and for them to excuse the centres, which are open prisons. People resent that they exist, feel that they are taking from them, the average tax payer is the victim here. Nobody seems to remember we are probably one of the largest people exporting countries in history. As soon as the shoe is on the other foot, we turn into assholes.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we all know tragically means suicide. In 20 years we're going to feel about direct provision the way we feel about the Magdalene laundries now, when all the horror stories come out. But then it will be too late. That what we do with 'socially inconvenient' people in Ireland, we lock them up and try to forget about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PICS: These previously unseen images of Nirvana playing in Cork are wonderful | JOE.ie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 01:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PICS: These previously unseen images of Nirvana playing in Cork are wonderful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 01:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Korean woman dies at direct provision centre in Cork </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 23:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I saw the headline I thought it was historic terrorism offences, but apparently not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Member of British forces arrested over alleged Northern Ireland terrorism offences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are government documents, you just admitted they were leaked. 2 + 2 = ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess they were just 'accidentally' leaked then, I don't want to disturb your bubble of self righteous condemnation of the weak. Carry on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this is the proper context to quote the Buddha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was an internal report 'seen' by the Sunday Independent. What do you think happened? It so obvious I can't believe how easily people are being swung by it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two sides to every story. The story published last Sunday in the Indo was a government hit job on a thorn in their side. It's startling and saddening how easily many people were manipulated by it into hating her. People need to learn to recognise propaganda when they see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done for sharing your story, it's a hard road, I can relate to some of it. You're coming out the other side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 18:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't ever let go of the hope that there is a bright future ahead of you. I know you can't see it now, but that's just now, there are a lot of twists and turns in life. Feeling hopeless can lead you down the path of depression, something I've experienced a lot of and something that helped keep me going was a hope that someday my life could be better, that I could enjoy it again, even though I couldn't see how that could happen from where I was. I guess that's called having faith. Hope is a flickering candle in your hand, don't ever let it go out, or if it does, relight it, it's really important to survive the dark times. There are better times ahead, I assure you. And at least you are willing to reach out and to change things, that's a big positive sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> way better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 02:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wondered about this for a long time 'What makes you a man (adult)?' In the end I decided it was choosing to do what you think is the right thing all the time, even when it's the hard thing. Especially when it's the hard thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 18:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sky is beautiful, the castle is beautiful, the two cars kind of ruin it a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 15:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This woman has obviously caused a lot of embarrassment for the powers that be, and this is their attempt to strike back and discredit her in the eyes of the public. I would be hesitant to jump on the 'crucify her' bandwagon, you can be sure there is another side to this story we are not being told. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 22:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can alright. Loads of the stuff there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT breakthrough doubles battery power of consumer electronics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 13:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MIT breakthrough doubles battery power of consumer electronics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 13:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 23:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm in thought, I turn to rock n roll for guidance - https://youtu.be/GNIMuvbiZcc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> t is pretty cheap, I guess ask them about it. Will they cover the full cost of getting new keys, will you lose your no claims bonus etc.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mate just paid 220 quid for someone to come out and open his car and cut new keys. So if you're the kind of person who loses their keys during a session, I'd consider it. How much is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Footage emerges of Pat Hickey being arrested: temporarily steps down as OCI president after Rio arrest; Shane Ross returning to Dublin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're back in business, boys, nothing'll go wrong this time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish builders are commanding 100,000 salaries as companies hunt for construction skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ocean Waves Could Supply the Worlds Power and Drinking Water </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More detail from the [Guardian](https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2016/aug/15/man-dies-taser-shooting-by-police-in-telford-west-mercia) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F is for Family is really good too. The Get Down by Baz Luhrman is out this weekend. iZombie sounds good but I haven't watched it yet. There's loads of good documentaries too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> out next month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 22:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> backatcha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cork Pride/Culchie Pride! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 14:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our politicians have learnt nothing, it will probably take another crash to force a change in thinking and approach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland warned of new housing crash risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 11:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand, I've also had very damaging relationships but I felt I couldn't give up on them because essentially, I was addicted to the feeling I got from that person. After that, I just thought 'she was the wrong person, I just need to find the perfect person.' Then anytime I found someone I thought fitted my idea of perfection, I became wildly infatuated instantly. It's an attempt to escape the unhappiness that was a result of my ocd and depression. This is a [test](http://centerforhealthysex.com/sex-therapy-resources/love-addiction-test/) I found online, it might give you some more insight into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 11:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I still take medication and journal and other things to help my mental health. I just think meditation will help almost anyone's mental health, even though it's not a cure all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's MCU? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I've suffered from OCD for a long time and mindfulness and meditation has given me great healing, so it helps with mental illness too, in my case anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it applies to you but I have old and used to suffer from what's called love addiction. Basically I was looking for love as a palliative for my depression and anxiety. I became deeply infatuated very quickly with a number of girls. Do a little research online and see if it applies to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So nicely put. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 12:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was Danny, you're thinking of Michael. Coincidently I was at the funeral this weekend (I'm from Kerry) and both the Healy Rae's were at it. I wanted to make a smart comment to Danny about the weather but it wasn't the time or place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Becoming Christian Mystics Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 08:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Becoming Christian Mystics Again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 08:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young footballers from Gaza heading to Ireland for a week of fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 03:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use meditation, try some guided ones online. Mindfulness has helped me to let go of the future and past and live more in the present. The power of now is a good book to start with. I also journal a lot, it's a kind of therapy for me. My faith helps me loads too, it's important to believe there is a light at the end of the tunnel even when you can't see it. Hope some of this is useful to you. It's what's helped me most. Keep on going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incredibly, the government seem to have had a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moneylenders hit in pocket with new State loan scheme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if we can trust his skills as a centre back if he can't get a simple lean right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 03:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if he's the replacement choice for Zelinski why didn't they just up the offer for said instead of paying much more Wijnaldum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey. I've been through years of depression and ocd, I know how hard it can be. The best advice I can give you is get into meditation, it's free and it really helps you heal your mind. There's tons of stuff online about it. Start off going some 30 minutes guided meditations once a day. Just Google guided meditations and try a few till you find one you like. I'd give you a link but I'm on my phone. Your life is important, as important as anyone's, and it's worth fighting for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 02:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't like going up for crosses, I heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps he can act as mentor to our two young keepers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely Gareth Bale should be in before Wee Joe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 19:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'tis cool, Einstein proved time is relative. It's whatever you feel it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 750,000 people in the Republic are now living below the poverty line, report finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see a graph comparing gdp growth to growth of debt (private and sovereign) per capita. I reckon we'd be winning there too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your therapist was highly irresponsible for suggesting your spikes have some truth behind them. OCD always lies. The only thing true about it is you truly fear the thought of stabbing your girlfriend. Ask yourself was there anything truth to you hocd?  It's important to starve your OCD of any shred of belief in what it's suggesting, because that if what it feeds on. Be well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis says church must apologise to gays and other marginalised groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 00:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 17:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the late reply. In the naughties the German economy was sluggish so the ECB kept interest rates very low in order to stimulate it, but this was the opposite of what was needed in Ireland as we were booming and the low interest rates only stimulated the housing market further.

By 'sacrificial lamb' I'm referring to the ECB threatening to cut off emergency funding to the Irish government if we carried out the haircut on bondholders we were planning to. This forced the government to pay 100% back of bank bonds covered in the guarantee. Most of these bonds were held by German and French backs so they were effectively bailed out at the expense of the Irish people at the behest of the ECB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Afghanistan, many girls are forbidden to ride a bike, so they ride skateboards instead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does it make the second guarantee illegal? Genuine question, not being sarcastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost certainly the politicians were in on it as well. This proves the whole ruling class of Ireland is corrupt. I don't know what we should do about it, have a revolution maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Damning files reveal Central Banks role in 7bn banking fraud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 16:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we set aside half the Earth for nature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we set aside half the Earth for nature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 03:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not in favour of Ireland leaving the EU but I definitely favour Ireland leaving the Euro which by any measure has been a disaster for us. We conceded too much of our sovereignty to Brussels and ECB in adopting it. It contributed to boom and Europe made us the sacrificial lamb in the bank crisis. It's mind boggling there's no discussion of it in Ireland.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The European Union has stripped us of democracy"- Tom McGurk on Brexit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 23:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 17:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Release the equity in your party to get a big return on your investment!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Ireland more international than it used to be,' after citizenship figures are released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 17:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 23:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, I've only heard about it since the news broke yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 21:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was jailed for ten years for abusing two girls. I wondered if the witness could have been someone he was abusing but was too afraid of him to come forward till now. I just pray they can locate the body and give the family some closure and peace after all these years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schoolbag of Philip Cairns to be examined for DNA evidence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 19:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 20:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed it. The writer's from Cork, I saw him give a Q A before the screening a few years ago. I thought the movie captured the 'craic' well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Eircode be scrapped?: A recent survey of logistics company found that 96% of them don't use Eircode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 18:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook, Google and Twitter 'face growing legal claims in Ireland' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 16:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 02:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Sceptre and crown

must tumble down

and in the dust

be equal made

with the poor, crooked

scythe and spade.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 15:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found whenever I've found the courage to reach out and ask for help, there's always been someone there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers in Trinity College Dublin have discovered a way of producing hydrogen that is 90% cheaper than existing methods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 23:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dil bills which contradict State policy could be blocked under new reforms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 15:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aston Villa takeover: Chinese businessman agrees deal to buy club for 60m </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 19:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 19:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

God Bless You! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terry Gilliam's Long-Awaited 'The Man Who Killed Don Quixote' To Start Shooting in Fall, Star Adam Driver: Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 20:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glen Hansard, Sinead O'Connor, Mundy And More Have Created A New Album To Fight Homelessness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 16:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 20:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was the right decision in the end. Sorry, internet, you've had your fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's not enough!! There must be more!!! God help me.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I think I'll try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for that book online, unfortunately it's popular title. Is it the one by Jennifer Traig? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 02:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have religious OCD too. I find it is important for me to remember God is love and He understands I have OCD, He forgives my thoughts and is eternally patience with my mistakes and failures. It helps me to trust that God is helping me through whatever I have to go through and is helping me heal. I think it is very important if you do believe to have a positive faith based on love and trust that God is unconditional love and not judging you but has compassion for your suffering.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 02:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know to be honest and I don't think people on a forum are qualified to diagnose you. You need to see a medical professional if you want that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 20:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would entail a whole government report, not a newspaper article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would rather get cancer again than be a patient in the Irish mental health service - Dr Martha Finnegan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 00:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An indepth report on a homeless shelter that gives out hourly doses of wine to chronic alcoholics in a harm reduction approach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The shelter that gives wine to alcoholics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'They are falling apart': the fate of lone children in Calais' refugee camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 16:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'They are falling apart': the fate of lone children in Calais' refugee camp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 16:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horrifying video emerges showing Nauru refugee setting himself on fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 03:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 18:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, I'm really sorry to hear that. The most healing experiences I've had have been at meditation. How do you think you got rid of it in first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 18:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find meditation and mindfulness the best thing to help me when I'm overthinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 18:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you, I have a religious edge to my old too. I think it helped to see God as unconditionally loving rather than judging me. Sometimes I think what I think about an upcoming event is going to affect how it turns out. Ocd is a tough thing to live with, God bless you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 20:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She mentions 'the farcical rte coverage of the election', I was wondering what she meant specifically. One thing I noticed at the time was when Sinn Fein exposed that the govt. was 2 billion out in it's estimate of the fiscal space. The govt had counted one 2 billion figure twice. Rte just referred to it in passing 'Sinn Fein disputes it's (the govt.) figures' and that was pretty much it. Now this was a govt pitching it to the electorate as the party of fiscal responsibility and they got the estimates dramatically wrong. This should be a huge story as it undermines the govt entire argument for re election, but it was discovered by the wrong party. RTE didn't want to be seen taking Sinn Fein side even though it was correct, in this instance it was a matter of fact. I feel if it was Fianna Fail that had discovered the error there would have been a lot more play on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish investigative reporter lashes media bosses for newsroom timidity: The Guardian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 18:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 03:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the action that his blaming on ocd, it's the never ending guilt and feeling of being a bad person that he's blaming on it. Correctly in my view, committing some minor sexual infraction just after puberty hits is completely normal and most people would have long forgotten about it but he's obsessed with it years later and it's crippling his life. That's not right, that's unhealthy. Try not be so judgemental, it won't help anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen, this a sub to support people who are suffering. If you are just going to come here to make someone suffering extreme guilt over a minor infraction years ago feel even more guilty, then maybe you should ask yourself what you are doing here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 02:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choose to love and forgive yourself you this, that's all you can do. Yes you committed a minor infraction when you were thirteen, most people do because we're left to figure out our sexuality on our own.  The never ending guilt you feel is ocd, nevermind what the other guy says, self forgiveness is a choice you can and need to make in order to move on with life. Everyone else has to too, there's nobody alive who hasn't crossed a line or two in their time. Take care of yourself, have compassion for yourself in your suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State spends 27k a week on security for US military at Shannon airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 00:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 22:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah, I didn't realise Sherwood says he had no say. There's no doubt whoever was in charge of recruitment at Villa should be shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 21:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much blame do you put on Tim Sherwood for bringing in those players? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spike Lee Directed a Bernie Sanders Campaign Ad Starring Susan Sarandon   Rosario Dawson  Watch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 22:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 18:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Monbiot outlines the emergence and ultimate failure of neo liberal economic policy and how it uses it's anonymity as a shield against opposition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neoliberalism  the ideology at the root of all our problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 18:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK and European allies plan to deal hammer blow to tax evasion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 03:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook, Google and Amazon to be forced to open up tax books by EU (x-post from worldnews) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 17:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 03:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 02:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reddit is not media now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 02:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well have a look at any thread on this sub about them and you will feel the heat of the hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 22:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the 'I am traveller' documentary present by John Connors from Love/Hate was great. How often do we get to look at travellers' life from their point of view. Of course, it was biased, but it was great to see it as antidote to all the anti traveller stories we always see in the media and hear about from each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We cannot look the other way as child refugees go missing in Calais </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We cannot look the other way as child refugees go missing in Calais </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 800 Dubliners offer to help turn empty buildings into homes for the homeless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 01:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like Im in prison: Qatars abuse of World Cup workers revealed  video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 03:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
