<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7668</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 02:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think they would prescribe this to someone who is already bordering underweight and has an ED diagnosis?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My started because I was self conscious. I started heavily restricting after a beach day with my boyfriend in about June because I remember feeling like a whale while he was ogling at the skinny girls who walked by us. That triggered me to drop 20 pounds that summer... and I just can't stop  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 22:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started with purging in chipotle last year around this time and and I began to restrict and stopped purging this past summer. That's when I actually dropped a decent amount of weight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 08:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE IT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 18:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay welcome! I started at 136 and am about 5'6! I also used to be a twig and prob around 110 all of high school and then gained 25 pounds in college. But I pretty easily lost the weight so you can do this!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 03:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of crying. Lol jk. So here I am at 133 for reference and a current pic 


So bc of my issues with binge eating I lost the weight by fasting (or eating sometimes SUPER small before like 6-7 pm or as long as I could go) then eating a bigger meal of like 600 cal or so. So even if I did feel some binge urges later on I could allow myself 200-300 cal of some low cal and high volume like carrots or fruit or sometimes I did even portion out junk food so I didn't feel as deprived.

Basically anything under 900-1000 cal was a success for me! I tried not to beat myself up too much. I lost about 2 pounds a week give or take.

Keeping the weight off is the real struggle.  http://i.imgur.com/3LpiHP8.jpg http://i.imgur.com/VXtcuLf.jpg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome! I totally relate. I knew i had gained some weight and was probably a little over 120 but when I saw 136 I lost my shit and dropped the weight during the summer. 

I've also been having major issues with binging. I got down to 113.5 and then have been binging for the past few weeks. I don't know my real weight ATM but I'm probably around 115.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically any beverage that's not 0 calories. I despise drinking my cals and get really nervous drinking diet Soda at restaurants in fear they gave me a regular instead of diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> love your brows </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no it doesnt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg yes! i forgot i bought this at 5below and just found it the other day and havent gone back. its incredible and long lasting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like toned slim boys and toned slim girls. I basically am attracted to the body type i want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 05:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS. IS. ME. and I hate it. Just know you're absolutely not alone in these thoughts my love.

I'm in therapy trying to work on myself to stop being this way but im worried I'll be this way forever ugh. Fuck this mindset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 136 my UGW was 115. Now I'm bouncing from 113-114.5 and I'm def not happy and would like to at least get down to 110.. possibly 105. 

Idk if I'll ever be happy tbh. I'm supposed to be in recovery so any weightless has to be super slow because I get weighed every other week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that one track heart rate ?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i drunkenly slipped to one of my best friends that I have an eating disorder. We were discussing body image and body dysmorphic disorder and then I said something like "I see myself as chunky when I know my bmi isn't like that" so it became clear what was going on with me. 

He told me that he's always there for me if I need to talk and that he's sorry for what I'm going though.

Since that day he has not brought it up, but I've noticed he'll send me more funny gifs and pictures randomly even though we don't text really and I appreciate it because it feels as though he's trying to brighten my day a bit. 


You absolutely do not have to tell your friend, but if you do end up telling them, you may be surprised with their reaction. Just be clear with them that you're not ready To go into details, but even opening up about it relieves a lot of stress for you and that you just want someone to listen so you feel less alone (if you do feel that way). Best of luck  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 18:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow your stats are incredible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 08:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please update! We care about you op </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is similar to how i feel. im technically trying to "recover" and im no longer heavily restricting but ill just so happen to "forget" about breakfast and lunch and then have a decent sized dinner and small snack and be oh-so-surprised by the scale still going down when i see my ED team at my college for weigh ins. I dont even feel too disordered anymore because i genuinely am not as hungry anymore, but i am also just not trying to eat more than what is considered "losing" for me. oh well... :----) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg this made me so happy 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 00:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've come to realize I'm out of my boyfriends league because people have either flat out told me that without me asking or will just be surprised when they meet him/compliment him on what a "catch" I am, and honestly it doesn't affect our relationship. Only once he has asked me if I think I'm out of his league and I've told him that leagues are a load of bs and I love him and think he's incredibly attractive. He hasn't brought it up since and we are happy together 


Really, try not to be too hard on yourself either. Leagues really are pretty dumb and not everyone is attracted to one type of "ideal" look.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 22:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gained 7 pounds in a month when I was on it ): </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 04:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For REALS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 02:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my gosh yes. I told my therapist that I feel dumb when I restrict for long periods of time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to embrace compliments rather than just be embarrassed/ashamed/not believe the person when I do get them. I used to post wayyy more often and stuff but I've deleted posts and haven't been around as much but this community really is very positive and wonderful. I'm so glad we both found it. 

Also, I really hope so. I am trying to trust what other people say about my appearance rather than let my BDD overrule the compliments. Thank you thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 05:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is horribly wonderful! i am jealous lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got called a model today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 05:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today i was showered in compliments and i was loving it. This is a petty conceded post but for once, i feel good about myself so im gonna really let myself feel confident and happy.

 People were telling me that i stand and look like a model, looked "beautiful" and was even called "perfect". I really hope i can feel this confident tomorrow tbh because its always fleeting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 00:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess in a similar way I do have those feelings when I'm around friends. Sometimes they will make comments about how I'm so skinny or that I've lost weight. My friend (who has a killer curvy body.. like small waist and huge hips) was telling me I had the body she wanted and it hurt to hear someone as stunning as she is would say that, especially because I'm starving myself to look this way. It made me embarrassed and I just wished I could shake her and be like "noooo shhh honey ur great and not suffering the way I am to look this way" 

As for my family, it's uncomfortable "showing off" my figure now because they know about the eating shit but luckily they've been pretty unobservant throughout this whole thing so I'm not too worried about them.

Does your family ever make comments to you or something? Is that why you feel shame or is it just that you worry you will worry them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 00:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha, I can relate! Like I'll be proud of my progress but also uncomfortable that my legs are really starting to look a bit too skinny. I used to be slim but very curvy and now I still (think) I have curves when I look in the mirror it I'm waaay thrown off when I see my reflection somewhere that catches me off guard because there's a weird disconnect between my reflection in a real mirror vs my reflection in a window as I'm walking by a store. I wish I know what I really looked like to other people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe an unpopular opinion here but when I catch a glimpse of myself in store windows I often think I look too thin and think about gaining a bit of weight but then when I see myself in front of a mirror I look huge and think I could lose 5-10 more pounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 02:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK UUUU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 02:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screen shotting this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 02:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cute af  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 45 cal hotdogs exist! 97 percent fat free. I forget the brand at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 05:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> under 900 is restricting, under 400 is heavily restricting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 20:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my temporary stats until im 114 again :'(

* Height: 5'5 3/4

* CW: glob

* HW: 136

* LW: 113.8

* GW: 112 (???)

* UGW: 110 (???)

* WL: idek

* BMI: ugh

* Age: 21

* Gender expression: f </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 19:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im in the saaaaame boat bb. the last two and a half weeks ive been trying to mindfully eat but then ill end up late night overeating/snacking and have gained four pounds from it. most of it was prob water weight but still im sure ive gained a pound or two of real fat. i have no self control when i try to not think about eating and try to enjoy it so i guess im doomed to a life of restricting so i can be skinny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we also are on the Peach app!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 22:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry for my lack of advice but I just wanted to tell you you're not alone  I've gained about 4 pounds and it's probably gonna be a lot more if I don't get my shit together soon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my mouth dropped when i read the comment one of his friends made at the party. jesus christ. you are certainly not overreacting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 23:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this resonates so much with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow your stats are incredible. I had a tough time losing 20 pounds so really that's amazing you dropped as much as you did!!! Congrats, I'm sure you look amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup. I feel like in photos other people take of me I look much smaller than the body I see in the mirror. Like sometimes in photos I don't recognize the body I see as myself right away because it just doesn't match my perception of myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been doing the same exact thing these past two weeks. I still am not positive If I've gained or maintained, but I feel so sure I've gained. However, last time I was sure I gained and got weighed at the doctors I actually lost .4 pounds.. and I even binges the night before! I'm totally like you where I can legit feel the fat covering my body. After over eating I look in the mirror and see a different person. I have faith in us that we'll be able to get back on track again 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i love noodle arms so much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 19:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh yeah it's so annoying when people try to push food on you even when you're eating. Like no one noticed when I was severely under eating and now they only care because I'm actually "skinny". At least you seem to be getting over your cold!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 04:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup that's why I'm terrified to show someone a pic on my camera roll in fear they'll swipe through all my almost-noodz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A THOUSAND TIMES YES. i know i was more physically attractive to other people at 130 pounds but im obsessed with wanting to stay juuuust below underweight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TW

I was pulling it off for a bit but then I literally almost killed myself so ya I'd recommend against it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOVE U ALL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 04:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So drunk and really love u all. Ur all beautiful and great. Thank.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I used to eat whatever I wanted and didn't care. I also used to get a ton of compliments on my body but I rarely get them now :/ i don't get how people thought my fat body was attractive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 06:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to rarely want chocolate. Now I want it ALL the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 05:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look so lean and I just look skinny fat! Do you workout?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> were stat twins and i swear you look so much thinner than me. you are incredible!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ME TOO!!!! ugh fuckin sucks. im right here with u 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 09:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Said this almost verbatim to my therapist..... weird. Like when I walk past store windows I look almost a bit too thin for my liking by in the mirror I look giant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 04:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right, just looked her up! Dang  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
