<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5644</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not on here per se, it shows up in my feed. I'd like to stay subscribed. This 24 hour delay's not ideal but I wouldn't spoil any details for anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, spoiler tag m8.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to agree with you on Mike's story line. He's such a great character. But you're right, it would seem a bit forced yeah. Could be that Hank and Gomez go order some chicken at Los Pollos. Even a scene like that would be enough for me. Must say, I like that they keep us wondering when they drop hints like that. It's the only universe from a series that I spend a lot of time on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annoying, yes. But remember we see Gene's story because of what happened in BB, so it's still very relevant. Besides, I'm sure Vince knows fans are hungry for BB characters to appear in BCS, because let's be honest.... BB was one of the greatest shows of our time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. Jesse said "this guy" got his friend off a couple of times so there's been no previous introduction between Saul and Jesse. IF they ever had to appear in BCS, it would be in the final season. I don't see either making an appearance in S4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but that's nothing to get fans really excited about.

EDIT: Grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I posted this discussion I wanted to add that I think it's going to be Hank. I just struggle trying to fit him into the s3 timeline. Then again, as mentioned in BB Gus has done a lot for the DEA in donations / charity events, so who knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ?? Nacho has been in both seasons of BCS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
