<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject713</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, after you. 

No, please, after you. 

I Insist, after you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more JPEG  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how he is SMOKING the competition. Savannah doesn't have shit on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was playing recreational softball and I hadn't been feeling well but I had to play anyway. I was playing center field, minding my own business, praying to God above that no one hit anything my way. He did not listen. I was staring off into the distance when I hear someone yell "Heads Up" and I turn to see the ball flying to a spot about a 15 yards away. I turned and started to sprint, about .01 seconds into my first full stride I felt a piping hot burst. I couldn't just hang a left and run back to my car. I HAD to go get that ball, so I waddled over to the ball and just quick threw it... I was 30 feet short of the nearest person. So I waddled to the ball, tossed it again, and immediately turned to my car. 

The next game, I was presented with a bag of diapers all signed by the team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very insightful. I have to place something every month and I'm extremely limited on my talent. I try to stay out of it but otherwise want to contribute. I'll try strategies  and let you know 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, I'll point out after the fact that he robbed a scene from his fellow players </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a team member and director but I I try to take a submissive role when it comes to the overall performance. Usually doing hosting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, we are not. We are a small local troupe that started because a local bar owner with a sweet venue contacted me. I did improv in college for 3.5 years and did workshops in Chicago.

I am the director, I don't think I'm great but I like to think I have a nak for teaching based off what everyone has said to me for years.


I live in an interesting community. Doctors, Maritime Business (Sailors, Captains, Etc), locals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've got an arrogant cast member. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a cast member that recently signed up to work with our troupe. We are a small troupe that needs people. 

This guy is the most arrogant and cocky ass I've ever met. He steamrolls scenes and has no idea. He doesn't understand that there are 4 other people.

However, he has great additions and enthusiasm for improv.

Any thoughts on how to tone him down without being a total asshole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a credible story? I thought Redditors were better than this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more JPEG  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
