<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5819</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It comes and goes, so it isn't us. It is based on our opponents who are lagging, and given that we are all on green wired connections with no lag, it would appear that matchmaking isn't exactly working as it should, hence the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trials is lagging and bugging hard Bungie..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems as though trials lag has gotten worse. I just played 4 rounds of trials where capping the point simply didn't do anything. It stayed at 100% with no enemies on it and it wouldn't allow us to cap it. People are lagging everywhere and this so called "latency matchmaking" accomplishes nothing, people are rubber banding across the map. Other times we are getting unable to revive bugs. It is starting to cost players games for no reason beyond the game breaking. We are telling people to be careful with your passage coins this run through, it seems as though Trials isn't working as it should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iron banner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keep an open bounty slot when doing any high level PoE, the exotic bounties are still bugged, and will require you to complete the run over again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 10:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just ran a run, got the drop but had my bounty slots full. When I ran to Variks I couldn't complete the portion of the bounty that requires speaking to him. Evidently the only solution working so far is to run whatever gave it to you again, so save yourself the headache and keep a slot open regardless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 21:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will say I am withholding total judgement until the raid comes out, but so far it feels pretty small.

Edit: Grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 21:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People can have different opinions, that isn't my issue with all this. It's the things people are saying that are objectively not true.

Good writing? Tons of content? It has about the same amount of "stuff" as TDB, and this writing is.... so bad...

I guess the point I'm making is people are accepting a slightly nicer TDB as this great thing, and that worries me, since it feeds into what makes the game feel like a grind. Then again it's just my opinion :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 21:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I, like you, have paid for this content. It is my prerogative to find fault with the things I pay for and demand better, much like it is yours to not worry about it and enjoy the game. I just don't like that people are saying the DLC is fantastic, when it is clearly not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't be the only one who finds this DLC.... underwhelming... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 20:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps I'm just too jaded, but it seems like everyone is too caught up on how much **better** it is than TDB. Few people seem to be examining the DLC as a stand alone piece.

Let's be honest, everything is shiny now, but in 2 or 3 weeks PoE will feel very stale. Even with all the new modifiers, the game hasn't grown mechanically beyond the scorch cannons and web grenade stuff. 

Where are the new monsters? New Grenade subtypes? New Crucible or PVP events beyond Trials of Osiris (Mini crucible... yaaaay.....) New supers? BETTER WRITING? ("He's pulling the entire house of wolves through time and space!" Really?) 1 new strike, which is pretty much the same as Sepiks prime but with the Archon Priest as a boss?

I dunno, I feel burnt out by how much mediocrity the community accepts as fantastic when we should be dissecting everything wrong with the game and not get too caught up on the hype. It's the only way the game gets better, but everyone seems to think this is the second coming of RNGesus.

Just keep an objective head guys, all I'm sayin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
