<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7467</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I had no idea it was a golden spot I took this pic 1 day after my arrival in the city, I do not regret moving here, the city is nice but the inhabitants are ever nicer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gorgeous Adelaide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great work mate ! I arrived in Adelaide 2 weeks ago and I'm loving it. I can't wait to discover SA s country side now ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only in USA. In Europe too. I just wonder are they more evil than banks ? Hell, sometimes banks are also insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So damn true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should encourage you and be proud of you going the right path. Keep going mate. I'm a skinny guy trying to get in shape and I feel like shit when surrendered by muscle guys. I too keep thinking about my pc and a fat join while training.

But man it feels good when you finally sit before your screen after training.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the pizza too. Industrial pizza are full of unhealthy shit but homemade ones can be healthy and good for after training! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We use it in France too, when its" ten past two pm" we use" fourteen ten". Much easier IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is not easy to read, not an action book. More like a psychological story. But yeah it is very tense after a while. I loved every page of it, I read it 3 times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only more country would take The Netherlands as an example. Your basically free to do almost anything you want as long as you are not annoying anyone.

Moreover, it works. Dutch people smoke less weed than any country in EU, the cocaine is cheap and easy to get, alcohol drinkable anywhere. 
Now I dare anybody to go there to check it out and tell me that they are uncivilized, poor and drug addicted. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hehe yeah I can see your happy face !  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drinking should be allowed anywhere. Behaving inappropriately shouldn't. That's it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just check his comments history and you 'll see how damn right you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm French so pardon it ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KaKraKrie in his very own swimming pool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you invite the retards from T_D ?  There is a shit loooots of them. I'm sure they 'll love to do jokes on blacks and Jews and anything which isn't a white male or a brain dead woman   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where should we punch a Nun ? 

I d say the liver or the vagina </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ja vol mein general!  *sounds of boots* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 12:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially when you know that the Dutch are the one that smoke the less in EU.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously how the hell do you think Hitler got in power ? He did not steal it, Germans (Jews included) gave it to him, because he gave to Germans the former greatness they had before being destroyed by the WW1.
 Which, by the way made your country rich. USA made so much money selling enough weaponry so Europeans could keep on killing each others. Yeah  thank you so much. 
Oh and the Canadians actually kicked the Germans away from my city.

I'm not even gonna talk about the mass rapes of French woman by the US soldiers afterward. Great people. Great country. Great president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 !? Your husband may never be back I'm afraid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My country has been occupied for 4 years and my great grand father fought the nazis. There is still German bunkers  near my house. I kinda know about them. 

I dont know much about Bernie I didn't follow the US election before I heard about Donald. So I cant tell. 

Socialism/communism are like insults in usa, not in Europe. But just reading you comparing Bernie with Nazis is hilarious. Hitler made Germany great again, and that's proven fact.

Can't wait to see what your so called "god emperor" will do for the USA. I wish you the best anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read a history book man, if you can't understand why Nazis where racists, and that you think like them, I can't do anything for you.
 You support a guy that had to swear on the bible to take office, but do the opposite of what the book is trying to teach. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is one race, humanity. Different cultures and colors.   Rascim is so old its hard to believe that in 2017, some people still think that there is different races of humans..

You don't agree with other cultures?
Who gives a damn? Live your life, I don't agree with everything concerning Islam, but hey that should stay personal, their choice, their life. 
I don't care as long as they don't piss me off trying to convert me like those Jesus guys in the street singing their crap out loud.

How annoying when your neighbor is checking in your garden to tell you that you should grow potatoes instead of carrots ?  Your garden. Your choice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont excuse yourself for openly being a cunt. I actually pity you.

If you can't understand that the fucking Nazis themselves where thinking the same way than you do, fine. You re gonna find a way to say they were not racist ?
  Thanks not everyone think like you, we would be in a perpetual world war.

America are one nation under God, read the bible again because I guess you forgot the points of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved to Adelaide 3 days ago so nop didn't catch the news! 
 Thanks for sharing the info  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I didn't know this sub. Thanks I 'll go there from now on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
