<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4640</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen prosecuted as adult for having naked images of himself on his own phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Model S racer can do 0-62mph in 2.1 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 13:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeepTraffic - gamified simulation of typical highway traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 11:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 10:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was disappointed by most responsive designers out there (most are either too complex or not working), so I created a free one myself, and named it RocketCake. 



It's relatively new but people like it very much. Maybe you'll like it, I'm always looking for feeback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 10:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get why you would want to use AMP at all. Why not simply create a lightweight website right from the start? It is easy to do, you don't even need tons of CSS or JavaScript for this. (I honestly want to know, this isn't criticism) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 10:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to send a reporter. A few years ago, people invented something called the telephone. And a bit later the internet. Would have taken just a few minutes for CNN to use one of those. But that would have meant that they would actually have to do their job.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 07:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It surely works for some people. They probably earn some coffee money from that. Some few, including me can even make a living from it. But I don't think it is a very safe business strategy, especially if you are just starting up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 06:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing just that, developing games AND gamedev tools, for more than 10 years now. (My game engine is named CopperCube, also on Steam)



From my experience, the market for game development tools, especially engines is getting more difficult each day. And more saturated. And you dont earn a lot any more, people now expect mostly everything  to be free. 




So I dont think this would be a solution to your problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting used to Software Half-Assery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Krass ist ja, dass der Prll nicht sowieso schon die Taschen voll htte. Aber man kann wohl nie genug bekommen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RocketCake 1.3 released (free responsive website builder / designer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 06:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   shouldnt be allowed on the internet anyways

I also think the pizzagate people are a bit crazy, but you shouldn't forget that for example the people who said that the banks are manipulating the gold price, or for example that the Iraq didn't have WMDs were treated the same way. They were right after all. Just because most people don't believe you doesn't mean that you should be censored away. That's even a bad thing. We are a democracy after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Mozillas hardware report, about 33% of all people still run a 32 bit system. If you build a 64bit game, you will might prevent 33% of all people playing your game. Not sure if this was the reason for him creating a 32 bit binary, just saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't use flexbox for overall page layout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 11:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> printbf -- Brainfuck interpreter in printf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 10:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That Russian meteor showed that

Man, I know Reddit hates Putin, but blaming him for meteors hitting earth is another level! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still depends on the country you are in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 10:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a game about politics. It's educating and entertaining. Saying an ad for it "is a shameless way to rake in cash from the election" is one the dumbest things I've read this month. Maybe you should take a look at what currently is happening in politics to see where people really are raking in cash from the election shamelessly, currently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 09:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just personal experience, unfortunately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 09:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that if you sell to the government, you have a lot of overhead. Ever tried to do business with any kind of government? The bureaucratic bullshit you have to go through is insane. On top of that, it usually takes at least 10 times longer to finish a government contract. Companies have to figure this in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 09:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so great. I can't wait to get rid of XCode. Even if this means I will develop using Xamarin from now on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be nice if this would actually be true. But although you now have some code running the same on all those platforms, it still will have to interact with the outside world, which is depending on the browser. And browsers still behave differently. And even if it is the same browser, it will behave differently depending on the operating system, device, screen, and so on. 

That small 'runs on everything' stuff already existed in several forms, like for example with Java. And we know how that ended up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 10:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to learn the basics, I'd suggest to try learning C++ with D3D or OpenGL. This is how basically all game engines are done (even Unity), and that way, you understand how everything works at the very bottom. It doesn't get much more low level than this.



For a bit easier start, try some older 3D engine like Ogre or Irrlicht. Those are a bit more high level, but you still learn very much by using them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Can deer hunt with it" - question from the Amazon product page of a bow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 09:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really interesting. Thanks for posting! How many people do you have working on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 09:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Das ist zwar traurig, aber das ist wirklich eine gute Lsung, die funktioniert. Mache ich auch so. Funktioniert fr internationale Medien genauso. Mitte aus CNN und RT, und gut ist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 09:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just uploaded this free update. New features are:


* Steam Integration
* Improved First Person Shooter Controller
* C++ source code
* Flash source code
* Android Multi-Touch support for 2D Overlays
* Android First Person Shooter Camera improved
* Scripting extension: ccbGetCurrentNode()
* And a lot more.


Any feedback or questions are welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CopperCube Game Engine 5.5 released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 09:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 06:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a sales person. And I don't know that many of those games, so it is difficult to say what is different in this one. Maybe take a look at the video and the description, it shows very well how the game works. If you don't like it, then it's probably not for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 16:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's single player only and will remain that way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has cities, villages and deep forest, but deserts etc is actually a good idea, never thought of that. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they didn't specify how much or what kind of UML is needed then the simplest way would probably be to create a Component diagram: each part you mentioned (physics, audio, etc) would be a component and you can model clearly how those are working together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just released the game 'PostCollapse' on steam. Redditors from this sub helped me with their feedback so far, some even supported the development with money (big thanks!). I try to create a game which is entertaining but a bit more realistic (no zombies etc). Which is difficult, because the life after collapse isn't actually fun at all. Actually it is rather boring, to be honest.

The game is "early access", that means it is not final and will be improved and tweaked. So any feedback is welcome. Is there something which could be added? Any suggestions, ideas?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'PostCollapse' released (survival simulation game) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 11:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woha, it is real? Cannot even think of how they engineered something complex like that back then. It also has a better form than me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 11:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on the country you are in. In most countries in europe, this is a problem. But a lot of companies are doing it anyway, because it is not worth suing because of that. But you can complain to Google and they will take down that ad sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 10:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very good point. Wondering why it doesn't come up more often in these type of discussions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 10:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. Who had thought that there would be one time where JavaScript would become more 'hip' or popular than Java.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
