<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9438</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this allowed? This submission is rule-breaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is wrong with that? Founding fathers were truly great minds. They foresaw so much things. For example if people had guns in Europe, Breivik would just kill one or two people... if a criminal wants a weapon he will get it anyway. Look at France for example, they had one of the heavily regulated laws on gun control and nothing stopped a muslim terrorist to shoot and policemen with kalashnikovs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice buzzwords </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Macron is a centrist in French spectrum. 

He is a former member of Socialist Party. 

He is a progressive globalist who loathes conservatism. 

He doesn't recognize Islam as violent religion, his quote: No religion is a problem in France today,. 

Wants to cut corporate tax to from 33% to 25% and wants to put sanctions on countries like Poland or Ireland. 

All in all France will get 5 years of same old shit and no real change. They have 10% unemployment and his policies probably won't solve that. And of course terrorist attacks will continue. 

As for me I am not very hyped because I wanted Fillon to win but oh well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably one of the few reasons that I supported Trump. Great to see conservative judges in courts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to announce nomination of conservative federal court nominees: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our founding fathers knew that democracy doesn't work. 

"A democracy cannot exist as a permanent form of government. It can only exist until the voters discover that they can vote themselves largesse from the public treasury. From that moment on, the majority always votes for the candidates promising the most benefits from the public treasury with the result that a democracy always collapses over loose fiscal policy, always followed by a dictatorship. The average age of the world's greatest civilizations has been 200 years. These nations have progressed through this sequence: "From bondage to spiritual faith; From spiritual faith to great courage; From courage to liberty; From liberty to abundance; From abundance to selfishness; From selfishness to apathy; From apathy to dependence; From dependence back into bondage."

EU is somewhere between abundance and selfishness and it will ultimately fail, probably during our lifetime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> France has serious problems with unemployment. All Marie Le Pen wanted to do was expand the welfare state.  Fillon was the candidate that France needed as Macron is too soft on immigration and Le Pen is too soft on economics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US isnt a democracy and never was. Our founding fathers knew that democracy is not the best system and created EC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What party in Canada is far right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browsing reddit I came to a conclusion that real socialism was never implemented so I don't know what are you talking out. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well either one of them are crappy. You have a socialist that doesn't acknowledge muslim terrorism and another socialist who wants to deport all muslims. Conservative candidate, Fillon, lost in 1st round. In my opinion he was the best option to get France out of debt and bring some liberty into France. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you care about them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, I don't like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You'd think Red voters would have learned by now You need to have a few brain cells to learn that. Stupid fucks will always remain stupid fucks. [+33] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it doesn't... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods said so in meta thread  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
