<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2331</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. I don't think describing someone by their race is racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year, my husband and I dressed up as Fry and Leela from Futurama. I got to dye my hair purple and dress up my dog as Nibbler. hehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Gary Johnson, Marry Bernie, kill trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically. Scenario: "Yeah talk to Drew." "Whose that?" "he's the heavyset black guy who sits near Theresa". "Wow, that's racist".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Constantly being told "I can't". I took that and ran with it. I am now 23, a homeowner (as of age 22) I make over $100k a year (if I deploy). I'm the youngest and most successful in my family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 4th grade teacher had every student in the class gather around me and say everything they didn't like about me. Thanks for the trauma, bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I'm white, if I mention that someone is black, I'm racist. How the fuck else am I supposed to describe them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think thats what OP is getting at. My husband has long locks and he gets quite the stares and comments.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, when I was in the military, my nickname was Meg, so I guess Meg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 16:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Financial Planning. Your day to day stress levels will be waaay down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my ass whooped. Only when I deserved it, but it only took 2 or 3 really good ones to make me behave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much. yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if you're my 2 year old nephew, you just start crying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm incredibly outspoken. I don't have a filter. I don't care to change it because it's who I am. I've been told that people notice when I'm gone because of this, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Futurama, Family Guy, Cleveland Show, American Dad, Bob's Burgers. I just cycle through them :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel at this point they would just let it happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn your loud ass, shitty music off by 10pm. I wake up at 3am and it's pretty annoying when I can't go to sleep. I PUT NEW FUCKING WINDOWS IN TO TRY AND DROWN IT OUT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a way to weed out the repeated questions. I have seen at least 5 "what tv show kept you hooked" threads just today. Maybe asking that questions once per day is fine, but when the same thread pops up hour after hour, it gets annoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nickelback </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told my mom I was bi and she didn't even blink. She believes it's pretty normal for women to be attracted to other women lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically any running shoe, honestly. I feel like the arch and the large tread are distracting. I usually wear vans or sandals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate when people wear clunky tennis shoes/sneakers with skinny jeans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 19:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a problem! I find that being aggressive doesn't really accomplish anything.

I get your thinking on the taxes thing. However, if you consider that a majority of low income individuals can't afford BC, it is also fair to say that those same low income individuals are going to end up on government assistance. Even if they choose to give the child up for adoption, that child is stilling going to be living off the system. It's a vicious cycle that doesn't have any true solution. Free BC would help alot of women, like myself, who have conditions that require oral contraceptive to balance hormones and such. Also, there are many men and women who know for a fact, without a doubt, that they do not want children. The obvious answer is for them to get sterilized, but most doctors will not do sterilization procedures until certain things have been met. Age and mental state are a huge factor in this. I feel there are more positive reasons to have free BC than there are negatives.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giving me a place to voice my opinions without any repercussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put it underneath the couch. I'm the only person that ever cleans under there lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When there are things to do around the house, I will say "Hey, we need to do A-B-C". He will do X-Y-Z instead. I guess he can't prioritize lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would go to the store, and get this, BUY IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brian Griffin. I love Family guy too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biting my nails. I have done it as long as I can remember. I'm 23. The longest I have gone without biting is about 3 weeks, when I had acrylic nails on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that gestation limits need to change. While 20 weeks is technically a decent amount of time, it doesn't account for error. Typically, a woman can find out at her 20 week ultrasound whether or not her fetus is viable. But, the 20 week ultrasound doesn't always happen at 20 weeks. So, if I go at 21 weeks and find out my baby isn't going to survive, most laws say that it would be illegal for me to terminate. That being said, some insurance companies will list that abortion as "elective surgery", even though it could be life or death for the mother.

Along with that, waiting periods and counseling. Enforcing a waiting period to get an abortion makes it that much harder to get one. Who  has 3-5 days to take care of a 30 minute procedure? Enforcing Counseling prior to the procedure could actually be very traumatizing. It could sway a woman to not go through with the abortion, which might be considered a good thing, until she regrets having that child. Which would then lead to possible child abuse and neglect.

The government shouldn't have as much rule over this as they do. What I do with my body should be none of their business. While I understand that most people view abortion as murder, I view child abuse and neglect just as bad, if not worse. The general consensus is " You don't want to get pregnant? Don't have sex". But there are so many reasons why that is completely off base. I am a married woman, who is on birth control, and my husband pulls out. It is quite obvious that I am not wanting to get pregnant. Sure, we could NOT have sex, but as humans, we are biologically wired to crave intimacy. Plus, not consumating can be detrimental to a marriage. Should I be forced to have that child? I don't think so. I shouldn't be foreced to carry that child to term, just to give it up for adoption either. My stepsister gave her daughter up for adoption, and I see the pain she endures everyday. 

In my opinion, birth control should be 100% free, no questions asked. You should be able to walk into a clinic at anytime, talk with a doctor, discuss BC options, and walk out with a prescription/IUD/shot, that day. Women's healthcare (gynecological care) and  men's healthcare (prostate, reproductive issues) should all be free. 

I could go on and on all day long. I've already gone far beyond what you've asked, but this is just the gist lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't Dream It's Over- Sixpence None the Richer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brings a tear to my eyes almost everytime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YAS~ I sing along everytime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a few things. Economics was a required class at my school. It taught me how to do taxes, to an extent. It taught me the importance of an IRA. Taught things like supply/demand. Definitely useful.

My senior year, I was in what was technically Alegebra 3. I almost failed the first semester, due to just not understanding a fucking thing. I ended up getting moved into "Liberal Arts Math". This class was literally ESSENTIAL to my financial success. We spent 9 weeks just on FINANCIAL PLANNING. I am 23, a homeowner, and I have minimal debt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't Dream It's Over- Crowded House/Sixpence None the Richer

If you listen, it's incredibly relevant to today's political environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abortion/women's reproductive rights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still trying to comprehend that she was FORCED to stay in the Psych ward and she still had to pay for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This legitimately sent shivers up my spine T__T
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have my tinfoil hat on about his whole campagin being a way to ensure a hilary presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 02:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ABSOLUTELY! I have met the best friends of my life in the smoke pit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sprint Katana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband and I dated for 9 months during Senior year. We broke up for 3 years, reconnected and got married 2 months later. Been married 2.5 years now.

On the flip side, my sister in law(23) and her (soon to be ex) husband have been together since they were 16 or so. In the past few months, he's decided he doesn't want to be married anymore, because he feels too tied down.

My sister and her husband have been together since they were 15, and are now 35, I believe. That's not to say they haven't had their issues, but they seem pretty stable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stressed Out by Twenty One Pilots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "IM IN LOVE WITH A GUY"!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEAD ON! APPLY DIRECTLY TO THE FOREHEAD!!HEAD ON! APPLY DIRECTLY TO THE FOREHEAD!!HEAD ON! APPLY DIRECTLY TO THE FOREHEAD!!HEAD ON! APPLY DIRECTLY TO THE FOREHEAD!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work with airplanes and I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I adjust the volume on the radio, it has to end in "5" or "0" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The irregular schedule. Monday I came in at 5 am, Tuesday at 9 am, Wednesday at 10am, and today at 6am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm great.  A little burned out and tired. But great nonetheless  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first kiss with my husband. We were in his room and we started tickling each other. We then slowly leaned in, and kissed. It was very movie-esque and sparky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> basically lol. I felt dirty watching that episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angsty, coming of age stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AND THEN ANOTHER LIE!!!! It's a never ending cycle lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I use it against myself. I think " you know, I'm married, with no kids. This guy has kids. I'd rather take the extra time than make him" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom's Ex-husband. He was a crack head who took advantage of my mom for 10 years. He was in his 40s with nothing to show for it. When he held a job, he was a top-notch worker, until he decided to go out on 3 day crack binges. His mistakes in life were my guide to success.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the MTV episode of "True Life" be a Financial Dominatrix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I think they should leave it alone. It ended well. While it was sad to see it go, I feel like it ran its course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good thing. Lying is soo much work. It's easier to just tell the truth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have TWC (now spectrum). I was paying $58 for 100 MBPS, with no data cap. Now, I'm paying $95 for 100mbps, with cable, because I love trash TV.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say Futurama.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a kid, "House On Haunted Hill" really fucking scared me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth It by Fifth Harmony. 

It's catchy as fuck in that PetSmart commercial </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came to say this as well. I thoroughly enjoyed the humor throughout </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I only have 3 cigarettes" Hubby caught me in that one real fast lol.

Other than that, I honestly can not remember the last lie I told... I just don't think it's worth it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like my purpose to be the positive ray of sunshine at all times. Especially at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toilet germs. I choose to ignore the fact that I'm going ass to ass with someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think she's spunky, wrap your monkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 2010 Honda Civic died after 2 years, with only 84k miles. :/ Air compressor went out, computer died...managed to get full dealer trade in value and got a 2011 CRV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That, and its at minimum an 8 year investment. I just paid $1500 for a king size bed and frame and I find that it's worth it just for the fact that it is for 8 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 03:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep it classy Jacksonville
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a reaction to purple ink. that shit looked NASTY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 22:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ain't cheatin', you ain't tryin'! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 22:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband and I met in band as well :) (after marching season, so concert season, ha!) There's a reason band kids are called nerds! We're somewhat excited to be there for the day lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 14:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone just needs to go get a lifeproof case -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was in 6th grade, 11/12 years old, a 13 year old boy punched me in the mouth because I told him to stop touching my Pokemon cards. Fuck that kid

First ACTUAL fight:
I was 14 I think. This girl had been teasing and making fun of me ALL day. I went to a teacher and was told to ignore it. There's only so much ignoring one can do. Finally, it was the end of the day and I was walking to my bus. This girl and her friends were standing by the door pointing and laughing at me. At that point, I had had it. I walk up to her, punch her square in the mouth. I back up to get another shot and trip over my friend who is right behind me. 

I'd say I won, since she never actually touched me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rebel Wilson. I feel like we could have a good ol time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either mind reading, or the ability to know everything :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the actual fuck
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing that is actually bothering me is the fact the her eyebrows look like stick on mustaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On my flight from London to Dallas, I was flying American/British Airlines, and got seated near the back where there are 2 seats instead of 3. I was initially going to upgrade my seat, but figured since the seating chart on the app had space between the seats, it wasn't worth it. I get seated on the plane and turns out the seats are in fact, right next to each other. The guy next to me was pretty large. Turns out, he actually paid extra money to sit in those seats because he thought, like I did, that there was extra space. I waited til the plane finished boarding and then grabbed an empty aisle seat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 17:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She actually just left the state for a new job, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Car Registration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 15:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there pf!

I'm writing today because I'm in a bit of a pickle. I live in California, and about a month ago, I purchased a 2002 PT Cruiser from a coworker for $1400.Runs like a champ! The only issue is that she had to file for a lost title, because her house was broken into a few months back, and that was one of the stolen items.

I've been driving it for the past month with no registration, since I have a month to register. I still do not have a title. I contacted coworker and she still has not heard anything, after being told initially it would only take 3 weeks. I will be heading overseas in about 3 weeks. The car is in my name. If I do not register it before I leave, I'll have a $1400 paperweight in my driveway. Is there anyway my husband can register the car in my name? Does power of attorney give him the right to do so?

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just remember that a majority of things are in our control. I've made good choices up to this point, so I have no reason to let someone else's poor choices affect my attitude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They hold my mortgage (it was sold to them), and my car loan. I have most other stuff through Navy Federal. Waiting a little bit of time to refinance and get the fuck away from them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 17:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know man. I was congested the other day and couldn't taste my food... It was unsettling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was taken last Halloween when we dressed her up as Nibbler :)
http://i.imgur.com/R4e6rQG.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom is like my best friend, I can talk to her about anything. 

But goddamnit is she a selfish bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a contractor and will be overseas during voting. Most of my area does mail in ballots. I'm still trying to figure out how I'm going to do mine while I'm gone. Mail takes about a month :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hunni. She is a black lab/hound mix and awesome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drank 160oz of water the other day and someone was convinced I was going to die lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hold on to it for groceries. You never know when you're going to run into hard times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I carry a small pikachu backpack as my purse :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 04:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol she's pretty. But so am I :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most of the games that I would want to play are also on PC.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy groceries on Amazin Prime with Prime Pantry. Save it for a rainy day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. If this money isn't going to "expire", save it for something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still enjoy a good visit to Chuckie Cheese </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good example is: You can't expect to get a job if you don't apply. Someone's not just gonna walk up to your door and offer you a job. You have to take the first step </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me feel good lol. I'm 23 with a 401k through work and a roth IRA through my credit union </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I told my SIL if she was going to wear a skirt, she needs to wear pantyhose. She wore a skirt with no hose. Told her that flats aren't typically professional, so she should wear pumps. She wore flats.

Its a good thing she's only going for minimum wage jobs, because she's definitely not dressing for the job she wants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, sometimes that is the only option to get them from point A to point B. I moved my dog and cat in a car for 30+ hours. Would have much rather flown them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is the only place I get my news. I see an article, read it, read the comments, article is debunked, move along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The soundtrack from "Disney Skate Adventure" for GameCube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just dont feel like it adds anything to the meal, except making me extra bloated lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the internet is a magic place with...pirates
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This Magic Moment - Ben E. King </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the bread just makes the burger harder to eat. I'd rather just fork and knife it :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't finish Breaking Bad, it just got boring.

Dexter.

And I didn't finish the last season of True Blood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Family Guy :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
