<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2868</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is absolutely true, generally speaking. however, just to add to /u/kyuz's point, your last line of defense (or one of them) if someone blows by your seated guard is to sort of do a half-backroll up onto your shoulder-blades to bring your knees to your shoulders, closing off the space he's passing into. at the same time, you put your hands on the mat to help you spin to square back up. 

so yeah, you definitely want to sit up at first, but if he's dancing around you, try the backroll to reguard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 05:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you only think it doesnt apply because you're subject to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dunning%E2%80%93Kruger_effect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dunning%E2%80%93Kruger_effect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I totally agree. All those no-gi world champions are totally wasting their time training gi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 to Reilly Bodycomb. Try searching Youtube for videos on "the saddle", "the knot", "the slide lock", etc. Awesome stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 21:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with /u/chokingmn, but my preference is to use the shield. I think it's a good habit to put up as many frames as possible. I find it helps keep them "floated" to facilitate sweeps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh damn, my bad dude. that must have been before you started claiming you were a brown belt. that makes much more sense. sorry man, my fault.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 17:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what would be a solid siphon brewer currently on the market?

also fun fact (not sure if it's true): despite the futuristic-looking design, siphon brewers were invented before the french press </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 13:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my favorite part was when /u/johnnykimura said that the rubber guard should have a 100% success rate. 

it was the white-beltiest comment i've ever seen on this sub. his flair was brown at the time, but forever after it was 100% guaranteed in my mind that he was a white belt. which of course turns out to be true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 03:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have a cool life; i would like to hear more about your 11-year progression, please. where did you go? what's your career now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 19:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you are both talking about the same thing, essentially. Cutting an extreme angle usually just means your hips are doing the job of moving his arm across, instead of your own arms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 03:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see this. 

/u/SmallManBJJ is the guy whose first and only post here is titled: **"Is this ok if I am too weak to posture in my opponent's guard?"**

http://www.reddit.com/r/bjj/comments/2z5x9u/is_this_ok_if_i_am_too_weak_to_posture_in_my/

My money is on /u/Kintanon for this one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 16:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely the biggest culprit for more serious neck injuries, at least in my experience, is people getting accidentally dropped on their head because they were trying to submit from guard and didn't let go, or didn't let go on a controlled way. They didn't get slammed, just stubbornly held on and then accidentally slipped off, or the guy stumbled. Gotta let go if you get picked up. 

The other way people get serious neck injuries is trying to double leg (or head-outside single) while their head is stuck in a guillotine. This is not as common-sense as the example above, so definitely something to watch out for. This is why folks need to learn proper takedowns even if they don't do much standup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 22:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually pretty new - people like Lloyd Irvin popularized it (expecting to be called Master, etc.) It's not a good change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made my own - unlike these inferior artificial versions, mine is perfectly distributed and made from sustainable organic material (mostly donuts).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 20:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar situation for me. With a lot of mediocre experience under my belt, I started off better than most, but then improved more slowly as I had to unlearn bad habits. 

But the grueling process of unlearning bad habits has now given me a more discerning eye for what is good technique... so I guess it all evens out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime - good luck! Send us some tape if you want, and I'm happy to analyze. 

EDIT: Who would downvote this? Is someone just going through my post history downvoting everything? You have too much time on your hands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 19:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree 100%. If they make a huge push, it's a lot easier. 

If they are pushing just enough to maintain space while moving well, agree that's much better technique, so a lot more finesse is required. I find if I'm being patient, circling with them while "floating" on their frame, my weight alone will be enough to eventually kill the frame OR bait them into pushing harder so I can deflect it. Against our best people though, that's still not always enough. 

So all-in-all, I completely agree that the bigger move is sometimes needed, especially if you're in a lower weight class than your partner and he moves well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 19:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more reliable than jumping over the legs or trying to dive for a leg lock.

Yes, and I would also add - the simple hip switch you describe is also more reliable than trying to circle-step to North/South. A lot of folks are suggesting North/South, and I agree with /u/cwrestler141 that forcing them to readjust their frame is good, but one shouldn't have to make such big moves to do it. 

Personally I don't like the North/South transition in principle. Somebody with really good guard frames and retention will probably be able to capitalize on all that space. In principle, the top guy has the advantage of gravity and mobility, so there are very few situations when the top guy should have to make big movements.  

So I also prefer the hip switch you describe. But to take it to the next level, I would also suggest seeing if you can make the hip drop an even smaller movement (e.g., so no recovery is necessary) while still creating enough of an angle to deflect his post. Especially on top, I'm always looking to use the smallest movement possible that still achieves the desired goal, since space and movement benefit the bottom guy so much more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 17:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he's stiff-arming your head/shoulder and/or blocking your crossface arm: do what /u/chokingmn says. 

If he's stiff-arming my hip, I like to use Marcelo's solution: swim my far knee around his arm and pin it to the mat. You can do it in two different ways: drive your knee inside his arm and then pin it to the mat, or drive your knee over his arm and then trap his arm between your armpit and thigh. 

I cant remember which Marcelo vids show this, but if you search for Marcelo's passing you'll find it. I find this has a higher success rate than rolling my hips against his wrist. But what they all have in common is "deflecting" his arm out of the way. He is doing you a favor by locking his arm out - when it's locked out, it's a single "piece" that you can deflect out of the way by switching your hips slightly. People who are really good will only stiff-arm for a split second to maintain space long enough to set up hip movement/reguarding. So at a higher level you will have to worry less about the stiff arm and more about the movement that follows it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 15:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense - glad to hear Eddie teaches a more legit version. I'd still encourage you to use your R hand for the knee tap instead of the ankle so you don't have to reach as far. Video 1 (above) is a nice example. 

Sadly, what you see in Video 2 on the other hand is way too common: scrubs giving 10th Planet a bad name by putting out laughably bad instructional videos when they have no business teaching.  

Especially since you train MMA it's 10x more important to test your A-game escapes when strikes are involved (and when people are generally being more aggressive, better wrestlers, etc.) In addition to the knee tap, I recommend the single leg low mat finish, since that will keep you safer in MMA: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CxjiuZWXvIE

To get this move from half guard, you're going to come up and get whizzered, then you sit back and grab the front of his quad by the knee instead of keeping your deep underhook on the body. You already have his leg trapped because you were in half guard. Then you tabletop his foot on your own thigh and run him over that way. This is far superior for MMA because there's no way you'll get hit - you have a better angle and more weight on him, and if he lets go at any point to strike, he'll fall right over. Usually into a fully-flattened back mount.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 15:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gustavo is the man, I love his old Great Escapes instructional </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 01:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, so my thoughts are:

Video 1 is good technique and I would **not** call this the old school. This is just a good ol' knee tap from the whizzer and works great. I use it all the time.

Video 2 is definitely Eddie's Old School, and in my opinion it's a bad technique when done like this. you're absolutely right that you SHOULD release the lockdown to push into them, but for some reason people teach it the way it is in this video (keeping the lockdown and reaching with your arm) which is a terrible idea. 

I'm glad it helped. Feel free to send me tape any time, or PM me with questions, and I'll do another analysis for you. 

I dont mind you asking at all. I try to keep myself on the down-low when posting online. Without giving too much away: I have trained a lot of places, but primarily in NYC these days. Aside from my current instructor, the biggest influence on my learning has been Ryan Hall.  From academy affiliations you might be able to guess where I train  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 00:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree - I actually think the Deep Half DVD is the most appropriate for a white belt. White belts are going to spend a ton of time in bottom half guard, so even if OP uses none of the actual deep half techniques, the guard concepts alone and guard structure chains from the half guard shell will benefit him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 23:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK yeah - a couple minor variations make all the difference here. 

The knee tap from dogfight is totally legit, especially if you let go of the lockdown and get up on your full base. Keep doing it. I would not call that the Old School. Here's a decent video of what I mean for the leg position that works well: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Kx5qdrX5q8 t=48

Where people get into trouble is when they do it like this - this is the Old School I'm talking about: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hnZhwPpf29Y t=101

Basically, in this video he does a good job getting up on his arm for base, but then he awkwardly dives/reaches for the ankle while maintaining his lockdown, giving up all the ground he won by getting on his base elbow. This is the move, but it's just such an awful idea to do it this way. 

Against anybody halfway decent, they are going to have steady pressure on that whizzer. As soon as the bottom guy reaches for the ankle, that steady pressure will immediately flatten him back out because he voluntarily gave up his basing arm. Also, since the top guy already has a whizzer, the bottom guy reaching is putting himself in fantastic position to get darced or guillotined (the common theme is that your head WILL get caught). 

Even if he gets the top guy's ankle, it's super easy to sprawl out if you have heavy hips and a decent whizzer. From there there are tons of options for the top guy - forearm in neck and pummel for underhook, forehead under the guy's chin to keep him flattened, etc. etc. 

So what makes the knee tap good and the old school shitty? The knee tap keeps you in good position throughout the whole sequence (good base, straight spine, tight arms) while the Old School basically requires you to get yourself out of position (arms out in space, legs tied up, voluntarily giving up base). That's ultimately why I think the Old School is a garbage move, but your knee tap from dogfight is just fine. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 20:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're absolutely right - the Old School is often used to set up the Electric Chair. I used that game for years, and it certainly works great for Eddie. 

However, in my very humble opinion, even though it does work, the way people use this combo is ill-conceived. I'll do my best to explain: Locking down your legs and using your one arm to either pull his base leg out (old school) or wrench it over you (electric chair) is a very inefficient way to get under him and sweep, even when you account for the whip up. 

Don't get me wrong: it absolutely works some times - it works for Eddie and it worked for me for years. My point is that there are just far better options when you're in that situation to get to the Electric Chair or Deep Half that don't involve reaching for his leg, Old School style. 

I strongly recommend watching Ryan Hall's Deep Half Guard DVDs if you want to take your half guard to the next level, even if you keep using the lockdown/electric chair. Ryan shares much more effective ways to get underneath that minimize the chance you'll get your head caught - I think you'll have much better luck with these than you will with the Old School. 

The Old School is just that - old. It comes from a time in BJJ when the half guard was considered a stalling position halfway to getting your guard passed where you triangle your legs and hold on for dear life. Several innovators came along (like Gordo) who turned the half guard into a totally viable position that people actively want to pull. They introduced far better options to get underneath, which have taken over at the elite level. This is partly why we now call sweeps like that "Old School."

I won't get into a style vs. style argument because I don't believe in that, but my honest advice to you as my BJJ bro is to retire the Old School and instead learn some moves that let you use your hips more efficiently and involve fighting up to your base, like the Twist Sweep, or getting up to the Dogfight. Against guys who are good on top, crunching up and reaching is going to stop working really fast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 16:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure! Rolling with Ryan Hall feels like this. He is not heavy (145 or something?) but he puts ALL of his weight on you, and puts that weight exactly where it needs to be to stop you from moving effectively. 

When I say he puts all of his weight on you, I mean literally ALL. His balance is so good that he will just surf on people (i.e., no part of his body is touching the mat). It's unbelievably exhausting and demoralizing in the most awesome way possible. It really makes you think critically about the right way to move on the bottom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 16:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not that it doesn't work, it's just not optimal when you consider the whole situation of bottom half guard. If you like to use the Old School sweep, I recommend trying the following drill/experiment:

Tell your partner "I'm going to go for the Old School sweep and I just want you to block me from doing it however you can, especially by crossfacing. Don't even try to pass, just see if I can do it."

If they have any level of competency on top, or halfway decent crossface, there's almost no chance you will sweep.  /u/erangalp identified the same issue below - reaching for the Old School and getting flattened. It's just a suboptimal approach to sweeping in general. If you want to sweep, you create movement and unbalance, you don't just lay down and reach for his base and hope you can pull out his base before he smears you into the mat. 

From any guard, if you don't create movement to unbalance and make him occupy his hands and readjust his base, you're going to spend a LOT of time just smashed into the mat and flattened against anybody halfway decent. That's why I discourage people from getting into the habit of attempting the Old School, despite the fact that it can work and looks intuitive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 15:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would feel bad because it means you're getting clowned :)

In seriousness though, I only do this to friends of mine who wouldn't take it the wrong way and wouldn't hurt themselves trying to escape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should watch some Marcelo ADCC vids, he did this advancing butterfly approach on everyone. He also had a DVD set where he explained it in more detail.

Yup, by far the most helpful thing for my no-gi open guard was good old Marcelo Garcia Series 1. The philosophy of taking initiative in the guard is baked into the entire thing and makes it very intuitive: https://www.groundfighter.com/Marcelo-Garcia-Series-1/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good stuff. vai pegar! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're honestly doing great, especially considering the layoff. My game is super similar to yours, which also means I've worked on a lot of the same problems. More grist for the (open mat) mill. Send us more of this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my other comment on comment (metacomment)

In addition to that, stop counter-fighting and baiting for mistakes. I want you to FORCE mistakes. Check out this thread: http://www.reddit.com/r/bjj/comments/2vqwhl/stallers_in_your_closed_guard/cok9sa9?context=3

When I start a roll with blue belts I know, from situp guard, sometimes I'll just push them to see if they'll fall over. Sometimes they do, but even if they don't, if they respond with forward momentum they'll fall right into my armdrag. 

Try goofy stuff on white belts. Kick out their base foot with your foot. If you're on top, stand on them like a surfboard and see how they get out. Adding a little bit of clowning has actually helped me in weird ways, including with staying active.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, I have BIG problems with pausing, assertiveness, finishing sweeps, scrambles, etc. The best advice I can give is to flow roll with a smaller, calmer, but seasoned blue belt, and just constantly focus on removing those pauses. 

At one point I set up an experimental drill like this: i told a good training buddy that if I stop at any point to think or weigh options, I am going tap and start over, counting it as a "loss." tried it a couple times and suddenly the pauses were gone! I find myself being a lot more active now, just naturally pushing and pulling a lot more to test the waters here and there, and the windows of opportunity just seem so much more obvious now. sweeps just seem to happen and my training partners tell me it's a lot less telegraphed and predictable. removing the analysis paralysis caused an immediate, noticeable jump in my success rate (though i got subbed a bit more at first) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a happy drunk and you're my favorite /r/bjj commentator, so you get comments on your comments. Comment the first:

My halfguard posture is an active problem. Sometimes I remember and keep my back straight, sometimes I don't and this guy had me thrown off of my gameplan enough that I reverted to hunching up and trying to get under him instead of playing long range halfguard.

So, it might be less of a posture problem and move of a movement problem. I look at it this way: in the guard, you can't just latch on and go for one or the other (distance or close range). You gotta be pushing and pulling constantly. Your body as a whole has two fundamental movements: full extension (like a deadlift or the first part of a clean and jerk) and full flexion (like the very bottom of a squat). If you want to keep good posture and reliably sweep people who are legitimately good on top, you're going to need to move between both full-body extension and flexion. That's what will create the off-balancing that allows for sweeps. If you keep moving in that way while protecting your neck, the sweeps just kind of happen and the good posture takes care of itself. 

EDIT: Comment the second:

Dude already had my head, which is why I went for the sweep. I was hoping he would let go if I started to sweep him, but he never did. Even when I'm on top of half guard he never loosened up on my head enough for me to clear it and complete the pass.

Totally hear you - this used to be a big problem for me, which is why I'm so vocal about it. If your head is caught, I still say don't try to sweep from bad position. Fix the bad position first, then try to sweep. Forcing him to post is the only way you're gonna free your head, so you gotta bridge R and bridge or twist sweep L in quick succession. He doesnt even have to post his whole hand - against the brown and black belts at my gym I can only get them to barely post an elbow for a split second, but that's enough! From there, swim your hands back in, then start working your sweeps from good position. 

Edit 2: Comment the third: 

 It definitely didn't feel like there was time to attempt anything between me tabling up and him stepping around to my back.

Drillers are killers. A lot of the stuff I called out for you is stuff I'm actively working on right now too - this included. Something about turtling up makes me hesitate too. The granby from turtle is a good one to try, but pick your favorite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 02:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, on to Video 2. 

00:17 Your posture is far better from the very beginning. I think you are feeling a lot more confident because you know the guy, and that actually shows very obviously in your posture. I bet you have a terrible poker face. You looked scared of the guy in Video 1. 

00:22 Genuinely excellent shot! Oh that was your buddy. Well, not much you could have done after that. 

00:29 Really nice active guard and good guard retention movement. 

00:40 Opponent now Schaubs, fearful of your scootery

00:48 Your guard is getting passed too easily relative to your overall skill level. Here this happened because you got lazy with the scoot for a split second. If you're going to play situp guard in no-gi, you absolutely must move forward at all times. If he gets out of range (which for me means I can no longer reach him with a butterfly hook at his ankle) you need to recognize the pass is coming. Bail to plan B like this: do a half-backroll motion to close off the space between your knees and elbows and to get your guard back in play, place your hands on the mat, and roll up onto your shoulders. Your hands on the mat will let you spin way faster than he can dance around you. And closing off your knee-to-elbow space will buy you time to get a guard going. 

1:10 good assertive guard pull - I'd say it was luck of the scramble here that got you passed 

1:20 haha his kesa gatame sucks, but your defense sucks more. swing your legs right to left and use that momentum to jerk your R elbow down to the mat. framing on his face is very old school and really just doesnt work if you don't combo it with leg/hip movement. 

1:43 bored and fast-forwarding...

2:04 sick arm triangle setup by your buddy, but terrible positional control when he got it. he needs to drop his hips and settle. then he uses it to go to mount? silly. 

2:40 your own arm triangle defense is what's keeping you in the arm triangle now. don't just "answer the phone" - you need to flare your elbow out so that your humerus creates a frame in his neck. and then as soon as you feel his head rise up a bit (which it did multiple times) you need to jack your elbow down to the mat, then you're out

3:03 OK seriously you're literally out of the arm triangle, just move your arm and you're out. jesus. 

3:10 you got out and then put yourself back in, prioritizing the frame to defend the crossface. why? bad trade. 

3:41 way to completely kill your own hips with the lockdown half guard. trying to lockdown in reverse kesa is just delaying the inevitable. do you know the twist sweep? step 1: let go of the lockdown because it sucks. step 2: swing both legs hard to your R and or stomp both feet on the side of his knee. this will move his trapped leg and force him to post. step 3: if that doesnt sweep him, shoot your R leg in for a butterfly hook and get to butterfly guard

4:00 aww he's a good friend

4:16 lazy situp guard. move forward or people are going to blow past you. 

4:30 you did a beautiful DLR guard pull and then didn't bother to protect your neck. I can't stress this enough: defending your neck is priority 1 in guard because you really can't do anything of value if you're getting violently smeared into the mat with a crossface. in my recent lazy years, I pass people all day by ignoring what they're doing with their legs in guard and go straight for the crossface. almost without exception, no matter what guard they're attempting, i try to crossface. if i get it, I pass 99% of the time, because it totally cripples them. 

4:37 you're defending well but not taking opportunities when the window presents itself. Case in point: you could get your elbow to the mat to stop this kesa before it starts, but instead your settling into the position and thinking about framing. stop it. if your arms are relatively safe, you need move your hips before anything else. 

5:00 laziness. if you're not going to bridge, at least swing your legs back and forth to create small spaces and force him to adjust. it takes less energy than a big bridge but can create just as much space. 

5:09 you get clowned. your arm was tight to defend but you allowed your elbow to cross the midline just enough to get wrapped up. 

5:43 what is it with you and the lockdown? your hips are totally free! you need your legs out of that stupid lockdown so you can bridge and shrimp to escape - you're just delaying the inevitable again. 

Final thoughts: As above, you have great fundamental sub defense but you need to trust it long enough to start working actual reversals and escapes. You REALLY need to protect your head and neck more, but even when you avoid the smash for a few seconds to survive, you then look like you have absolutely no plan after you defend the first, second, and third sub attempts. You need to convert on that defense!  

It also looks like you have no plan in half guard, kesa, and side control. Why are you not bridging or at least swinging your legs to create some space? If you're going to grab a lockdown, USE IT. Or better yet, stop going for it, because you need to remember to bridge and shrimp a LOT more than you're doing now, and the lockdown encourages stagnation. 

Keep the confidence up and remove the pauses from your game - my comments may not fully reflect this, but you are a beast!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 01:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already drunk, stay tuned please...

Edit 1: Video 1: First impressions. Haircut motherfucker, get you one. 

Edit 2: Video 1: 00:28 Ever heard of Judo? How about grip fighting?

Edit 3: Video 1: 2:00 Are you for real? Please stop doing the Old School sweep, it's garbage. Why? The exact reason it caused a scramble for you - reaching with your R arm got your head caught. Priority #1 is to PROTECT YA NECK in half guard. You also locked down your hips unnecessarily. Next time, post with your R arm instead and hip into him to force a reaction. I want you fighting up toward your base, not trying to sweep from your back. 

Edit 4: Video 1: 2:28 Opponent felt bad for you and gave up superior position. You now have top half guard. 

Edit 5: Video 1: 2:40 Checking the time - at this point I would like to point out that you have spent the entire match hunched over. Posture dude. Fight your arms inside, arch your back hard, bump to both sides, do whatever you can to get that spine straight. Let's see if posture improves as video continues. 

Edit 6: Video 1: 2:57 You did all that work to get to turtle and then completely half-assed it from there. Your opponent has awful top turtle control and obligingly opened his arms for a competition eternity as he circled, but you did nothing. Why not at least pretend you might granby roll?

Edit 7: Video 1: 3:05 OK I get it now, you're a counter-fighter. Nice job taking your back away from his sternum to mess up his back control. He should be toast from here, really should not be able to recover good back control. Let's see what you can make out of this. 

Edit 8: Video 1: 3:05 - 3:35 Oh you moved your hand, thank god. For 30 seconds there I thought you were unconscious or dead. You know, 30 seconds ago you were basically out of his back control, but you gave up and conceded the position. Dont do that k?

Edit 9: Video 1: 4:03 Look where his head is. LOOK AT IT. His head is way out in space and his hands are periodically letting go to gripfight. At any point you could have jacked your L arm down toward the mat and significantly improved your position, despite the body triangle. 

Edit 10: Video 1: 4:19 His face says "I can't believe I won - was it really that easy?"

Edit the 11th: Video 1: Final impressions. OK, two things. 

1) As /u/gunslinger_006 says below, your technique is looking great (especially for defenses and sub counters) but you're just not being assertive and active enough. You're making it too easy for him when you're on the defense by not using motion to create space and force him to readjust. So what does that mean? TRUST your good defense and TRUST that it will still be there when you then create movement to escape. Don't wait to be ready to move toward the escape, just trust your defense and go. Was it partly a cardio issue? You need to take the pauses out of your game and let your game flow - and trust your defense is good enough not to get subbed. 

2) If there's one move you need to learn it's the wrestling single-leg LOW FINISH ON THE MAT. Here's a mediocre youtube instructional (you can definitely find better): https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rfr0UomatdU
You're just latching on to his leg in both half guard and turtle - you need to CIRCLE STEP while keeping the pressure on him if you want to make anything happen from here. He's still in superior position from top half guard and top turtle, but ONLY UNTIL you can cut an angle on him, then you're winning. 

Overall, I give you an F+ for effort. JK, good stuff. Watching the rest now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 18:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that student (who I have always kept my distance from)

That's an odd thing to say. Why have you always kept your distance from one of your fellow training partners?

Until she's willing to say who she's accusing and what they've done, it's just piss in a firepit to me.

Yeah? Why's that? Sounds like she only requested info about the gym's harassment policy, which it's apparently required to have by law. So what does naming and shaming her alleged assailant have to do with it? It's absolutely her right not to name the person. Maybe she doesn't think they deserve to be nationally shamed. That's a totally separate issue from whether the gym has a harassment policy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 17:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's this for character? 

Ari attempting to downplay and cover up the repeated sexual harassment of one of his students, for example:

https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=1421157718182259 id=100008641324196 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 05:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of classic fallacies and misinformation in your argument, but I'll just share my 2 cents. In every poll I've ever seen of the "best instructors in all of BJJ," Ryan Hall's name was included. People on /r/bjj and other forums ask all the time about best instructional videos, and Ryan is #1 the majority of the time. 

I've informally talked to black belt instructors at both BJJ and MMA gyms across the U.S. and in the past 5 years I'd say 90% of the time the conversation about "people who most influenced their game" comes up, they mention Ryan as at least one of the people, along with Saulo and Marcelo. 

I could care less about Ryan as a person, and I barely use any elements of his game, just telling you for a fact that you're wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahah that's what I like to see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this conversation thread will help you: http://www.reddit.com/r/bjj/comments/2vqwhl/stallers_in_your_closed_guard/cok9sa9?context=3

Long story short: if people can do goofy stuff like pressure points while in your guard, it's because your guard is not active enough yet. If you have an active guard (moving your hips, and pushing/pulling with your legs and arms at the very least) they will be forced to occupy their arms to maintain balance and regain proper position. 

You don't have to be pulling off sick sweeps and subs yet - just off-balancing them with movement will be enough to keep you pretty safe. Just keep moving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respect. *fist bump* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's good at least. You did the right thing. 

Next time, do the right thing because it's the right thing, not just "to please everyone."

I get what you're saying, but I believe people are at least partly responsible for how other people interpret what they write in public. So now that you've learned the real circumstances, I think you have done the right thing by taking it down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 04:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of people who are new to BJJ have a very similar experience. They start doing BJJ at whatever gym is nearby, but then quickly hear about 10th Planet because of the marketing (Joe is a big part of this). 10th Planet ends up sounding like this revolutionary system that is "outside the mainstream, man," but poised to change everything, if only people would give it due credit. 

Except... that's the same narrative we've been hearing for 10+ years and that certainly hasn't happened. Don't get me wrong: Eddie is the man and 10th Planet gyms train solid techniques just like plenty of other gyms, but those other gyms don't market it as if it's going to change the world. Keep an open mind, try lots of things, and do what works for you. 

No matter what you do, for the love of god, don't become one of the typical 10th Planet internet fanboys, and/or the guy who interrupts class to do a white belt seminar on rubber guard in the corner. Especially the latter. Don't be that guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 13:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So be a big boy and write a retraction. Or at least an update for clarification. At the time you said you agree with his action and essentially called the girl a "bad person." Now you know that's not true. So be an adult and rectify it.

I had never heard of your site until now, but can definitely see why people on here downvote your shit. You sound like a sociopath.

It's great that doing this makes you happy, but I reserve the right to call you a piece of shit if you leave up an article glorifying Keith for bullying a teenage girl and don't post a correction or write a retraction.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You blogged about a grown man bullying a teenage girl as if it were some kind of heroic gesture. You're a piece of shit. 

Also, your website is bad and you should feel bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 19:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely the same for me. In a lot of schools I visit, every blue belt seems to pull out crazy berimbolos, rubber guard, exotic lapel guards, etc. Against purple belts and below, the vast majority of guard techniques can be stuffed by simply maintaining a straight spine and low, wide base. You don't need a vast library of counters, just posture, base, and balance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
