<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6749</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Learn something about everything and everything about something" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Brothers Bloom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I just have your paycheck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The likelihood of you possibly knowing somebody that I know just increased so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coolworks.com has changed my life by working seasonally in a few different national parks. It's a great way to see the country and meet folks from all over the world. So cheap to live in these places, too. In sequoia national park the rent was $100/month. I seriously recommend this as an option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 08:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been a cook for about 12 years (female here) and I get it. Men have always been the group of people to go out with. It's just way simpler and I enjoy the comedy and company. Females have always made me feel so insecure and awkward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've worn it once maybe twice because I thought it's what I'm supposed to do and all I did was touch my eyes and smudge everything on my face. It felt exactly what it was, something on my face and I wanted it off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Female  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to watch this show called "Greetings From Tucson" and it ended prematurely because one of the main characters was killed in a small plane crash. I loved this show. I'd watch it with my dad. I didn't know all of this until many years later. Did anybody else see this show? I just feel like it's  all my imagination that it even existed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct center of the North American continent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
