<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4125</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lactic acid triggers prion formation in fermenting yeast, reprogramming carbohydrate metabolism and leading to less alcohol being produced. This explains why lactic acid-producing bacteria are often found in failed wine fermentations, which is something that Pasteur pondered over 140 years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An antidepressant that increases the amount of serotonin circulating in the brain (an SSRI) boosts motivation in healthy people by reducing their perceived cost of putting in more effort. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 11:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human skin cells converted into brain cells in the laboratory importantly retain the age of the original donor. This discovery could open up new avenues of research into late-onset illnesses like Huntingtons disease and Alzheimers disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reprogrammed human, chimpanzee and orangutan cells have been grown into brain organoids in the laboratory, revealing important similarities and differences between the species. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 14:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to the [research paper](https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e19766).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A small transparent crustacean allows researchers to see how limbs regenerate, which could lead to breakthroughs in regenerative medicine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 13:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer simulations model the crowded cytoplasm of a bacterial cell in atomistic detail. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 12:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
