<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8487</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations to you as well!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.  I will probably do the same.  I can put an additional $500 in savings in probably 2-3 paychecks; after which I will pay off car ASAP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With snowball rollover - January 2018 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $218.20/month at 3.5%... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good advice, thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a dark, jobless period.  Been 6 years at current job and loving it.  (Knock on wood) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was most recently at 779- maybe a little nudge further now?  Fingers crossed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read about the snowball effect- the money I was putting towards the credit card will now be rolled into my car payment.  

I only have $1000 in savings- should I bolster that first to say 2 or 3,000 before hitting my car loan with extra?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prioritizing this hurdle over superfluous expenditures and dumping tax returns at it.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks- it's an amazing feeling! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, veggie tales are evolving  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sights are set squarely on my car loan next. $3,600 to go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took a few years but... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $11,000 in credit card debt is gone as of 5 minutes ago.  
I'm glowing!

Just wanted to share my happiness :)


EDIT:  The love here is blowing me away.  What a great community this is for people in hard times.  Nice to find advice when needed and help celebrating the victories.  If I could buy you all a drink, I'd be right back where I started.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just elegant.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankyou!  I didn't know this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saved approximately $1500 on labor doing it myself.  Wholly satisfying.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when you say repair, you mean non-routine maintenance, right?

So if my car needed new brakes, what I factor that into the $2400 a year? Or is that just routine maintenance that I shouldn't count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To keep or upgrade my car- that is the question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have, what to me seems like a quandary.  I am a housing inspector for a gov. agency and spend most of my day driving from zip code to zip code. My car is essentially my office. 
I own a 2008 Honda Accord sedan.  142,000. Lots of life in the car.  I recently spent an afternoon changing all the brakes, rotors and struts.  
Should go another 100,000 easy. I take care of it. 
I owe $3,900 and change on it and am nearing the end of a long battle with a credit card.  I owed $11,000 on it a few years ago and now it's down to $500.  I can smell victory. 

I'm debating a newish Honda Civic with many extra safety features.  A lot of the brake and lane assist type stuff that my car doesn't have.  

It would get better gas mileage.  I currently get $.48 cents a mile reimbursement to use my personal car for work.  

It seems appealing from a few standpoints, mostly additional safety features since I'm on the road so much.   

All that and then I'm back in the hole considerably with a car payment though.  Currently $220/month. More when I finish my CC bill.  

Is it worth it?  Do I drive my Honda clear into the ground and sell for basically nothing later on or get rid of it when there's still some value in it?  Is there a "sweet spot" for a time to sell a car and get a newer model? 
Am I thinking about this all wrong? 

Reddit geniuses unite!  :) thanks for any help in thinking about it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT clown- sans makeup.  They all float down here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which way did it go, George? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She bangs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her areolas seem to be melting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 10:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those legs! She appears to be assuming her final form.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MY EYE!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't chevy chase save him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had some extra time while your mom was washing off.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Booger sugar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's way past Robitussin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As Chris Rock said: "what is sexual harassment?  When an ugly man wants some?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually hoping that once everyone was in the truck he'd open up a can </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. No. No nothing that extreme.  I'm actually feeling quite a bit more settled after some of this awesome feedback.  I'm not sure where or even IF magic happens,all I know is that abortions just generally suck but women have their reasons and that is sufficient.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *did a crap job.   Oh the irony there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 07:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree with basically everything you just said.  I wanted that to come across in my post but maybe didn't a crap job of it- walking in someone else's shoes is damned near impossible.   Broad stroking a requirement to take pregnancy to full term makes zero sense.   I consider myself somewhat analytical, so your stats helped my thinking along.  
Appreciated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do actually.  Especially as an atheist.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your last paragraph I think summed up what I'll say to myself and others going forward.   There are just WAY too many x-factors that go into a huge decision like this to be able to properly judge someone AND absolutely no way we can paint with a broad brush.   
I appreciate your feedback.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said.  You're correct.   There is a lot of obfuscation that takes place in this debate, generally.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.   Thank you.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re: forcing women to be pregnant- definitely not.  
I hear what you're saying but wonder if your analogy isn't quite spot on?   If I had no attachment to the person who needed a kidney or it was just a total stranger I would feel no obligation.  Both sexual partners, though, created this fetus so do they bare more personal responsibility for it?  

If I accidentally stabbed someone in the kidneys (not sure how that would happen) I would then most definitely feel like I owed them a kidney.  If there were no other donor and I was compatible I feel it would be morally obligatory to right a wrong I created.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm definitely not concerned with anything Jesus said about anything-  I like that you called me out on being the arbiter of what's legitimate.  I missed that when writing the post so, thanks for that.  
I think I'm more feeling on some level that a viable fetus should get to have a "go" at life.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This won't be popular but, can we talk about abortion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 05:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been a soft-atheist for about 6 years now.  I won't get into the 'why's and how's', but I've prided myself on being pliable on issues and open to evidence. I always assume what I know isn't exhaustive on any particular issue and always take on each conversation with the intent on trying to learn something. 

That being said, and this could be a cross-over post to r/changemyview, in the past year or so, I've begun wondering about abortion and whether being staunchly pro-choice is the moral high ground.  Granted, there are innumerable one-off cases involving just about every scenario concerning mother's health, or baby's health, and on most of those cases I generally fall pro-choice, but when it comes to abortions of convenience (if that's a term even, I realize I have only a side perspective as a man) is it really right that we are terming "candidate members of society" as Hitchens called them?

I realize this may be an unpopular post, but it's just been on my mind lately.  My parents are still very Christian and very right wing, so when I ask them:
"I understand you're concerned about innocent lives being aborted but once the child is born into any number of non-viable family situations, who takes care of this kid?" they never have an answer. 

And, as classic right-wingers, they frown on tons of subsidies.

Still, the whole issue just doesn't seem to sit right with me.    Wondering if anyone out there in the Reddit ether can maybe help flesh out what I'm feeling and help me arrive at a safe port?  

I would say I'm still Pro-Choice, but it feels wrong somehow on a level I can't identify. 

ok, thanks for any input, and if I just ranted to myself, that probably helped too.  


EDIT: Thanks for all the feedback!  You've helped settle my mind quite a bit.  Apologies if I came off as arbiter of what "convenience"  meant.  It was too broad a brush-  I blame the strawberry lemonade I drank earlier.  Was hopped up on juice.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We definitely need more giant statues in the world.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even I can see the "Twins" are great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anjou want more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 07:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way downs south! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 07:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Falls in a well, eyes go crossed; gets kicked by a mule, eyes go back I don't know" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 06:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, Trump built a wall around Mordor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overly excited.  Reddit disapproves.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
