<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7624</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boredom. I wasn't thrilled about going to meet him anymore and the relationship was starting to feel like a chore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illiteracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had one of those names. Changed it when I came of age. I don't know why parents do that to their kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of parents let their kid do that! Yuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you say it? I've never heard it pronounced any other way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they're not in the mood to debate. Maybe they don't care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hard liver pate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love pate, especially when it is as a soft, fluffy dip I can spread on bread.     
But so often I will go to a restaurant and the pate is cold and hard - far too thick. Chicken liver pate always seems to be like this, too.      
What gives? What is the difference in the cooking process when it comes to pate? What should I ask at a restaurant when ordering this, so that I don't end up with cold, hard pate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ninja kung fu" is an oxymoron. Ninjas are Japanese and kung fu is like korean or something. Ninjutsu or karate or judo or that stuff is what they were doing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney Star Wars is just princesses again, now in space. Zzzz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Japanese "okama" has an effeminate and unique way of speaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cost and demand. If you want subs, then by golly you should write to Netflix Japan and demand subs, and get all friends of yours who want them to demand them as well.      
Each individual project is produced and created by a different company with different budgets and different distribution intentions. Not all subs come from the same company. It's up to the producers of any given project to decide whether they want to spend the extra money on a project to broaden their audience to the international market. However, if Netflix (or Hulu, or Abema or whatever) makes subtitles a requirement (for example, all new projects this season must be filmed in 4K, etc. despite the prohibitive costs), then all future projects will come with subs. So, start demanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of those internet sites (search engines, databases, etc) are fakes designed to be really simple, and only link to pre-designed pages which are fast-loading and relevant. The reason is that licensing use of a website can be both expensive, and cause trouble in the future if the program is shown on a medium (TV, internet, film festival, etc) with conflicting sponsors. (Like, if a block of time on TV is sponsored by Bing, they don't want characters in a movie showing how awesome Google is by using it.)
     
Some movies do license it, though. See "Look Who's Back," a recent German film that uses YouTube heavily. They actually had an agreement with YouTube in their country in order to use it from the film's inception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could also ask the shop owners. They surely want to be asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When calling an elevator, is there any difference between the handicapped button and the regular button? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are often two buttons for calling an elevator - the regular one and one with a handicapped symbol. Is there any difference between the programming for one button or another? Will pressing one button make the elevator come faster, or doors stay open longer or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to upvote this picture. But stupid "cheezburger" misspelling really irks me. So, I guess, here's a comment instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see no dam in this picture... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure you should be eating that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Cut" as in, he just got neutered or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Frying" was brought to Japan by the Portuguese. The Japanese developed that into *tempura* as we know it today by themselves. Other stuff that falls into the same category it *katsu* and *kara-age*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hurt Locker, La La Land and Frozen. God, they were all so boring. To be fair, I compared La La Land to musicals like West Side Story or My Fair Lady, and of course Frozen can't hold a candle to the (animated) original Beauty and the Beast or Little Mermaid. All three movies suffered from a lame and unsatisfying plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a small breakfast, drink water and coffee until lunch, and then just have a latte for lunch. You'd be surprised how filling a latte can be, as the milk tends to satisfy. Other times when I want to snack I have some miso soup or broth. The sodium in that also calms cravings.     
I read somewhere (maybe Reddit, actually) that you are training yourself to eat smaller meals after having been overeating for too long. Your stomach is stretched and your body is used to having sugar and such often during the day in the form of snacks. It'll be difficult for the first week or so to wean yourself off tha old lifestyle, but it gets easier after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are so many American girls dying their hair strange colors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unnatural colors like blue and purple and hot pink. This is a strange trend. You can always tell these people are American tourists, too, because of the odd head colors. Why do they do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
