<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5813</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid tip. I'll have to get some of this. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize this might be a little basic compared to the other DIY's here, but thought someone who doesn't like to let things go without a fight might find this interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Accidentally bleached the knee of my Levi 511's, then decided to finish the job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! It's awful. It randomly dips to the lowest level and needs to be turned off and on again to get it to function correctly. Sometimes it stays at full brightness for absolutely no reason until I manually turn it down. It's mind-numbingly annoying at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just your average Packers fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the picture you show it doesn't appear to be level, but in the picture below, that light fixture does. Could have just been wind, perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill hasn't been good since Towers. He turned into a cynical douche after he left. Stoney is awful as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Lions fan, it's nice seeing "0" and "winning" mean something positive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smooth as silk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's it like having to sit to pee? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tinder date that started at a cafe. She agreed to the date after I told her that I had cats and she started by saying she wasn't a fan, then went on a thesis-length rant about how much she hated them. I weathered the storm and she came to admire my nonchalant perseverance.

Got to the date, she goes on about her being a paralegal and how she loves debating, studied it in college, yadda yadda. She talked about living on a river and how she was nervous about her house flooding because it was close to sea level. She then told me I should be worried too because my house was at sea level 30 miles inland. Queue the bullet dodging.

I tell her she's wrong and that my house is a couple hundred feet above it. She refused to believe me, so like most people who I would think are looking to be lawyers would do (or in my case, engineers), I presented evidence supporting my hypothesis via topographical maps and multiple sources of data using the ever-so-magical Google via smartphone. I also would think that insurance companies would know better, and me not being required to have flood insurance should have been another dead giveaway that she was wrong.

Girl refused to believe me even when presented with this, proceeded to tell me she is frustrated by my idiocy and that I couldn't adequately present my side of the argument in a format that made sense to her. I figured that someone why can't process indisputable data as fact including something as stupid as my town being above sea level and then call me the idiot was no longer worth my time and left. My friends got a kick out of the whole thing afterwards, though.

TL;DR Got in an argument with a girl over my house being above sea level. Ended the date after she still called me an idiot in the face of facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a theory that one of the biggest reasons that Google is such a popular search engine involves the fact that it is the easiest to reach in the first three keystrokes before the address automatically fills in. Typing the word "Bing" or any other three-separate-characters-to-autofill engine is just so...cumbersome by comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/lecutinsideman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Did he accidentally bluebook the SSR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Detroit has a pretty solid house scene as well. Source: lived in the city for 4 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does oppression have to be government-sponsored? When there are large factions of people all over Europe trying to elect leaders who will ban you from their countries and groups in America that stand in front of your place of worship with assault rifles to intimidate you and the second amendment allows them to do so, that's oppression.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Followed you up to the Muslim part. Undoubtedly oppressed at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bend my knees slightly when elevators are about to stop when going down or start when going up. Irrational fear that my knee ligaments will snap from the slight force. 

It's strange considering how rough I am when playing sports and don't think twice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enjoy it while it lasts, buddy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not passionate about my engineering job in the slightest. It does pay the bills, so there's that. I get my real engineering fulfillment with hobbies outside of work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grew up there. That's a tough spot for that. The downtown Rochester bar scene isn't bad. Shelby kinda sucks. There's the occasional good show at the Royal Oak music theatre if you're interested in that. If you're willing to drive a little further for dive bar metal shows, look into Hamtramck. Tons going on all the time there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pettigrew approved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You did WHAT?!?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the [stitch background](http://imgur.com/a/bnC0b) with the S7E curve. Almost looks like it's actually tufted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those being turn knobs for some ungodly reason, it appears they are purposely staggered to allow the latches to avoid hitting each other. Are there striker plates in there as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do people not understand that the blue Xs haven't been played yet and that it's asking what your next move would be?

Also, the game is an inevitable tie based on moves played so far, so I guess that would be the crappy part of the design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you don't have any cash for repairs but you have a few bucks on your Lowe's credit card. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In honor of the man with his own invitational this weekend; mid 1960's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In honor of the Arnold Palmer Invitational </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engineer who went through hell with 4 calc courses here. I found that your way of studying is pretty good, but to be effective it should be a regimen.

I would take examples that are verified complete the correct way and memorize the processes between steps. "How" and "Why" were the questions I'd ask. If you understand the steps, you can apply them to any question.

It's a more efficient way of studying. You can really focus on two or three questions and their concepts rather than going through endless examples and hoping it sticks via repetition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like Jack Black's aborted fetus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Richard "White Boy Rick" Wershe has been in prison since January 15, 1988. He was arrested for possession with intent to deliver at least 650 grams of cocaine, which at the time fell under Michigan's 650 lifer law, which gave him life in prison. He is Michigan's longest-serving nonviolent criminal.

[More of his story, for those curious.](http://www.alternet.org/fascinating-story-white-boy-rick-feds-made-him-drug-kingpin-age-14-then-threw-him-prison-life) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chance At Freedom? White Boy Rick Gets Appeals Court Hearing Today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rachel really doesn't like cats. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like Patagonia printed their logo using your teeth as a stencil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took 5 seconds of my life to actually look up his account on Twitter. Definitely not satire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My head immediately went to [Manchester City.](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/e/eb/Manchester_City_FC_badge.svg/1024px-Manchester_City_FC_badge.svg.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May you always feel like there is a hair in your mouth that you can never find when trying to get it out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm. Take 696 through rush hour every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like [Wayne Rooney](https://www.google.com/search?q=wayne+rooney source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwim9tj75I_SAhVL7iYKHRlXDMsQ_AUICSgC biw=1422 bih=852#imgrc=yGdSVptMqyOrXM:) having an allergic reaction after being stung in the face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detroit, Michigan checking in. YNWA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was completely out of boost too. I felt pretty helpless while I was basically driving in sand before spinning that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was going to say "slo-mo?"

Thanks! I haven't played that much, but the save/goal combo felt pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turning 2-2 into 3-1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 22:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With news that Tiger is pulling out of the next two events due to injury, I'm curious if anyone has any golf related injury stories themselves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 04:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all fine and good, but completely useless when my apps move themselves back to internal storage and Max it all out every couple days when 40 apps update. Then I have to move them all back one by one.

Most infuriating part of this phone is the SD/internal storage conflict. Been a problem since at least the S5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow northern golfer here. Went a simulator just like that last week. Definitely not the same, but having it built into a brewery makes it enjoyable nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 21:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/titlegore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 22:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post gave me cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 04:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True that it's not typical, but it's still public to Detroiters and we had the choice to put her there. If we're talking honestly about demographics, there may have been one Asian in her class; emphasis on "may". It was 90% black, 5% white, 5% Asian, essentially.

The point was it's not a death sentence to have a child there. It was an eye opening experience that none of us regret. It's a safe, friendly school like any other would be. I only hope the rest of the schools can get funding to catch up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 16:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girlfriend and I had her daughter in DPS for a year; second grade at Burton International Academy. 

Everyone there was friendly and helpful. The class size was around 20/room, she had a bus that picked her up downtown, the after school programs were great. Her teacher was available 24/7 via call or text. The homework was consistent and challenging enough that when she moved over to Ann Arbor this year, she was well ahead in math and reading while on par with writing.

The after school programs included a full on Wizard of Oz musical with a few of the grades tied together. It was honestly amazing; they really got her to sing her heart out. The schools also had a weekend soccer program put on by volunteers in Southwest that was a ton of fun.

The school itself was somewhat of an issue; they had no A/C and you could tell that most supplies were pretty old. There are lots of companies that donate tons of supplies, backpacks, winter jackets, etc. to all of the kids, which was nice.

We did have an opportunity to hand pick our school. Burton has a solid reputation and after meeting the staff we could tell that they really cared about succeeding. Also taking into account that the state will partially fund colleges if you come out of DPS and it's not a bad set-up. The care is there, but the funding is what's really hurting them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're going to talk about retarded memes, we can start with your post history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because we all have jobs LOL! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inauguration turnout explained </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is everyone missing that he's actually autistic? I'm not kidding; he has shown legitimate symptoms for awhile now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 23:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toronto high rise to Warren. Sorry to hear that man.

However, if you're talking true high rises and me having no understanding of your budget, downtown Detroit is pretty awesome (source: lived in a 25th floor high rise there for 4 years).

Other areas you might want to check are Ferndale and Royal Oak. Those won't be high rise settings, but are pretty cool towns close to Warren.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6'4" checking in. Buy one of the $20 shower heads with the hose attachment. It pushes the head about 6-8" higher because it clips in the area where the jet is in this picture and the actual head is well above the clip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [2.2x zoom/low light, Hopcat, Ann Arbor (RIP)](http://i.imgur.com/Or5QI8y.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see your shirt says ATM. That's an appropriate label since your contribution to the league is handing over your money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: If you have Comcast TV, your default broadcast setting at set-up is at 720p and isn't usually changed to 1080p by the installers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody but you calls Michael Jackson the Prince of Pop. He was known as the King of Pop, not the Prince of Pop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm American and skinny.

I still love my McD's, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately, I don't need validation by anyone who goes by u/MisterPooPoo to prove anything. Also, picking out three posts from a subreddit that literally asks for people to make jokes about themselves is not being a jackass. Cute that you took the time to go through my post history to nitpick that, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I got your back too, fam.](http://i.imgur.com/S9aEH7A.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how to defend the fact that I do just fine without sounding like an ass, but I'm doing just fine.

Regardless, the execution is cringe even though the concept was obvious. Not sure if you noticed, but that's the thesis of my original statement; implying it was cringeworthy while congratulating the endgame. It seems you may have missed that part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second time in this thread you mentioned someone "confirming" or "proving" your point, and also the second time you'd be wrong. 

As of now, "This gave me cancer" has 524 upvotes, which are 524 other people who you must also find unappealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I, like what seems like a majority of people here, cringed? Fortunately, most of us can carry on a real conversation without needing someone equally as autistic to reciprocate.

Apparently, you aren't "most of us" in this regard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading that made me want to punch you both...You did get the W with that contact info though, so congrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an American, I think baseball is a slow and stupid sport. Soccer, on the other hand, is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, I clearly knew that I didn't fully mask the face. If you can identify this person as-is, then I deserve to be razzed about it and you deserve a prize in internet forensics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a type 1: See you soon, Diabetes American death count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It doesn't matter if you're black or white. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we not cross-reference r/firstworldanarchists? That whole subreddit is meant to be that way.

We can do better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 20:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw your face and immediately thought you looked like [this.](http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-kl_fFsSDksc/T6tSAF3vLVI/AAAAAAAAAHE/sq_gmGlMC5Q/s1600/oompaloompa.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Locked in as the #1 seed as of last week. I'll be taking my second loss of the season today, which puts me at 21-2 since week 7 of last season.

Team "Ed Hochuli's Bowflex" looking to go back to back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 19:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I looked like you, I'd get a ton of piercings to distract everyone from the rest of my face too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 17:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your girlfriend is coming to the conclusion that she likes men instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 20:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Focusing the conversation on themselves. My brother does this and it's infuriating to talk to him for an extended period. The world doesn't revolve around you. Consciously focusing on avoiding making everything about you can go a long way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Saints defense puts up about as much of a fight as Darren Sharper's women. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rolling... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charlie Leduff leaves Fox 2, nothing definitive on what's next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giving the Browns 4 wins. Now that's bold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 01:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearing that the gym is a solution relating to posture as one of the top answers is mind boggling to me...Here's what I did.

I went through a regimen to try and be with the in-crowd moving from high school (where I was generally considered a typical dork) to college. This included perfecting a signature, facial expressions, developing a fashionable pallet of clothing, and yes, posture.

I paid attention to people who I thought exuded confidence and mimicked them. Everything from:

 -Walking with my hands slightly closed with knuckles facing forward rather than sideways,

-Exaggerating my weak (right) arm movement to go with my strong foot,

 -Concentrating on not looking at the ground when I walked which forces your head up,

-Breathing through your upper chest while keeping your stomach stationary to naturally square your shoulders,

-and standing taller by pushing my shoulders back (but not over-exaggerating).

Turns out that worked very well. I'm currently in a very public sales position, I've had my run with beautiful women who have told me specifically that they admire my confidence, and I did all of this without spending a single damn day in the gym.

For what it's worth, I'm a scrawny 6'4" bean pole. Basically exactly the same as I was in high school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explained that in the imgur album, but it was because I sent the picture of my screen to my friend on mobile because a mobile screenshot wouldn't have fit all of my text in. He deleted his post and posted about voting before I could properly capture my original comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Convinced my brother's friend to vote with one comment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pumpkins out for Harambe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 03:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unravel.

Cried like a baby. Beautiful environments, interesting gameplay, and wonderful story. 11/10 with rice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> De Casa La Habana is a top notch B M downtown. Used to live within walking distance, and frequented that spot on Friday and Saturday nights for the live jazz.

If you're looking reasonably upscale restaurant wise, I'd recommend 24grille. Everyone loves it's brother restaurant Roast, but the people who live in the Westin know where the real spot is.

Grand Trunk is a spot where actual Detroiters like to hang out, and they have a pretty great Michigan beer selection as well.

Mercury Bar has, in my humble opinion, the best burgers in the city (if you're interested in something like that).

Thomas Magees in Eastern Market is my favorite sports bar (the owner Erik is a good dude and a friend of mine), and Stache International next door makes the best bologna--yes, bologna--sandwich you'll ever have. I'd recommend walking the market on a Saturday or Sunday morning. It's the biggest open market in the world, for what it's worth.

The DIA is that second largest museum collection in the world. It's pretty fascinating and worth at least a quick walkthrough for 5 bucks or so.

Feel free to ask if you're looking for anything in particular. I've lived there for four years now and I'd like to think I can point you in the right direction for pretty much anything.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
