<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6129</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunno but last time s/o called his fleet 'armada' it didn't pan out good for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China overtakes US to become worlds top crude importer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 10:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China seeks Russia's help to 'cool' N. Korea situation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Drops the Mother of All Bombs on Afghanistan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia warns US of 'grave consequences' of further intervention in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I know. Was just poking fun and talking metaphorically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do me a favor while zooming - you know how Dems love the minorities - can you find a 'minority' kid there or any minority staff/public besides that lonely security/maintenance guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Melenchon Crashes Front-Runners Party as French Risks Rise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 09:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The WH Easter Egg Hunt Horror the kids will never forget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Truth Is First Casualty of War': GOP Rep. Skeptical Assad Carried Out Gas Attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Tao Porchon-Lynch, the world's oldest yoga teacher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why American Airstrikes Go Wrong
By ERIC SCHMITT and ANJALI SINGHVI	APRIL 14, 2017

The Pentagons laser- or satellite-guided bombs and missiles almost always hit their intended targets. But because of human error  sometimes compounded by technical glitches  the military has a history of mistakenly killing civilians or allies. Here are five causes.

Poor Communication
An American gunship hit a Doctors Without Borders hospital in Kunduz, Afghanistan, last year, killing 42 people.

In major military blunders, rarely is there just one culprit. Human error as well as equipment and procedural failures can add up to devastating consequences. That was the case in the attack on a Doctors Without Borders hospital in Kunduz, Afghanistan.

The problems started when missile fire forced a lumbering AC-130 gunship, sent to eliminate a compound swarming with Taliban fighters, off course. Its targeting systems homed in on an empty field instead.

The crew spotted a collection of buildings that roughly matched the description of the Taliban compound. The gunships navigator called an American Special Forces air controller on the ground to seek guidance.

The response was immediate and unequivocal: Open fire.


Location of American
commander on the ground
Position first indicated by aircraft sensor
Intended target
1,080 feet
1,320 feet
1,450 feet
Hospital attacked
The New York Times |Satellite image by DigitalGlobe via Bing Maps
The air controller was wrong. Even after Doctors Without Borders frantically alerted American commanders that a gunship was attacking the hospital, the airstrike was not immediately called off because the Americans could not confirm that the hospital was free of Taliban fighters.

Sixteen American military personnel, including a general officer, were given administrative punishments for their roles in the strike.

Right Target, Wrong People
A coalition airstrike on Tuesday aimed at Islamic State fighters killed 18 Syrian fighters allied with the United States.

In the fog of war, distinguishing between friend and foe can be perilous. Allies and enemies are commingled on the battlefield. What looks like an insurgent from data gathered from spy satellites or surveillance planes may be a more complicated target.

In the airstrike Tuesday in Tabqah, Syria, Syrian fighters allied with the United States were mistaken for insurgents. Allies on the ground had called in the airstrikes and identified the target location as an ISIS fighting position, the Pentagon said, using another name for the Islamic State. But the location turned out to be a position for the Syrian Democratic Forces, who have been fighting the Islamic State alongside the Americans. The military is investigating.


Aleppo
Mosul
Raqqa
Tabqah
Location of
strike
Deir al-Zour
ISIS
control
Homs
IRAQ
SYRIA
By Rebecca Lai, The New York Times |Source: IHS Janes (areas of control as of April 4)
Without eyes on the ground, targets can be misleading. Several missiles fired from a C.I.A. drone in March 2011 struck a meeting in northwest Pakistan among locals and Taliban mediators who had gathered to settle a dispute over a chromite mine. While some of the three dozen people killed were Taliban fighters, Pakistani officials said, most were elders or simply residents.

American officials sharply disputed Pakistan's account, saying that all those killed were insurgents. These people weren't gathering for a bake sale, an American official said. They were terrorists.

Reliance on Local Allies
An American airstrike called in by Iraqi special forces to kill snipers ended up killing as many as 200 Iraqi civilians.

Ideally, American spotters would be able to call in all American airstrikes to help avoid accidentally striking civilians. But in war zones like Iraq and Syria, where small numbers of American Special Operations forces are advising indigenous troops, the advisers must vet and approve information relayed from allied troops closer to the fight. Its an imperfect arrangement forged in the crucible of combat.

American commanders in Iraq say that an airstrike in Mosul last month that killed scores, if not hundreds, of civilians hit the right target, but that the choice of target relied on partner forces who may not have the same values or standards, especially when it comes to risks to civilians.

mosul-airstrike.jpg
Rescue teams work on the debris of a house destroyed by an airstrike that killed more than 100 people in Mosul. Felipe Dana/Associated Press
The top American commander in Iraq, Lt. Gen. Stephen J. Townsend, acknowledged that the airstrike most likely led to the building collapse that killed the civilians. But American officials have also said that the Islamic State may have herded the victims into the building as human shields, or that the attack may have set off a larger blast from explosives set by militants inside the building or nearby.

Maj. Gen. Maan al-Saadi, an Iraqi special forces commander, has said his men called in an airstrike to take out snipers on the roofs of three houses in Mosul. The Iraqi forces, General Saadi said, were unaware that at least some of the houses were filled with civilians.

Nearby Civilians
Two American airstrikes in 2016 and one in 2015  both in Mosul  killed civilians near designated targets.

Often, civilians stray too close to a target after an American or allied warplane has dropped its weapons, and the pilot is unaware or cannot abort the strike.

In a significant number of the 85 strikes involving civilian casualties that the United States has acknowledged in Iraq and Syria, noncombatants entered the so-called killbox after the weapons were released, according to Airwars, a London-based organization that tracks civilian casualties in war zones.

On Feb. 12, 2016, and again four days later, airstrikes were carried out on Islamic State car-bomb factories in Mosul. American commanders concluded that two civilians were unintentionally killed in each strike when they entered the target area after the munition had been dropped.

American commanders also concluded that an attack on an Islamic State headquarters building in Mosul in 2015 killed four civilians in the building and wounded two others.

Flawed Intelligence
A B-2 bomber mistakenly struck the Chinese Embassy in Belgrade, Serbia, in 1999, killing three people and wounding 20.

American military planners draw on a range of aerial, human and other intelligence to help plot airstrikes, always seeking to prevent civilian deaths. Even so, that planning sometimes goes awry. Most famously, flawed targeting techniques, outdated maps and sloppy follow-up on the ground led to a disastrous result in May 1999.

Satellite-guided bombs from a B-2 bomber struck the Chinese Embassy in Belgrade during the Kosovo War because C.I.A. analysts misidentified the building, and military databases used to catch such mistakes had the wrong address for the embassy. The intelligence failure led to a deadly case of mistaken identity that killed three Chinese and wounded 20.

When the target was initially checked against electronic mapping data in American military and NATO computers to protect against civilian casualties, no red flags were raised because half a dozen government databases listed the old location of the Chinese Embassy, in another part of Belgrade.

A secret document that President Bill Clinton used in authorizing the strike, obtained by The New York Times in 2000, described the Chinese Embassy as a warehouse.

flaw.jpg
The intended target was the headquarters of a Yugoslav arms agency. Intelligence analysts in Washington apparently picked the Chinese Embassy, which had been in that location for only two years, without vetting from anyone on the ground.

Additional work by Sergio Peanha
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why American Airstrikes Go Wrong - The New York Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers release files indicating NSA monitored global bank transfers | Reuters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Russian Orthodox Boat Church </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ,   . ===:))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was from my POV though the stress was on the "enemies of the US" formulation and by "no longer around", if taken literally, you mean around their own countries 'cause as I said, the only countries around the US are MX and CAN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.N. experts warn Saudi-led coalition allies over war crimes in Yemen | Reuters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest you factor in the R D too: http://www.thefiscaltimes.com/2017/04/13/Heres-How-Much-Mother-All-Bombs-Costs

And no, we are talking war here and not a single bomb of 16 Mil, and what's more important we are talking many unwinnable wars all over the world and a Pentagon budget of trillions, financed from the taxpayer. WHAT FOR ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So funny how ppl who most likely don't pay taxes and live with their parents, and obviously can't do math tell me that a single 314 Mil bomb cost me "10 cents 40 years ago" while forgetting that the previous 8 years a total of over 26 000 bombs were dropped. Then it's /r/worldnews, where kids defeat enemies on the PC as if it is a video game. Some joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISIS: REEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE :))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It got some people laughing too. Btw who are those enemies of the USA? Mexico and Canada? Cause those are the only ones I see around. And why we have so many enemies all over the world? I don't think anyone in the ME wants to steal our "democracy" and "liberties" simply they can't ship them that far and are not halal for them. I guess our "justice" is not their taste too. What else -American Football, Coffee, Health Care? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you are spewing dumbshit warmongering BS all over the subreddit from behind your PC (like everyone else here, in your defense). Here are some bullet points for you to consider before mouthing off your rather ignorant and idiotic war apologetic. First, no US admin built the bomb (MOAB), it was my and other taxpayers' money who paid for it. Hammer that in your head if you are a taxpayer (which I doubt) and when the next 9/11 happens. Although bombs fall from the sky, it's the taxpayers that pay for them, so i.e. there are no innocent people in the game called war. Take it whichever way you want and remember that chickens come home to roost next 9/11. Second, unrelated to this post but to your other BS, China will NEVER join the US in attack on NK, so the US is on its own there with SK. I bet a million bucks SK would not like to see a war conflict a la Korean War 2.0 with nukes, fo sho. Whatever the result, the victory will be a rather bitter one. The global outcry and everything else even worse. Why? Cause NK might be whatever the half-witted MSM brainwash ppl to think but hey, they didn't attack anyone. Same goes for all the countries like Iraq, Libya, Syria, Yemen, Somalia etc that the US ATTACKED. Third, the US Govt/CIA financed those tunnels (w/taxpayers' money), now they destroy them again w/ taxpayers' money. Do you see the idiocy here? I doubt it. WHY is all this ??? What is our interest in Afghanistan and NK when 99% of the US population can't find those on the map? So quit watching TV and solving world problem on your computer if you are not aware that you are actually paying (in case you pay taxes) to create more such. My pleasure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, THAT too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's rather difficult/hard to get him when you are that young. But the condensed imagery and shocking metaphors which were delivered not only thru the content/semantics but also conveyed thru the form/syntax and lexical material (words, neologism, literary techniques) were what swept me off my feet. He deconstructed the whole system of language - words, word order, even the graphic arrangements on the page to deliver the message in the most powerful way i.e. he was ready to break any rule of grammar/semantics to get to the point. For me he was an epitome  and embodiment of his time.  

PS. To illustrate what I mean here is:

**   **

 ,

 :

-.

.

.

.-

 ,

 

 .

  

,

 

  ,

   ,

,

   :

- !

- ! -

 .

  

      .



 

 ...

 ,

 -...

**The poem structure forms the dead body of a horse, lying on the street, with hoofs in the air if inverted at 90 degrees.**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US says 'mother of all bombs' hits ISIL in Afghanistan . Reported 35 killed. Most expensive body count EVER! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the best-known Russian poets and my top favorite one, Vladimir Mayakovsky, tragically took his own life on April 14, 1930. He was 36. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I strongly believe that the so-called ATO and the murders of ethnic Russian and Ukrainian civilians should be addressed by the Duma too. If they offered Samoilova to take part via satellite let the Ukrainian soccer team take part in the World Cup next year thru Sony Playstation console. After all, no one is going to acknowledge the civil war in East Ukraine if Russia doesn't take a strong and principled stand, including temporary military mission. There's no difference between Syria and Novorossiya. None at all.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 10:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we left Afghanistan in 1989. [Guess who's still there bleeding?](https://www.rt.com/op-edge/384474-afghanistan-us-taliban-troops-war/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 10:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 09:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Encouraged the mujaheddin fighters"? Ohhh, the same ones that fly planes into buildings, bomb embassies in Africa and attack battleships. Pretty smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America's Best Stout Beer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A secret court order: The FBI suspected Carter Page was working as an agent for Russia | The Economist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ...  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   , ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House claims on Syria chemical attack obviously false  MIT professor (VIDEO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>    -  i    /        .        /          .       , ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A troll is a title and requires subtlety and craftiness, that one was a plain doofus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ,    e- /   .    . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US-Russian ties 'at low point' as Syria tensions rise | Syria News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause Russia, and not California, won the WWII and saved Europe from Fascism, and the schmucks across the pond, joined in (Europe, the greatest war theater) when the war was almost OVER and in it's LAST stage. That's why and that's why China is there too. Why the French pussies are there is the relevant question here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UN: 'Look at me when I'm speaking' - Moscow hits back at UK during UNSC on Syria. Shit got real, no dilly-dally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "AQ is on our side in Syria" So who are "we" again, kemosabe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia vetoes UN Syria resolution proposed by Western powers. Photo brings memories of Churkin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's too much irony in that for Sean Spicer to handle - 2/12/1943     ,       1000   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
