<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4934</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the 'n' word

Bruh it's in the clip, you don't have to say "the 'n' word" when talking about the clip you just watched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but then you focus more on the trap or have trouble farming because you're trying to find where it is

Ok, so now it's no longer a bug or anything, but simply a good strategic placement. They are called traps after all. If one is placed behind the tower that's simply a good trap spot because of camera angles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fallout 4 was ruined for me because I finished playing Witcher 3, 3 times over, just days before the release of Fallout..

It was safe to say it felt lacking in almost every way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same thought. I'm anxious dancing normally in a packed club where not a single eye  is on me, but I'd imagine growing up in that culture it's something thought to you at an early age, so no matter what, when it happens you feel safe doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure he's still funny, he just knows that he can make shitty movies in exotic places with his 5 closest friends and make a hundred million easily. 

I doubt he's lost his sense of humor because of his movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She's high on life.

Oh no... Facebook teenagers are creeping on to Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like listing my personal reasons are completely different to those of someone else, so I'll just say it should be obvious enough why people would visit a country outside the US. History alone is enough for some people, then weather, then food, the people. 

Also, assuming that no one at all wants to go to Africa is ridiculous, given how huge it is, and how common safari resorts are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best way to go about viewing the Fate series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been interested in this series, and I just got it recommended once again, so I decided I'll give it a real try.

Buuuuut, there some to be a few different shows, a movie or two, then some visual novels? (not sure how they work)

Also, I've heard the original show isn't too good, but that may be the minority opinion. If however, they are right, I'd appreciate being told to skip it or not.

Thanks for any advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While the game looks like a stealth only version of Farcry, I'd like more videos of the guys playing it in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to show a clip or an episode of your favorite show to sell it to someone, what clip/episode would you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm a 20 year old white guy trying to get into anime. All I have under my belt so far is Attack on Titan, and Tokyo Ghoul. 

I've been looking up show's to watch for days now, but can never pull the trigger, because although they're only 25 minute episodes, I find it oddly intimidating. Especially given a lot of recommended shows are straight up hundreds of episodes, or simply 12. 

So, pitch me your favorite show as a way to help a guy get into anime without being scared off for the umpteenth time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to show a clip or an episode of your favorite show to sell it to someone, what clip/episode would you choose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are oddly aggressive for someone who is talking to the team behind the game you play... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to tweets huge thanks to them for not milking a show that deserves theright ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's giving context, he's not an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was... Surprisingly average. Especially after the EU opening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and while Huni has improved, so has Hauntzer.

To be fair, it's not even close to the same degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Hauntzer baby noooooooooo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a 48 year old guy, you'd think you'd be past the stay of being an arrogant prick by now. 

Oh well, enjoy your day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you know of these hobbies, jobs, footware in thailand because of the internet. Something people in their second half of life simply don't use too often. They get their news from the prompt they read, and the gossip on set. They don't go to Reddit and google to learn new shit. 

Also, even though I'm saying you know it all from the internet, I genuinely refuse to believe even you have an ego big enough to assume you know every job/hobby/piece of clothing on the planet. Using the footware in Thailand worked because it's rather niche to know that, but that in no way backs up what you're saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it was a busy weekend, and in some cases, one pair of shoes may not fit what you're wearing for the event, so you grab another pair. Not that big a deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, of course not, but that makes him a more reliable source than your opinion of someone. There's nobody on this subreddit that can confirm or deny Kyle visiting this sub, so having someone who he probably talks to every day be the guy saying he hasn't linked or talked about anything in years seems kind of worth mentioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, how so?

He's here pretty often, and is basically the ambassador for PKA at this point because no other host interacts (Taylor occasionally, but still rare).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japan, Norway, Poland, New Zealand, Australia, Africa.

Quite frankly it's all taste, and believe me I know the US has a lot of fantastic stuff in it, and the landmass itself is huge, but I'd be damned if I were to agree with never having reason to leave it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Huh, I was right..] (https://www.reddit.com/r/PKA/comments/66vbe7/pka_331_daddyofive_child_abuse_japanese_condom/dgmj275/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, there are many reasons to go to places outside the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   for me?

That's the key part. Kyle takes this, and makes it fact. Instead of "best for me" it's simply "this is the best, there is no better". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a funny picture, and the bio is solid, but why the fuck is it here?

Is a picture of someone roleplaying Jesus really that offensive..? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you expect? 

They play against each other, and have been classed as the top 2 players on the planet for... Quite a few years now and we still can't decide. 

So yes, of course a picture from El Classico will bring up the talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I'm slightly lost now. You're talking about hobbies? And you expect news anchors to have a full grasp on the life of you, and literally everyone else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not brainless readers, but they are middle-aged to mid 60s white people. 

Furry culture is very much based on the web in most places. Its not even remotely close being in the circle of events that a news anchor would be aware of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy used one of the strongest ults in the game on two champions. If the fight went the whole distance, that would have been a huge deciding factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boy bjergsen at the center of buggy midlane drama once again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even need actual gameplay. I'd watch Kyle and Murkah nerd out and just talk about the cards in their Magic decks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well god damn. Riot really have good writers working on the scripts these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just fucking ridiculous to ask such a thing. They cover day to day news by reading off a prompt, they are not paid to be walking encyclopedias.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bjergsen hasn't been this caught off guard since that time his mom walked into frame during a stream of his. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the best two back to back episodes ever. Going from Funhaus/Cow Chop to Drunk Jeremy this week... 

I wonder if next week will keep up the level of quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YouTube has a comment section too. Also, just maybe, someone else shared that kind of thing with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope they continue playing this. That was an incredibly entertaining 14 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't think he does. He has too much pride to come here after saying how he hates it, and his ego/above the fans vibe definitely goes against him seeking validation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Including the content on this sub lately, we've been at a genuine high. Murkah even commented on a post yesterday regarding the Blackfeet game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not OP, but I feel it is simply because of who said it. Kyle only really ever has one mindset for the US and that it's better than any country at almost everything. Whether it be for the show, or genuine opinions, the guy clearly has a huge dick when it comes to USEveryOtherCountry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I read a few comments and thought about saying how I was never a huge fan of old Cadbury... But in reality it really doesn't matter at all. Candy is candy. Everyone has a special spot for one type or another, and another person will hate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I may be using busty in the same sense of thick and that's my bad, but nonetheless I'll stand by what I said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this name for over 2 years. It's just the recent months that have been a struggle to get through at times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  well your dad is probably a fucking piece of human shit cunt face

This is probably the most hyperbolic statement in this thread, and that says a lot. The guy called him a cunt, and you turned it into a vitriolic statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He could have, but I bet that guy takes a look for people crossing the next time he tries to glide through a zebra crossing that's being used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've been cycling around Dublin for nearly 2 years now and I've never once had a run it with a bus, car, or taxi. (and that's rather hard to do with the taxi drivers we have) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really not sure why you included "nerd", but I wouldn't call it busty. Just a babe having fun. Her thigh, arms, and overall body just isn't what you'd call busty. Now that's not saying she's not hot, I still upvoted and think she's hot, but if you browse any kind of busty related sub, this girl just doesn't fit the build.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's been a while since I've been in tune with Cod, but they have a 3 year rotation right? So it goes: Sledgehammer, Treyarch, Infinity Ward. Sledgehammer have been making this game, either since the release of Advanced Warfare, or the release of Black Ops 3. 

Battlefield 1 came out late 2016. That means Sledgehammer started working on this game, at minimum, 1 year before the release of that game.  (not including all of the brainstorms and planning that happened before production, that most likely started taking place as they shipped their own version 3 years ago)

Believe me, I understand how the past few games have had a leach sucking the fumes of cash out of the games, but you can't say this game is happening simply because of the success of Battlefield 1. There were cries for a WW1/2 game for a while before the release of it, it just took Cod longer because of their god awful rotation system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Asian demographic takes up 5% of the US population. I'm sorry, but that's not nearly significant enough to believe it's dragging down the large dicks of America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the map DLCs were how Battlefront made it's money, but here we are, it looks like Battlefront 2 will only have cosmetic dlc you pay for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only questionable thing about this episode was Woody bringing up Nolan's Batman Trilogy when talking about Power Rangers. It's good, but it's just that. Good. 

Apart from that... God this was a fucking fantastic episode. Even with Woody's tech issues, having Chiz get the show down worked perfectly. I am 50/50 on episodes these days, but damn did this show make me legitimately laugh out loud at least 5-6 times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it expected for them to go back in time? They've done nothing but progress through their future warfare for.. 4-5 games now. If they can go back in time and listen to the community, why can't they be willing to drop the crate shit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Busty"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I find it hard to believe any game based in the past, or on historical events, could ever possibly live up to being as entertaining as the modified versions of history we have now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 07:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally nothing but an image has been released and people are already completely shitting on it. Nobody ever believes in the turnaround..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait for him to be nerfed a little bit so I can play ranked without expecting both of them being mindlessly banned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been a fan of him because of his personality, but never once in my life have I thought "wow, this guy is a pretty good actor".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way it was announced was fantastic. I'd say it was the highlight of the show, but being honest, this week killed it. So many actual laugh out loud moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait for people to say they're either copying BF1 or they're going to be too basic with it. 

I'm hyped as shit for it, and of course I'll wait it out for more than a WW2 announcement, but this is easily the best choice a Cod game has made in 3+ years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Or if Rhaegar and Lyanna were secretly married it would make Jon their legitimate child

I'm pretty sure there's is some level of belief or evidence behind this. I remember hearing that Sam may be the one to find some documents to it because in the Citadel.

That aside, I don't mind his name being Snow, although Stark is a soft spot for me.. It's more of him knowing about his mother, like he has wanted from episode 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they looked incredible for their time too. Imagine one for the current gen/pc.. Please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a joke, but aside from the countless things I want from this show, him finding out about his true parentage may be the highest on the list. He is so dramatically haunted by not knowing, and by being a bastard.. Just write in a way to give him the truth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Those who claim to be above the fray are cowards, and wrong. You can't escape the left/right dichotomy, you can only pretend to. Those who pretend to are leftists 9 times out of 10.

Or, you know, you could do without with having 2 options for what is the biggest voting event on the planet, that only takes place once every 4 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think I sound a lot like one though. I've spent almost every comment making sure it's clear I have no agenda, and no political party. Quite frankly it turned into my main point to push as we moved away from my thoughts on the tweet. 

Also, what's the point in intentionally trying to trigger someone? The post is about a shooting in Paris, why did you come in here and decide to try troll or trigger someone with a certain type of political belief? It's really not the time or the place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ he acts like a child. How is he known as one of the most toxic players at the top of the game, yet riot lets him continue to play. 

This is literal proof of him being toxic and abusive. Riot really need to put their foot down to set a precedent.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..You are actually trying to make this appear like I'm an angry leftist that is losing an 'argument'. Dude, I'm just a 20 year old Irish guy having a conversation while I research a a job I'm interviewing for next week. 

Not trying to push an agenda, and I'm in no way mad or irritated by this talk. Quite frankly I've enjoyed it because of the insight it's given me into someone with genuine passion for their political belief.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like you just said though, you did prove me wrong, and I did admit I was wrong, so continuing to try take the high ground and make me say it.. What's the point? 

I was having a legitimate talk about my point, and when I was wrong I proved it, I said I may have misread it, then we discussed something else, but you've just slowly become more and more of a dick as we've messaged back and forth. 

Most of what you're saying now is pointless. You wrote two seperate sentences about my thoughts on him being casual, and ending the sentence with fucking stupid, because for some reason we're now cursing to emphasize our points. You also contradicted yourself with: 

  I proved you wrong with my first comment and you admitted you were wrong

and

Let's hear you be the mature one and admit it now. Go on, wise one.

Also, given your general tone progression throughout this endeavor, I genuinely doubt " I only continued the conversation for entertainment" is true, given that it's not like you're ramping me up and annoying me, but it's clear it hit a spot with you. 

All of this because I had an opinion on a tweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, now you're changing the playing field. You've gone from saying I have an agenda and a deep seeded love for one party because I'll need one when OUR nation guys to war.

Now because I'm not from the US, your argument has no ground to stand on so you resort to saying my opinion is worthless. It's okay to admit you're wrong/defeated sometimes. It shows maturity and reason in a person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, we have something to thank the Muslims for. What a way to end the night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, this is entire conversation is defused because you have just assumed I'm American. At no point have I actually stated I live in the US. Quite frankly I did somewhat the opposite by making it clear I don't support either main party. 

Not being from the US also should, at least to a reasonable person, clear me of any intent to push an agenda or party. 

Now I'll sit back and wait for you to try explain how my opinion is invalid because I don't live in the US, because for some reason unknown to me, you are taking this talk of ours very, veryyyy seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pilots make pretty good pay though.. Are we sure we can trust them that far up? They might try pickpocket the guy in front.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   you as either a leftist (whether you identify as one or not) or just plain ignorant.

I'm in tune with Trump and I know how strong his views are on Islamic terrorism, and no, I'm not a leftist. I don't understand why people feel the need to have an absolutist title when it comes to politics. I simply saw what he said and it came off as a "well, terrorism, you know.. shit happens. Just watch out for it". 

Sure, I may have read it wrong, and if so, my bad. But good lord, what is with your need to make it all about political beliefs and parties? Can I not have a simply opinion on a tweet without having a hidden agenda for supporting "my side"? Because, this may be shocking, but I don't have a side. I don't have an agenda. Can we agree to move on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The left literally calls everyone

Are you implying I'm on one of the two sides? I'm in no way a supporter of either main party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's how absurdly casual he seems about the matter. Oh, we're sorry for it, terrorism, amiright? 

Shit, I'm not even 100% against him but this just rubbed the wrong way. Imagine his response if it was on US soil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I see. I assumed you were making a genetics joke at him, but that's not it at all. You're pumping you're own ego, that's way fucking funnier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitboxes in general

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  BTW. I really want to see Hell or High Water.

I'm not going to say watch it right now, because I don't know your schedule, but if you do find free time to give it a view, it's definitely worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Gotta love how he's tearing you down as a person, and all you can do is call him fat.~~

EDIT: Was woefully wrong in this, it's way funnier in reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God these costumes are fucking stunning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   It's happening again... It looks like another terrorist attack. What can you say? It just never ends.

Jesus fucking christ.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it seems like a really lazy way out I'll admit that, but who knows. Only time will tell if they're doing it for real this time or if I regret ever defending it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have a task that makes you nervous coming up. What song do you listen to that hypes you up before it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize there's a big difference between companies like Respawn and companies like dice right? It's not just EA it's who is actually making the game and dice has been shit recently.

I'm with you on this. I've been looking at past EA games to receive shit. They're all DICE.. Battlefield 4, Battlefront, Battlefield 3. But it's always EA to take the hit in the eyes of Reddit. 

You said they fixed battlefront 1 problems which is the farthest thing from the truth. The game is still shit and divided. 

So is there anything to back this up? Yeah, the people are divided, and yes they may not allow ground to air/ air to ground, but a lot of the flaws and cries from the community have been added and fixed. You simply can't deny that. 

 Instead we will get people camping the main menu for a vehicle to Respawn like in battlefield 1. 

That's not my BF1 experience at all. While some people may do that, and that only, there is never a lack of on the ground players. 

What they did do however is give up on battlefront one because "fuck it we got out money"

This is just a shitty thing to do and I'm with you on it.

Hopefully this reply isn't downvoted because I'm defending a new EA game like my first comment was, but if you see from my replies to each point, I'm not a blind fan who is going to pre-order  instantly, I'm just seeing some potential and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Because since then, I've seen Titanfall 2, Battlefield 1, Unravel, Mirrors Edge Catalyst.

So you ignored this section? Quite frankly their track record is just fine. Reddit just love to take a few examples and act like that's all the company puts out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhh, they're on the other side. Shit, my bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not in tune with how this works.. Can someone explain how they can simply step out of being investigated? Like, if I were to say.. Be spotted leaving a bank with my hood up the day it was robbed, and then police knock at my door asking what's the deal, I can't simply step aside from their questions and investigations... So why exactly do these guys get to? 

Like I said though, this is the image/comparison I have in my head. A different comparison may be needed, and if so, I'm sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but have you paid any attention to it? 

I'll link [this thread from /r/gaming] (https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/66cr5z/baby_dont_hurt_me/) 

From what I've seen so far, they, and yes, they being EA, seem to have tried fixing most of the flaws with the first game. 

Believe me I understand the first one was underwhelming, but since the release of Battlefront, name a game that was widely renowned as an awful game. Because since then, I've seen Titanfall 2, Battlefield 1, Unravel, Mirrors Edge Catalyst. 

EA are still the money hungry tyrant, sure, but that doesn't mean their games are going to be lazy cash grabs. Give the game more than a trailer before deciding everything outside the graphics are awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How active is active though. I've read like 5 comments now talking about how active BF2 is on PC. Are we talking about knowing the overall names of those you play against every few games, or is it rare to see the same name twice in one day?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if mine is around here somewhere.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, this, while it is pretty unhealthy, is also nothing like what is happening in their content. 

Did you and your brother hit each other for new toys? Did you ever throw him off the trampoline thinking "Maybe I'll be the star of this video and get something new"? 

Not only are they abusive parents, but they are teaching their children to abuse each other when the camera is on because it'll get views and be rewarded. They literally had a video up based on the kids slapping each other in some weird competition, and the dads message was "hey! You don't slap girls!!! But she's your sister so that doesn't count." Guess what. The kid proceeds to slap his sister pretty fucking hard, and she just lays on the bed crying while the dad gives the typical prank "ohhhh" reaction. 

I genuinely do no care to talk about your childhood, because I somewhat get it. I didn't play as rough as you apparently, but in bickering is a thing. This DaddyofFive thing is not even close to the same case. He has brainwashed his children with toys and goodies as long as they do WHATEVER the fuck he wants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this. 

I started watching when I was.. 15, 16? I'll be 21 this year so having his content as I aged felt like I cheated because of the experience he was sharing with us. 

No matter how much he irks me and does some shit I don't like on PKA, I'll never truly dislike him simply because of his help, his work ethic, and his devotion to family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case, I simply don't care. It does exactly what it says. It's chill music to study to, and people have exams almost every week now as the school year closes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks absolutely nothing like GoT in space. Like no even closely related.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick question. If I have all champions, and buy a champ shard, is it guaranteed that it's the rakan/xayah? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and reddit thread already

Apart from a view back-forth comments at the bottom, I really don't see these people you speak of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, when were Hunter/Burglar updated, and how serious was the update?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care for anything that streams a shitty, cam quality movie to an app. Mostly because I see a movie almost every week, and tend to wait for DVD/Bluray releases because I'm a snob, but I also don't care for an app called "Free Movies HD" because it reminds me too much of the old days, when you'd dodge 100 viruses trying to find a movie on a sketchy site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Streaming theater movies? Yeah... Im gonna avoid this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unpopular opinion: Faker is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like the song aimed for general radio IMO. That's not even a bad thing, I enjoy the song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kendrick Lamar - DNA. [Rap/Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh snap there I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video for PKN, along with a group call once a month I believe, but I never went that high on the list. I also don't subscribe anymore. Probably been about 6-7 months since I've paid them anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to care wayyyyy too much about what somebody else has on their body.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man of Steel had an incredible trailer, so did Avengers Age of Ultron, and BvS..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  pretty selfish of you.

I'm sorry, but I paid them a significant amount of money for promised content so no, I don't think I'm being selfish here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crackle and pop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the hosts are busy guys

2 of them don't have jobs, and don't upload consistent content. I'm sorry, but there's no fucking reason to not provide more adventures/plays.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Netflix and Spotify Premium combined aren't even $10

Um... This is off a bit. Netflix has multiple plans, and only 1 of them are under 10 euro, while spotify is exactly 10 post-free trial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go coin, but sighstone, blind the adc and give the damage to help win the lane.. Do what you gotta do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we should wait it out to see if 2 is a hit, before we start assuming it could be the historic "praised trilogy" that we want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I also didnt queue as support

This is reason enough. If the Teemo, or whatever champ you go with, legit tries to play the role, then do what you gotta do. Tbh, I'd kill for a support with a blind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an 8th grader with a dope ass playlist. 

Gotta love that she said it would turn him into a psychotic person though. Classic suburban mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youtube dropped the ball on streaming and ignored it. Now Twitch is here. If they continue to spiral downward, another source will find it's way in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a support main, that upcoming skin list makes me cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .. Did you even read my comment? My biggest point was that I'm not judging their viewers, I was just taking a reasonable guess at their core audience. 

Like with PewDiePie. If you watched his content 2 years ago, you could see it's very clearly aimed at a viewer under the age of 14 or so. But now, you watch his content and he's changed to appeal for that late teen, early 20s viewer. 

But going off an hour of content with Cow Chop, it's clear they just assumed they'd be their normal selves, rather than ease into a new viewer base, and sure, it may have worked for some viewers, but I just got the vibe from them that they appeal to people around the age of 15, but being the cool dudes who do whatever they want. (EDIT: Which, once again to be clear, is not a bad thing. People have to appeal to that demographic, and if you're not in that range but still watch them, you do you. I'm just saying every channel has a target, and I'm guessing mid-teens is theirs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean this in a condescending way, but given the way everyone talks about their behavior and general shenanigans, they are a channel aimed at mid-teens right? 14-16 or so?

And like I said, I'm not knocking anyone who watches them, it just seems that they go for the "woooow dude, sick" kinda thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to go watch episode 10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  5 years?

Might be slightly off by 5 or more years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 06:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been out of school 8 months now. I've tried cafes, restaurants, shelf stocking, warehouse work... No responses. 

First interview in 7 months coming up this week. I don't believe in a god but you best believe I'll be praying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the survivability on Shadow like compared to Guardian?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But wait, is the original quest a seperate thing? Like the newer expansions being their own deal, rather than the character you currently have.. Sorry, I'm just slightly lost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you describe/summarize each class? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm choosing a class, and right now I'm leaning on Jedi Knight simply because I want that 'classic' feel. I also tend to lean towards tanks, so there's that too. 

With that being said, I'd love some class rundowns. I understand there is a page devoted to this on the website, but it doesn't tell you how the class feels, if that makes any sense.

For example, I've played Rogue in WoW, and Burglar in Lotro. Shadow seems to be this game's version of that, but Shadow can also tank/heal/dps.. And given how different Rogue is to Burglar, assuming that dps Shadow is the same as Rogue/Burglar is kind of tricky. 

Being honest, I just want the game as a single player experience and have a lightsaber. I just don't know which class can manage that the best. I'd expect a spellcasting jedi class to be tricky to quest with at certain points, and it would also limit my saber fighting. 

This got really jumbled, but I hope someone understands what I was going for. Thanks for any help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   plus all the original 8 class stories,

Wait, is this different than the class' opening area/questline for a saber? (I'm a jedi knight) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, well that's cool to hear. Had no idea the post-show was a thing, and seeing the post from yesterday about how it's edited.. What time does this show air, because I'm genuinely considering a First membership to catch it live, along with my RTP and Always Open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell of an hour... But holy shit am I curious about the events post-filming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That look on his face when it set in, then minutes later when he's like "why do i look like I'm dying.." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at the thumbnail, and the first 5 minutes with the Rude boys (I don't know them), along with the post from yesterday about this episode. I'm so ready for the next hour of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes a guilty plea in court to make it true? 

So what you're saying is that you were wrong about Anthony, and you spoke out of place about the guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His "us retards have a hero" voice was straight up hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um... Woody COMPLETELY changed the playing field for his Tiger argument, and his only defense for a full on change of pace was to joke about Wings years ago, but still go on to feel victorious when he gets Anthony on his side for the now knife wielding fighter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've opened the main one, and the one from the swtor folder but that doesn't seem to be opening. Am I missing something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITT: People joking about a failed ballistic missile launch. 

Do you not realize one day it won't fail and it will become a serious issue very, veryyyy quickly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you might want to read the rest of them too.

Why would I want to read the amendments for a country I don't live in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Moreover the manga has a monthly release and I keep forgetting the characters.

I've been reading comics for quite a while, this is something I'm sadly used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back before that, Woody's shtick for GFuel was always "I use it every day, I know a lot of people pimp stuff they don't use, but I need trust in something like GFuel before I tell you to buy it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That explains the confusion. Thank you.

EDIT: Also puts my reading from 117 chapters to 257.. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to have done that again. Tokyo Ghoul RE is the right one, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That means nothing to me, but after googling it, it seems season 1 condensed 60 chapters, so I guess the manga isn't as far ahead as I assumed, but nonetheless I bet it's much better post 60, or at least that's the idea being sown into my mind right now amid the research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'm completely down for starting at the start. At most, it'll take away an hour or two from my life, and on top of it, it'll be a nice trip through the experience I just had (enhanced to a degree I'd imagine) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The manga is still going too? I've read two comments before yours and I've decided to pick it up. How far in is it? Watching season 2 close out I realized how much content was left, and I realized it could be another long running show, not like Naruto in its hundreds, but much more than 3-4 seasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just read xmonsters comment, and I've decided I'll look into the manga. If the show was considered sloppy I should fly through the manga.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, this is why I'm terrified of starting up with my anime viewing. Everything that is recommended by Netflix is simply because of how big it is in the west. Attack on Titan, Tokyo Ghoul, Death Note etc. 

I'll look into the manga because of this, but I'd also genuinely appreciate some recommendations for anime. I also don't have a preference for anything, so I guess my tastes are completely open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do not tell me how to learn patience. At not point ever did I say I was going to buy or pre-order the game. I'm saying I hate people that do the typical /r/gaming "fuck preorders". 

I will be waiting for the beta/actual gameplay. I'm not 13 years old. I just see the potential from this, given that they seem to have taken every problem with the first one and made it work here. But once again, I never once said I was going to go drop cash on it tomorrow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After years of constantly sanding by "i won't support something i don't use/like" it realllyyyyyyyy rubbed me the wrong way that they got a gaming sponsor from Dell. I legitimately feel bad for anyone who uses this as an entrance to getting a gaming pc.

EDIT: Yes, I know the "money's there ___" thing.I also know it was said on the YOLO Boys episode, so there's more humor to it than people say. Woody has also definitely given a "trust me, i believe in it" feel to his sponsors in the past. They're also Dell PCs. Overpriced shit, and the guys know that, but continue to push it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard the manga is incredibly confusing or sloppy compared to the show. Of course that was the opinion of a single person, who tried it quite a long time ago, but nonetheless that's what I've heard.

EDIT: So... It seems like I've been wrong about the TG manga, and after looking into it. 117 chapters seems totally doable. Looks like I have entertainment for tonight, although it't not anime like the original plan. Thank you guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given that the first game had no real campaign, I kind of half expected them to double down this time round. Nope, they gave us campaign alright.. Campaign from the Empire's side too. Looks pretty fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  REMEMBER PEOPLE, ITS EASY TO GET HYPED. NO PREORDERS

I thank you for such a well organized list, but would also very much appreciate it if you were to not tell me how I should spend my own money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah bruh, Ice Ice Baby was released 27 years ago and people still listening to it/referencing it. 

Ain't nobody gonna be listening to Writter in the Stars in 20 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Because your government

 The American government

Huh, TIL I'm an American. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit that trailer came out in October.. I had no idea it's been so long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I genuinely laughed out loud at the fact that you're upset about sharing a birthday with two people you will never meet. A connection that means absolutely nothing makes you mad because they're two people you find to be obnoxious, which is a whole other situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask why? I'd love to have an idea of what is blurred when I'm looking at it later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we're not getting it this season? Because there's no way they'll get everyone to move over until they've fixed everything wrong with the new one. Even now with all the patches, it's still insanely buggy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slavery is illegal in every modern country on the planet. 

Why do we continue to allow and ignore this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 12:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I imagine it's plenty loud, it's capped out at 15k people.

The average high-level soccer(football depending on who you are) is probably 50k+ or more, and that's the low bar, considering the biggest in the UK is 90k, and second highest is 76k. That is also ignoring a lot of the straight up goliath stadiums out there, and on top of that, you have NFL stadiums too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 11:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, to be honest, I liked the sound of it, so if the money's there that's just a bonus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a support main, this post has me in need of new pants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't something I expected, but it's great to know, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the Falcon and got genuinely excited.. I watched the trailer 15 minutes ago and this comment reminded me he's dead. Fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Floor staff. Cashier/shelf stacking and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of research should be done for an interview in a store like Lidl/Aldi/Tesco? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an interview coming up and I've been told by family to make sure I do some research, but in reality that's all they've said. I have no idea what I'm meant to research. Are they really going to ask me how many stores they have in the country? What kind of questions do they ask that require research..

Thanks for any help lads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rohirrim Charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

Every time I see one of his video's come out I always go in genuinely wanting to enjoy it, but by the time he gets in the air the audio drops so far in quality that it's hard to listen to and I end up skipping along to see if it gets better, or if he has more on-foot/studio audio and I always leave feeling kinda sad I can't ignore the audio.

With that said, I also understand it's something he's very aware of, and if so, it's a damn shame he can't fix it. Maybe I'll try again in a few vids and see if it's any better I guess. 

This vid did have an incredible view though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just come to the realization that I'll be reading titles related to how genuinely terrible Trump is at his job for the next 3 years.. Fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, he'd survive in LCS... But why in the world would he do it? The dude is making money hand over fist and clearly loves the gig he has now. Jumping back into the grind, the pressure, the drama? Fuck that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   can't tie a sentence together

Um... The guy makes music for a living, I think he knows how to tie a sentence together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Negev: Price reduced to 2000

Jesus fucking christ.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a paper and write them all out and follow the proper stroke order 

This has been my life for the past few days. Probably gone through 40 pages of a notepad just writing and writing and writing. Sometimes the same letter per page, or the same sound (a, ka, ga etc.) 

it also helps now that I've found videos that quiz me along the way. It actually made me go back to the k row because i wasn't 100% on it. 

As for the link, this looks fantastic. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ninjas. They were trained to their core and spent their life to master everything they attempted.

Pirates are straight up villains. They raped and pillaged. They were the thieves and murderers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When she does something absolutely infuriating, and you feel like screaming.. Then 2 minutes later you're awe struck by how lucky you are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'll look out for that. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your progress sounds like my goal. Ever since leaving school a few years back, I have little to no patience when it comes to failing at something, so learning such an complicated new language has been daunting, but I'd like to believe I'll end up in your spot within the month or so. 

Is [this] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6p9Il_j0zjc) the video you spoke of? seems to be the only true Hiragana devoted video by the channel.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These movies are always poorly written, with a subpar story, but at this point I've accepted them for what they are and shit are they fun most of the time.

That being said.. The editing in this trailer felt really weird after the half way mark.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 10 minute music video, that opens with bare ass sex...

That being said, it's probably the easiest 10 minute music vid I've ever sat through. That shit was hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  rather than farming upvotes

"2 points"

Also, I come here for the content, I don't post it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll look into it, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat jokes and political humor...

Fuck this sub went to shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  kept getting better to a point where it became the best of the DC/CW shows this season

Holy shit this. If you told me at opening week that I'd be enjoying Arrow more than Flash as they come to their final few episodes.... What a weird TV season it has been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if I remember it right, even Stephen Amell found it hard to truly defend the show around that time, and this guy gives his heart and soul to the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was wondering how it changed everything tonely, given that I was still laughing at the parts that would have had the track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could someone recommend me a good book based on Japanese history or folklore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got done watching Silence and absolutely loved it, but the best part for me was easily the side of the movie focused on Japan's heritage, it's way of life, and being realistic.. I just love Japan. 

So I'd appreciate any recommendations that can fill in the void I have right now. I've often found myself on Youtube straight up searching "Japanese history" but I always end up on a video that requires viewing (I do a lot of driving/travelling) and it falls flat.

Thanks for any suggestions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first trailer didn't entirely sell me, apart from the cast and director of course... But damn does this movie give off one hell of an artsy vibe, as far as car chase movies go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Seriously one of the best games ever

I'm not sure if this is pc-release-hyperbole, or a genuine title it's worthy of.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marrying the mother of his child was honorable, but breaking his agreement with Walder was not. In the moment, it was a good thing to do, but being realistic... Not marrying Walder's daughter was the reason everyone died that night. It was both honorable, and dishonorable, depending on the view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  playing as someone like Robb

roleplay as the character, your commitment to honor and justice

You'll need to choose one here friend.. :') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm pretty sure its bad on purpose

Yeah I'm with you on that. Ain't no way he thought this cover was good after releasing his vid for Humble. Two completely different vibes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I agree, but I still enjoy each new release.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> two weeks after Spiderman, one week after Planet of the Apes, and the same week as Dunkirk. 

I feel bad for the movie now, but good fucking god is that an expensive month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bold opinion you got there kid. I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, to be honest I've been using the lack of dlc as an excuse to stick to basic. I have no idea where to start in the mod. Do I go as Stark, and start with the entire North at my back? Then what, conquer Westeros? That's not the Northern way. Start as a Stark vassal and steal the North? Nope.

To be honest, I'd love some advice on what to do with the mod, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The buses are on strike in/around Dublin. FUCK.THIS.TRAVEL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The colors are plenty vibrant,

The only movie with genuinely vibrant coloring is Guardians. The rest of the movies have color, of course they do, but it's incredibly bland and very poorly edited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the top comments on this post are about his casting being in part with his fanbase being able to see the movie, and he's a gimmick.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently being part of a boy band removes your ability to act.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
