<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject405</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Stoicism is a philosophy that is suited toward difficult situations

While it is certainly true that Stoicism helps a prokopton to deal with difficult situations indeed, I don't think this is the whole point of Stoicism. You don't have to feel guilty for your excellent living conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rejecting orders to do something illegal is honorable, no matter how happy (or unhappy) your boss is with your decision. You should stay calm and rational though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stoicism is not about *"suffer and do not care about it"*, it's really all about virtue and justice is one of the main virtues. However, don't care only about justice towards yourself, since justice should be our concern in a much broader sense.

Try to be the best person you can be, do what you can do as good as possible and be indifferent about the outcome. Endurance can certainly be what is to be done in certain situations, but in general just enduring injustice is not the best thing one can do, since there are most often other (more virtuous) options which usually require courage, another of the main virtues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The lazy argument, determinism, and the concept of fate | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 08:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Claudius Maximus](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Claudius_Maximus). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China deems Dalai Lama's Kalachakra ceremonies taking place at Bodh Gaya in India illegal to attend and threatens punishment to those who attend or spread news of the event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Triteness and Hypocrisy of Marcus Aurelius: Thoughts on Mary Beard, SPQR and Stoicism | Kevin Kennedy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 09:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dances of the Luminous Bardo | Joseph Houseal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 18:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyrenaic Reasonings | Hiram Crespo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 11:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 08:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic find indeed! Advertising with Epictetus is not anything I have expected to happen until now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoicism for Dark Days | Scott F. Aikin and Robert B. Talisse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic advice column: Stoicism vs skepticism, and whether the Stoic bar is just set too high | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 16:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 16:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We may not be able to know the truth (and indeed I think we really cannot know it), but if anything is true, it certainly has to be universally true. I don't deny anybody to find their own way to happiness and I assume /u/bytor99 agrees to that as well, but since I am convinced that Stoicism is basically true, I consequently think that Stoicism must be universally true.

That being said, I really think that it is not possible to really know the truth. This may not be the traditional Stoic view, but I cannot ignore all good arguments of philosophers from other schools. We know only so little and are very prone to errors. We can only follow reason to where it leads us and this is certainly true for other people holding different views as well. Thus, it's not reasonable to expect other people to share our own views indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 15:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too often these opinions are caused by major misunderstandings of Stoicism. Even the ancient Stoics had to deal with some of the same misunderstandings. It may also be that people falsely believe that as Stoics they have to become Stoic sages, which would be way too challenging to virtually everyone indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 11:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  While many thought it was unreasonable to be like him, they still revered his judgement.

Because most people take caring for the consequences for granted and simply cannot understand or imagine basing their actions on virtue alone. Rigorous virtue ethics can be quite brutal in the eyes of consequentialists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 11:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't think stoicism encourages you to be courageous, its more that it teaches you how to live in a way that makes it so external factors cannot effect your own internal tranquility. I don't think there are any mandates about publicly standing up for what you believe is right.

Just change 'Stoicism' to 'Epicureanism'... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  be aware that his advice is often brutal

I basically agree, but I have seen it more nuanced after reading the *Discourses*. These make it clear what Epictetus actually meant and show that the meaning of brutal passages within their contexts often differs from one's first impressions based on the *Enchiridion* alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Stoic your goal is excellence of character, living up to your full potential as rational and social animal. Be a good person and make your decisions based on wisdom, justice, courage and moderation as a socially responsible member of society. This is basically what we Stoics mean by being virtuous.

Don't fight your emotions, but don't let them corrupt your judgement either. Let your decisions and judgements be consistent with your goal, virtue is the only good after all.

Accept whatever happens to you, unless it is your character flaw. Being a good person is what counts. Although prosperity is preferred to hardships, both are opportunities for personal heroism, albeit no one may know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome to EpicureanDocs.com | Stranger, here you will do well to tarry - here our highest good is pleasure! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 14:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rebuilding history? Debate rages over lost Afghan Buddhas | Anne Chaon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 00:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I searched for the line of the quotation and was wondering where you've got that from (I've had just enough time to skim over the article and missed that, I'm going to read it more thoroughly now).

And after re-reading my comment I want to add: Although I realize now that my post could be understood as an insult, it was not intended as such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you citing this from? What's the source? That's not part of the linked article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Greek ''

For people who cannot read Greek letters: in Latin letters this is written 'thiks'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is by far one of the worst articles about ethics I have ever seen. This article is so fundamentally flawed that it is hard to know where to begin with. Here is a [good article about ethics](http://www.iep.utm.edu/ethics/) and let's quote just the beginning:

 The field of ethics (or moral philosophy) involves systematizing, defending, and recommending concepts of right and wrong behavior. Philosophers today usually divide ethical theories into three general subject areas: metaethics, normative ethics, and applied ethics. Metaethics investigates where our ethical principles come from, and what they mean. Are they merely social inventions? Do they involve more than expressions of our individual emotions? Metaethical answers to these questions focus on the issues of universal truths, the will of God, the role of reason in ethical judgments, and the meaning of ethical terms themselves. Normative ethics takes on a more practical task, which is to arrive at moral standards that regulate right and wrong conduct. This may involve articulating the good habits that we should acquire, the duties that we should follow, or the consequences of our behavior on others. Finally, applied ethics involves examining specific controversial issues, such as abortion, infanticide, animal rights, environmental concerns, homosexuality, capital punishment, or nuclear war.

Most relevant for Stoicism is [virtue ethics](http://www.iep.utm.edu/virtue/) ([another article](https://plato.stanford.edu/entries/ethics-virtue/)) which Stoic ethics is one of the best examples of. Virtue ethics, for example, is no set of rules at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 15:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mostly agree with you. I don't run into those folks too often, either. There is value in Stoic concepts outside of Stoicism, which is shown by the efficiency of CBT, for example. I don't see any reason for keeping back Stoic concepts from people just because they are not being applied within the original context.

That being said, I am opposed to calling the life hack "Stoicism" as if that were what the ancient philosophy called Stoicism was about. That's not honest, in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  have the life you've always wanted, without all of the pain of living.

This is what the author of the article, Michel Daw, criticises and certainly not what Stoicism is about (to what you seem to agree to anyway). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 11:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can really identify with his ... imperfections

I think I understand what you mean... However, given that Marcus Aurelius' *Meditations* is a philosophical notebook for himself where he is constantly calling himself to order, I don't think your reason for prefering Seneca is less true for Marcus Aurelius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 07:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was not sure if I should share the article or not the first place and reconsidered it when I read your comment, which was constructive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I really like Seneca's writings, too, for me it's Epictetus' *Discourses* and Marcus Aurelius' *Meditations* which I like most. If I had to choose, it would be Marcus Aurelius. His *Meditations* is the most inspiring book I know and I cannot read it often enough.

On the other hand, there are other great Stoics, too, who belong to my favorites: Chrysippus, for example. I would love to read his works so much, but unfortunately they are lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've disabled the adblocker to see what you mean and yes, the ads are annoying. I don't want to support that and deleted the thread, since there is no discussion going on yet. Thanks for your comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the page with the best collection of links to Stoic resources I know: [A Brief Introduction to Stoicism](http://www.philosophyforbeginners.com/philosophers/introduction-to-stoicism/). I also have a high opinion of [our FAQ](http://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/wiki/faq). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoicism: Life Hack vs. Life Style | Michel Daw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 12:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have saved quite a few comments and some of them may be interesting in that regard:

[Keeping a Stoic Journal](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/3xyjfc/keeping_a_stoic_journal/cy925wz/)

[How do i detach from the "outside" and being more unaffected by my environment?](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/54a7og/how_do_i_detach_from_the_outside_and_being_more/d80b5at/)

[Should I always strive to do my best in everything?](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/55z1zr/should_i_always_strive_to_do_my_best_in_everything/d8exbdp/)

Note that I have linked to single comments only, you may be interested in the whole threads, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original article:

[**M1 muscarinic allosteric modulators slow prion neurodegeneration and restore memory loss**](https://www.jci.org/articles/view/87526)

by Sophie J. Bradley, Julie-Myrtille Bourgognon, Helen E. Sanger, Nicholas Verity, Adrian J. Mogg, David J. White, Adrian J. Butcher, Julie A. Moreno, Colin Molloy, Timothy Macedo-Hatch, Jennifer M. Edwards, Jurgen Wess, Robert Pawlak, David J. Read, Patrick M. Sexton, Lisa M. Broad, Joern R. Steinert, Giovanna R. Mallucci, Arthur Christopoulos, Christian C. Felder, Andrew B. Tobin.

 **Abstract**

 The current frontline symptomatic treatment for Alzheimers disease (AD) is whole-body upregulation of cholinergic transmission via inhibition of acetylcholinesterase. This approach leads to profound dose-related adverse effects. An alternative strategy is to selectively target muscarinic acetylcholine receptors, particularly the M1 muscarinic acetylcholine receptor (M1 mAChR), which was previously shown to have procognitive activity. However, developing M1 mAChRselective orthosteric ligands has proven challenging. Here, we have shown that mouse prion disease shows many of the hallmarks of human AD, including progressive terminal neurodegeneration and memory deficits due to a disruption of hippocampal cholinergic innervation. The fact that we also show that muscarinic signaling is maintained in both AD and mouse prion disease points to the latter as an excellent model for testing the efficacy of muscarinic pharmacological entities. The memory deficits we observed in mouse prion disease were completely restored by treatment with benzyl quinolone carboxylic acid (BQCA) and benzoquinazoline-12 (BQZ-12), two highly selective positive allosteric modulators (PAMs) of M1 mAChRs. Furthermore, prolonged exposure to BQCA markedly extended the lifespan of diseased mice. Thus, enhancing hippocampal muscarinic signaling using M1 mAChR PAMs restored memory loss and slowed the progression of mouse prion disease, indicating that this ligand type may have clinical benefit in diseases showing defective cholinergic transmission, such as AD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alzheimers advance: early stage study in mice show new drugs that restore memory loss and prolong life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clean room, no beetles wanted: how a young Kafka hoped to write budget travel guides | Will Coldwell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicureanism and Sympathy for Animals | Cassius Amicus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merry Christmas! And thanks a lot for providing this beautiful garden for all swines from Epicurus's herd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fullheartedly agree that Stoic principles can be very helpful even outside of Stoicism. However, if one wants to see how Christianity and Stoicism fit together, one should not concentrate on what can be applied within both Christianity and Stoicism, but at the core teachings which define Christianity and Stoicism. There were several highly gifted people who tried very hard to combine Christianity and Stoicism (Neostoicism)  and failed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I suppose the closest conception I hold true is that there is a natural ordering to the universe and everything in it. That is, there are iterative patterns and laws that bear the traces of design. Humankind is very much a part of the natural world and are equally subject to a certain natural ordering.

In other words, if I understand you correctly, you may agree to the view that there is some kind of rationality being inherent in nature (or cosmos, respectively) which humans share some part of? This may even come close to the Stoic *logos* to a certain degree, which the Stoics identified with god.

It may be discussed, however, if it is still correct to call that 'god'. The Stoics identified *logos* with god, but today we just cannot prevent people misunderstanding that with a theist god like the Christian god. Personally, I don't want to grant theists having a kind of monopoly on the word 'god'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why not?

You may find part of the answer [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Buddhism/comments/5jbuey/any_good_buddhist_novels/dbfde7y/). Buddha and Siddharta share some similarities, but Siddharta rejected Buddha's teachings when he met Buddha. If you want to call a novel Buddhist because Buddha appears in it, then you may call it a Buddhist novel. However, I think that a book with a protagonist rejecting Buddha's teachings and finding a very different way to salvation can hardly be called Buddhist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not necessarily saying you are wrong, because there are some elements which made me initially suspicious, too. And, by the way, I am certainly not among those downvoting you. I know such claims by Christian apologists and I am highly annoyed about them (the claims and the apologists).

However, although I suspect some Christian influence (for example, because of the identification of the god mentioned in Stoic literature and the capitalized God and [his answer](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/5jd4ho/do_you_believe_in_god/dbf6ji4/) How does that fit in with your Stoicism? to someone who confesses being an atheist), the evidence that Marzilli is just a Christian who wants to confess here does not seem to be unambiguous enough to exclude other explanations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes indeed. Buddhism certainly inspired Hesse, but so did Hinduism, the Upanishads and the like. Buddha even plays a role in the book, but Siddharta does not agree with him and therefore does not follow him and finally finds his own way. People seem to misunderstand the kind of Buddhism's influence on the book quite often, but I think this misunderstang is not really based on the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't consider it especially virtuos to accuse people being liers without presenting any good reasons. You may be even right, but Marzilli's posting history actually does not seem to support your claim.

^(edit: typo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all have to start somewhere... The Stoics believed in some kind of rationality, *logos*, being inherent in nature. That *logos* was what they identified with "god". Today we may not call that "god" anymore, but it makes sense to consider nature to be inherently rational, because we are able to describe nature mathematically so well, for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm far too ambitious to be a regular stoic.

I don't know any other philosophy which is more ambitious than Stoicism where virtue is the only thing being worth to live for and where one is either completely virtuous or not at all. And don't forget that being virtuous basically means living up to one's full potential. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 15:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no God (written with an uppercase first letter) playing a significant role in the philosophy of Seneca. Seneca was no Christian and did not believe in any other personal god either. The Stoic concept of god basically was pantheistic which is very different to what Christians (or any other theists) believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 13:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a great and inspiring read indeed and I recommend the book, too, but it is no Buddhist novel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 08:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Gods" can be interpreted in a pantheistic sense

As far as I know, that's what the ancient Stoics actually did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Epicurean Way: Rediscovering The Good and Meaningful Life Through Work | Hiram Crespo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Recap of Principles of Epicurean Physics | Cassius Amicus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 11:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The life and philosophy of Epicurus | A lecture delivered at Peninsula College by Wesley Cecil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apollo 5: Lunar Module 1 is being mounted in its adapter, in preparation for launch (January 22, 1968) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Confident and Amicable Life: A Defense of Stoicism | Sean Skedzielewski </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 08:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The history of space exploration on a single space map </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 02:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Oistrakh plays Debussy's Prelude "A girl with flaxen hair" (piano: Frida Bauer; Great Hall of Moscow Conservatory, 1972) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tuva: Sacred Land of Turkic Shamanism and Tibetan Buddhism | Lyudmila Klasanova </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We can add Ceres to the list of places where life may have formed: Data from scattered gamma rays reveals a lot of water ice left over even today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 15:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newly formed stars shoot out powerful whirlwinds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 14:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract:**](https://www.academia.edu/30387941/The_Annicerean_Cyrenaics_on_Friendship_and_Habitual_Good_Will)

 Unlike mainstream Cyrenaics, the Annicereans deny that friendship is chosen only because of its usefulness. Instead, the wise person cares for her friend and endures pains for him because of her goodwill and love. Nonetheless, the Annicereans maintain that your own pleasure is the telos and that a friends happiness isnt intrinsically choiceworthy. Their position appears internally inconsistent or to attribute doublethink to the wise person. But we can avoid these problems. We have good textual grounds to attribute to the Annicereans a doctrine of non-hedonic habits, which allows them to abandon psychological hedonism while still maintaining hedonism regarding well-being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Annicerean Cyrenaics on Friendship and Habitual Good Will | Tim O'Keefe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How on Earth Does NASA Choose a Landing Site on Mars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 22:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rice University astronomers and their colleagues have for the first time mapped gases in three dark rings around a distant star. The rings mark spaces where planets are thought to have formed from dust and gas around the star. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 11:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wheres the nearest planet where we could all live? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 07:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hubble photo shows gravity warping up the distant galaxy NGC 4388 in the Virgo galaxy cluster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Voyager 1 had failed at its Saturn mission, it would have been possible to use Voyager 2 as a backup for Voyager 1 instead of continuing its Uranus and Neptune mission at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is correct that the launch dates are in reverse order. However, the numbering of the spacecrafts was not thought to be in the order of the launch dates. It's also interesting, that Voyager 2 was thought as a possible backup for Voyager 1 at a certain point.

 *Voyager 2* was launched on August 20, 1977, followed by *Voyager 1* on September 5, 1977. The decision to reverse the order of launch had to do with keeping open the possibility of carrying out the Grand Tour mission to Uranus, Neptune, and beyond. *Voyager 2*, if boosted by the maximum performance from the Titan-Centaur, could just barely catch the old Grand Tour trajectory and encounter Uranus. Two weeks later, *Voyager 1* would leave on an easier and much faster trajectory, visiting Jupiter and Saturn only. *Voyager 1* would arrive at Jupiter four months ahead of *Voyager 2*, then arrive at Saturn nine months earlier. Hence, the second spacecraft launched was *Voyager 1*, not *Voyager 2*. The two Voyagers would arrive at Saturn nine months apart, so that if *Voyager 1* failed to achieve its Saturn objectives, for whatever reason, *Voyager 2* still could be retargeted to achieve them, though at the expense of any subsequent Uranus or Neptune encounter.

Quoted from [Voyager: The Grand Tour of Big Science](http://history.nasa.gov/SP-4219/Chapter11.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's talking about the launch dates.

Yes. And /u/uncertainquark has explained what /u/mai_cake was wondering about perfectly fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Stoicism And Rational Psychology: Humanistic Ways To Mental Health | Frederick Edwords </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article has already been linked and is being discussed [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/5hp3g3/ryan_holiday_writes_about_stoicism_today_for_the/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Memoirs of Hadrian

I want to second your excellent recommendation.

Joseph Epstein's article [Portrait of Power Embodied in a Roman Emperor](http://www.wsj.com/articles/SB10001424052748704116004575522281643976468) may be interesting regarding Marguerite Yourcenar's famous book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first live concert is something very special indeed and it's beautiful to read about your reaction! So especially for you: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cbJZeNlrYKg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Oistrakh plays Debussy's Claire de lune (recorded in Paris, 1962, with Frida Bauer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 18:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Oistrakh plays Sibelius, Belshazzar's Feast N2, Nocturne (with Frida Bauer; 1972) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  label that person a con-man or a charlatan. Not only are those two facts mutually exclusive

I basically agree with your comment, but I am not sure you are right here. Merriam-Webster, for example, defines [con man](https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/con%20man) as *a person who tricks other people in order to get their money* and [charlatan](https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/charlatan) as *one making usually showy pretenses to knowledge or ability*. [According to Wikipedia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Charlatan), *A charlatan (also called swindler or mountebank) is a person practising quackery or some similar confidence trick in order to obtain money, fame or other advantages via some form of pretense or deception.* This would mean that *charlatan* and *con man* are not mutually exclusive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wish I was projecting.

As far as I know, the word *charlatan* has a centuries old history and can be found in several languages like French, Spanish, German and Italian. I have looked up its etymology and it seems that its meaning has been negative from the beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was an interesting read, thank you! Until now I mistook him just as another blogger, albeit a very successful one. I think that this kind of success lets envy arise easily, which explains many reactions I have seen after mentions of his name to some degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 16:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I generally don't consider people who basically achieved writing successful blogs about success and not much else as authorities other than about writing successful blogs.

I have never read or listened to anything by Tim Ferriss, so please don't understand the following question as purely rhethoric:  In which way does Tim Ferriss differ from other bloggers of his kind apart from being more successful than others?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been contributing to /r/Epicureanism for more than two years now and have never tried shoving religion into here. I have never been religious and certainly never will. However, I also study other traditions and like to do comparisons, which helps with not becoming too ignorant. Your comment is furthermore close enough to my submission to have reasonable doubts that you actually read the linked academic article. So what's the point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practicing meditation for only 10 days may not necessarily be suffient for a major impact on your state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract:**](https://www.academia.edu/30207493/_Was_Epicurus_a_Buddhist_An_Examination_and_Critique_of_the_Theories_of_Negative_Happiness_in_Buddha_and_Epicurus_)

 Comparisons between western and eastern philosophies are uncommon and this, among other things, hinders global philosophical discourse. Thus, in this essay I want to compare the philosophies of the Buddha and Epicurus for similarities, particularly in regard to what I call negative happiness, or the belief that happiness is intimately connected with non-suffering. Ultimately, I will maintain that while this understanding of happiness is helpful, it remains inadequate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Epicurus a Buddhist? An Examination and Critique of the Theories of Negative Happiness in Buddha and Epicurus | Adam Barkman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ode to Leonard Cohen, From a Fellow Zen Monk | Shozan Jack Haubner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The hidden heart of Natsume Soseki: With two important anniversaries in relation to author Natsume Soseki being celebrated, Damian Flanagan attempts to dissect the psyche of one of Japan's greatest modern writers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 00:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The quote you are refering to actually is a fake quote (see, for example, [here](https://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/Epicurus#Disputed)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I want to believe [...]

And do you succeed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the point of regret? | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 23:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russias Golden Triangle of Buddhism | Lyudmila Klasanova </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 20:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Does Buddhism Require? | Jay L. Garfield </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hard Truths and Happiness | John Sellars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the world of Chinese science fiction, with Three Body Problem translator Ken Liu (about his anthology Invisible Planets, the process of translating science fiction, and how Chinese authors see the future, at New Yorks Book Riot Live festival in early November) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 00:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sviatoslav Richter plays Chopin: Etudes Op 10 (Nos 1, 2, 3, 4, 6, 10, 11, 12) and Etudes Op 25 (Nos 5, 6, 8, 11) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 19:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kula Sutta: On Families (AN 4.255) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Kula Sutta: On Families (AN 4.255)**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/an/an04/an04.255.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)

 In every case where a family cannot hold onto its great wealth for long, it is for one or another of these four reasons. Which four? They don't look for things that are lost. They don't repair things that have gotten old. They are immoderate in consuming food and drink. They place a woman or man of no virtue or principles in the position of authority. In every case where a family cannot hold onto its great wealth for long, it is for one or another of these four reasons.

 In every case where a family can hold onto its great wealth for long, it is for one or another of these four reasons. Which four? They look for things that are lost. They repair things that have gotten old. They are moderate in consuming food and drink. They place a virtuous, principled woman or man in the position of authority. In every case where a family can hold onto its great wealth for long, it is for one or another of these four reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Zen Acceptance and Non-Attachment Really Are | Domyo Burk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 10:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is more than one world indeed and there are also more than one realm of existence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evolution doesn't bother Buddhists | Stephen T. Asma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No matter what the praise from fools or the censure from those who know, the censure from those who know is better than if there were praise from fools. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 21:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thag 14.2: Godatta**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thag/thag.14.02.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)

    Just as a fine, well-bred bull
        yoked to a load,
        enduring his load,
                crushed
        by the heavy burden,
            doesn't throw down his yoke;
    so, too, those who are filled with discernment
         as the ocean, with water 
            don't look down on others.
    This is nobility among beings.

    Having fallen in time
        under the sway of time,
    having come under the sway
        from becoming   non-,
    people fall subject to pain
              they grieve.

    Elated by the causes of pleasure,
      cast down by causes of pain,
    fools are destroyed by both,
    not seeing them for what they are.
    While those who, in the midst of
        pleasure   pain
    have gone past the seamstress of craving,
    stand firm
        like a boundary pillar,
        neither elated nor cast down.

    Not to gain or loss
    not to status or honor,
    not to praise or blame,
    not to pleasure or pain:
        everywhere
    they do not adhere 
        like a water bead
        on a lotus.
        Everywhere
    they are happy, the enlightened,
        everywhere
            un-
        defeated.

    No matter what
        the unrighteous gain
        or the righteous loss,
    righteous loss is better
        than if there were unrighteous gain.
    No matter what
        the status of the unaware
        or the lowliness of those who know,
    the lowliness of those who know
                is better,
        not the status of those
        unaware.
    No matter what
        the praise from fools
        or the censure from those who know,
    the censure from those who know
                is better
        than if there were praise
        from fools.
    And as for the pleasure
        from sensuality
    and the pain from seclusion,
        the pain from seclusion
                is better
        than if there were pleasure
        from sensuality.
    And as for living through unrighteousness
    and dying for righteousness,
        dying for righteousness
                is better,
        than if one were to live
        through unrighteousness.

    Those who've abandoned
        sensuality   anger,
        whose minds are calmed
        from becoming   non-,
    go through the world
                unattached.
    For them there is nothing
            dear or undear.
    Developing
        the factors for Awakening,
        faculties,
          strengths,
    attaining the foremost peace,
    without fermentation, they
        are entirely
        Unbound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 18:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is linked to [here](http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/webbin/book/search?author=Marcus+Aurelius amode=words):

 Marcus Aurelius, Emperor of Rome, 121-180: [The meditations of the Emperor Marcus Antoninus : a new rendering based on the Foulis translation of 1742 / (Edinburgh : O. Schulze, 1902?)](https://catalog.hathitrust.org/Record/100245314), also by George William Chrystal (page images at HathiTrust; US access only)

I am not in the USA and cannot access it indeed, but maybe you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This and https://www.usna.edu/Ethics/_files/documents/Stoicism2.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not sure why the translation in the OP is used so often...

Unfortunately, translations which are available online for free are mostly old ones written in archaic English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Argument for Hedonism | Ole Martin Moen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Many Forms of Avalokiteshvara | Meher McArthur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 22:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dhamma protects those who live by the Dhamma. The Dhamma well-practiced brings bliss. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 07:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thag 4.10: Dhammika**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thag/thag.04.10.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)

    The Dhamma protects
    those who live by the Dhamma.
    The Dhamma well-practiced
        brings bliss.
    This  the reward
    when the Dhamma's well-practiced:
    one who lives by the Dhamma
    doesn't go to a bad destination.

    For Dhamma and non-
    don't bear equal results.
    Non-Dhamma leads you to hell;
    Dhamma, to a good destination.

    So you should engender desire
    for acts of Dhamma,
    rejoicing
    in the One  Well-gone,
    the one     who is Such.
    Standing firm in the Dhamma,
    of the foremost
    One Well-gone,
    his disciples are guided
     enlightened 
    to the foremost
    refuge supreme.

    Burst       is the root of the boil;
    the net of craving  uprooted.
    He, having ended his wandering-on,
    has no stain 
    like the moon
    on a clear full-moon night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 00:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting discovery!

I have searched for the author and found the following book, which may be interesting: [Essential Themes of Buddhist Lectures](http://www.buddhanet.net/pdf_file/thittila.pdf). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 22:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a beautiful time lapse video indeed. Many thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 15:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  six types of rebirth

Or five... Some schools combine the realm of the Devas and and the realm of the Asuras and therefore count five instead of six realms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kathmandus Boudhanath Stupa Formally Reopens After Reconstruction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 12:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Rift Near the Center of the Milky Way (image by Rogelio Bernal Andreo; mosaic of over 100 telescopic image panels; about 130 hours of exposure) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 23:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seneca: on Providence | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 08:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make the day not-in-vain, a little or a lot. However much the day passes, that's how much less is life. Your last day approaches. This isn't your time to be heedless. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 07:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thag 6.13: Sirimanda**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thag/thag.06.13.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)

    Rain soddens what's covered
      doesn't sodden what's exposed.
    So open up what's covered up,
    so that it won't get soddened by the rain.

    Attacked by death
        is the world,
    surrounded by aging,
    beset by the arrow of craving,
    always obscured by desire.

    Attacked by death
        is the world,
      encircled by aging,
    constantly beaten, with no shelter,
        like a thief
    sentenced to punishment.

    They encroach like masses of flame,
        these three:
        death, aging,   illness.
    There's no strength to confront them,
    no speed to run away.

    Make the day not-in-vain,
        a little or a lot.
    However much
    the day passes,
    that's how much less
        is life.
    Your last day approaches.
        This isn't your time
        to be heedless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Human Family | Ajahn Sumedho </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All griefs have been cut off, abandoned, brought to this end, for I've comprehended the grounds from which griefs come into play. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thig 6.2: Vasitthi the Madwoman**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thig/thig.06.02.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)

    Overwhelmed with grief for my son 
        naked, demented,
        my hair dishevelled
        my mind deranged 
    I went about here   there,
    living along the side of the road,
    in cemeteries   heaps of trash,
        for three full years,
    afflicted with hunger   thirst.

    Then I saw
    the One Well-gone,
    gone to the city of Mithila:
        tamer of those untamed,
        Self-Awakened,
        with nothing to fear
        from anything, anywhere.

    Regaining my mind,
    paying him homage,
        I sat myself down.
    He, Gotama, from sympathy
    taught me the Dhamma.
    Hearing his Dhamma,
    I went forth into homelessness.
    Applying myself to the Teacher's words,
    I realized the state of auspicious bliss.

    All griefs have been cut off,
        abandoned,
        brought to this end,
    for I've comprehended
    the grounds from which griefs
    come into play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 16:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract:**](https://www.academia.edu/29366003/Living_in_Agreement_Stoicism_and_Daoism_on_the_Sage)

 Although arising in different cultural contexts, Stoicism and the Daoism of the Daodejing characterize the life of their wise man, or Sage, in surprisingly similar ways. Both see persons as integral parts of the world, who fulfill their natures as individuals by harmonizing their experiences, thoughts, and actions with the natural or cosmic context in which they are embedded. Because of their different conceptions of humanity and the nature of the world, however, the philosophies develop different ideas about how we ought to go about achieving this harmony. I explore the implications of some of these differences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Living in Agreement: Stoicism and Daoism on the Sage | Benjamin A. Rider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 16:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 13:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is excellent! I would enjoy listening to the complete talk, but unfortunately I have not found any information about which talk this is taken from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Living in Agreement: Stoicism and Daoism on the Sage | Benjamin A. Rider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 09:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Living in Agreement: Stoicism and Daoism on the Sage**](https://www.academia.edu/29366003/Living_in_Agreement_Stoicism_and_Daoism_on_the_Sage)

by Benjamin A. Rider

 **Abstract:**

 Although arising in different cultural contexts, Stoicism and the Daoism of the Daodejing characterize the life of their wise man, or Sage, in surprisingly similar ways. Both see persons as integral parts of the world, who fulfill their natures as individuals by harmonizing their experiences, thoughts, and actions with the natural or cosmic context in which they are embedded. Because of their different conceptions of humanity and the nature of the world, however, the philosophies develop different ideas about how we ought to go about achieving this harmony. I explore the implications of some of these differences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> See the Dhamma's true rightness! The three knowledges have been attained; the Awakened One's bidding, done. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thag 6.6: Sappadasa**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thag/thag.06.06.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)


    Twenty five years since my going forth,
    and no peace of awareness
     not a finger-snap's worth 
        attained.
    Having gained no oneness of mind,
    I was wracked with lust.
    Wailing, with my arms upheld,
    I ran amok from my dwelling 
    "Or... or shall I take the knife?
    What's the use of life to me?
    If I were to renounce the training,
    what sort of death would I have?"

    So, taking a razor,
    I sat down on a bed.
    And there was the razor,
    placed ready to cut my own vein,
        when apt attention arose in me,
    the drawbacks appeared,
        disenchantment stood
        at an even keel:

    With that, my heart was released.
    See the Dhamma's true rightness!
    The three knowledges
    have been attained;
    the Awakened One's bidding,
            done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, Epictetus' surviving works are lecture notes written by [Lucius Flavius Arrianus](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arrian). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Epictetus was a great teacher and his lectures, as far as they have survived, belong to the most fascinating texts ever. The *Enchiridion* is a collection of short passages taken from his lectures and for someone knowing the lectures a great tool for bringing Epictetus' teaching into memory.

That being said, many people enjoy the *Enchiridion* for itself. Although there is nothing wrong with that, knowledge of the lectures makes it more valuable and more understandable. A lot of critiques and misunderstandings comes from not knowing or ignoring the broader context of Epictetus' lectures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 20:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't forget that there are a lot of people who do not live at the bright side of life, people who feel somehow forgotten by society. Many of them are uneducated, untrained in subtle thinking and very easy to be deluded. There is a reason why people become victims of seducers easily.

One doesn't have to agree with them, but one may try to understand the situation as best as possible which may eventually lead to compassion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You make things worse when you flare up at someone who's angry. Whoever doesn't flare up at someone who's angry wins a battle hard to win. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 07:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thag 6.12: Brahmadatta**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thag/thag.06.12.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)

    Whence is there anger
    in one without anger
        tamed, calmed, living in tune,
        released through right gnosis,
        Such?

    You make things worse
    when you flare up
    at someone who's angry.
    Whoever doesn't flare up
    at someone who's angry
        wins a battle
        hard to win.

    You live for the good of both
         your own, the other's 
    when, knowing the other's provoked,
        you mindfully grow calm.

    When you work the cure of both
         your own, the other's 
    those who think you a fool
    know nothing of Dhamma.

    If anger arises,
    reflect on the saw simile. [See MN 21] 
    If craving for savor,
    remember the son's-flesh simile. [See SN 12.63] 

    If your mind runs loose
    after sensual pleasures
      states of becoming,
    quickly restrain it with mindfulness
    as you would a bad ox
    eating grain. [See MN 19] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whoever wants to do later what he should have done first, falls away from the easeful state   later burns with remorse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 23:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thag 3.15: Harita**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thag/thag.03.15.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)

    Whoever wants to do later
    what he should have done first,
    falls away from the easeful state
          later burns with remorse.

    One should speak
    as one would act,
      not
    as one wouldn't.
    When one speaks without acting,
    the wise, they can tell.

    How very easeful:
        Unbinding,
    as taught by the Rightly
    Self-awakened One 
            sorrowless,
            dustless,
            secure,
    where stress
      suffering
    cease. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best Remedy: The Venerable Sayadaw U Panditas last advice for attaining peace in our inner and outer worlds | Alan Clements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comments like yours make this subreddit a great place. Thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 07:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laughter is not foreign to Stoics. Chrysippus, about whom the ancient said But for Chrysippus, there had been no Porch, literally laughed so heartily that he died:

 Another account is that his death was caused by a violent fit of laughter; for after an ass had eaten up his figs, he cried out to the old woman, Now give the ass a drink of pure wine to wash down the figs. And thereupon he laughed so heartily that he died.

Source: [Diogenes Laertius, *Lives of Eminent Philosophers*, Chapter 7. CHRYSIPPUS (c. 282-206 B.C.)](http://www.perseus.tufts.edu/hopper/text?doc=Perseus%3Atext%3A1999.01.0258%3Abook%3D7%3Achapter%3D7) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iconic seventh-century Buddha at Jahan Abad, Swat valley, was restored by Italian archaeologists nine years after it was defaced by the Taliban | Fazal Khaliq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 20:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very sorry for your chronic illness and it's great that you have found something which helps you to live with it and wish you the best. I did not intend to offend anyone and certainly none who cannot become a monk due to illness. That being said, I am no monk either and, as far as I can tell, I won't ever become one. If I sounded too judgemental too lay people, I am one of the targets myself.

My comment was thought as response to the mentioned urgency and the luck of becoming human as it is described in the [Chiggala Sutta](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/sn/sn56/sn56.048.than.html) which I read shortly before (it was linked in this subreddit recently, if my memory is right). I really should have written the second paragraph differently, I certainly would not write it exactly the same way again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 17:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The documentary is interesting by itself, but his voice makes it special indeed. I have already posted the link today: [Tibetan Book of the Dead (Narrated by Leonard Cohen)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nOs8s5zTGnA). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember seeing that more than once, this poster seems to spread this all over reddit which seems strange enough (if the incident even happened, he may just make fun of reddit users). This explanation is one of the most bizarre ones I have ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 08:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/R1Adam writes

 I'm a pretty bad person, in terms of Buddhism. I drink, smoke, take drugs and have a lot of sex. I suppose this is why I'm not ever going to be able to be fully Buddhist. I'd like to try my best, nonetheless.

This implies that /u/R1Adam does not claim that these things would be condoned in Buddhism.

Why on earth isn't there a /r/badBadEasternPhilosophy subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 07:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be interested in the documentary [A Day in the Life of Zen Monk Leonard Cohen: A 1996 Documentary](http://www.openculture.com/2015/07/a-day-in-the-life-of-zen-monk-leonard-cohen.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tibetan Book of the Dead (Narrated by Leonard Cohen) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 07:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 07:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The article doesn't mention it, but he was a very committed Buddhist who lived at the Mt. Baldy Zen Zen Center for several years.

The article mentions it:

 Mr. Cohen, raised Jewish and observant throughout his life, became interested in Zen Buddhism in the late 1970s and often visited the Mount Baldy monastery, east of Los Angeles. Around 1994, he abandoned his music career altogether and moved to the monastery, where he was ordained a Buddhist monk and became the personal assistant of Joshu Sasaki, the Rinzai Zen master who led the center, who died in 2014. He took the name Jikan, which means silence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The triumph of triviality: Is consumer society too shallow to deal with the deepening crises facing the planet? | John F. Schumaker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it must not remain unmentioned that I actually like your post and appreciate it. It's just that your definition is not the Stoic's definition, according to my understanding. This does not need to be bad at all. The Stoic understanding of virtue was criticized a lot in ancient times.

There is also a reason why there are different types of ethics (consequentialism, deontology, and virtue ethics) and discussing and comparing them is interesting. My personal preference, however, has become virtue ethics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am with /u/skip_hunter, this understanding of virtue actually opposes Stoicism. The Stoics defined virtue very differently to your definition and also to those other ancient philosophic schools. I think that /u/MinotaurWarrior defined quite well in [this comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/5agbgf/what_is_virtue_to_you/d9gcjr6/) how we may understand virtue without sacrificing too much:

 Living in accord with nature. Meaning, living at peace with the universe, and living according to the high ideals of the writ deep within yourself.

 This manifests itself in courage (the acceptance of all things that come), temperance (the acceptance of all things that do not come), justice (the recognition of ones' place in relation to others, and the associated duties), and wisdom (awareness of what all of the above mean)

In fact, it's even more complicated, since one is either virtuous or not without anything in between. Only the Stoic sage is virtuous and it is virtually impossible to become a Stoic sage. However, there are differences in how advanced prokoptons are. It's a life-long journey. For more info, you may read Julia Annas' article [Is Stoic Virtue as Off-Putting as it Seems?](http://blogs.exeter.ac.uk/stoicismtoday/2016/11/05/is-stoic-virtue-as-off-putting-as-it-seems-by-julia-annas/) I have posted here recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great and exactly what I was looking for! Thanks a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm impressed, many, many thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your comment! I think this makes the mentioned number 360 of which I've read recently rather questionable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an interesting sutta on the luck of human rebirth: [Chiggala Sutta](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/sn/sn56/sn56.048.than.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why is speed/efficiency the most important part about Buddhism?

It seems that my comment was too unclear (I'm no native speaker). Speed and efficiency being the most important parts of Buddhism certainly is not what I believe (and wanted to communicate). I answered to /u/Meditativo's comment

 Do not waste this rare and fortunate opportunity! Remember to have a sense of seriousness and urgency in your practice too, you never know how much longer this opportunity will be available to you...

which is not the first time I have read something like that. If this argument is to be taken dead seriously, then it is reasonable to do what makes one attain nirvana the most promising way, which seems to include becoming a monk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suttas for the Householder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddha taught mostly to monks, but there are also several suttas directed at householders (I have read somewhere that there are about 360 such suttas). Unfortunately, I could not find a complete list, but at least [this one](http://www.patheos.com/blogs/americanbuddhist/2010/05/suttas-for-lay-people.html) certainly is a very good start.

Do you know a more complete list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoicism after the elections | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in Buddha's time lay people rarely attained nirvana and becoming a monk was significantly more efficient than staying lay people. I don't think that this has changed much.

Since you are right, according to Buddhist teachings (as far as I have understood them), one may take the fortunate opportunity, become a monk, and practice Buddhism as sincerely as possible. It's certainly much easier as monk.

I know there are a lot of sincere lay people and don't say it's wrong not to become a monk. But in a way this may be seen as inconsistency. So why not become a monk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm gathering that logos is similar to the laws physics, like the random motion of electrons and the interactions of subatomic particles with each other. Am I far off with this idea?

/u/bytor99 wrote an excellent text post about Stoicism a while ago  [Stoicism In One Page](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/4t4t0z/stoicism_in_one_page/) , which you may be interested in. It included an explanation of *logos*. I described [my own understanding](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/4t4t0z/stoicism_in_one_page/d5evrfj/) of *logos* in that thread as follows:

 In my opinion, it is not self-evident that the cosmos can be explained rationally and that working mathematical models of the cosmos can be developed. It's like there is an inherent rationality of the cosmos, which is something the ancients called *logos*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  **Abstract:**

 The idea of gratitude () appears, both explicitly and by implication, in many Epicurean texts.  I propose that Epicureans think of gratitude as an important virtue of character, directed at no particular benefactor, but distinguishing the best kind of human life. In particular, it represents the proper disposition or mental stance toward the goods in ones life.  As a virtue, it is a state one must cultivate, through daily habits of reflection. With this virtue, one is able to maintain the proper attitude toward the objects of ones desires, thus avoiding unnatural, empty desires that make a life of  impossible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ethical Significance of Gratitude in Epicureanism | Benjamin Rider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haughtiness   contempt have been abandoned  rooted out  the conceit "I am" is extracted, all forms of pride, destroyed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thag 6.9: Jenta, the Royal Chaplain's Son**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thag/thag.06.09.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)


        I was
    drunk with the intoxication
    of my birth, wealth,   sovereignty.
    Drunk with the intoxication
    of my body's build, coloring,   form,
    I wandered about,
    regarding no one
    as my equal or better,
        foolish, arrogant, haughty,
        my banner held high.
    I  disrespectful, arrogant, proud 
    bowed down to no one,
    not even mother,
            father,
    or those commonly held
    in respect.

    Then  seeing the ultimate leader,
    supreme, foremost of charioteers,
        like a blazing sun,
    arrayed with a squadron of monks 
    casting away pride   intoxication
    through an awareness serene   clear,
        I bowed down
        my
        head
    to him, supreme
    among all living beings.

    Haughtiness   contempt
        have been abandoned
         rooted out 
    the conceit "I am" is extracted,
    all forms of pride, destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a short article about some apparent problems with Epicureanism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicurean Paradoxes | Jon Avery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 23:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a Stoic? Some Historical Reflections | John Sellars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's too cold, too hot, too late in the evening  people who say this, shirking their work: the moment passes them by. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 18:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thag 3.5: Matangaputta**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thag/thag.03.05.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)

    It's too cold,
    too hot,
    too late in the evening 
    people who say this,
    shirking their work:
        the moment passes them by.
    Whoever regards cold   heat
    as no more than grass,
    doing his manly duties,
        won't fall away
        from ease.
    With my chest
    I push through wild grasses 
        spear-grass,
        ribbon-grass,
        rushes 
    cultivating
            a seclusion heart.

It's too hot, it's too cold  what's *your* excuse? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm happy that you like the article (which I obviously do, too)!

Some comments are rather disturbing indeed. It's rather unfortunate having to deal with ignorant and destructive people. However, we know that such people exist and therefore it's no surprise having to deal with them from time to time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, but we shall be careful with our own reactions, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is more than stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just another arrogant westerner knowing it better than Asian Buddhists how to practice their own tradition...

If these monks are doing right, may be open to discussion. I am quite sure they were discussing that themselves, too, before they started doing what the article is about. However, I think that comparing it with running a brothel is far enough from good conduct to completely disqualify oneself for participating in such discussions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 10:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes indeed. We are no statues, human nature is not the same as the nature of statues and therefore living according to nature does not mean living like statues. Stoicism is not even against passions per se, since there are also good passions: to each bad passion there is a good passion which the bad passion may be transformed to (e.g. *anxiety* may be transformed to *caution*). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So yeah, going blind would be very difficult, but I imagine after a while you would get used to it and just deal with it.

I have read that people who have become disabled are usually as happy as before within a year, according to research. There are differences among people, however, and I guess that someone practicing Stoicism may be able to cope with situations like that in a better way than other people, because Stoic practice certainly strengthens one's resilience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 07:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting, many thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marcus Aurelius' *Meditations* was not intended as systematic introduction to Stoicism for the 21st century. It is the personal philosophical notebook of an ancient Stoic containing reflections, affirmations and the like. It's the result of someone's personal spiritual practice.

Personal reflections are of a different nature than lectures, essays and letters. Therefore, the *Meditations* is certainly not of the same kind as Epictetus lectures or Senecas essays and letters which were directed to other people than only the author himself.

I don't agree that Epictetus and Seneca wrote better material. They wrote different material. If one is looking for more systematic texts, Epictetus and Seneca are the authors to be preferred indeed, but that's simply due to the nature of personal reflections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rouse yourselves. Apply yourselves to the Awakened One's bidding. Scatter the army of Death as an elephant would a shed made of reeds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 23:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Thag 3.13: Abhibhuta**](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/kn/thag/thag.03.13.than.html)

(translated from the Pali by Thanissaro Bhikkhu)

    Listen, kinsmen, all of you,
    as many as are assembled here.
    I will teach you the Dhamma:
        Painful is birth,
        again   again.

    Rouse yourselves.
        Go forth.
    Apply yourselves
    to the Awakened One's bidding.
    Scatter the army of Death
    as an elephant would
    a shed made of reeds.

    He who,
    in this doctrine   discipline,
    remains heedful,
    abandoning birth,
        the wandering-on,
    will put an end
    to suffering   stress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an interesting story indeed, but also a sad one. Thanks for the linked articles which seem to be interesting, I am going to read them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddhist Monks Extend a Helping Hand to Japanese Singles Seeking Romance | Craig Lewis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hard Truths and Happiness | John Sellars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Stoic Virtue as Off-Putting as it Seems? | Julia Annas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Different perspective on empathy | Ajahn Brahm | 15 Jul 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 00:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I understand Seneca, he thought that nobody owns the truth: If something is true, then it is universally true and the Epicureans don't own it. He wrote in a very clear way, that Epicureanism is wrong. Therefore, I agree that it is certainly wrong to assume that Seneca was eclectic because he quoted Epicurus surprisingly often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nepals most popular Buddhist nun is a musical rock star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 00:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing wrong with a reasonable and well thought out eclecticism. However, don't put a wrong label on it. Better give yourself no label at all. [Keep your identity small.](http://paulgraham.com/identity.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 22:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an article from *The Oxford Handbook of Eschatology*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddhist Eschatology | Jan Nattier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 22:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chimp study shows how hanging out with friends makes life less stressful  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 15:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As for Art in the way of paintings and such, I don't see much virtuous value.

I think it is wrong to judge certain art forms negatively just because one cannot connect oneself with them as good as with other art forms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 15:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   And it does contribute to personal development.

Literature can contribute to personal development indeed, but I think that's rarely true for a certain kind of trivial literature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  panpsychism

At the moment there is a [discussion](https://www.reddit.com/r/philosophy/comments/5ajnfj/is_the_mind_just_an_accident_of_the_universe_a/) at /r/philosophy about an article which was originally posted at the OUPblog: [Is the mind just an accident of the universe?](http://blog.oup.com/2016/09/panpsychism-universe-mind/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 13:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently reading Reinventing the Sacred. He is said to go even further in Humanity in a Creative Universe regarding panpsychism, according to a review by Christopher Fisher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 11:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The alleged violation of Occam's razor is not the only detail which puzzled me, it's also his reference to being a scientist which makes him reject pantheism and panpsychism. Curiously, some of the best scientists (Albert Einstein, for example) believed in the god of Spinoza. I am currently reading an excellent book by the biologist Stuart A. Kauffman who is a further example of someone not sharing Pigliucci's opinion.

^(Edit: grammar) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why you need to count time, not money: What a new study reveals about this so-called dilemma of happiness | Oliver Burkeman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic theology: pantheistic or panentheistic? | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 22:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding Stability in Turbulence: Meditating When Things Get Tough | Michael Stone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 11:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 10:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with your posts in this thread. However, technically speaking, his argument is not an *argumentum ad absurdum*, but a good example of the  *straw man* fallacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 07:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a handout of pss. accompanying a talk given at the Association of Latin Teachers (ARLT) Summer School, HMSG (July 2015). It contains quite interesting quotes about the Stoics' and Epicureans' view on the end of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoics and Epicureans on the End of the World | Jonathan Griffiths [handout with interesting quotes] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 07:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract:**](https://www.academia.edu/26340894/N%C4%81g%C4%81rjunas_Pa%C3%B1cako%E1%B9%ADi_Agrippas_Trilemma_and_the_Uses_of_Skepticism)

 While the contemporary problem of the criterion raises similar epistemological issues as Agrippas Trilemma in ancient Pyrrhonian skepticism, the consideration of such epistemological questions has served two different purposes. On one hand, there is the purely practical purpose of Pyrrhonism, in which such questions are a means to reach suspension of judgment, and on the other hand, there is the theoretical purpose of contemporary epistemologists, in which these issues raise theoretical problems that drive the search for theoretical resolution. In classical India, similar issues arise in Ngrjunas Vigrahavyvartan, but it is not entirely clear what Ngrjunas purpose is. Contrary to the theoretical interpretations of several recent scholars such as Jan Westerhoff according to which Ngrjuna is proffering a contextualist epistemological theory, I argue that Ngrjuna as well as the later Madhyamaka Candrakrti, much like Pyrrhonian skeptics, employed concerns about epistemic criteria in service of purely practical purposes. There is no positive epistemological theory to be found in Ngrjunas Vigrahavyvartan and Candrakrtis Prasannapad; furthermore a putative thesis of universal emptiness is self-undermining, a conclusion which itself can be seen as part of a therapeutic program. Nonetheless, the historical persistence of these epistemological issues shows that they ought to continue to be areas of theoretical inquiry for epistemologists today. I end with reflections on the wider relevance of my conclusions, particularly with regard to demonstrating the value of philosophy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ngrjuna's Pacakoi, Agrippa's Trilemma, and the Uses of Skepticism | Ethan Mills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Manifesto for Modern Stoic Communities | Donald Robertson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 20:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case *akashic records, etheric plane, astral realm* is thought to be the goal and that's not what Buddhism is about indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Pleasure The Secret to a Good Life? | Thought Experiment: The Experience Machine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 08:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting, many thanks for pointing that out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exploring Buddhisms Tensions With Modernity: An Interview with Prof. David McMahan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 23:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can People Knowingly Do Wrong? Epictetus' View | Gregory B. Sadler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 00:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Strange Friend Marcel Proust | Philippe Soupault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 00:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Most don't believe in Zeus.

You are certainly right that modern Stoics dismiss much of ancient Stoicism, too, which makes calling oneself a Stoic somehow problematic, because all divisions of Stoic philosophy (physics, logic, ethics) were regarded as unity by the ancient Stoics (which makes sense). However, Stoic theology did not require literally believing in a deity called Zeus. The god of the Stoics may be described best as pantheistic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically, Albert Ellis is the founder of the *rational emotive behavior therapy (REBT)* and Aaron T. Beck the founder of the *cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT)*. Both based their therapies on Stoicism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this case the founders Albert Ellis and Aaron T. Beck are also the best sources, because they have written about that themselves. For example, Donald Robertson cites them in his book *The Philosophy of Cognitive-Behavioural Therapy: Stoicism as Rational and Cognitive Psychotherapy* quite often.

There is also an interesting interview with Albert Ellis in which he mentions Epictetus and Marcus Aurelius in this context within the first two minutes:

[Albert Ellis: A Guide to Rational Living - Thinking Allowed DVD w/ Jeffrey Mishlove](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GyRE-78g_z0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 17:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can't help but feel suspicious toward your strong comparisons.

I fully agree to your comment. That makes me feel suspicious, too, and that the three 'superior' philosophies which Buddhism 'can't hold a candle to' are so strongly different from each other makes me feel even more suspicious. The philosophies being involved in the comparison also seem to be a bit arbitrary. Most often such people have not studied any of the involved philosophies thoroughly (or are just trolling). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 14:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one?

*Abraham J. Malherbe, (1977), The Cynic Epistles: A Study Edition. SBL* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
