<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TesseracT. They're a British progressive metal band that's only been nominated for like 3 awards, nothing notable though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A blowjob assembly line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it brutal!? I was actually in grad school a year and a half ago but left because I hated what I was doing. I somehow scored a job as a contract copywriter a few months afterward. I loved it and was absolutely killing it, but I've been doing it for a year now, and it's gotten monotonous and has zapped all of my creative energy. Now I'm struggling to pay the bills due to my lack of productivity :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, what tips do you have for someone who's suffering from occupational burnout? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Swingers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My productivity and motivation have gone completely out the window. I work from home as a copywriter, and I have pretty bad ADHD, but I've grown a tolerance to every medication I've been prescribed. Given that I can't focus and get paid based on my output, I haven't been making much money at all. I'm very close to being unable to pay the bills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, didn't expect this to get downvoted so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mulholland Drive. No matter how many times you watch it, you'll still have no idea what the fuck happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going on the internet during a keyboarding class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if it's really a fashion trend, but I hate it when girls tie their hair into a bun that just bounces around on top of their head. I like them locks that flow freely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most bizarre mystery that remains unsolved? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were a Shark on Shark Tank, what stupid businesses would you invest in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kate Beckinsale. Hugh Jackman had his face in her cooch in Van Helsing and I'm so jealous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most ridiculous thing someone got offended over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shieett. I'll eat my hat if it goes well now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the plan if all goes to hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a dude and I'm not a virgin. It's just been 2 years since I've been on a date.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First date tomorrow. What happens now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Queen of the Damned's soundtrack was the only good thing about that movie. Holy shit what a soundtrack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before the opening weekend, what movies were spoiled completely by their trailers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
