<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5149</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks so mesmerizing. Please share the recipe you followed. With ingredients. And some tips if you can
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like

Liverpool: hey


Real Madrid: I have a bf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The city of Madrid is probably tired of shutting down all the tine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahaan so we will try to meet in the final matey! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real Madrid have scored in over 50 games, that's why they are an unstoppable force.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monaco can be the underdogs this season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe even Nesta-Maldini. If they lift the UCL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be interesting to see Real Madrid take on Juventus.
Will finally know what happens when an unstoppable force meets an immovable object.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wasn't he this astute when the downfall of AC Milan had begun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I buy a season pass, what all matches will that include? Is it just the home matches? And of only La Liga or can I watch home matches of UCL and other cups too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone do this for Friends (1994)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really our fault that he skied it? 

Lets not talk about Barcelona then. How about that red card to the Arsenal player? That definitely was game changing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize 13 of Suarez's goals last season in the La Liga were offside right? Wrongly called as onside. 

Even his goal in the first el clasico fixture of this season was offside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really dont see a reason to cry. 3 decisions were wrongly made for Bayern and 3 for Real.

In the PSG Barca game the ref was one sided.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice conspiracy theories. 

But you seem to have overlooked the three decisions the refs made IN FAVOR of Bayern Munich.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game would have been killed at the 90 min mark. Had the correct call been made in Bayern's second goal. We wouldnt have gotten to see 2 more offside goals if the first one was called correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 offside goals* Bayerns 2nd goal was offside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using video technology we'll all be winners, except for you know, our country rivals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong calls by the referee in this helluva quarterfinal. 

In favor of Real: 
2nd leg: 
Casemiro survived a second Yellow. 
Ronaldo's 2nd goal.
Ronaldo's 3rd goal.

In favor of Bayern: 
1st leg:
Wrongly called Penalty. 
2nd leg: 
Vidal should have been sent off earlier.
Offside 2nd goal. 

Refereeing sucked but I bet it evens out the wrong calls. Real Madrid will go through without any guilt. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Showerthought: If Vijay Mallya repays his debt of Rs.9000cr then we'll no longer be a poor country and Snapchat will finally expand in India. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about 678 999 8212 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want us to start like this. 

Our attack gets weakened because of the absence of Bale. Instead of Vasquez and Asensio, starting Isco would strengthen the mid. Something that we need. If you analyze the first half of the first leg, our mid was completely out of form. 


GK Navas

LB Marcelo CB Ramos CB Nacho RB Carvajal

CDM Casemiro

CM Modric CM Kroos

CAM Isco

LS Ronaldo RS Benzema </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the points are calculated like this. 

The score at that time is kept in mind. Messis first goal is +2 points as the score is 0-0 and Barcelona would have got one point out of it. Messis 2nd goal was worth 0 points as they were already winning. 

What bothers me is how the points are assigned to the player who is making a come back. Like the player who scored Sociedads 1st goal, did not bring any points to them but it sure as hell was worth something as it could have provided a path to a comeback. Similarly Paco Alcacers goal was worth no points. 

The only worthy goal in this match goes to Messi because of his 1st goal. 

In the case of Real Madrid vs Gijon, the first player to score in the match for Gijon was worth 2 points. Iscos first goal was worth 1 point. Second Gijon player also gets two points. Morata gets 1 point for equalizer and Isco gets two more for the winner. 

In this case, Iscos goals were worth 3 points, Moratas goals were worth 1 point. 
Gijons points dont get calculated as they lost the match.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone help me get some context with the peanut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is winter soldier an avenger yet? All he did was murder some people and then beat the shit out of a couple of avengers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It becomes complicated when you are assigning points to each goal. 

Although I couldnt agree with you more that its the team effort that counts, but OP is trying to say that Leo's goals are somehow more point worthy. 

It was Sergio Robertos goal that kept Barcelona in the UCL up until now. Is he the real GOAT now?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 12:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if Paco didnt score then it would have been just 1 point.
I see a paradox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I love this. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is, it delayed 99% peoples time even when the doctor was getting thrown out.

 I'd be much happier to be one of the 99% in Etihad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
