<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5027</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guess I'll just die now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I feel off the couch last night and almost died. I had to meditate for an hour to regain my health.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Little Nightmares" is releasing Friday and I'm pumped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, it's mostly neckbeard nonsense. By an exclusive release date standard the nes classic is suddenly current gen. 
Next gen is generally used to refer to a significant increase in technology between systems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang, I need a potato masher that can reverse time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that I was hoping to get some more information on specifically PIA, if they have more than one region available or at least if someone could verify certain regions through experience rather than go poke at their website. 

Yeah I've heard about that, blocking torrent traffic,which kind of seems ridiculous to me. I've always been a fan of the old adage "more laws, more criminals". In context here we can see a bunch of people scrambling to learn about VPNs, redirecting and hiding traffic when it wasn't a problem (for most) just a few years ago. Now it's going to be every Tom, Dick and Sally understanding how to hide traffic and reroute things online because it becomes forefront knowledge... It's ignorance of that stuff that's let law enforcement even try to come close to the new age of dark web hitmen and pedophilia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's what I thought. This is the first thread I've seen were people were saying it's their least favorite in the series. On average I've only heard great things about it, played it for myself, absolutely loved it. The mechanics were wonderful, the combat an absolute joy to watch and partake in, I mean it was wonderful. I bought the collector's edition after.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that can be done through a change of your DNS address as well though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're using PIA from which region? Just curious for my own sake. Can anyone here validate PIA speeds from East coast, from Canada, and from Europe? And judging from your edit PIA is logless?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Archer is fucking great. Neat little concept this season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad how few people you must know

http://www.ibtimes.com/forget-cable-cord-cutting-83-percent-american-households-still-pay-tv-2081570

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something sounds stupid as fuck here for sure.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got your John Hancock for ya right heeerrre oh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn paparazzi! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boof! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This dog licking a Popsicle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool story bro. You're pretty cool. Can we hang out some time. Ya wanna go to prom cool guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you thought damn well correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. So you do know what's happening here haha

Don't call me pal, guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is clearly not karma farming. I'd post a gtav "how to shoot a photo" if I wanted that. This is funny. And gaming related. I laughed when my friend sent it. And I posted it. He was not aware of the Nvidia hair works, nor was i. While I appreciate your context you can add context without being cunty and that will usually get you more upvotes.

Carry on....

Edit - Spelling
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /iamverysmart was an insult.

This comic features no father and son.

I feel like you have no idea what's going on here bud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I didn't really give any details eh. Great piece not seen by all, figured it would be appreciated here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because Geralt's worth it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The battle to create on a deadline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to sue Bethesda over removing weapon degredation in fallout 4 but ya don't see me jumping on that band wagon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a rather large lawsuit filed against Blizzard IIRC. Dude lost his wife and job cause world of Warcraft owned him. It got thrown out of court in the end I'm pretty sure. I figure it's precedent that keeps cases like this from being filed relentlessly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TROGDOOOORRR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true. Big grin, big fat goggles on, staring up at the ceiling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really works well with the yolks honestly. I guess the moisture content/Removal really pushes the flavor into it. So honestly tread lightly at first. But with meats it's the opposite, the flavor takes a long time and has a hard time penetrating to the core in a meaningful way. So I really pound it in the cure for meats. But light for the yolks. Truly a cool way to keep an individual flair to your cured products </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boom this guy got it. The salt is really the star, you can use sugar as you please but alternatively blitz your cure with spices or herbs, in this case I'm using lavander flowers and dehydrated beet root, nice color to the dust in the end. 

We also hang in cheesecloth in this kitchen but I've used the dehydrater for the best result. Just be careful not to go too far in which case we created a neat cured egg yolk glass. Unintentional but awesome if you want to try it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers mate!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha holy fuck I massacred that post title didn't I 
Oh well, fuck em chef </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude you can definitely cut your own egg, I'm not a monster. But for the pictures sake it had to be cut. I agreed.
And whiskeys are my game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who have never made their own pasta and think Barilla spaghetti is as good as it gets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck me haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Duck, chicken, and goose yolk comparison before we cure 'em </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2008 I believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Translated without autocorrect apparently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I died a little at that. So everything I thought was true?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing how people become interested in massive news stories and read up on them. Just
Fascinating
:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HHahhahahahahahhaahahahhahahahaha
Now that, is funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cat. The cat is cuter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awwwcckkttuuuaaalllyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I believe throwing a party for your crush is a closer comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8 Rules of a Super Player, translated from Japanese </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right you are my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's super neat, I think you're right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeez you seem to be jumping to conclusions and very agitated in general.

People like attractive characters. End of story. 

Are you going around life fucking girls, or guys, or toasters, that are 4's at best? Nah... you probably prefer a 7 at least, and you imagine a 10 when you're about to blow it. I'm really not going to be sensitive on the subject and say I'm fighting for men's rights. I mean I know where I stand. I'm like, a 6 at best, but I'm funny and got a beard, so I can work with it. 

All I was saying is three left's make a right and people prefer attractive characters. Either sex. Cry about it some more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final Fantasy XV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you that's all I'm really saying here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha nice. Nice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Dean   Elizabeth Taylor, 1955 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha sorry. Hopefully you got another pair to start the day, sun will be up soon you're almost safe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I noticed that last night. Insane. 

Just sensationalism and personal bias rather than just reporting news. The altercation was started by her and the guy stood up for himself after *repeat* abuse... with corroborating stories he shouldn't even have been taken in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet that was the most excitement that little guy has had on years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thing of nightmares </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I remember that. It was almost as if he tried to distance himself from the home alone days it was such a night and day comparison to see him in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly. What a grin!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parent of the year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well when your wallet gets to and gets a job to support *you* then it can get as mad as it wants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed it but after the initial buzz I found it just dropped off so quick. Waiting in a lobby for long long long times, and heaven forbid if you wanted to be a killer, might as well start tonight to play tomorrow. 
But a great game definitely not dissing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say that, good eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doggo is listening. Tell doggo everything :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple Brown Betty with a scoop of vanilla ice cream, you boys come on in now and have a snack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salt the snail!! Salt the snail!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the evidence to support this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even think twice, I told that asshole to fuck himself and chose death wish option because let's be honest, you'd just go straight up and tell the gang what was happening and do your fucking best to fuck em all up. Everybody knows the bad guy kills you after you do his bidding anyways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finished it last night for the first time, so fucking satisfying. Icing all those cock suckers was all you wanted for hours and hours and hours on end. The FIB guy, the rich movie agent, the Chinese yukaza boss, the ghetto gangster. Just getting all of them in one massive fuck you mother fucking run was so fucking good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spot the protagonist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of detail and anger in here. I get it.
But this is blatant discrimination and showing favoritism is going to have a bad effect on those young girls, so hopefully one of the young girl's parents speaks up as well as the young boys.

Also the teacher sounds like a gash and a half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one seems to have heard of the scruff of the neck in that video, but god damn good on them for helping a doggo in need </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish it was just my account </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. Some guys posted they're number one on this game no one plays so I'm saying we all pile on board and ruin their chances </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you're kidding. I feel like the idea of tragic romance is so basic you have to be kidding me. You're kidding me right. Gotta be. This guy. This guy over here, real Kidder. Good one. Good one. Kidder.
But yeah. Tragic romance, you toaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't had the chance to dream in fifteen years!! Get back on the fucking line chef!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you sarcastic little girl. Duality of life really left you tranquil and understanding didn't it mannnn. Sorry brooooo, but that's exactly what they meant. They're more dangerous in captivity duuuuude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just some scared child who thinks that a couple of introductory courses have opened her mind to something that no one else is privy to. 
That she sees this huge change happening in the world when really this has always been the same game, she's merely projecting her little mind riot outwardly.
She thinks that she's ready to join an ill conceived, poorly led, faceless organization with a vague definition, facing down the exact same as it stares back with another bunch of clueless children so happy to be a part of something finally. All for the want of gang violence they seen on the tv when they grew up in middle America, where mommy fucked the mailman and daddy fucked her young friend Jenny and the world escaped them both, but not her, it won't be like that for her.

Now it's her turn to belong, and that guy on the wooden crate seems convincing. She'll say one thing, believe another, change her words again, bleed for her cause, beg for mercy, deny, change up, repeat, until one day she finds herself with a few memories she cringes about while she gets fucked by the mailman.

Middle America has always been the same joke. This poor child deserved to get punched in the mouth but instead of standing up and admitting it she's asking for preferential treatment. I know where some of us come from we call that a "little bitch.". Under them dreadlocks hides a little blonde girl who need an excuse to be herself. Wake up little blonde bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A valid point. Or dooooo they...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not nearly as threatening as it seems at first glance.  It's important to keep in mind that this nation has survived on a very visible sanctions/rhetoric/aid cycle... While I don't think Mr. Trump creates a stable geopolitical environment, I also don't believe this is anything out of the normal for North Korea on the global stage. 

For instance here's an article from 2013 citing over 20 similar provocations:

http://foreignpolicy.com/2013/03/21/a-running-list-of-north-koreas-near-daily-threats-updated/

It's actually incredibly difficult to count the number of times this kind of occurrence has happened, that is to say, the number of times North Korea has blamed another country for bringing nuclear war closer to a reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anybody else drink themselves into the past last night? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well she used to bring me surprise chocolate milk. I mean come on. Who doesn't like surprise chocolate milk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayoooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting top comment on ask Reddit.
I know people shouldn't listen to me but I talk all the time regardless. Horrific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neon stimulants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poorly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of this seems new. And honestly talking about sweetening trade deals with China seems redundant since Trump backed out of the Pacific trade agreement, which now ultimately puts China in a great position to be the primary trade partner for the rest.

It's almost as if Trump isn't paying attention. Giving China a box of candy before he offers them a lollipop isn't going to have a dramatic effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh my god my favorite!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good work :) very impressive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And a million gamers cried tears of salt and pity! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you're totally right, hated is definitely not real, but maybe like a bit of the rage, toss the remote with a good "come on!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's obviously worry. Should they just let someone live stream another murder? Should they do nothing and suggest vigilantism is the way to go. Listen you seem like you're intelligent enough, it's just you're wrong in this case. They had to exert an effort to shut down an active broadcasting vigilante and thats very very clear and simple. Their sworn duty you reference is in fact to stop a vigilante such as this, I'm not sure why you're so hell bent on this but the only one looking like a tool is you right now madam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I still live with the mentality that cops are crooked and scarier than criminals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a big fan of wooden chopsticks thrown out every meal. Mostly for poop reasons, secondary because I want to watch the world burn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's fucking brutal man and no one gives a fuck. This sub is dead it really bothers me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great ask Reddit, I'm fucking late for dinner!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit also there's a huge update coming. Gonna change the map and shit. So do not get attached to your current base. Use your first run as a way to get familiar with it all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude it's like very close to my setup, runs great. My only advice is take it back from highest resolution and increase graphics and draw distance. Beautiful. Fucking beautiful game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take salary and have contractual hours dictated in your contract. Very common in other industries and successfully managed it in our industry. 

X salary is for x amount of dollars with x vacation accrued at x hours/week. Any hours above x will be paid at x dollars/hour. Etc etc. 

Never say never ... Except in that case. Maybe? Hrm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've worked in kitchens with unions. Would not recommend. Low man on the totem takes the most work, massive turn over rate of the newest employees as it takes months and months to get into the union, and usually you're just supporting the highest paid, least working, long standing top dogs. 

I've been in several unions across several industries and besides these very obvious flaws there's also Union dues that you pay in, taking another chunk out of an already meager check. 

I do fine for myself, and I suggest to nonyabusiness that you work contractual hours into salary negotiations and anything beyond the contacts standard needs to have an hourly wage assigned, as that's often overlooked in our field.. but also it seems like you thatwasyouraccount have no Union or kitchen experience. And fair market value is a great concept but also very much not a consistent truth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll support the internet answer. But the real life reply of nothing is not very insulting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current winner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that kid is probable dead now.

Damn. Now that's trashy of me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have been like, "I'll fuck your mom dude, gimme strategies" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm with you, r/gaming is a bit of a toaster lately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second the Witcher. Beautiful game, decent learning curve, very engrossing. Considering you like wrestling or fighting games maybe try out assassin's Creed: black flag... Sounds strange but the fighting system really works so well and reminded me of old school n64 wrestling games in its hit/counter fashion. Plus it's a gorgeous world with lots to do and you can get a fucking pirate crew and catch whales and sing mother fucking sea shantys when you're having a cigarette break. Awesome game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just don't tell strangers your profession?
Or leave it vague. 
You seem very concerned about a non-issue toaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they were basically just describing a cat, there was more going on? Hang on I'll re-read after I toss this angry bastard over the tv real quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most dangerous animal of all!!

*It turns out it was man* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultimately you want people to play the game if I'm not mistaken.

So adapt with on the fly tutorial, on rails tutorial, or however you see fit. Complex or not people will often skip tutorials, so you'll likely need to make them do it without giving them the option. I would suggest an "on rails" fun super powered version trimmed to just the absolute essentials </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mother fucking red dead redemption did it best.
No witness, no crime.

Otherwise bring on the notoriety or karma or reputation or mystical spaghetti monster casting judgement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you don't like fork anal rape don't take it out on us, and stop PM'ing us for pictures of us dressed like your step dad holding a broken bottle and your first babysitters panties you toaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The answer you're hoping for is the correct one, no you will not see either again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dip it in ranch and get it back in ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butthurt toaster with internet spelling. You must be a real hit at parties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the whole "nothing to hide" argument is widely attributed to the Nazi Minister of Propaganda Joseph Goebbels, make sure the Facebook knows that. 

Snowden's comment rings out when he said that citing this argument is like removing free speech because you have nothing to say. 

You tell them kids on Facebook to shut the fuck up and let us Redditors handle this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing wrong with this at alllll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck what a great track that was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's gonna have him invade Canada so bitch can blow Justin "the pump" Trudeau </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
