<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1409</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Happening: Wall Street is beginning to turn on Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takes time to find jack shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department requests more time on congressional inquiry into Trump's wiretap claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carina Nebula, by Hubble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a hydropower renovation project in southeast China lowered a reservoir 30 feet. When the water dropped, a 400 year-old Buddha statue carved into the reservoir wall during the Ming dynasty emerged. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McCain to Trump: Provide wiretap evidence or retract claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump scammed many of his working-class supporters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 11:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After firing Preet Bharara, President Trump beware </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aurora Borealis, Lofoten, Norway by Joe Azure [1500 x 1000] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-Trump adviser swaps messages with DNC hacking suspect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I thought there would be one court date. I thought I would show up and the judge would look at this and say. This is absurd and it would be over," said McLafferty speaking at the Legislative Office Building in Albany.

McLafferty has been defending the case for two years and it's cost her over ten thousand dollars.

Brooklyn Assemblywoman Maritza Davila calls it an abuse of power and that's why she's introducing Collette's Law.

"I don't think that should happen to anyone just because you graduated from a law school," said Davila, D-Bushwick.

The bill would require the plaintiff to pay for the defense's legal fees if a judge rules a suit "abusive".  The assemblywoman says abusive suits are filed all the time.

The lawsuit against Collette was finally dropped after two years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a NY woman spent 2 years defending herself against a $10M lawsuit by an aspiring musician who alleged that her unattractive appearance at a gig destroyed his potentially very profitable idea to form New Yorks first Pink tribute band. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo is by a Turkish photographer named Aydin Buyuktas.  His photos are generally of Turkish cityscapes that are skewed and bent in this manner.  You can view more of his work [here](https://www.aydinbuyuktas.com/).  There is also an upcoming documentary called "Bend it like Buyuktas."  Just kidding about that last part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While on approach to Chicago OHare International Airport last week after a business trip, amateur photographer Mark Hersch glanced out his window at the setting sun and decided to pull out his iPhone to take a photo. Right then the plane banked for a 180-degree left turn over Lake Michigan for a final westward approach when an unexpected play of light occurred: the entire skyline of Chicago was suddenly projected in shadow from underneath the cover of clouds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aerial View of the Chicago Skyline as Reflected on Lake Michigan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skewed photo of a trainyard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey just kicked a major refugee aid organization out of the country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Topographic map centered on the Venusian North Pole. Gaps in the Magellan data were filled in with radar images from the Arecibo telescope. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
[much more here](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2014/04/new-underwater-ink-plumes-photographed-by-alberto-seveso/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photo of an underwater plume of ink by Albert Seveso </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunset reflected in a broken mirror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> photo by [Stephen Hamilton](http://stephenhamilton.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> photo by [Stephen Hamilton](http://stephenhamilton.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I get out of this alive, I will shred you while you sleep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graham McGeorge spent a quiet 6 hours trying to get the perfect image of this eastern screech owl out of its nest. Okefenokee Swamp, Georgia

[photographer's website](http://www.grahammcgeorge.com/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graham McGeorge spent a quiet 6 hours trying to get the perfect image of this eastern screech owl out of its nest. Okefenokee Swamp, Georgia

[photographer's website](http://www.grahammcgeorge.com/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This owl blending in perfectly with a tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This owl blending in perfectly with a tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump disinformation bubble: A new study shows how toxic right-wing media narratives sway coverage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Ivan is probably an asshole, but couldn't she also be stressed because she is in an enclosure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> House Speaker Paul Ryan, R-Wis., said last week that the decision to appoint a special prosecutor is up to the executive branch.

Well, *that* might be a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Most Want a Trump-Russia Special Prosecutor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The White House demands a Congressional inquiry into something Trump likely read on Breitbart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That thumbnail just shouts 'slimy douchebags' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump sons, planning expansion of family business, look to leverage campaign experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japan has a rich tradition of food carving called mukimono. If youve ever eaten at a fancy restaurant in Japan you might have found a carrot carved into a bunny, garnishing your plate. But in the hands of Japanese artist Gaku, the art of fruit and vegetable carving is elevated to a new realm of edible creations.

One constraint to carving fruits and vegetables is that sometimes you must work fast. The moment a peel is removed, oxidization will start to discolor your artwork. So, depending on the variety, Gakus carvings are probably created within several minutes. Armed with a tool similar to an x-acto knife and a fruit or vegetable from the grocery store, Gaku carves intricate patterns that are often inspired by traditional Japanese motifs.

Gaku points out that the banana is great fruit to practice with because its cheap and easy to carve. When asked what he does with all his creations after hes done, his reply is simple: he eats them. Except for the banana peel.

[lots more](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2017/03/next-level-food-carving-on-fruits-and-vegetables-by-gaku/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> carved apple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I call it brocoloodle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps second-rate Reagan impression: Supply-side economics will work  for the ultra-rich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 12:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy UGC 12591, 400 million light years away. The galaxy and its halo together contain several hundred billion times the mass of the sun; four times the mass of the Milky Way. Photo by Hubble. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> three pack of Pallas kittens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Walled Off hotel may sound utilitarian, even bleak. Its owner says it has the worst view of any hotel in the world, while its 10 rooms get just 25 minutes of direct sunlight a day.

But, nestled against the controversial barrier wall separating Israel from the Palestinian territories, the West Banks answer to the Waldorf offers travellers something more elusive than any luxury destination.

The lodging in Bethlehem is a hotel, museum, protest and gallery all in one, packed with the artworks and angry brilliance of its owner, British street artist Banksy.

much more information [here](https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/mar/03/banksy-opens-bethlehem-barrier-wall-hotel) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the very moment when the best defense against "fake news" would be to uphold professional reporting, Trump is mounting a relentless attack on the thousands of professional journalists that have historically been part of America's bulwark against hostile nations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's war on reality is truly baffling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [research article](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/early/2017/03/01/science.aal1810) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time, scientists have created an artificial mouse embryo from stem cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby Fennec fox has a built-in umbrella </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find more of Mark Mawson's work [here](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2017/03/aqueous-roses-and-liquid-blooms-photographed-by-mark-mawson/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find more of Mark Mawson's work [here](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2017/03/aqueous-roses-and-liquid-blooms-photographed-by-mark-mawson/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London photographer captures swirls of dye underwater, choreographed to resemble flower blooms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London photographer captures swirls of dye underwater, choreographed to resemble flower blooms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is tarnishing America's brand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> baby fox with a mouthful of mama's tail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House lawyer twice briefed Conway on ethics rules following Ivanka product pitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo is by Krisztian Birinyi, and you can find more [here](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2014/06/budapest-trams-long-exposure/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long Exposure Photo of Budapest Tram Lit Up with 30,000 LED Lights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Subway denies its chicken is only 50 percent chicken meat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a man in Shaanxi, China, recently realized that the long-handled, blunt-ended object hed been using for 25 years to crack walnuts was actually a live hand grenade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hes A Performance Artist Pretending To Be A Great Manager </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cottonmouths are straight up assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [full video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AJ2l4owxC7s) if you're interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Large cottonmouth pounces on a rattlesnake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would take guts to do the same in D.C.'s hyper-polarized environment. Many Republicans would see it as treason. When Jeffords retired after three decades on Capitol Hill, only one of his former colleagues took the floor to praise him in keeping with the tradition in the upper chamber.

But today, some Republicans who are skeptical of Trump would understand  and even applaud  the move. And of course they would become heroes to millions of Americans who fear for their futures under this president. It's also very likely that in the future, history would look back kindly on their courage in defense of the republic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wanted: Three Principled Republicans to Save America From Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been 30 years since I first saw it and I still can't quite understand how it started out as a solid block of marble. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First installment on the butchers bill: Donald Trumps supporters will be made to pay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 11:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Horizons scientists made this false color image of Pluto using a technique called principal component analysis to highlight the many subtle color differences between Pluto's distinct regions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> photo by [Kris JB](https://www.facebook.com/kjbshoot/).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> perfect shadow of Mt. Fuji at sunrise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> photo by [Kris JB](https://www.facebook.com/kjbshoot/).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perfect shadow of Mt. Fuji at sunrise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> baby emus are so dang cute! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a Manhattan driver recently set a record by hitting 240 consecutive green lights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we finally ditch the white working class myth? Obama-then-Trump voters werent the problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 11:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California city's council votes to impeach Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slightly windblown-looking fuzzy baby cheetah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women in the U.S. are routinely killed by their husbands, boyfriends, ex-husbands and ex-boyfriends.  These incidents are typically experienced as individual cases, and not folded into a broader phenomenon of urgent concern, with blame attributed to a particular religion or culture.  

Different explanations surface for cases of violence against women, depending upon the identity of the perpetrator.  Bad acts by Muslim immigrants are blamed on Islam; bad acts by white non-Muslim Americans are ascribed to individual deviancy or psychological pressures.  

Gendered violence by Muslim immigrants is attributed to the category of honor crime, fortifying the presumption that there is something unusually misogynistic about Muslim societies; the same categorical attribution does not happen with gendered violence by white non-Muslim Americans.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's mentions of 'honor killings' betray the truth of his 'Muslim ban' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo by [Emily Blincoe](http://www.emilyblincoe.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oddly Satisfying Leaf Art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL in Thailand, pigtailed macaques are trained to harvest coconuts. Males can harvest up to 1,600 coconuts in one day, while their human overlords can only harvest about 80. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Moving To Delay Rule That Protects Workers From Bad Financial Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump's fear-based immigration orders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see video [here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p5GPNZubCYM) of how the shot came together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drone photo of nine climbers atop the summit of the Jungfrau in Switzerland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA analyst resigns because of Trump's 'disturbing' actions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 11:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photographer is [Kilian Schoenberger](http://www.kilianschoenberger.de/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German landscape photo straight out of a Grimm brothers story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "For-Profit President": A Look at How Trump Is Pushing Wholesale Corporate Takeover of the Gov't </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2014, Dutch newspaper De Volkskrant contacted conceptual design studio Lernert   Sander to create a piece for a special documentary photography issue about food. Lernert   Sander responded with this somewhat miraculous photo of 98 unprocessed foods cut into extremely precise 2.5cm cubes aligned on a staggered grid. Looking at the shot it seems practically impossible, but the studio confirms it is indeed the real thing. 

[more](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2015/05/cubes-lerner-sander/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A variety of unprocessed foods cut into precise 2.5 cm cubes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Trump cant be bothered to recognize black people as fully human. He seems to see black American life as a never-ending barrage of gunfire on bombed-out city blocks. The black people closst to him are celebrities who share and reinforce that view. This fantastical narrative obscures the real problems facing black communities, like housing and employment discrimination, divestment from education, over-policing, depressed wages and poisoned water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Donald Trump Doesnt Understand Black Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first month of Trumps presidency looks like a missing chapter from Lord of the Rings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic overreaction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted for the second half </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username does *not* check out.  Was *fuccinbusinessgeniusbutt* taken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *From text of petition*:

Donald Trump's well documented misogyny and vulgarity disqualifies him from being received by Her Majesty the Queen or the Prince of Wales. Therefore during the term of his presidency Donald Trump should not be invited to the United Kingdom for an official State Visit.

I love how there aren't any conditions at all.  Just a straight up "nope" for as long as he's president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photo by [Marc Mol](http://www.marcmol.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheetah holds a baby deer by the throat in the rain. Metal but more like a power ballad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British Parliament To Debate Withdrawing Donald Trumps Invite For State Visit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the last 6 years, Scottish wildlife photographer Alan McFadyen spent an estimated 4,200 hours seeking the perfect shot: a symmetrical image of a kingfisher diving into its own refelection in search of prey. Last month, after 720,000 exposures he finally got it. McFadyen certainly snapped hundreds of other successful images along the way, but this particular photoas it existed in his imaginationeluded him for years.

Kingfishers dive so fast they are like bullets, so taking a good photo requires a lot of luck  and a lot of patience, McFadyen told the Daily Mail. The difficulty is compounded by the fact that female kingfishers only rarely dive, so timing is essential.

[source](http://www.thisiscolossal.com/2015/11/kingfisher-symmetry-alan-mcfadyen/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kingfisher diving for prey, after 4,200 hours and 720,000 exposures waiting for the perfect shot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Perhaps the small illegal businessman of today will become the large-scale legal businessman of tomorrow," said the school's headteacher, Stefano Fava. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL an Italian schoolboy who was selling snacks on campus at a lower price than the cafeteria was suspended for 10 days. He also received a prestigious scholarship from an institute that said the boy's initiative should be "encouraged, not persecuted". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common prey of great white sharks, Cape fur seals normally feast on small fish, squid and crabs. But instead of going for the bait, this young seal turned its ravenous attention to the blue sharks, some of which were up to 4.5 feet long, or about the same size as the seal. The seal first snatched one shark, tearing open its abdominal cavity and feeding on the dark viscera inside. Then it went for another, and another. Fearing for his tourists safety, Fallows sent them back to the vessel. But he stayed to witness the scene, photographing the seal as it killed and consumed five of the ten sharks. He left before the seal had finished its meal, afraid that his presence was somehow aggravating the situation. Sharks of this size are certainly not usually considered food for seals, Fallows (the photographer) said at the time. 


[source](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/fur-seals-caught-preying-sharks-south-africa-180954779/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seal turns the tables, hunts and eats a shark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat sleeping in an excellent circle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M42 Orion Nebula. Happy belated Valentines Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> watch out, leaves! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its important not to dismiss the presidents reply simply as dumb. We ought to assume that its darkly brilliant  if not in intention than certainly in effect. The president is responding to a claim of fact not by denying the fact, but by denying the claim that facts are supposed to have on an argument.

He isnt telling OReilly that hes got his facts wrong. Hes saying that, as far as he is concerned, facts, as most people understand the term, dont matter: That they are indistinguishable from, and interchangeable with, opinion; and that statements of fact neednt have any purchase against a man who is either sufficiently powerful to ignore them or sufficiently shameless to deny them  or, in his case, both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Dismiss President Trump's Attacks on the Media as Mere Stupidity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not My Presidents Day: Thousands Plan Anti-Trump Rallies Across U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 12:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [NASA image source](https://www.nasa.gov/mission_pages/WISE/multimedia/pia17553.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Witch Head nebula, hundreds of light-years away in the Orion constellation, just off the famous hunter's knee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [research](https://www.geosociety.org/gsatoday/archive/27/3/article/GSATG321A.1.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is an eighth continent called Zealandia which is mostly submerged below the sea save some bits of land (including New Zealand) above the surface of the Pacific. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [original research](http://www.thelancet.com/pdfs/journals/lanpsy/PIIS2215-03661730049-4.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People with ADHD have slightly smaller brains than those without the condition, according to a study which insisted it is a physical disorder and not just bad behaviour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump isnt mad  hes the arrogant boss weve all seen before </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 10:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this dark moment, we can celebrate the vitality of the institutions of a free society that are pushing back against a president offering the country a remarkable combination of authoritarian inclinations and ineptitude. The courts, civil servants, citizens  collectively and individually  and, yes, an unfettered media have all checked Trump and forced inconvenient facts into the sunlight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Admit it: Trump is unfit to serve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL when a Long Island woman accidentally threw away an envelope with $5000 cash intended for her mortgage, sanitation workers sifted through tons of trash until they found it. They refused to accept a reward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not holdin' out on me, are ya?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby lumpsucker fish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a map of the entire internet from 1973 was recently discovered in a box of papers that belonged to a Carnegie Mellon computer scientist. The whole map fit on one sheet of paper. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 23:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There was an obvious typo in Donald Trump's official inauguration portrait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 11:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Refugees cross to Canada to escape Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 12:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photo of Venus from Magellan mission, 1996. Dark spots are meteorite impacts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hidden in the darkness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump has been sued more than 60 times since becoming president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 12:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New and Rising Price Tag for Trumps Wall: $21.6 Billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can Trumps self-defeating behavior be explained? One theory, subscribed to by a number of mental-health professionals, is that he suffers from a narcissistic-personality disorder that prevents him from turning the other cheek. Whenever anybody crosses him or says anything critical about him, this theory goes, Trump suffers narcissistic injuryan intense feeling that his entire self-worth has been called into question. And this prompts him to lash out, regardless of the consequences. John Garner, a Baltimore psychotherapist, has launched an online petition that says Trump manifests a serious mental illness that renders him psychologically incapable of competently discharging the duties of President of the United States. So far, more than twenty thousand mental-health workers have signed the petition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Donald Trump lash out at everybody? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A newly developed flow battery stores energy in organic molecules dissolved in neutral pH water. This new chemistry allows for a non-toxic, non-corrosive battery with a lifetime up to a decade and offers the potential to significantly decrease the costs of production. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transit of Venus past the sun, 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nordstrom broke the curse of the Trump tweet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We need to hear all points of view," said Sanders, adding it was incomprehensible that a letter written by Coretta Scott King, Martin Luther King Jr.s widow, could not be presented and spoken about here on the Senate floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL to help airline passengers deal with travel anxiety, San Francisco International Airport has hired the nation's first airport therapy pig. LiLou wears costumes and performs tricks to help travelers calm down before boarding their flights. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is gaslighting us  again!  with his silly terrorist-attack list, but journalists can fight back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 11:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact check: Trump makes false claim about murder rate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 01:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican lawmakers face rising anger at town halls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Al-Qaida Leader Taunts Trump After Escaping Capture in Botched Yemen Raid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 01:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uber Alles California  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California and President Trump are going to war with each other </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Focus on Trump, not Gorsuch: His presidency should be legitimized before vote on his SCOTUS pick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL researchers have developed a portable HIV test which can test a single drop of blood via a USB drive plugged into a laptop. Its accuracy approaches that of traditional tests, and it could be used in remote areas as well as allowing people to monitor their condition at home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South of the border, Mexicans are puzzled by Trump's relentless and pointless antagonism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'No hate, no fear' as thousands protest President Trump near Mar-a-Lago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matterhorn at sunset is so goddamn beautiful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 01:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Bulgarian stray cat named Pooh was fitted with two titanium back paws after being hit by a train and is back to motoring around like a champ. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from 2013:

An unusual type of solar eclipse occurred last year. Usually it is the Earths Moon that eclipses the Sun. Last June, most unusually, the planet Venus took a turn. Like a solar eclipse by the Moon, the phase of Venus became a continually thinner crescent as Venus became increasingly better aligned with the Sun. Eventually the alignment became perfect and thephase of Venus dropped to zero. The dark spot of Venus crossed our parent star. The situation could technically be labeled a Venusian annular eclipse with an extraordinarily large ring of fire. Pictured above during the occultation, the Sun was imaged in three colors of ultraviolet light by the Earth-orbiting Solar Dynamics Observatory, with the dark region toward the right corresponding to a coronal hole. Hours later, as Venus continued in its orbit, a slight crescent phase appeared again. The next Venusian solar eclipse will occur in 2117.

[source](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/heres-an-incredible-image-of-venus-passing-in-front-of-the-sun-340691/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venus is that little black dot at the top, passing in front of the Sun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> melting candy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Backers Want Ideology Test For Extreme Vetting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 12:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The roundness of this bichon frise's hair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upward lightning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
