<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand, they didn't immediately burn all written material that had s's that looked like f's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's important to remember that elongated verfions of the letter S were only ufed in the middle of words, not at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adding on to what /u/legumey said... in fact, /u/LasMatzos, you want to be sure you can answer "no" to the following question:

* If someone knew the location of the computer that was used to send this email message, would that someone have any clue that you were the sender?

You mention that you work remotely, so if you send an email message from a library in, let's say, Cleveland Heights, and you're the only person at the company who works in Cleveland Heights, there's a good chance that they can figure out who sent it.

Ideally, get a friend to send it for you from a computer in a library that's halfway across the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pssst... /u/Back2Bach has posted on /r/AskReddit enough to give me the idea that girls that went to high school at the same time as he did are no longer anywhere near under 30. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes, it's clearly more stability making the coach, rather than the coach making stability.  Consider this coach's seasons:

* .688, lost in first round of playoffs
* .563, lost in first round of playoffs
* .750, lost in second round of playoffs
* .688, lost in league finals
* .625, lost in second round of playoffs
* .688, lost in second round of playoffs
* .438
* .375

Time to get rid of the coach yet?  Let's consider a few more seasons.

* .563
* .813, lost in second round of playoffs
* .667, lost in second round of playoffs
* .375

Are you still keeping this coach around?  If you are... then here are the next two seasons.

* .938, lost in second round of playoffs
* .688, Super Bowl XL champions

This is Bill Cowher, of course.

(He stayed around for one more season after winning the Super Bowl, going .500, and then retired.)

Edited to add mistakenly omitted season; thanks, /u/AndrewHainesArt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Girls' Generation - I Got a Boy](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wq7ftOZBy0E)

I speak almost no Korean, but it's a catchy tune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
Both Election Data Services and Real Clear Politics agreed on the states that would lose congressional seats by 2020: Alabama, Illinois, Michigan, Minnesota, New York, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island and West Virginia. Election Data Services projects that Illinois will lose two seats.

States that would gain seats: Arizona, Colorado, Florida (2 seats), North Carolina, Oregon and Texas. Texas could gain three or four seats, the projections indicate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said this before: when multiple law enforcement officials leaked the information that Carter Page was under surveillance via a FISA warrant, it was the hurricane warning for all low-lying areas of the Trump administration.  The warning was twofold:

* After the warrant was issued last summer, any communications between Page and any members of the Trump campaign/administration, including any communications that might have occurred between Page and Trump himself, could reasonably be assumed to be in the hands of the FBI.

* Leaking the existence of the warrant meant that law enforcement already has everything they wanted from surveilling Page.  That's not good news for anyone who thought they may have managed to hide any scurrilous behavior.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EEN-EEN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, he came close to stunningly losing a vote for Republicare in deep-red Kansas last week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, did they have [takotsubo cardiomyopathy?](http://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/broken-heart-syndrome/home/ovc-20264165) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Social Justice Warrior".

The implication is "look at this horrible person, fighting for social justice!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *This gun's for hire    
Even if we're just dancin' in the dark*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel about Toys Ya Us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/OnePercentLifeProTips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Jaguars, [it was holding.](http://www.post-gazette.com/sports/2008/04/02/NFL-Spring-Meetings-Notebook-Radio-helmets-for-defense-gets-OK-too/stories/200804020229)

The tribe has spoken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article makes an interesting point: even if Trump and Russia are legitimately on unfriendly terms nowwhich itself is by no means clearbackstabbing that occurs later does not erase the criminality of having conspired earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Per Wikipedia:
An acronym is a word or name formed as an abbreviation from the initial components in a phrase or a word, usually individual letters (as in NATO or laser) and sometimes syllables (as in Benelux). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For many years, my least favorite team was a fellow ELoE team.

[That all changed on January 9, 2016.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g3vcdYNwQ6k)

Bengals, the tribe has spoken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although no longer an acronym, the word "Glomar" did initially come into existence as an acronym for GLObal MARine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Passenger rights are certainly necessary, but it's important to remember that part of the reason that United's behavior was so atrocious is that they violated existing passenger rights.  Needing to put your own employees on a plane **does not constitute overbooking.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, that format logically places all units of time in descending order of length: YYYY-MM-DD HH:MM:SS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrocaw has friendly people, great food, beautiful bridges and rivers, and is very reasonably priced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Menton is a great suggestion: less touristy and more laid back than much of the rest of the French Riviera.  And popping across to Ventimiglia, Italy is especially useful on market days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it depends on exactly where in eastern France you are, but think about a weekend in Luxembourg.  Luxembourg City is in a stunning geographic setting, perched on two hills that nearly meet and on the valley below them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psephology tells us that party identification is fluid, and the number of survey respondents who identify as Republican will drop as Trump becomes less popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. GOP decides it wants to get rid of president.

2. GOP-controlled House impeaches president.

3. GOP-controlled Senate holds trial, and removes president from office.

Note that we're not at Step 1 yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (I myself use military format for dates, not because of my nonexistent military experience, but because I'm a geek who prefers to avoid ambiguity, especially when possibly communicating with people around the world who use DD/MM/YY instead of MM/DD/YY.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But at least he isn't comparing himself to MLK any more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama won the Nobel Peace Prize by not being George W. Bush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the lighthearted article:
Whats unforgivable is Spicers brazen assault on spoken English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When multiple law enforcement officials leaked the information that Carter Page was under surveillance via a FISA warrant, it was the hurricane warning for all low-lying areas of the Trump administration.  The warning was twofold:

* After the warrant was issued last summer, any communications between Page and any members of the Trump campaign/administration, including any communications that might have occurred between Page and Trump himself, could reasonably be assumed to be in the hands of the FBI.

* Leaking the existence of the warrant meant that law enforcement already has everything they wanted from surveilling Page.  That's not good news for anyone who thought they may have managed to hide any scurrilous behavior.

^(edited to fix typo of "Pat" for Page) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill O'Reilly is Joe Namath? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump pledged Tuesday [November 10, 2015] to declare China a currency manipulator on his first day in office, breaking with at least 20 years of presidential restraint in that area to force Beijing to the negotiating table.](http://www.politico.com/story/2015/11/donald-trump-china-currency-manipulation-215679) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to [Joe Nedney.](http://www.titansonline.com/video/videos/Titans-Flashback-AFC-Divisional-Win-vs-Steelers/f28bb0b7-a8b6-4aea-addd-206b5d58f49b) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [But how did the Steelers do that season?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h2gt-PN5-Hg)

I didn't watch that Super Bowl live on television.  ^^because ^^I ^^was ^^there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Guess_2/3_of_the_average </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:
[I]mmigration hardliners in the Trump administration and Congress are reportedly threatening to shut down the government in an effort to compel so-called sanctuary cities to cooperate with federal law enforcement officials.

Republicans, do you want to lose a hundred House seats in a Democratic wave in the 2018 midterm elections?  Because shutting down the government is how you lose a hundred House seats in a Democratic wave in the 2018 midterm elections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still need a warrant to conduct surveillance of someone suspected of money laundering crimes... but that warrant doesn't need to be from the FISA court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 13:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should really credit the creator of this gif, [Parker Molloy on Twitter](https://twitter.com/ParkerMolloy/status/851867144400900096), showing the reactions of April D. Ryan and Ashley R. Parker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tuesday night: the Post reveals that Page is under a FISA warrant based on probable cause that he's a Russian agent.  Wednesday morning: the AP reveals that Manafort did receive Russian-linked payments.  We're clearly getting close to a real bombshell: the pace of developments is speeding up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **law enforcement** and other U.S. officials said

Emphasis added. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If law enforcement officials blow active surveillance operations by leaking, they are begging to go to prison for conspiracy to obstruct justice.  So law enforcement officials almost never do that, especially not in countries, like the USA, that have a relatively low incidence of corruption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are leaks and then there are leaks.  Multiple law enforcement officials leaking "this dude is under surveillance right now" would be extremely unlikely if law enforcement still cared about keeping the surveillance secret. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only is the investigation not coming up empty, *law enforcement officials and other US officials don't need to keep their surveillance of Page a secret any more.*  We know this because they're leaking the existence of the surveillance to the press, and thus ultimately to Page.  FBI officials must have already gotten all they wanted from surveilling Page.

This is the officially the first scene in the climactic act of this drama.  The climactic act may not be the *final* actthere could be another act with the anticlimax, plus an epiloguebut matters are certainly coming to a head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Page was the subject of a FISA warrant, then the FBI can legitimately have in its possession *any* communications that he had with *anyone* after the warrant was granted last summer.  That includes any communications that Page had with any members of the Trump campaign, or with Trump himself.

The Trump administrationhas been distancing itself from Page for a while, and now we know why.  We'll also eventually find out whether they lied about his impact in the campaign and in the administration, and if so, how many times they lied and how much they lied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here it is: the payoff for Putin.  If the USA doesn't care about Ukraine, it doesn't care about sanctions against Russia, and Putin rescues his crippled economy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Credit to [Parker Molloy on Twitter](https://twitter.com/ParkerMolloy/status/851867144400900096), showing the reactions of April D. Ryan and Ashley R. Parker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the White House Press Secretary says that Hitler "didn't even sink to using chemical weapons" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Credit [Parker Molloy.](https://twitter.com/parkermolloy/status/851869116361265152) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That distinction founders on the use of chemical weapons by the Nazis at the [Defense of the Adzhimushkay Quarry](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Defense_of_the_Adzhimushkay_quarry#Events). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allied combatants who survived the [Defense of the Adzhimushkay Quarry](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Defense_of_the_Adzhimushkay_quarry#Events) allege otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Survivors of the [Defense of the Adzhimushkay Quarry](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Defense_of_the_Adzhimushkay_quarry#Events) dispute your "FACT". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spicer: Hitler 'didn't even sink to using chemical weapons' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe [this link will work?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kcHskmhd7vo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm given to understand that the result of this game is not official yet, because a protest was filed after the final whistle.

By Costa Rica! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those who like snow: Vancouver Whitecaps-Real Salt Lake Highlights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 19:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll be happy to re-accommodate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did Santi Mina lull the defender to complacency?  "You are getting very sleepy... you are on the right, but when I count to three, you will watch the ball on the left and not me... one... two... three..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even Republicans admit he's "a terrible choice for congress."

Might want to change this to:  
Even Republicans admit "Ron Estes is a terrible choice for congress."

As written, "he" appears to refer to "our candidate", i.e. James Thompson, not Ron Estes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The USA had a huge bargaining advantage in that the 1994 World Cup still holds the total attendance record at 3,587,538 for 52 matches... even though every World Cup *after* 1994 has had 64 matches.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Trump Model Management regularly employed immigrants illegally, such as [Canadian Rachel Blais](http://news.nationalpost.com/news/canada/modern-slavery-of-vulnurable-young-girls-canadian-says-she-modelled-illegally-for-trump)
and [Jamaican Alexia Palmer.](http://www.jamaicaobserver.com/entertainment/Alexia-lands-Chanel-campaign_11147051) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to such high-altitude CONMEBOL notables as Bolivia and Ecuador, I'd love to see Mexico.  The stadium, the myth, the legend: the Azteca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The commentary on *Dr. Horrible's Sing-Along Blog* is itself a self-contained musical*Commentary! The Musical*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that Eric Carle was taught not to write to strangers until he was an adult, which would explain why he was a poor correspondent as a fourth-grader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Can we agree that duels are dumb and immature?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got hit by a line drive on the hip when pitching softball once.  Third baseman caught the ricochet for presumably the strangest way that batter had ever lined out.

Trivia question: what's the correct notation in the scorer's notebook for such a play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As will yours, moo-cow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He and his staff should find it easier there to secretly meet with Russian spies.

(Keeping the secret from the American press, that is.  The Chinese government, of course, will know.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  My point was that the increased cost for her security detail may only be partially related to the death threats, and may instead be more closely related to other considerations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long does each repair take in and of itself?

Also, how much time do you spend on "overhead", such as posting on Facebook, contacting potential clients, tracking your revenues in spreadsheets or wherever, etc.?

Once you've answered those questions, you'll have an idea of what you're making per hour *including overhead time*, which should let you know whether you're underselling yourself, and by how much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stickied comment would be equally as enormous as the self post at the top of a megathread, so it's a wash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if the first thing rising *isn't* just a headline with two sentences, nor clickbait?  What if [Politico writes 13 paragraphs about Nunes stepping down?](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/63syvz/nunes_to_step_aside_from_russia_probe/)

I understand that *sometimes* you want to make megathreads; why are megathreads your *only* solution to sweeping up articles?

You say "equalize all sources" as if it's always a good thing; it's not always a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A news story breaks.  The article that breaks that news story rises to the top of /r/politics and gets hundreds of comments, perhaps thousands of comments.  Simultaneously, other articles about that news story are appearing in /r/politics.  

The moderators of /r/politics want to sweep up those other articles; fair enough.  Why do they need to start a megathread to do this, hiding all of the hundreds of comments in the most popular article and starting the discussion all over?  Why not just put a stickied comment as the first comment of the most popular article, and keep it updated with the list of all the other articles that you're sweeping away?  You can sticky the most popular article itself in /r/politics, or not, as you wish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glittering prizes and endless compromises shatter the illusion of integrity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swore my allegiance to the Evil League of Evil, and my oaths are for life.  I will vote out no Evil League of Evil team until only Evil League of Evil teams are left.  I trust that Patriots fans feel the same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A note to Jamie:

bro do you even lift and invert commas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A U.S. official, speaking on condition of anonymity, said that she had received more threats than previous education secretaries.

Let me make it very clear that I utterly condemn threats against government officials.

I also think it is likely that the increased cost for her security detail is wrapped up with two other factors: the security risk in having a billionaire become a government official, and the additional peaceful protests that she has incurred by being wildly unqualified for her position.

Maybe -- stay with me here -- it isn't such a good idea to nominate wildly unqualified billionaires for Cabinet posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a list of those who will think less of Jared Kushner for concealing his meetings with Russians:

* most of the media

* much of Congress

* a majority of the American people

Here is a list of someone who definitely won't care:

* Donald Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's fun to vote out the Raiders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [For convenience, the link for voting out the Raiders.](https://goo.gl/forms/zoPpuxpQNwQx33Ms1)

I'm a little too young to truly despise the Raiders.  Steelers fans a little older than me remember 1972-1976: five straight seasons of the Steelers facing the Raiders in the playoffs.  But it's fun to vote out the Raiders nevertheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Pittsburgh Steelers**

1. [Post and comment in ELOE, 18 months ago](https://np.reddit.com/r/EvilLeagueOfEvil/comments/3nhppc/evil_chalice_excitement/cvo717i/)

2. [Post in /r/Steelers, 15 months ago](https://np.reddit.com/r/steelers/comments/3yetxq/im_far_from_home_and_went_looking_for_somewhere/)

3. [Post in /r/NFL, 17 months ago](https://np.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/3qs3rj/bill_austin_was_the_last_steelers_coach_not_to/)

I, /u/subject4211, of house /r/Steelers, swear my allegiance to the Evil League of Evil.  If my team is truly not one of the unholy 7, may the Football Gods curse my stupid non-evil team next season and until the end of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, the most he can do is drop him from the 2020 ticket, under the tenuous (at best) assumption that Trump is still president in 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. There isn't an "it's okay if you donate the money later" exception to the emoluments clause in the Constitution.

2. Even if donating money later were somehow acceptable, when China granted trademarks for Trump brands, they gave Trump emoluments that cannot simply be donated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an exception to Betteridge's Law of Headlines: after reading the article, the answer in this case appears to be "yes, he publicly revealed a lot of classified information." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely intelligence officials knew they were taking a bit of a gamble with the election results, but thought it was a good gamble.  If they could have gotten through the election and then carried out the investigation under a Clinton administration, the risk of playing politics would have been greatly reduced.  As it turned out, though, it wasn't a good gamble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3\.  To make your "3." stay a "3.", put a backslash ("\") before the period (".").  Like this: "3\\." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> David Duchovny, why won't you love Bree Sharp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trey Gowdy, who is assisting Conaway in the investigation, was **on the executive committee for Trump's transition team.**  It is wildly inappropriate for him to be involved in this probe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trey Gowdy was **on the executive committee for Trump's transition team.**  It is wildly inappropriate for him to be involved in this probe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -?  Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, we have this already.  It's called the [Green Card Through Investment.](https://www.uscis.gov/green-card/green-card-through-job/green-card-through-investment)  Invest $1,000,000 anywhere in the USA, or just $500,000 in a targeted employment area, and you and your spouse and your unmarried children under the age of 21 all get green cards.  Once you all have green cards, then it's just the usual waiting period and test to become citizens.

Congratulations, Rep. Rohrabacher (R-CA) and Trump, you just reinvented the wheel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This case still makes no sense to me.  Why do Giuliani and Mukasey believe that there's going to be a "diplomatic solution" to the case of an Iranian-Turkish dual national? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apology for poor english

when were you when rice job does

i was sat at home drinking horchata when trump ring

'rice job doe'

'no'

and you?????????????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game was [actually from 2015, and the Chargers won.](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/boxscores/201510040sdg.htm#all_pbp)  Notice that the game is in San Diego; the 2016 game was in Cleveland.  Notice that the "50" is in gold, as it was for the 50th Super Bowl season, 2015-2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, [anyone can check the play-by-play.](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/boxscores/201510040sdg.htm#all_pbp)  It was certainly 13-13 on 3rd   13 with 13:13 to go in the 3rd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check the center's hands: this photography was taken shortly after the snap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great, and Maine's adoption of ranked-choice voting last year was a promising step.  In the meantime, flawed system or not, we still gotta vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"Excellent!" I cried.*

*"Elementary," said he. "It is one of those instances where the reasoner can produce an effect which seems remarkable to his neighbour, because the latter has missed the one little point which is the basis of the deduction."*

-- "The Adventure of the Crooked Man" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would a Democrat winning the Georgia special election seat also cause panic?  A win seems more likely in the purple Atlanta suburbs than in deep-red Kansas.

Strangely enough, [Bannon is following the Georgia special election closely.](http://thehill.com/homenews/campaign/327018-bannon-closely-watching-ga-special-election-report) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likewise. By Friday the story will probably be how "Trump never met him" and "he only played a very limited role in the transition team" and how it's totally unfair of the lying media to try and use whatever he's accused of doing to smear the administration Bannon was never really a part of anyway...

/u/salec1, why did you plagiarize [this comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/63m8sv/bannon_removed_from_national_security_council/dfv7377/) by /u/absolutenobody?  Imitating Gorsuch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we post in both this thread and the other thread in which you promised this, are you going to give us $2,000 or only $1,000?  I just want to clarify this now, rather than when the time comes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The United States has not abandoned its commitment to human rights.

Unfortunately, the Trump administration has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There seems to have been a recent decision by some members of the press to redefine the word "filibuster" to mean "voting against cloture" exclusively.  I find this decision to be bizarre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems as if Merkley's total filibuster time was around 15 hours and 30 minutes, which appears to put him around sixth or seventh on the [all-time list](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-fix/wp/2013/03/06/measuring-rand-pauls-filibuster-against-history/), well ahead of Rand Paul's tenth place for a 12:52 filibuster.  The most recent filibuster longer than Merkley's was 23 hours and 30 minutes in 1986 by Senator Alphonse D'Amato (R-NY). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  The red is for denying a goal by deliberately handling.  If a goal is scored, there was no denial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You hold your nose, vote for the Democratic candidate for Senator, and then vote in all of the other elections that year; ideally, some of them will require less nose-holding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once had a cab driver in Columbus, Ohio who asked me to guess his nationality.  He made fun of me when I started guessing West African countries, because I apparently should have known that he looked East African.  He was mollified, though, when after that hint, it took only a few more guesses before I successfully identified that he was Eritrean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also what a real, honest-to-goodness filibuster looks like.  Votes against cloture are fine, but this is the real deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I told the other redditor, I don't have $1000 to spare, but I'll bet you reddit gold right here, right now that Donald J. Trump will not be president on January 19th, 2021. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disapproving of Congress sounds like a great reason to vote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't underestimate voter apathy.  I'm just a little personally mystified by it.  I've voted in every election, primary or general, presidential or midterm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> senatorClaghorn*That's a joke, ah say, that's a joke, son.*/senatorClaghorn

But seriously, psephology tells us that party identification is fluid.  As Trump's approval rating drops among the general population, a significant proportion of that drop will be reflected in fewer people self-identifying as Republican, not just in lower approval among Republicans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has enormous power over the Freedom Caucus.  If they don't do what he says, then when it comes time for 2018 Congresional elections, he can **endorse** them!  Imagine how quickly his abyssal approval rating will scuttle their reelection campaigns! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... the day Trump was elected to the presidency, he ensured that his eventual death, in prison or otherwise, would be front-page news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video buries the lede at the very end, but here it is:

* Sources report that Prince personally met Flynn and Trump during the transition.

* Sources report that Prince bragged about his closeness to Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Don't know what you got till it's ^almost gone     
Don't know what it is Obama did so wrong* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For your sake, I'm sorry that we didn't cross paths before the election, although for my sake, I'm glad.  I offered several times to bet reddit gold on the election results, and would have paid up.  Apparently, though, I made those offers to Russian bots or something, because no one ever took me up on my offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to go, /u/maltedwhiskeyshot, I can't believe I've never seen this before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's time, actually, for Wikipedians with vastly more experience than me to go through the Gorkas' pages carefully and edit them to be  unbiased and well-sourced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have $1000 to spare.  But I will bet you one month of reddit gold, right here, right now that Donald J. Trump will not be president on January 19th, 2021. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just here to get my $1000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usenet is, roughly speaking, decentralized reddit without upvotes (and is still around.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried to spoil as little as possible, but a very mild spoiler for an otherwise fantastic children's book follows.

The misconception that the Mona Lisa is painted on canvas is not limited to the grandparent poster; it was shared by Pat Hutchins, author of *The Mona Lisa Mystery* (The Bodley Head, 1981). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah.  This is not the first result of its kind.  In 2012, the full USWNT scrimmaged the U-17 USMNT, and the boys won 8-2.  That  USWNT went on to win six of six matches in the UK, en route to the gold medal in the London Olympics.

There's an endearing story from Bruce Arena's first stint managing the national (men's) team.  The USWNT had just won the 1999 Women's World Cup, and some clueless general sports journalist asked Arena what he thought the men's team's chances would be in a match against the women's team.  Arena apparently said, "Well, I hope we could give them a good game." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usenet forever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making a list of particularly notable Turing Award winners is, as you imply, a bit redundant, because all Turing Award winners are big names with huge accomplishments.

That said, while I can restrain myself from highlighting the various giants of artificial intelligence, I can't avoid a special mention of Ken Thompson and Dennis Ritchie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Well-deserved" is an understatement.  My reaction was "oh, they hadn't given him the Turing Award in some past year already?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mona Lisa has **certainly not** been "rolled up and brought all over Italy".  It's painted on wood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey, Russia, you're welcome!" -- Rex Tillerson, probably </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than just the headline?!  But this is reddit!

Seriously, though, it is worth reading this article to discover that Kellyanne Conway, if anyone still cares about her, also praised Cernovich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For convenience:

* Sk-gorka's [contributions page on Wikipedia,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Special:Contributions/Sk-gorka) that is, history of edits by that username.

* Sk-gorka's [user talk page on Wikipedia,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/User_talk:Sk-gorka) in which the conflict of interest is called out, before Sk-gorka forges on to edit the Sebastian Gorka page some more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're going to need to narrow it down for us in the headline, TheHill.   A "writer who pushed 'Pizzagate' conspiracy theory" could be anyone from Mike Cernovich to Michael Flynn Jr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Devin Nunes: The House Will Be Feckless in Russia Investigation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a serious question, not a rhetorical one: How likely is it that Trump's closeness with Sissi is related to Bannon's sweetheart Breitbart rental deal with an Egyptian politician? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take "members of the Trump administration resigning in disgrace" for $800, Alex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first rule of the scary devil monastery is... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Senate Intelligence forges ahead with their hearings

* House Intelligence gets left in the dust </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't spell es**p**ion**age** without Page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superuser superidiot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get a Pulitzer!  You get a Pulitzer!  You get a Pulitzer!  You get a Pulitzer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, to test how far an American citizen can go before actually getting prosecuted and sent to prison for violating the Logan Act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  The Congressional Review Act bypasses the filibuster for review of recent federal regulations.  That was the procedure used for S.J.Res. 34 in this Congress, disapproving of the FCC rule that protected ISP customers' privacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, from context, SES is socioeconomic status. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the health care bill that he's discussing in the context of this article.  Let's hope he keeps losing that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A decade or so ago, I saw a video online of a speech you gave at an atheists' conference in which, inter alia, you noted that the proportion of atheists was unusually low among mathematicians.  Do you think mathematicians might be more likely to understand Gdel's second incompleteness theorem, and therefore more likely to lean toward agnosticism instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, that clip is the only fragment of *American Dad* that I personally have ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, here's the latest release of evidence everyone should see: the then-National Security Advisor of the USA, Michael Flynn, [listing thirty sources of compensation on a disclosure form, but somehow omitting any disclosure of Russian propagandist compensation.](https://www.dropbox.com/s/ao33b0bfim14awi/Flynn%2C%20Michael%202-11-17.pdf?dl=0)  News broke yesterday that he had actually also been compensated by Russian propagandists.  Oops.

Now, this is not yet a "smoking gun" for the Trump administration, and neither is any of the other evidence that has come out so far.  That's why no Russian-collusion impeachment trial has started yet.  But when you ask yourself "which explanation is more likely: that the Trump administration has colluded with Russia and is trying to cover it up, or that this is all much ado about nothing?"... I think the answer is clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
