<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2635</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 23:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adulting can be confusing! But at least I know what I don't know, and when to ask for advice. Thanks for helping me make sense off this.

Years back, he had a seizure of some sort. We were close to the hospital so I take him to the ER to get him checked out I knew the hospital was in network, but for some reason the doctors wasn't. And some of the tests were paid for and some only partially covered.

The whole thing was a mess, and only gave us a "we dunno what caused it."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 23:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always feel better when I have a backup plan, so I appreciate your help! 

When I ask the office about correcting the information, is that the way I phrase it? That I would like them to resubmit with the doctor he had an appointment with, since he's in network? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 23:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is really helpful! It sounds like there's a chance to get this fixed. It's a shame, too. The PA was great. But I'll give them a call and try to approach it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having problems navigating denied claims in Maryland (GEHA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 22:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Edit: sorry, I meant to put "medical" in the title**

Some time ago, I took my son to the doctor. It was a general checkup, but there were some minor concerns we made sure to address with the doctor.

Problem was the doctor wasn't available for the appointment. They suggested I see the PA and assured me he was in the same network.

Now a month the later I get a bill saying GEHA denied the claim. They say the PA wasn't actually on the plan and that the office billed the visit as a medical... uh... thing... a problem type of visit, rather than a routine checkup. 

The bill is for the deductable, but even that amount was unexpected since it would have otherwise been covered completely. Am I SOL?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 16:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... OPSEC success? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse. Just talking about it, you now have GonoSyphaHerpes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for pointing me in the right direction! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see this sub active again, and would like to heartily support /u/kalez238's request. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Katie_Pornhub should give a stern lashing to the quality control team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 17:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that means a lot to me!

We're still working with the software. I'm letting him do the bulk of it, since he enjoys solving problems. He's really excited to get it working and start recording Five Nights at Freddy's songs, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 13:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> biker rally tit pics

Ah, yes. The very *definition* of good taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 15:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't mind the question, do you still have a relationship with your mum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good tool/technique for building a list based on selections? [X-Post /r/web_programming] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 02:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a very long list that's broken into different categories. I'm trying to find a way to let the user select the categories they want and end up with a list based on their selections.

I'm doing this in wordpress, but I'm really not sure where to start. I'm also pretty new to design/programming. Are there any tools, techniques, or plugins that I could use to make this work?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good tool/technique for building a list based on selections? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 02:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a very long list that's broken into different categories. I'm trying to find a way to let the user select the categories they want and end up with a list based on their selections. 

I'm doing this in wordpress, but I'm really not sure where to start. I'm also pretty new to design/programming. Are there any tools, techniques, or plugins that I could use to make this work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 02:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great advice. He was in strings class last year (5th grade) and will be in an IB program next year, which seems to have a strong music program. I loved music when I was his age, but I hated math so much that I held myself back a bit in that regard. 

Did you keep with it? Music, I mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 02:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great advice, and thanks for taking the time to make me a little smarter! I'll definitely check out reaper, but either way it sounds like I should be able to get him up and running tonight; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 01:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll be thrilled :)

But that sounds like a great way to start, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 01:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a relief, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 01:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks! So I *don't* need any additional hardware to get him started? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got my son a midiman keystation 61. Not sure what to do next. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 01:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son (11) wants to make music, so it seemed like fate when I found a midiman keystation 61 at a thrift store. Problem is, we're not quite sure what to do with it. 

I found some videos online, and it seems like I should be able to plug straight into the computer via USB and control the software (per the manual, we're trying Ableton Live 9 Lite). But in the manual [online](http://kb.inmusicbrands.com/media/files/Keystation%2061%20-%20User%20Guide%20-%20v1_1.pdf), it looks like I might need a sound module to do... something. 

Any advice on how to get started with this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! You have whole potato? Joke is funny, but all are sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 19:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 19:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darn. Is there a way to ask for help here without violating this rule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrest details on my mother-in-law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 14:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (I think he was joking) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 14:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the boss... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, that came across wrong. I was thinking that taking that page off was a strong indication that the site wasn't very effective. But if it's still there, that kills my theory lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 13:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you still have that deed, out of curiosity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 04:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Or, rather, has been for a while. It just means they lack government services that they may need, so sometimes the private sector fills in the gap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google invested a good chunk of change into your company. Are you aware of any plans to integrate your tech into their current offerings (gmail, for example)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 06:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'd say that I'm as dead as a doornail, but why's it gotta be a doornail? It's because that's the only nail that it makes sense to be dead as. 'hey, you're dead. yeah, as a... carpet! Nail.' or maybe a fingernail instead. That would work, because at least a fingernail used to be alive. So I'm as dead as a fingernail. I got bit off by life and spit. Owt." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoilers! I haven't gotten that far, yet 

(Kidding) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who you then eat... You monster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did the adults react after your rescue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 13:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that feel.

I moderate /r/MrRogersNeighborhood. Only 77 neighbors, but I love 'em all.

Edit: 78! Hello, new neighbor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 18:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (just my layman, intro to religion class understanding here)

There's actually a lot going on there. 

First is a translation issue. The greek word that we interpret as 'fulfill' is pleroo, which can mean both 'to complete or accomplish' OR 'to make full' or 'fill up.' So he was either saying that he came to complete the law or to make them more full. I suppose I can only draw inferences as to the context. I am not a ~~rapper~~ scholar.

The second piece is what was meant by "the law." In Matthew 5, Jesus (a Jewish man) was speaking to a Jewish audience. As such, he wouldn't clarify what he meant by the law. They would all know that he was referring to the law of moses. That is, the commandments that moses brought down from the mountain. Not ten, there were a bunch of those things. So he was saying that nothing of *that* law would disappear until the end of time. 

Remember that a lot of the most disputed rules in the old testament came from Leviticus, which means literally "for the Levites." It was a book written for the priests of levi to tell them what is expected of them. Jesus would not be telling that particular audience that he is completing / making more full the rules for the priests of levi, particularly as he was not a priest of levi.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you dropped a nugget of your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISIS makes a great deal of it's funding from private donations. The more they're in the news and forefront of the world's attention, the more relevant and appealing they are to wealthy sympathizers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 15:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You keep posting this. We've seen it. Do you have anything else to add? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 12:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 07:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's the one about a clown and kids going on an adventure in the sewers. What kid wouldn't live that?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 05:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't come across as mean at all! 

It's actually a very fair point, and I completely agree. He has been pursuing things through his school and local resources, but just not a redditor (or so he claims). In that sense, taking into account some of my reddit activities, he might be the mature one, lol.

I really appreciate the advice and thoughts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 04:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope she had a good time swimming, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 00:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell us it got better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 21:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, we'll look into that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 00:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 16:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! That's what redditing after a few drinks'll do to ya. 

Thanks for the assist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 16:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an interesting idea! I'll look into that. Right now, I just have two landing pages: 

https://www.discreetwriters.com/writers

and 

https://www.discreetwriters.com/clients

I just finished the second one about ten minutes ago, so I'm not sure about it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 14:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's really good, buuuuuuut..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 14:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [They're older](https://i.ytimg.com/vi/4HJ-Y8YTo8Q/maxresdefault.jpg), but you can find some from the 80s and 90s at the [Malware Museum](https://archive.org/details/malwaremuseum) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 05:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aaaaaaaaaaaaaaay Macarena! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 04:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished [my website](discreetwriters.com) and added a landing page to attract writers to the service. Now I'm up to about 50 writers!

Now I need to figure out how to attract the clients... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 22:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Musical BBQ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 22:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The first article is not gentle](https://photographyisnotacrime.com/2016/06/southern-california-woman-steals-drone-then-lies-about-it-exposed-by-drones-camera/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 18:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great idea, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 18:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's getting there! I have about 40 writers on board already (some of them from here!). Now I'm trying to attract the clients to keep them busy and paid. It's exciting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 18:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the pleasure of talking to Ian about his book and the information in it, and I highly recommend taking him up in this offer. He gave me some great information that really helped me move in the right direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mister Rogers Remixed: Garden of Your Mind - PBS Digital Studios </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 16:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 04:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant quote by a great man](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/Cj4IA_qWgAIjwIe.jpg:large) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 02:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! 

If you decide to try it out, send me your username so I can add a $10 credit to your account. You know, so you can see if it works for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 01:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were ever looking for more content, would you consider supporting a fellow redditor? I just launched discreetwriters.com to match people like you with ghostwriters, who will bid for the jobs. 

The only problem is that I don't have any actual customers yet :( 

Maybe my ghostwriters could give you an even better value? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Bird Sings at Jim Henson's Memorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 14:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theme from Barbara Broadcast (1977 porn. Later used as people's court theme) - Alan Tew </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 18:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 15:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! Sure as hell beats Barstow, CA though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 22:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://bfy.tw/15OW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's just keep those two things separate, shall we? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 19:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 21:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 21:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moms, right?

I remember being a kid and barely noticing that our coffee table had disappeared. I didn't care, though, because we were going to McDonald's! 

We hardly ever went there, so it was such a treat. My sister and I ate as much as we wanted and played for hours on the play place. My mom, of course, at nothing.

I didn't realize until much later that she had sold the coffee table to take us to McDonald's. All so we could eat and have fun.

I love my mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 21:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a time and a place to be edgy. This isn't either one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really admirable attitude. Seriously- the world needs teachers for those of us that want to learn.

"I hope you're proud of yourself for the times you've said 'yes,' when all it meant was extra work for you and was seemingly helpful only to somebody else."
  -Fred Rogers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 01:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'm sure I'll learn a lot. I really appreciate your time and help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm really sorry to bother you. I'm looking up grid systems as they relate to design, but I'm having a little bit of trouble finding the right  info. Could you please point me in the right direction or give me a search term hint? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 00:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh. I can pencil you in for now, but there's a pretty long waiting list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 23:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It didn't sound condescending at all! Quite frankly, there's nothing worse than rejecting good advice because of pride. And if someone takes the time to tell me what I'm doing wrong, I always appreciate it!

~~Do you have any advice on which font to use? I always have (even more) trouble with that part.~~ Disregard, I missed that part. 

Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 23:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that's very helpful! I'll do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 22:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it, pal. You're on the list, too.

Anyone else want to go on the list? I can do this aaaaaaalllll day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 22:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this comment's going to seem *reeeeal* funny next time you fly. You just made their "third knuckle" list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Flyer] DiscreetWriters.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 18:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The target audience that I had in mind was University Students. But I was hoping to create something that could apply to different audiences as well. 

I know it's not great, but what to you think about this? 
http://i.imgur.com/hXsW34r.jpg

I'd appreciate any advice or feedback!

Edit: Fixed those pull tabs: http://i.imgur.com/oih6Nvt.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 22:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO: Information Management Officer, for those OOTL
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 19:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah! I was putting the href in the IMG class part. Thank you so much, that worked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 18:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I think I used the wrong term. I mean where do I add the URL that people will go to when clicking on the icon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 18:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! 

I'm so happy that you and your family had a special time! I remember being a child and wishing I could visit the neighborhood. Isn't it great that we actually can? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Rogers Guest Appearance on Dr. Quinn, Medicine Woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One important thing to note: Don Chance says that his reference to Mr. Rogers was [only a metaphor](http://thinkprogress.org/politics/2007/07/07/14586/rogers-retraction/) and he enjoys the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 35 Facts About Mr. Fred Rogers - mental_floss on YouTube (Ep.2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mister Rogers Explained To Modern Kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extreme inconvenience

Don't flatter yourself, KFC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about using a specific template </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 16:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, /r/web_design. I only know basic html and css, so I'm having a little bit of trouble with this template I'm trying to use. How do I add an actual target to this snippet?

        div class="container"
            div id="social" class="social" data-lead-id="social"
                a class="facebook" data-lead-id="facebook"img class="img-responsive" src="img/facebook.png" alt=""/a
                a class="twitter" data-lead-id="twitter"img class="img-responsive" src="img/twitter.png" alt=""/a
                a class="google" data-lead-id="google"img class="img-responsive" src="img/google.png" alt=""/a
                a class="download" data-lead-id="download"img class="img-responsive" src="img/download.png" alt=""/a
            /div    

I'm having the same problem with this part, but I assume the solution would be the same. 

    a class="btn btn-inline" data-lead-id="header-btn"TEXT/a

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 13:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which of course introduces the sequel: The Tower's Balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think toyota might disagree, when their profits dropped 10% after the recall issues some years back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 14:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Shit, I forgot I'm getting married today!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 05:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or one huge box. It's a bitch to move, but you only have to do it once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 05:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, look, it's this argument again.

Sorry, but the "threat" of invasive rock species is all hype. It's actually quite simple: you take the rock's natural predator from it's native environment and bring it to the new territory. 

In short order, the invasive rock will be eradicated and the balance will be restored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 05:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you please clarify or give an example of what you're referring to? Because I'm having a little bit of trouble visualizing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'm getting ready for the soft launch, so I hope you'll bear with me while I fine tune things a little bit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 04:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! It would be perfect for something like this. 

There's the guaranteed discretion element, where your chosen writer has already signed an NDA agreeing not to disclose their connection with your site. That's important to some folks- I know it is to me. 

But regarding your question, DiscreetWriters works on a bidding system. That means that the writers would submit bids within the range you've set (if you chose to specify one), and you can choose the one that best fits your budget. 

Honestly, it's possible to get content written on the cheap. But of course you get what you pay for. Myself, I fell into that trap and once thought I was getting a great deal when I paid $5 for 500 words. They had all the right keywords stuffed in there, but not much else, lol!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problem installing Asgaros Forum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 03:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to install Asgaros Forum using the built-in plugin installer. I'm following the instructions, [here](https://github.com/Asgaros/asgaros-forum/blob/master/readme.txt). 

They say to use the shortcode [Forum]. Unfortunately, when I do it turns out [like this](https://www.discreetwriters.com/forum/). Somehow, I don't think that's what it's supposed to look like. 

Anyone seen this before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 03:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can give you gold! I think that might be a little more valuable in the foreseeable future, lol :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 01:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course! I assume you take future equity or startup stock? If not, I have a pretty decent beanie baby collection. Some of them even still have the tags! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 01:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. It really seems so simple, but so perfect for the audience. I really can't believe I didn't think of doing that. Really great addition! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 01:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. You rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 01:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a hell of a lot better than what I came up with! At least the one you made has some meaning behind it, rather than my "uhhhh... I guess I'll just italicize one of the words!" 

Thanks, I really appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 01:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't show up in the preview if you're using res. That's because it's white on a transparent background. Yeah... I told you it was terrible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] My logo is terrible. Can you help me make it better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 00:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The logo is just one of the problems with my site: https://www.discreetwriters.com/. 

[Direct link to the logo](https://www.discreetwriters.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/06/logo.png)

But it doesn't really represent the site. It doesn't seem, I don't know, discreet. What can I do to make it better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thank you! Hopefully it won't be too long, lol (I'm not the best at wordpress). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really interesting, and makes a lot of sense.

It's funny, isn't it? It can be so easy to get tunnel vision and assume that visitors will use the site the way you want them to. But them someone comes along with a different perspective, and it makes things much more clear. Thanks, I really appreciate that. 

Would it be okay if I sent you a message when I change the layout around and see what you think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 21:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, congratulations on your successes. I'm working on my second personal novel, with another pair ghostwritten for others. I guess I enjoy the former more than the latter!

Thanks for the feedback, and you're right on all counts. 

I think the logo is pretty weak. It doesn't feel very professional.

I'll need to see what I can do to improve the logo, as well as other cosmetic and layout changes. 

Why are "all categories" and "all posted projects" separate?

I don't recall why I had those separated... hmmm, I should probably know that. I'll add that to my todo list. 

Your Facebook link in the footer is broken.

Thanks for the catch on facebook. It was active, but I think they suspended my account for inactivity. 

How do reviews work on your site? Pretty standard to other freelance gig sites?

Yes- reviews work like any other site, or at least the ones you and I probably use. I'm thinking about making reviews mandatory and double-blind once I can find and pay a good coder to do that. 

And a question that I always get asked by my clients, how is the client's privacy valued/assured? 

That's exactly what this site is trying to answer. Each writer has a signed NDA (as you may have seen; thanks for the signup, by the way!), which is essentially their promise to not reveal the names or nature of their clients. Unfortunately, that's only as enforceable as any other NDA. We make it free (whereas other sites make the client pay extra for one), so at least the client can be assured that there's one on file. 

But the real reason that the client can feel that their privacy is ensured is that they can remain completely anonymous to the writers. They don't need to provide a real name and the writer can't even see their email address. Assuming all communication is made via the site, the writer shouldn't be able to reveal the client's information even if they wanted to. Of course that does assume some amount of discretion in the information provided by the client. 

It's something that I believe strongly in. I want to help writers find another avenue for work, and I want to help people get the work done that they need. I really hope I don't let you down :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see where you're coming from. It is a pretty basic/common theme, now that you mention it. 

The *idea* (for what that's worth) behind the search bar is that it's a quick way to start the hiring process. The bar is supposed to be asking people "what do you want done?" They would answer, which is piped over to the new project page. So someone might say, "write me a vogon poem" and BAM! They're on the project page and only a few clicks away from being done. 

But that's the way it looked in my head. Sounds like I may have missed the mark. 

Thanks for the advice and feedback. I'll play around with the layout and appearance and see if I can improve it based on your suggestions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! And I definitely agree that it's going to be challenging. But fortunately I can afford to take the time to nurture it. 

I hope to be able to give you good news in a few months! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, WOW. I thought I deleted the test accounts. Thanks for catching that- I didn't. 

Okay, now that's out of the way. Thank you so much, this is all great advice. And it really gives me a lot to consider. I know you're busy, so I'll just convey my sincere gratitude for your time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! I got the same thing. They said that they saw my post in /r/smallbusiness and they thought I might "benefit from their services." 

They're referring to the post in smallbusiness, where I was talking about the upcoming launch of my own freelance-type website. 

I replied, "Just so I understand, are you inviting me to become a customer of a site that completes with the one I'm building?" But I didn't get a reply and the account was banned. Too bad, I would have liked to see what they had to say.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello! You gave such great advice to /u/karsoa. Would you mind taking a look at my site as well? www.discreetwriters.com

I appreciate any feedback or advice you may have! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 20:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've finally worked the bugs out of my freelance marketplace, and I'm about ready to do a soft launch. I'd really appreciate some feedback before I do:

www.discreetwriters.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 12:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He would be proud](http://i.imgur.com/6Z5asA7.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 03:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Tomorrow Wendy- Concrete Blonde](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NZ_elh12SFs)

A very dear friend committed suicide when I was in high school. Something about this song, I don't know, made me feel a little better somehow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 19:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/flipping is selling used printer ink and old jeans, and somehow making a killing on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 17:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naw, just a big fan of wordplay and punctuation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 16:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/weedful_things says "Jesus people," as an exclamation. But he forgets a comma that would make that clear (as in, "Jesus, people!"). So /u/umopaplsdnwl takes the phrase literally and humorously reads it as "Jesus people," which are often (but not always) Christians (followers of Jesus).

Or, to put it simply, it's "Jesus, people" versus "Jesus people." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 16:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. [Reference](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/cmwov/hey_reddit_what_tattoos_do_you_have/c0tpyls)

Dear God, has it been five years already? What am I doing with my life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 15:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are afraid of the unknown, and clowns are unknown. They're wearing makeup, so some see them not as human but as gross caricatures of what a human might look like. 

The horror genre, doing what it is meant to do, took that natural discomfort and turned it into a trope. It's just like how our natural fear of the dark turned into countless scary movies or how our fear of death turned into zombie movies. Yes, I know I'm oversimplifying things, but it's pretty close. 

That's why the clowns in horror (and people's fears) are normally [whiteface](http://www.allaboutclowns.com/images/bozo.jpg) clowns. They're harder to read, if that's what you're looking for. Examples include Pennywise, Gacy and others. But the [Auguste](http://www.allaboutclowns.com/images/knute_auguste.jpg), [Hobo](http://paragondesignonline.com/images/shinbone_the_clown-2.jpg) and other character clowns (like rodeo clowns) are generally accepted. Or at least not feared. 

I was raised with a connection to the circus. I don't tell many people (except for countless strangers, apparently), but my grandfather was a professional circus clown. He traveled the country with different circuses. He loved entertaining the children the most- they all did. I was taught (and shown) that clowns are supposed to be loving, and loving people are those that are best fit for the nose. 

He told me once about a friend of his. He was a stiltwalker clown- one of the ones that walk around on stilts. They were doing a clown show for the children there, and everyone was having a wonderful time. The thing with stiltwalking is that there are certain risks involved, but theres safety measures in place to protect the clown and the audience. 

If you ever see a clown on stilts, youll see (or should see) another person (normally a clown) nearby at all times. That person has one job: to keep people away from the legs. Remember that scene in Star Wars when they bring down the Imperial Walker? Thats generally undesirable for the clown. But if that fails, the clown has practiced falling time and time again. They know how to fall without serious injury, so its as safe as could be. 

After a long day in the sun, people get tired. One little boy slipped past the handler. He just wanted to give the tall clown a big hug, and he wrapped his arms around the stilts. Or, as far as he knew, the legs. No one could react in time- the stiltwalker was coming down. But, of course, they know how to fall. They know how to save themselves in such a situation. 

Unfortunately, in this case, the proper way to fall would bring the clown down on a group of small children. The weight of an adult falling from such a height on tiny, fragile bodies would hurt them at best. Kill one or more, at worst. According to those watching, the falling clown didnt even hesitate. He fell the *wrong* way, landing on his head and neck. The other clowns did what they could to play it off as a silly accident, but they all knew. 

He was conscious long enough to pretend that he was okay. The happy little boy never knew that clown died later that night. All because he made a split-second decision to put himself at risk instead of the children that loved him. According to my grandfather, they all would have done the same thing. Because a clown is love, and love would never hurt a child. 

My grandfather is too old to perform now. He hasnt in years. He takes care of my grandmother, whose health is failing. But Ill always remember how he came alive when he put on his costume. He was a different man then. He wasnt Jack or Grandpa. He was Patrick the Clown. He would show me the cage that had the Worlds Silliest Monkey (a mirror behind a screen) and balance a huge stack of plates (only to drop them! But its okay, they were all connected by string). He will never perform again. 

I have his costume now. A real clown costume, with a beaver skin wig and original Vans shoes (yes, they used to make clown shoes). It needs cleaning and maybe a little bit of tailoring, but its been worn by three generations of my family. 

For me, I dont plan to join the circus. I have a job and a family- I dont have the time. But theres a childrens wing of my local hospital. If a clown is love, they could use a clown. Did you know that hospitals have [clowns that come in to entertain ill (sometimes terminal) children?]( https://erlhelathcomm.files.wordpress.com/2012/02/pr_clown-visit-017-b.jpg). There are hospital clown care programs in every state in Australia, New Zealand, the USA, Canada, Israel and all over Europe. According to Wikipedia:

 Clown Doctors use techniques such as magic, music, storytelling and other clowning skills to empower children with doses of fun that help them deal with the range of emotions they may experience while in hospital: fear, anxiety, loneliness, boredom.

The healing power of humor and laughter combats stress, reduces pain by releasing endorphins (the body's natural painkiller), boosts the immune system by increasing the level of T cells   lowering serum cortisol levels, helps promote a positive outlook, helps people to cope with difficult situations and helps to create bonds and therefore support between people, all of which aids the healing process.

So, yeah, Id like to be a part of that.

Clowns arent scary. They dont hurt people. Ive never met a clown (and Ive met so many!) that didnt legitimately care about every child or adult that they met. They only want to make you laugh and forget about your troubles for a little while. So if you meet a clown and he or she squirts you in the face with a bottle of seltzer, thats their way of saying, I love you. 

Not to plug, but my grandfather wrote a fictionalized historical novel about his experiences. Heres [an excerpt]( http://assets.booklocker.com/pdfs/1664s.pdf) that talks about his decision to become a clown. 

Edit: another story. I used to read my grandfather's clown trade magazines (yes! There is such a thing. Apparently the decision to go color caused quite a bit of controversy in the community). I remember a story about a hospital clown. I never met this clown, so I can't vouch for his story. But it aligns to what I know about those that pursue the calling.

This was a hardcore hospital clown; he used to visit the cancer ward. I couldn't imagine how emotionally taxing that would be, seeing so many children so ill. But he did it every week, and they all knew they could count on him to be there for him. 

Those children don't have many choices in their life. They didn't choose to be ill, and they can't choose what happens to them on a daily basis. They can't decide not to have another shot or another round of chemo. They can't say know when the doctor wants to come in or the nurse needs to wake them up for medicine. But he gave them a choice- sometimes the only choice they had. They could choose if he came into the room or not. They could choose what to talk about (not just their illness or symptoms, unless they wanted to). They could choose what balloon animal he made or even how long they spent together. They deserved to have choices, so at least he could give them that. 

One day, a child made the choice that he didn't want to see this clown. That's okay, he smiled and waved and gave a small toy to the mother for the child. And he went on to other rooms and other children. Some time later, the mother found him in the hallway and said that her son had changed his mind, and could he please see him if he had the time. He probably wasn't ever going to leave the hospital, and his prognosis was very grim. He was, to be blunt, there to die. Could he please, she asked, spend just a few minutes with him before he left?

A clown always has the time. 

He went in to see the little boy. He looked so small in the big bed. He had tubes in his arms and sensors on his chest. He was clearly very ill. But he smiled so wide when the clown came in! And for the first time in a while, he laughed while the clown danced and joked. It was a good day. A welcome distraction from his illness. 

He asked if he could hug the clown, but the equipment and the bed made that difficult. So the mother found a nurse who helped them arrange the tubes and wires, so the little boy could sit on his new friend's lap. He sat there for a long time, and the clown let him stay for as long as he wanted. He knew that the little boy was very, very ill, and this may be one of the last memories that he had. When he fell asleep, the clown let him stay. He needed the rest.

That's where he died. On the clown's lap. He was very sick. 

The clown knew that the child was dead. The mother knew it, too. But the other children that could see them didn't know. There was an unspoken agreement between the mother and the clown. If the doctors and nurses knew what had happened, they didn't interfere. It was a very serious thing in that ward when a child died, and the last thing anyone wanted to do was to traumatize the other children that were fighting for their own lives. So he held the child for just a little bit longer, put him back on the bed, and allowed the medical staff to do what they needed to do. 

He didn't cry until he was outside, away from the children. Later, he heard from the grieving mother. She took some small comfort in knowing that her child didn't die in a hospital bed, but in the arms of someone that loved him. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 14:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two are dead. One is blind and insane. 

So... Quite a while? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 23:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the feeling I'll regret this, but... link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 15:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. Not a very good one, either. No subtlety. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was trying to figure out what to do for lunch today. I didn't want to do McDonald's because I'm trying to eat healthy.

Shit. This really puts my "problems" in perspective. It's good to remember what's going on in the world sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 04:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much dawg. What's up with you?

Wait. Shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 20:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For an organization that size, if it can't survive without the CEO for a few weeks then something's terribly wrong. I would imagine he names someone (or multiple people) to run things in his absence. And if he doesn't have anyone competent that can run the show, then the company can only live as long as he does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 12:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except they're not military personnel. Legally and technically they're an insurgency. Unless you're talking about people forced to commit suicide attacks, as in the hypothetical you were responding to. What would you call those people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 16:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he really did buy a replacement belt before the accusation was made, and if he can prove it, that would certainly help validate his story  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 03:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe they rubbed off on her

They're not supposed to do that. That gets them a sad face sticker for the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 23:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty big part of their school curriculum. Pretty much all of groep 1 through groep 5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 21:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really comes down to evidence, and testimony is evidence. Two people telling the same story is stronger evidence than one person (the accused, who has a motive) saying something different. 

I'm not saying he did it, or even that the evidence presented should have been enough for a conviction, but it's what was given to the jury. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 21:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 21:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, that's his answer to everything. On the other hand, it works more often than you'd expect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most interesting true story from your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get a month of free reddit gold, so there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 17:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like we're about to have an aww-locaust.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 16:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard she got a couple new ones, though, so it's cool. It's the transitive property of cat ownership. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 14:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, exactly. It's what happens when a corporation tries to be "hip". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A security firm was giving out custom CAH decks at a conference. It's about what you'd expect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 03:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 22:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Wow, people sure want my fagas straps today... What? Why do people ways snicker when o say that?"

edit: forgot an 's' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 21:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to brag about your full range of motion, you smug bastard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 13:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ([We're not really scientists](http://i.imgur.com/EUTZcdn.mp4)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 17:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell yeah! If he's with in driving distance,  I'd totally RSVP that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both. You're arroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What "Street smarts" get you by in your city/country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 18:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 00:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On an unrelated note, I really like your artwork. I'm not really someone that "gets" most art, but I know when I like something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 00:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I viewed it on my phone, and your mobile site looks great. It's clean with enough context (your artwork) to draw me in but not so much that it looks cluttered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 23:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I missed it, but as a user I'd  like to know what makes your parking experts... Well, experts. If I understand correctly, either way I'm paying money, so I (as a hypothetical user) would like to feel confident with my odds of winning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 23:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I'm a little bit nervous because I JUST finished working out some of the bugs (specifically PayPal integration). But I'd really appreciate any thoughts, feedback or sign ups for [DiscreetWriters](HTTP://www.discreetwriters.com).

Now I'm off to give back a bit and sign up for some of the great services here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 19:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that would imply that you're the one enjoying the meal. If your friend asks you for a dinner recommendation and you suggest the steak, there's not much you can say when they choose pancakes.

That being said, I prefer steak. And boaty mcboatface. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 19:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Submarine" is the shortening of the original name, submarine boat. Naval tradition still uses the term boat to refer to submarines. So it's technically correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 19:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He doesn't look like he would care all that much](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/e/eb/Sub-Mariner1968n1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not all passengers are assigned a seat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were there any repercussions for Captain Lawrence Chambers for his decision to push the aircraft overboard in Operation Frequent Wind? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 00:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that he believed he would be court marshaled when he gave the order to push several aircraft overboard to allow the South Vietnamese Major and his family to land, but clearly he wasn't. But we're there any repercussions for his decision? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 00:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, in a very literal sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 00:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Image posted a year ago...

For those curious, here's the original post: https://reddit.com/r/funny/comments/348b31/was_pretty_stoned_last_night_i_wonder_why_i_didnt/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 16:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the value of the home was roughly the same as the amount she owed, the amount she spent on the gutters probably wouldn't have made too much of a dent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 16:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did it end up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 01:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's normally recorded for posterity in /r/thathappened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/yarTiE9.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 21:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amazing thing is that there's room for so many of us back there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
