<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3414</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you follow your head, your heart, or your gut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 00:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to cut a long story short. 
Recently started dating a new guy (we are doing long distance, and I see him on the weekend), when I was at his house this weekend I noticed something was a bit off, and it clicked that a few of his paintings were missing. I asked him about it, and he told me his ex came and picked them up Tuesday (I noticed they were gone Sunday), he didnt mention to me that she had gone around to pick them up, and so I asked him about it, and he kept trying to avoid the conversation. 
This isnt the first time the there has been something with his ex, once again, long story short. I was at his friends first birthday, when all the boys got drunk as anything, and I was left with the girls (including his ex), this was my first time meeting them all, and to say it was awkward was the least. I was left with her for 7 hours. She ended up talking to me about her mum and their problems. At the end of the night when i'd had enough, and couldnt hold myself together, I asked to leave and we spoke about it in the car, to which he said he didnt know she was going, but she had told me that night, she'd messaged him saying she was going. 
I dont want to get in to deep with this guy if he is still talking to his ex. 
My head says give it a bit longer and see what happens, my heart says I really really like him, but my gut is saying im going to get really hurt. 
HELP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 06:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually really glad I read your comment. 
Having a bit of a shit time myself and all I want to do is go to bed, damn well knowing it wont fix anything. 
Might go for a run to take my mind of this when I get home.
Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 02:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god you look stunning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 07:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a shame, but their music lives on!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 06:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of these guys until I saw your comment.
So happy I did, they are amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 02:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually not even close to what you think its doing.
In the picture the brushes are upside down and handing apart as they've just been cleaned. By hanging them upside it lets all the excess water drip off and keep the brushes in the natural shape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 01:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah see I am the same, all I think about is food!
Did you have a coffee or something like that when you wake up to give you a bit of energy, or do you find that your body adjusted to that? 
I think im going to start this periodic fasting, it sounds right up my alley!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 08:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow!
I'm actually really interested in this now. So, I usually have my lunch at 1pm, and then dinner around 6-7pm, would those times be okay? 
Did you struggle with the huge portions sizes at first? And also, did you allow your self treats here and there?
Sorry for all the questions!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 07:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU LOOK AMAZING!
Like my god. 
I read some of the comments and noticed you only ate two meals to start off with. Do you mind If I ask in more details what meals you were eating (breakfast/lunch/dinner), and what kind of foods were in that meal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 08:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the first album you have an Anastasia dipbrow in the 3rd photo, can you tell me what colour it is and how much, as its not listed :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 02:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you get this?
I need one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 02:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you do any exercise or was it just all eating?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 03:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing! Super jealous! 
What is your food intake like? also how long between each photo? :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 03:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dayumn!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 08:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the feeling.
My 'pill' makes me not even want sex. 
Sometimes I just initiate things so my partner thinks im actually interested when really, I couldnt give two fucks about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 00:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who pays $15 for MAC lipsticks?!
In Australia its like $30 minimum!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 06:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! 
Your transformation is amazing. 
SOOO jealous of your flat stomach.
If you dont mind me asking, why is your daily food routine like?
And what exerciser are you doing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 04:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god. This explains so much. 
So you squeeze with my hands as much water out as I can and let the rest air dry? 
Sorry I'm new to this sub, and my hair is like a birds nest!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-20 02:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell me why you should not use a towel to dry your hair?
I normally wrap my hair up after the shower and let it dry a bit in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 03:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone able to tell me what they are protesting for?
I live in Australia and havent heard a single thing about this until now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 02:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you pleaseeeeeee do a tutorial on this!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 03:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Own it, love it! However, I find it is really really dry, and I just want to smother my lips in chapstick or gloss, but due to it being matte that would ruin everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 07:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me a year ago. 
My friends want nothing to do me, no matter how much I've tried to patch things over and explain. 
Im so lonely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 04:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like ellie goulding :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 06:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad I saw your comment, you just got yourself a new r/motivatinggiraffe subscriber! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 06:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in Prada the other day with a friend who was buying a new handbag, and she complained that the zipper on purse (also prada), kept sticking. Guy says he will fix it for her no worries, goes to the back and comes back out with a can of WD-40. I was in shock. It was amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 02:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love your colour!
Im looking at going the same colour, but so nervous to take the plunge!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 08:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! 
Thanks so much for your comment! 
Looking forward to trying these now :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 05:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I havent been to the doctor about..?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad dandruff from sweat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 04:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Guys, 
Ive recently been going to gym 3 times a week, and since then, i've noticed i've been getting really bad dandruff around my hair line and Im guessing its due to the sweat. 
I am using an dandruff shampoo but its not helping.
Any help would be great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 02:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love your glasses! 
What brand are they?!
You look stunning by the way :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 08:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Counter Strike: Source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 06:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> girl* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quotes on being positive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 03:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a girlfriend who is going through a divorce, and i'd really like to be able to send her a message every now and then with just a nice quite to staying positive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 08:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freshly washed bed sheets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-23 02:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the top comments, /u/brbdead, he emailed the address, and they found him on his personal facebook.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 07:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this feeling!
Started an new job, wanted to test out how many posts I could get before someone came to the front desk/called. 
I get less then 10 calls, and do nothing in my new job. 
Really dont think I could do this job without Reddit. 
I also have camera that are faced right at my screen. 
My boss thought I was reading HTML codes, and said keep up the good work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 00:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [THANK YOU!](http://img1.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20130821093610/the-house-of-anubis/images/2/25/ThankYou.gif)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 03:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> need. more. hints! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 00:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, still stuck lol
edit: now on level 21!
edit: now 22  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 08:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im at level 20. HELP ME?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 07:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would, but I've gone back, and got no clue how the hell I did it. 
Sorry dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 06:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anddddd im stuck on 15.
edit: Now stuck on 17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 06:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first found him, he was in my back yard and I estimate he was only about 10-12 weeks old. He was extremely skinny, and very shy. 
Now, he is the most cuddly cat, who loves sitting in front of the fire, eating everything in sight, and drinks gallons of milk! 
There isnt a day that goes by where he doesnt put a smile on my face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy 2nd Birthday to my cat Colt! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 06:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 03:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your eyeliner is amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 00:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh fantastic! 
Might have to wear my glasses next time I go! 
Knowing me, I probably walked straight past it without even knowing haha :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 00:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thank you!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 08:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hrmm. I will have to have a look again on the weekend.. 
Thanks :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 07:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone brought on NYX online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 07:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Ladies! 
I live in Mildura, VIC, and I cant get NYX here. 
Was on their website and was thinking of purchasing a few things, but it says i've got to sign up with some company who will give me a US address and then it gets forward to me. 
After reading that I decided I wouldnt purchase what was in my cart. 
So I was wondering if anyone has brought of there before and can tell me its a safe way to get NYX, or where I can get some? 
I will be in Adelaide in a couple weeks if I can get some there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 06:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad you posted this, I just ordered the Pure Heroine last night on their online store, never actually seen it on lips/skin till now!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He gets all the pussy in town. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 08:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 02:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May I ask what you use them for? 
I've never seen or hear of these before.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 01:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any tips with how to get a good winged eyeliner? 
I suck at it so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 06:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god, you are absolutely gorgeous!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 03:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [THANK YOUUUUU!](http://media.tumblr.com/022c89f083711e52d47f5dc75db33db6/tumblr_mocdvvCOSs1srujzdo1_500.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 01:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my lord, you are absolutely stunning! 
Please tell me, how do you do your eyebrows and eyeliner?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 04:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my floordrobe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 07:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait.. these arent the lyrics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 06:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Oh hi there Reddit!](http://imgur.com/a/91VFx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 02:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im in need of getting a brow kit, any suggestions?
Yours look perfect! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help! I need an Eye Brow Kit, but I dont know what one to choose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 08:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Ladies, 
I've just stumbled upon this sub, and it couldnt have come at a better time. 
My eyes brows are horrid and i've heard people talking about how you can get kits. 
I've looked on the net and found different ones, but have no idea about what one to get. 
Any insight would be much appreciated!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 06:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought having 32FF natural was bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 06:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably the most adorable baby picture i've ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 01:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look absolutely stunning!!! :)
Great job on maintaining the weight as well, thats the hardest part!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 04:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hauntingly beautiful. 
Im so sorry for your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 00:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've also got mousepads, business card holders and money clips at the moment, just not up on ebay yet!! 
We've got lots of other things such as pens, memo holders, pen cups, staplers and such in the works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 00:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if you ever need one, let me know!
I have plenty of them!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've started doing Carbon Fiber office products. Here is my first one if anyone's interested! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 08:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 07:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you **pleaseeeeee** do a video on how to do winged eye liner? 
I just went through some of your post here and am dying to know!!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 04:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flat stomach and no love handles! 
Why is this so hard to achieve!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 06:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-19 06:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I can see is pain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 06:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hauntingly beautiful.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 07:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am one of those ladies, and I hate it. 
I think im at the stage where I need to start investing in toys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 06:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you buy these. I need dem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
