<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High speed continual shooting mode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or to be on the ground yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American news programmes, love 'em! They put Buzzfeed to shame! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely would.  
Source: RP Speaker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's awesome at free throws! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you'll be COVERED IN BEEEEEES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where he engraves the ball with "Homer"  
And then she takes up bowling out of spite and meets some hunk! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fewer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on... are you correcting his grammar by correcting his "Math". That must make you an awesome arsehole! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that dog was about to wipe himself out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All companies around the world pass on their costs to the customers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> United Airlines could learn a thing or two from Kenya about how to handle too many people turning up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was making a point that "finding the absolute limit" is not the same as having a perfect lap. One only really finds the limit after it's crossed... and that happens all the time :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree.  
When someone over cooks it and loses traction in a corner because they pushed too hard, then they just found the absolute limit of the car at the exact moment they lost it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He usually just says "I'd like to thank you for coming" not that they're the "best".  
I think it's a nice gesture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's Rolf Harris doing there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What car is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replace it. They're cheap as chips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't pay for an entry visa in the UAE, but you do pay for an exit visa. However, if you fly in, the exit visa is included in your return flight ticket. You may have issues, beat check with embassy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first decent comment I've seen you write that isn't padded with obscenities. Nice one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What DOES it mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admit it, that doesn't make sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a licence from your home country? If so, what country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expenses:  
15% on rent.  
5% on expenses (food, car costs, bills).  
5% on entertainment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't think we disagree. I mentioned that the roast can either be very light (e.g. Saudi) or very dark (e.g. Jordan) so there's not a specific "Arabic roast".  
As for the beans themselves, yes they can come from Yemen (see my note about Mocha) but you don't need that to make Arabic coffee. I'm not going to get into the Arabica as a species, as I don't think that's relevant here. But most beans you will buy here will be from Colombia or Africa, and are still perfectly suited to make a good Arabic coffee, I.e. Yemeni beans not required.  
However, I do believe discussing the plantations or even whether you should stop the roast at the first pop is well away from what OP was asking. They were more likely asking about the pre-blended coffee... about which I will concede that I know very little... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean 20/4? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything North of the Creek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they'll have subscribed to /r/Sharjah instead, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dubai residents can be a little snobbish about living in the up market Dubai and can look down upon those who live in the squalor and filth of poorper's Sharjah.  
I however, am totally unjudgemental of those less fortunate underlings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may actually be lucky enough as you're starting in April. However, you'll still (most likely) have to pay NI as your family are back in the U.K. That's roughly AED2k/m. Tax status and NI status are different. There are "indicators" that you still have "significant ties to the UK". Having immediate family there is a sure fire way to be eligible for NI for the first 52 weeks (if you stay beyond that, you don't need to pay NI even if you have ties)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Factor in that you will still pay UK Income Tax and NI.  
Edit, roughly equates to AED15k a month in tax. Depends on pound.  
Will likely have to self asses, as PAYE unlikely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree that one shouldn't accept that "can I go" to mean "may I go". However, as a teacher, their job is to teach what's correct. I don't dress smart, and talk in perfect English every day, but during an interview, it's important to know how to do so.  
It's also important to understand the difference in the case of having to leave no ambiguity. The teacher may be being pedantic, but then clients can also be equally as pedantic if they bring any legal case about something you've inadvertently promised due to an ambiguity (equally, it can get you out of a legal issue if they used a term incorrectly too). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  modern English conflates "can" and "may"

Doesn't make it right, and certainly worth [teaching the difference](https://youtu.be/J7E-aoXLZGY) for more formal use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad... Mea Culpa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I make "Tea Boy" sound that glamorous? :p  
Actually, my profession if far from anything to do with making coffee, even if my colleagues do always get me to make the coffee (because they know I'll make it well) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just get the beans from the US?  
As the resident /r/Dubai coffee expert and advocate of Raw Coffee Co: If you want to get good beans from UAE, just go to Raw Coffee Co. Qahwah beans are no different from your regular beans. The "Arabic coffee" as a drink is actually more in the preparation rather than the beans. The roasting can range from a VERY light roast, right through to dark, depending on part of Arabia. The preparation is what really distinguishes Arabic Coffee from regular (European) coffee; for example by adding cardamom. If you're looking to get the beans, then there's no specific "Arabic Coffee" beans, but if you want pre-mixed-and-ground coffee... not sure where's best (I don't get pre-made).  
That said, I have also been looking for a nice, *good quality* dallah, but have so far been unsuccessful, and only found the plasticy/insulated ones. Please PM me if you find a good place.  
Bonus Arabian coffee fun fact: The "Caff Mocha" comes from the coffee that was exported from ["Mocha" in Yemen](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mocha_coffee_bean), which has a distinctive chocolatey taste. It was more recently when they started to add the chocolate to any old coffee and call it a "Caff Mocha" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're [currently in the middle of the 6th mass extinction](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Holocene_extinction) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the relevance of eating a Snickers?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "votes could have been manipulated"  
Isn't that the ENTIRE world of politics? The political parties spend billions on researching how to sway people's opinion. It's no longer "Here are my policies, vote for me if you like them"  
I feel that if there was something more sinister here, the title should reflect that it's not simply traditional "legitimate" voting manipulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "11,445,638 eligible voters - and every one of them voted" Don't try and discredit the man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't need it to fly one metre. 30 or so would be more effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the benevolent dictator, [I can't promise utopia...](https://youtu.be/rStL7niR7gs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  i don't count the Blair years as Labour

By making up your own definitions, one can say Labour have NEVER been in power, or always has been. You rendered your own statement useless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just goes to show how badly it works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ~~Labor~~

Labour. FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 10:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was saying that he must be in the U.K., as he hasn't been promoted. Not that he's ACTUALLY in the U.K. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, there are some places in Dubai where the khutbah is in English. It's just most are Arabic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ikea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't even get me started on the parking. Soooo many people double or even triple park other people or simply park on the street illegally. They should have their cars crushed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is the masjid only allowed to do khutba in Arabic? Who's rule is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure they were, on a 5 bazillion pixel sensor, then cropped... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 12:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not mutually exclusive, at least from and Islamic point of view. Stephen Hawking's brief history of time deals with some interesting aspects of the initial state of the universe and how it came to so orderly (at least where we are) when entropy is always increasing. In reading more about science and our origins, I have never found anything which contradicts my Islamic beliefs, and if anything they are strengthened when learning more about science. I think this is a big difference with Christianity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For today's next [10,000](https://xkcd.com/1053/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are leather gloves not fashionable? I and many other guys wear leather gloves in winter. They're the warmest whilst still giving some dexterity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something something correlation  
Something something causation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or our sat-navs as phones...  
I probably spend more hours with the sat-nav app than the phone function. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the recommendation, I will try and check it out but life is hectic at the moment so might not have time for a while. However, based solely on the title, and your very short description of "both sides", I'm guessing this looks at the arguments for evolution and religion? If so, is it specifically Christianity? If so, then I can see that there is a debate. However, for info, the theory of evolution and Islam are not inherently incompatible. There is nothing in Islam which states that there were not dinosaurs, nor that species cannot adapt and evolve.  
Source, am Muslim (albeit not immune to mistakes and certainly not a scholar) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Brit who did that, I am acutely aware. What I'm saying is that asking for schooling, or asking for higher salary is the same thing. They will be willing to pay X. They don't care if you ask for a smaller Y added to Z or X as a whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but OP implied that religious people were so irrational that ignored the "sufficient and clear" evidence. I'm not saying there should be, but OP implied it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not explicitly, but "such things" yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why it looks such a mess. It's actually two cars, massive collision! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but the implication on the previous post was that there was evidence, and it was STILL insufficient because the religious people were so stubborn. Maybe I mis-read it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Disproving existence of the Christian God"? I think you mean, "disproving Christianity". Although the Bible is a very unreliable text, to claim it "disproves" is a bit much. I agree it doesn't prove the existence either. That said "Christianity" and "religion" are not synonymous as a lot of Redditors seem to think (not saying you, here). I get irate when there's a whole "science beats religion" argument, when in fact what they mean to say is "science beats Christianity" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your previous comment implied that you'd tried showing this proof to one, and that it was futile. So was curious as to what indisputable argument you'd made. Apologies, I may have mis-read your post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both arms... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying there is "sufficient and clear" evidence for the non existence of a God? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would that really help? History teaches us that people ignore such things, or quickly forget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I just curious what qualified as quintessentially English. I was wondering what traits you associated with the stereotype. (Am English... be nice! :p) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 10:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In getting schooling/housing etc, one will reduce their base salary. When one negotiates with a company, they have a figure which they are willing to pay. The breakdown is rather academic in negotiations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practice, that's all you can do. Hope you get it next time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you sir, are you waiting to receive my limp penis?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ryanair is basic

When you just want to get from A to B, cheap, no frills, on time, then they're spot on. Good customer service in my experience.  
As for extra charges, they're just taking them out the cost of the ticket. One could fly BA, and get full meals, and luggage etc, but pay 100 more for a ticket. Well, I don't need a meal, and only have cabin bags, so why should I pay those "extra charges" when I don't need them? I appreciate that I'm purely basing it off my own experience so not exactly a great sample size. But I'm a frequent flyer on multiple airlines around the world so have a fair amount of references. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Touch. That's a very good point. However, is it not still "hanged" regardless of whether that was the cause of death? One can be "hanged until dead" so one must be able to be "hanged, but not ceased to live during the process".  
I honestly don't know, you make a good point though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RyanAir is leagues above United, and AA (from my anecdotal experience). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok, yeah I see your point.  
My high school crush also described me like the text...  
  
"creepy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  nice ordering of words

Even that's debatable. ~~hung~~ hanged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, that ain't how the aviation industry works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [which one you wanna watch first?](https://youtu.be/-jr-giYNYWc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, what's Bruce Willis doing here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 14:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy, what you're hearing is the sermon (or kutbah). The prayers, and the call to prayer are always in Arabic.  
99.9% of sermons here are in Arabic, but it doesn't have to be, so if the Imam feels that another language will be more relevant to his audience, he can use any he chooses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you not aware of how interconnected the world is, and how we all depend on each other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought we were since 2001 when the US declared War on Terror. It was a technicality which means they can treat people as combatants, and not civilians (who can't be kept incarcerated indefinitely without trial) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the AC gets stuck on.  
Sincerely,  
- An Emirati </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "He's got his rear wing wiiiide open!"  
For sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this, my mate had the same problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just one question... what's so great about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stopping at zebra or pedestrian crossings"  
I'll have to remember not to stop when someone's crossing next time!  
I can understand not stopping ON the crossing, but we can't even stop AT it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Driving a vehicle that causes environmental pollution"  
So... Driving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 11:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spend a penny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 10:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you missed the pause... whilst his brain was whirring... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 08:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  large scale political campaigns would be inaccessible to anyone who was not privately wealthy or famous

But this hasn't been resolved. It simply adds one degree of separation. Ok, so Average Joe can't run because he's poor, but the wealthy donors can effectively buy him for their purposes, or at least give lots of money to a candidate who says what they want to say. By campaigns being expensive, you've by definition excluded the poor.  
  
Very good ELI5 though :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And my MP ignored the result of his constituents.  
Democracies are flawed anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why did my MP vote to sanctify the Brexit when his constituency voted to remain, and he was a remainer himself? Because he's spineless, that's why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh yes, the country comes second to one's carrer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much most places have an allowance over. It's actually nice, because if you're doing the speed limit at 120, and it drops to 100 and there's a camera soon after, you are fine. The speed usually drops by 20 at a time (though not always, but that's usually on roads where they don't have cameras anyway) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
