<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! It's so satisfying to defy the crappy financial setup that is expected of you. My parents have terrible credit, we're constantly in debt, couldn't get a loan at all, spent like crazy. I had adopted those practices as a teenager but when I moved in with my fianc (then boyfriend) he helped me get my stuff together. I only use credit cards to build credit, I have never had a late payment, I pay my balance completely every month. My mom thinks it's practically a miracle, like it's just not possible for your average person to do that! 

I had a 720 credit score by 22 and have slowly built that up to 760. Feels good. Congrats on paying off your debt, that's so awesome!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he needs mental health services. He may think he's fine because it's "just his parents", but his reaction to his parents is something that terrifies YOU. He can't keep the two situations separate and claim everything is okay, because you being forced to watch him explode is putting a lot of stress on you. You shouldn't have to feel startled and afraid because he won't make an appointment to talk to someone. 

I have a lot of pent up anger regarding my parents. They were not the best parents growing up, they were abusive many times. I luckily don't have to deal with my father much anymore but I still have to see my mom all the time. She makes me feel powerless and weak, and LOTS of therapy has made me realize that. She tricks me, twists truths, does things I've specifically asked her not to. I am a small disabled woman so getting physically angry is not a real concern, but I throw my phone all the time and sometimes other small things within my reach. Lots of therapy has made me realize this sucks, but I still feel this incredible burst of anger. So instead of getting mad wherever, I go into another room, stomp my feet, throw balled up shirts at the wall, and then go talk to my fianc. Is it a good fix? No. But it's miles ahead of where I used to be, which was letting something my mother did affect several days of my life and make me an ass to deal with. But I take mine into the other room. My anger is my problem. I haven't yet learned how to deal with my mother. But I'm not making my fianc watch me get that angry. It's not his fault, he doesn't need to see that. 

I think when you talk to him again you really need to drive it home that he cannot possibly separate the two groups of people (his parents and you) because his problems with his parents are causing YOU distress and scaring you. If he tries to say "I would never get angry like that with you!" Again, tell him that you might believe that, but even if he never once got angry like that with you, you having to suffer the effects of his violent outbursts is just as bad. What if his physical anger resulted - even by accident - in physical harm to you? He can't guarantee he can control physics. He kicks something with you around and it hits you? That's not okay. 

He's hurting you, emotionally, and he won't admit it. Tell him you refuse to let him hurt you like that. That you love him and want him to feel his best, and you want to work together, and that means finding a way to end these outbursts so that you aren't feeling afraid of him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reeeeally needs an NSFW tag, please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FINALLY. WDW wifi is far from perfect but still a million times better than trying to load, oh, anything at all at DL on a crowded day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I complain about bleeding and still get up and go to work and get groceries and cook and stuff, FH says "Thank you for your service!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh those are pretty. And I am so excited to put this crown on my head, I'm dying, it's so pretty I just can't deal with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yaaass date twin! I will eventually buy my dress but... I'm not in a huge rush. I will get there. And the Petra is BEAUTIFUL and if it were still available, I would be trying it on. Just... deep breath. Aaaahhhhhh!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like another commenter said, eyeliner seems slightly off. My only other note would be that your crease color could come up a little higher - with hooded eyes, you tend to lose the color unless they blend it farther up. The shading is so pretty but it needs to be more visible! 

Also I saw you mention a lipstick sealer thing - for me, they just NEVER worked. I just looked dry and wrinkly. Some work differently than others though, and there's always a lip mask/heavy moisturizer in the weeks leading up to the wedding. 

The colors are so nice on you though! My own trial is in just a few weeks and I'm freaking out lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck yes! I'm wearing the glittery Kate Spade keds. There were a few of the older biddies that balked at my wearing SNEAKERS but I don't really give a rat's ass what they think, actually. And I'm getting married in the freaking mountains and walking through a forest. And I hate heels to begin with. My feet will be comfy and not in pain. Yay!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yayyyy! I'm so glad things are working out. The dress can be difficult but it is a VERY pretty dress, and when it actually fits you correctly I'm sure it will look gorgeous! I love the top of your dress and the transition around the middle - it's super pretty and flowy and ahhhh 

I expected to be in a tizzy about dresses. Since I was young, I dreamed of the big frothy ball gown with the corset laced back and the bling. And when I started trying on dresses, that's where I started. But I'm getting married up in the mountains and having a much less formal wedding than I thought I wanted. And like you, I'm losing metric shit tons of weight (I'm only 25 down right now, hoping to lose another 35-40 before September), so dress shopping is doubly difficult because how am I supposed to pick a dress for a body I don't know? That's why I'm going with BHLDN. I live near a store, so I can try stuff on whenever. And their stuff isn't special order. If I ordered a wedding dress today, I'd have it within a week. I'm not actually going to wait until it's that soon, I'm watching it like a hawk to make sure it doesn't go into backorder, but I can wait until I have a better idea of what size I'll be. I want to show off my waist, damn it! Okay, okay, rambling. But this similar dilemma is frustrating and ahhhh 

For reference, the one I liked best when I started was BHLDN's Hayden. The one I'm looking at now is BHLDN Genevieve. The only thing the OLD dress has in common with the NEW dress is... it's a dress. That's about all. Lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend did this super sweet thing basically like a first look, but for her dad. As soon as she was ready, she went to meet him (followed by photographer), gave him a gift, and they got a really beautiful moment together before the ceremony.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 03:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconding BHLDN. They're also not special order so you can order closer to your date if you want. They have a gorgeous tea length (at least it's tea length on me, lol) dress named Saylor that is To. Die. For. I'm obsessed. I'm probably wearing the Genevieve for my actual wedding but I want to buy the Saylor just for... rehearsal? Brunch? Idk it's gorgeous. They also have some white/ivory "bridesmaid" dresses that would work for a casual bride. 

I saw a post a while ago with this insanely pretty goldenrod yellow dress, I think it was Sarah Seven so, pricey, but it was a simple, solid colored gown. I think a simple evening-type gown and a few accessories can easily look bridal, with hair done up and all that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like you're me only my sister is saccharine sweet to me in front of family and a shit communicator and a weirdo on our own. She and I are still... friends? We were closer when we were younger actually but she turned into a mini version of my mother. My mom had a rushed wedding to my Marine father when she was 20. They divorced a while back. Mom and sister have both had a lot of shitty situations arise in their lives, I got lucky in many aspects (like, I'm grateful I have chronic spinal pain instead of the emotionally turbulent lives they have been shoved into...) and FH and I have been together and lived together for almost 5.5 years, so it's been easy(ish) sailing for me for a while. 

FH and I have divorced and re partnered parents. Three sets are contributing. And my grandmother is also contributing. So, we've got a decent budget. We're planning cool stuff and a badass honeymoon. My mom and sister are pretty blunt about jealousy. My sister is only 23 but she's still green. My mom just sort of broke up with her long term partner so she's... well she's always dramatic but this actually sucks. 

I feel bad for being happy sometimes. And also worried. They both have made promises that they clearly do not intend to keep. I am basically quietly doing the work for them and just including them where necessary so I don't stir things up too much. But I'm not holding back my excitement and enjoyment for them. You and I are allowed to be happy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be me if they would let me bring a giant blow up unicorn into the cruise ship pool :( I'll have to get a drink in a giant coconut or something to make up for it. But, we're leaving on our honeymoon the day after our wedding, like... wake up - brunch - drive home - double check packing - nap - get on plane and hopefully sleep - drive to cruise... so hopefully I'm not just knocked out unconscious on day one. Lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also my secret for awesome loose curls. I curl it the night before, spray the shit out of it, sleep, and brush out in the morning. Best hair day I've ever had came from that method. Magic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! My 10M has had some explosive tantrums in the past, MB and DB had him try CBT. It took some time to become habit but it's like night and day now. He's so much less reactive and angry, and if he feels like he's getting angry he just says he needs to go to his room for a while and disappears for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oof, I need this so bad. HH was always a guilty pleasure/comfort food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're going to be doing the same thing in about five months! We're taking a short cruise from Miami beforehand, renting a car and driving up to Orlando, spending the day in Disney Springs/CA Grill, and then 7 more days at WDW. Have fun!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds better than the $650k starter homes in So Cal!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kids rat out their dad's weird musical choices all the time. Apparently, DB will listen to Miley Cyrus in the car with no complaint. If Party in the USA came on, they allll knew the words. And Justin Timberlake. And stuff like that. He's a big Pop fan, DB. Soooo not expected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god that's so cool! Docs! Ah! Ren Faire! If we could have gotten our whole crew to do that, we probably would have. I JUST bought a new skirt an hour ago, lol. I'm gonna need it since it's going to be a zillion effing degrees when we go in a few weekends. Ugh. 

Our wedding has a lot of ren-ish/woodland forest/GoT-esque (new high score for most complicated descriptive term!) elements without being overtly themed. I am loving throwing all of these little details in - including the ones FH doesn't know about yet. Woo!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is! Dude, I saw her stuff forever ago and kept it in the back of my mind until I started doing real planning stuff. I am more excited about this than my dress, so whatever. But I'm all about cool unusual shit so I'm good. Aahhhhh I'm so excited to put this on my head  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just the kind of friend everyone needs in this world. And awesome! Yeah when you find someone who "gets it" it's like "oh, hi, we're stuck together forever now, sooooo"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my comment!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Amaroq. The crown I'm having made is basically a cross between the Caia crown with the spikes, but with the addition of some copper elements, and the Caleniel comb elements - tons of greenery and flowers, crystals, the spikes, metal fun stuff. Her custom stuff is generally between $250-800, and I was expecting to pay something like $600-700 but I'm probably looking at more like $350. It's an absurd amount of money to spend on a crown, but at this point I'm not feeling overly inspired by any dresses, so I'm basically having this bitchin' headpiece made and finding a comfortable/affordable dress that goes with it. Weeeee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 10:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a baby about false lashes too. The bands never fit my lid shape, and they're uncomfortable. Have you considered individual false lashes? The little bunches are waaaay more comfortable for me, and the look is a little more natural too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that amazing time suck, friendo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have reached -1 fucks to give. I am not acknowledging any family questions about the wedding. I will be wearing sparkly keds. I am having a ridiculously expensive custom crown made. I am five months out and I have no dress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahhahahahaaaaa 

You know when you reach that level of annoyed where you start to feel invincible and nobody else's opinions matter and people's concern is comical? 

Mentally I am sipping a martini, atop the iron throne, blowing raspberries at anyone who wants to have an opinion about anything. 

I reached zero fucks a few months ago. Everyone had their opinions, everyone had Things To Say. FH and I have had a very clear opinion of what we want for this wedding, pretty much since the beginning. No compromises. Four sets of parents? Too many differing opinions. We haven't expected anyone to contribute financially, we basically just said "thanks if you do, it'll help us have an awesome wedding" and away we went. 

Still. People have tried. Phrased as "questions" or "I wonder if you guys could..." or "you should...!" 

So I have literally stopped responding to people's questions. If someone asks, I just say "oh, you know wedding planning! We're working on it!" And change the subject. 

We had our second tasting today and I basically said "fuck it, I want the drink station and the coffee station and the short ribs and three extra hors d'oeuvres and the gold chargers! And the special lemonade! I want it all!" And FH raised his eyebrows but he knows better than to come between me and food. 

And then my mom started getting on me about a bridal shower and kept trying to pester me about a theme or some shit, and I just told her "mom just literally go check Pinterest, I have like zero friends and you know what the family members like" after she apparently picked and booked the date without me even knowing. I literally growled. GROWLED. Not on purpose. Just this... guttural noise of disapproval. And told her I needed to be included in big decisions. She can throw the shower if she wants, but it miiiight be nice if the bride can actually... be there. Maybe. 

Good news: I have been drooling over this designer who makes these gorgeous crowns and headpieces for... a while. They're these beautiful natural things with preserved flowers and greenery, crystals, fun metal ornaments, metal spike things that look super pretty. Like a crazy woodland fairy queen. I finally bit the bullet a few weeks ago and emailed her hoping to get a custom piece. We start working on it. And I brace myself for the quote... and it's half what I was expecting! So I'm going to go even a little fancier and I guess I'll pick whatever dress matches the crown best. And my sparkly keds. I do not care if I look like a weirdo. I AM a weirdo. Everyone who knows me knows this. 

I keep telling FH: if there's not at least ONE good candid of me stuffing my face while I'm all done up and pretty, I will be disappointed. Photog, get on it. 

Weeeeeeeeeeee  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god now I know this isn't just my awful luck. I don't understand why my face hates colors? But also the second I put on a foundation or blush that's even a quarter of a shade too dark, I look like a patchy orange.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh this is awesome! I am at 2 years 4 months. I just recently started to feel like I'm in the clear, but then again I only recently started taking my medication like I knew I should. Medication is a total game changer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that stood out to me, too. Why does HE have to be the one to do it? Why isn't SHE helping her brother out? Is it because she KNOWS he's a less than stellar employee and doesn't want to risk her own ass?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not every insurance plan has it, but some do. Have your dad check with his company HR people. My mom has Kaiser in CA, and luckily there's a department for disabled dependents within Kaiser that has paperwork and a whole process. But if you can't do the disabled dependent thing, depending on how your taxes are filed/your income, you can get some decent tax credits to help offset the cost of a purchased insurance plan. At least, that's how it works here. I'm assuming there's something similar in other places.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded. My DH read the whole book in one sitting after we had a particularly bad fight and I went to my mom's with the idea that I wouldn't be home until he was ready to talk and work on things. He read it in a few hours and called me, rambled on for like ten minutes (he's practically nonverbal otherwise so I knew something was up). He picked me up, explained how he realized how different we are and how we're just not speaking the right languages. Of course we're not going to feel great when we're not getting the type of love that we want most. Disagreements and problems have been handled a zillion times better since then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Syringomyelia. Degenerative is kind of an off term to use for it, but basically I have fluid filled cysts within my spinal cord and up near my brain stem that cause a bunch of nerve problems/weakness/dizziness/numbness, and it's slowly getting a bit worse as they grow a little/my spine moves (I'm losing weight, which we're not sure if it's helpful or harmful but either way I need to lose more weight.) Luckily mine isn't too bad! I can still walk and move fine most days, but as I get older I could get really weak and have problems with limbs. I shouldn't need a wheelchair probably ever, but things get tricky. I need MRIs at least twice a year, I have all kinds of maintenance pain management things. I'm just lucky it's not too bad and is manageable!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it came to that, we totally would have done it. Or paid out of pocket for the five months until then. We had a whooooole line of options in case this didn't work out, but it did!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm not going to lose my insurance! I can stay on antidepressants and take care of my back! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I turned 26 in February, so technically I'm supposed to get kicked off of my mom's insurance. 

However, I've been treated for a degenerative spinal condition since 2012, and recently started medication to help with some awful depression. Just in the last few months. Things were looking up. I just had to get some paperwork signed by my neurologist. Except she kept fighting me on it. I've only seen her for a few months and I don't have my FULL history so she wasn't sure. I was really afraid she wouldn't sign it. She's kind of... tough, I guess. 

She signed it! I picked it up this morning, I have to fill out one more page and send it in and then I'll keep insurance! I don't have to go off my antidepressants! I can stay in care! I'm getting married in September so I know I'll have insurance then, but this will bridge that five month gap and keep me healthy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was thinking. This kind of behavior goes waaaay beyond depression. She's obsessive, paranoid, she lashes out at OP, she's making completely untrue connections to her abuse. Sounds like having a baby triggered something deep. To not even let him get up and walk around with the baby? Beyond paranoid and distrusting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this shot so much. The lighting is so so beautiful and ahhh! Oh gosh. And also, heck yeah with the heavy apps and open bar. FH and family insisted on dinner so we're doing a "nice" buffet, but they don't know I picked like eight passed apps and a giant charcuterie board. Oops?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morning wine sounds so lovely and pure and sweet lol it made me think of fairies. Except I have my morning wine to deal with family and emails and cramps, sooooo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a ton of inexpensive washcloths for face towels. I just keep buying them, and at like $2 a piece it's a good thing to have around. I think I have like 15 now though haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck yeah. It's like, I understand there's a stigma, but it's so gooooood! 

Case in point - about a year ago, my depression got really bad and I decided I needed help. Medication level help. I told fianc about it and he seemed really hesitant but couldn't explain why. He admitted he was scared that it would change me, and I was scared of that too... but two sessions talking about it, he FINALLY admits that there was a relative in his family who committed suicide after going off meds without supervision. Such a HUGE thing! But he had a hard time verbalizing it and that's why he was so scared. It opened up the dialogue and now I've been getting the help I need and he's been supportive the whole way through. Therapy can be straight up magical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My FH was like this at first. Hesitant to get married, didn't want to go to counseling, the whole thing. I eventually told him he could go to counseling with me or he could call off the engagement. I hate putting out ultimatums but he was a TERRIBLE communicator and I tended to get dramatic. It's just how things were. 

Fast forward a few months - we hated our therapist (or at least, I did) but she helped us think about the important questions and gave us a neutral space to air our concerns. That was the biggest part for my FH - he was afraid to speak his mind because I'd throw a fit and cry. Jesus. Thinking about it now, I don't know why we did that. I have a myriad of mental health issues that I was not treating at the time but it was no excuse for how immature I was. Now I'm getting help and it's much easier to be reasonable. 

Anyway I'm rambling, but I think presenting counseling in a different light might help. My FH refused to go to counseling for two years. I kept giving in and saying okay but you get to a point where it is necessary for some couples. Present it as a neutral space. It doesn't have to be the condescending premarital counseling that everyone expects. It can feel crappy and dumb but it can help you become more in tune with each other's communication style. 

Tell him that if he refuses to have a real conversation with you about his reservations with getting married, you need to escalate it. It's mediation, not punishment. 

It saved my relationship. It totally did. I always thought of us as being basically married, but with those problems in the way, we weren't ready yet. Now I KNOW we're ready. We've gotten so much closer, and I didn't even think that was possible before we fixed stuff. 

He can either: 
A: help you pick a date 
B: commit to having real open dialogue with you about why he's hesitating, and work on a timeline with steps to get there 
C: go to counseling 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cycle breakers 

I am so proud of you. Fighting against the circumstances and way of life that you've been born into is so so difficult. 

I am in a similar situation. Women in my family have a history of not getting treated for mental health issues and being... interesting moms. I wish my life had been normal when I was younger, but at the time I didn't know there was any other way. One side of my family was poor hicks who didn't care about their health at all. The other were middle class white folks who turned a blind eye to bad parenting. Maybe it skips generations. My great-grandmother was not the best mom to my grandma. My grandma was an awesome mom to my mom. My mom was a nightmare and I'm glad I can recognize that now. I'm so terrified of having children because I don't want to be like my mother was. But I am getting active treatment for my depression, PTSD, anxiety... a whole laundry list of problems really, but I'm thriving now that I trust doctors and am on the right meds. 

I am the first woman in my immediate family/some others, that hasn't been pregnant by 21. I am the first (besides my grandparents, again, skipped generations?) to have a loving, supportive, non-crazy partner. 

I am seen as the weird one because I don't fit into their weirdo norms. But I'm okay with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interested in the skin79!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not who you commented to, but I issued an ultimatum to my fianc a year ago. I told him he could go to therapy with me and work on our communication issues and his harmful criticism or I would leave. We did the therapy thing but once we got to a certain point, we realized we were solving our problems better AFTER therapy rather than during. It helped us figure out each other's communication weaknesses. 

Telling him how he made me feel sometimes and that I would not continue to be with someone who made me feel like that opened his eyes. 

He's been committed to being a better partner every day. I forgave him, and that's how I can continue this relationship after we had to go through that whole thing. Ultimatums don't work for everyone, often the person on the receiving end is too stubborn. But it's worth a shot when you're at the end of your rope but willing to give it one last push.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Gimme Brow to fill first, then take an angle brush with some Gimme Brow on it to drag out my tails and fill in sparse areas. I look groomed without looking too strong. Game changer for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I drove that point home this afternoon. I was like "I literally just got through the worst part of a binge eating disorder, I am not going to let your shitty comments over-correct me to the point that I don't eat." And he was like uhhhhhhhhhhh ok sorry I won't do it again. wanna do better. Blah blah. I told him next time I want a treat like that to look at it for what it is - is it a single donut? I can have that. Am I stockpiling ice cream and brownies and sushi and steak and cheese? Help me knock that shit out. Really easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha it's funny you say that, because that was his suggestion. "What about the salad bar? Or something premise?" Yeah, like a 1000 calorie sandwich? Or a 700 calorie salad? I'm not eating dry lettuce. And I explained that to him and he was like bu-but... nutrition! And I just rolled my eyes. I eat vegan 6 days a week, I meticulously plan our healthy meals. He knows it. 

He later admitted he was wrong (I have in the past asked him to help me - when I am engaging in DESTRUCTIVE behavior, aka not a single donut) but he's a little... emotionally naive, I want to say. He had a weird childhood and never had a relationship before me. And I'm a bit of a handful. But still. He went too far. 

Still gonna treat myself at some point today or tomorrow and just stare at him while I do it to make him uncomfortable. Mmmm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case, it kind of sounds like grandma was either completely mislead and doesn't understand that this is not your normal deal, or that she knows how her kid is and wants to make it easier on you. 

How long are you stuck there? If it's only a few days... might be better to just grin and bear it for that amount of time. If it's longer than that, you need to talk to MB. This is pretty unfair. 

My old NF started slowly adding more and more chores onto my plate. I was basically just supposed to make sure kids (9, 11, 13) had breakfast and lunch and clean up after that. Then it was "can you throw in a load of laundry?" And it snowballed. I was too timid at the time to say anything. Soon I was coming in for extra hours during the day to catch up on laundry for the whole family. I should not have been putting away laundry for a high school freshman who was a little turd. But the mom was generally super nice while the dad was a total tool. It was hard to say no because I wanted her to like me still. 

Eventually I had to just go for it. I told MB that I was really uncomfortable with the amount of chores DB was asking me to do, and that he now expected to have done every day. I reminded her that I was hired as a nanny, not a maid, and that I would no longer be expected to do laundry for the whole house. That was it. She and DB were a little miffed, but it was easier to just accept that than fire me and find someone else. 

Don't feel like you HAVE to do anything. If you feel like you want to help/grandma is nice enough, I suggest finding a way to be in the kitchen during cooking so that you can clean up along the way. This is how I do things at home - I am known for making big messes when cooking. FH would rather clean up behind me for fifteen minutes than spend fifteen minutes afterwards cleaning up the bigger mess. Ask grandma if there's a way to sneak in and do stuff like this. You might want to frame it as "I'm not used to doing this amount of cleaning when we're at home, as I'm a nanny and I'm usually spending my time taking care of the kids. Is there a way we can work out a short list of things I can do to help out, so that once I'm done I can have some down time to rest?" She'll probably work with you. 

Next time MB yells at you though, just go total stone face and let her know that she has put you in a really uncomfortable position and that you'll have to discuss what happened when you're all home. She IS paying you, but she doesn't get to suddenly change your job responsibilities. She is paying you as a NANNY. Not a maid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you take a bus home? Buses are cheap. Not public transport, a real long distance bus. Or is there anyone near where you live that could pick you up? If you can manage it, do it. Just get out of there. That sounds awful. 

If not, I would do this - speak with the grandparents. Let them know that you're not sure what their daughter told them, but that your contract states you're only to clean up after the KIDS. You're a nanny, not a maid. Let them throw a fit if they want to. If they don't respect your job title, that's their problem, but don't keep cleaning up their huge messes all day because their daughter said you would. If they brought you on this vacation to clean instead of care for kids, they did it on purpose. There is clearly a "nanny will clean the house!" deal going on here. 

You can always remind MB of your title too. Nanny, not a maid. You clean up after kids, not adults. If she wanted you to clean her parents house, she should have asked about that beforehand, but holding your pay over your head and expecting you to just clean anyway is really shitty. 

Once you get home... find a new job. It sucks to leave a family but it's worse to be taken advantage of and treated like crap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cheeks and jaw get itchy all the time. I find myself washing my hands constantly to keep them clean... the other obvious being to clean anything out from under your nails - even if you have super short nails and don't think they're dirty, they accumulate so much junk in so little time. One scratch and you're not only messing with the skin by scratching it, you're basically injecting bacteria into those spots with your nails. Yuck. I also learned to itch small spots with a knuckle, and bigger spots by gently scratching in an outward motion, for less fingernail drag. Like... instead of the scratching motion being dragging your fingers inwards, you push the TOP flat part of your nails closer to the skin and drag just a little. 

I used to have awful acne on my cheeks... learning to not touch/touch safely saved my face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you like the spray moisturizer? I've been so curious but I don't want to get it and then have it feel weird haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really not a big deal. They were probably super embarrassed when they realized who it was, and once one person pretends they don't know the other one, you just kinda go with it... it's hard to go back from that because it seems like they're hiding something, but it's not that bad. You know it was from a long time ago. It's highly likely that they had a fling, it didn't stick, they hadn't seen each other since the old days and were so shocked they just ignored it. 

I met my fianc through one of his really good friends, who I was hooking up with for several months. Everyone knew. I had even previously slept with a different one of their friends, but that was a one time mistake (ugh) and that was before I met all of the friends. Nothing ever really went anywhere with it, we stopped seeing each other but stayed friends. I noticed my fianc from early on but he's shy so we didn't talk at first. Hookup invited me to a party at his house, and I wanted to see the friends so I went. Ended up meeting fianc for real and we've been inseparable since. He's never cared, he knows I had partners before him. 

Think of it that way - you know your buddy had girlfriends. You know your wife had boyfriends before you. It doesn't have to reeeeally mean anything that they knew each other. You are totally justified in being upset that they lied. But unless it's going to end either your friendship or marriage, it's not worth getting mad about. 

I would say you should sit her down, explain you're not mad but a little confused. Tell her about the picture and explain that you just don't know why they hid it. She'll probably be mortified, she may snap at you (even if she didn't do anything wrong, being embarrassed can make people defensive) but just explain that it doesn't change your relationship, you love her, it's okay that they used to see each other, it's not a big deal. 

Same with your buddy. You don't need to tell him you love him though. Just tell him you secondhand saw the picture, you're not mad, you just don't know why they hid it but it's fine. Just that you know now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My FH and I had some issues over the last few years. Anyone in our place would. He had some awful, manipulative, dangerous friends, he was naive, he had never kissed a girl until we got together when he was 23. I got sick about a year in with a chronic spinal condition. One of his friends changed how he behaved in our relationship. He's always been a bit... robotic. He's a software engineer and is all about efficient systems and organizations and perfect balance sheets and I can barely find matching socks in the morning and often waste my spending cash on bullshit. I have made strides to be more responsible, I was making an effort, but for a year or two there he was being kind of a dick. He was still super affectionate and loving but basically shut off emotions when it came time to have serious conversations and would say things that he later realized were awful to say. (Much of this behavior comes from his mom, who is very big-picky and didn't want us to ever share finances or whatever and makes rude comments literally everywhere she goes. He was a momma's boy when we got together. Not anymore, lol.) 

I almost left him. But I stuck with his weird ass and kept putting in work. I reached a point where I wasn't sure he was going to change. I very seriously thought about leaving, the logistics of it. We were in therapy but it was making things worse. 

And then something flipped. Like, night and day. We got in a fight one night and I went to my mom's. He didn't know what to do because I wouldn't come home until he was ready to talk, so he actually read one of those dumb self help relationship books (in one sitting. Seriously.) and it really opened his eyes to how different we are and how what he was doing (and not doing) was depriving me of the basic benefits of a relationship. 

It was a little rocky at first, we still have minor disagreements. But he's been MILLIONS of times more patient, understanding, supportive, the whole bit. I don't know what exactly did it for him. It took three years (of a five year relationship) for it to really happen, but it has. People do change. People do put in the effort. Some of the things he said and did were things this sub would tell me to leave him for. But I knew it wasn't really ever out of malice. He just didn't know how. Then he did. 

We're planning our wedding, it's in September in the mountains. We're splurging on food. He came to watch me try wedding dresses on because I trust his opinions more than anyone else's. He's absolutely the person I was meant to be with. He was not my "type" at all, and is quiet and analytical to my rambunctious and spontaneous. It took us a while to find the same rhythm. But we did it! Success story! And we're stronger for having been through all of this together. He shows emotions with me now. He is attentive and considerate. He is still at times infuriating and a bit of a weirdo but he is my weirdo, damn it. Nobody shoots my buddy but me! 

I am just so happy every day that things worked out. I got so close to leaving, several times. That was always my response in prior relationships. Flight. This time I chose differently because some crazy little part of me decided this was worth everything. And I am soooooo glad I did. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love the internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of mother just buys something to wear like that? Oh yeah.... my FMIL. Haha. We have discussed colors a few times. We're not going super formal so idk if parents are even walking down. Probably my mom, his mom. And his dad and stepmom. Anyway, I knew a long time ago that I was going to tell everyone that they could pretty much wear whatever they wanted. Our wedding party is all VERY different in size, shape, height, all of the above. Super. Just try to stay in this vague color palette, you're great. 

But I hadn't yet told FMIL this. But she'd already decided to buy a green suit. 

Green. Suit. Not sure what shade, but... ok. Good thing I don't actually care. She can wear what she wants. She's a little odd anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I'm imagining a bouncy jelly heart with multi colored glitter in it. Like all those bouncy balls in the 90's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oof. Sounds crappy to say it this way but honestly, it's the best outcome. You stayed strong and her lack of response and half-assed "apology" proved that you were very right in doing so. She didn't value the friendship enough to not be the center of attention during your wedding. That stinks. But you'll be better off without her. 

One of my "bridesmaids" is my best guy friend. I've known him since we were five, he's a little... out there. His fashion sense has always been a little funky to begin with. I have always loved it, the dude is not afraid to be himself EVER and really helped me with my own confidence. When I asked him to be my bridesmaid he kept saying he was going to wear a dress. Some of FH's family (and all of mine) would have been totally cool with it, but the rest of FH's family would have made a stink about it (fairly conservative gossipy old people who think their word is law and that everyone should know their opinions every fucking second. But it doesn't piss me off. Nope.) 

I explained to him that a dress wasn't really going to be in the cards but that we could find him something special to wear. He could wear a pink shirt and sparkly tie, some shit like that. He totally understood and then proceeded to tell me he wanted to get a ruffled baby pink tuxedo shirt. I know he likes a little extra sparkle and a plain suit or some shit is not him AT ALL. I told him to go right ahead, as long as his girlfriend matches and/or throws on a feather boa. Just enough to rustle up the old people. Just enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really stood out to me too. Nothing about how the husband feels about it. Maybe he's not aware of how upset his wife was over someone else's relationship with her "2nd husband". And naturally, he's not going to expect that there would be any feelings between his wife and his best friend unless they mutually gave him a reason to be suspicious. I feel like the husband either knows his wife is a little kooky/too emotionally invested in his friend and trusts it to never come to fruition, or... he doesn't know at all, and this is all just some weird thing that's happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, blunt is sometimes the best way to handle things. I was ready to call it quits with my FH about a year or so in because my schedule had to work around what his mommy wanted. We were sometimes over at their house or having dinner out with them four times a week! It was so excessive and stressful. I kept trying to hint that it made me uncomfortable but he kept ignoring it and saying he felt bad and he wasn't going to ignore her. Uh. SO not what I was asking. Then on top of that, she kept trying to convince him to co-sign a loan (because she knew she wouldn't get approved, even though she's got money) so that she could build a second floor to her house. So that FH could live in it. With me and our future kids. Just when I was saying "hey can we spend LESS time with your family?" He tells me he signed the application. 

I finally got fed up with it and said "fine! Go ahead. You help her get that loan. Make sure she builds a nice second floor suite. And then have a nice life, because if you're moving in with her, you're doing it alone. We are adults in a relationship living on our own. I just escaped my parents, I don't need new ones. We need to have our own adult lives.  This is not normal." 

Somehow, plans for the loan and build fell through, and the schedule started changing, and we saw her less and less. Hmmm.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, but there's no way to prove that the family wad aware of this before they hired OP. The AGENCY said she would be paid for holidays and vacation, not the family. The family may have never heard that line or agreed to it. Agencies and families don't have any kind of universal agreement to when nannies should or shouldn't be paid. Some work differently than others. Obviously the parents didn't agree with it (verbally or legally) since they refused to pay federal holidays. 

I think the only party that really took advantage of the lack of contract is the agency. Asking the family to pay up for the agency's crappy practices is what's not professional. Agencies sometimes have really shady practices - they tell nannies they'll get vacation time, sick days, holidays, this rate of pay, yadda yadda. But they can't really guarantee any of that without a contract. So they get girls to work through them with promises of all these benefits, then they don't have to deliver when a contract is never written or signed by either party. "Oh, it's just what you COULD get."  I had an agency do the same to me. Told me I'd make $20 an hour, 30 hours a week, paid sick days and holidays but unpaid vacation. That's what a family was offering. Sounded fine to me. Only when I went to go in and sign it, suddenly "the family" would only agree to $15 and no sick days or holidays. Yet, the family wasn't there when I went to sign the contract. Uh. No. I left those guys pretty quickly. Shady.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad did this to me. I was young, he didn't really let as much of his N flag fly as my mom did at the time. They divorced and I moved in with my boyfriend. I found out I was sick, couldn't work for a while. My dad offered to give us some cash to tide us over for a while. Cool. Part of their divorce agreement was also that my dad would give me $2k to help me get a car. He gave me $1500. Whatever. Still helped us out, though there was no way we were buying a car at that point. 

Literally three years later, he gets "laid off" (he got fired, I'm 99% sure of it, since he's happened to get "laid off" four times in four years, I shit you not) and asks when I can start paying him back that money I owe him. Um. Excuse me??? No. I tell him that he was very adamant that the initial amount he gave me was a gift, he repeated over and over that we didn't have to pay him back. And that the second part I DEFINITELY wasn't supposed to give back as he was legally supposed to give it to me. I was barely getting back to work at that point. I told him I could give him $50 a month, to help him out, but that there was no way I could return all of that to him, even if I wanted to. 

He said "don't bother" and didn't speak to me for six months. When someone shows you who they really are... that whole thing. 

He also promised to help pay for sooooo much shit when I was first talking about getting married. My dress, the rehearsal dinner, all kinds of crap. Then I actually got engaged and all of the sudden he's laid off again, he can't really help pay for anything but they can help plan! (And it sounds awful, but he and my stepmom's taste is all caps TACKY. no thanks.) at this point, he's lucky he's even INVITED to the wedding. Honestly at this point I expected him to do that, so I never really expected a contribution from him. 

Oh yeah, and during all these periods of time where he was destitute and needed to try and steal money back from me? They've managed to buy four new cars in five years, they don't pay rent living in her mom's house, they go on trips constantly, and he's always talking about some cool new gadget he bought. 

Good job OP, I wish I would have learned this lesson ages ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what brunches are for, lol. You're right in saying that it would be rude for the couple not to attend. 

We're getting married up in the mountains. Most guests are staying Friday through Sunday. The big main house has a big kitchen/room off to the side, so we're going to make big batches of scrambled eggs, bacon, maybe pancakes or something. Put out juice, coffee, and muffins. Nothing fancy. We're even reusing some of our decor from the night before. We're just giving people a two and a half hour window where they can show up. Then it gives people time to shower, pack up, whatever, and swing by for some food before they depart. We'll be there for the middle hour and a half, spending time with people and making sure everything is packed up and ready to go at noon. 

Is there any other reason besides "alone time" that he doesn't want to attend? An hour and a half to spend time with people who just came to celebrate with you doesn't seem like anything terribly inconvenient. At a friend's recent wedding, they let everyone know that they could convene in the hotel restaurant for breakfast, show up between 8-10, and that they'd be there for the first hour before leaving. Easy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with hounding the agency because it is THEIR mistake, but there was never any written or verbal agreement with the family that they pay you on days you aren't there. You already knew this. Sitting down and begging them for money when they've already made it clear they will not be doing so does NOT look good. They have benefits for their jobs because they have written, signed contracts from their employers that outline those benefits. Begging them for "wiggle room" is unprofessional. They said they would pay you when you're there. Clearly. You can't force them to do otherwise. 

But a bigger part of this IS the agency, since they stated you would be getting paid for this week. Get in contact with whoever handled you and let them know that since they never presented you/the family with a contract to sign, your family is refusing to pay the week's vacation and that you're now expecting compensation from the agency to cover that vacation time. You can discuss with them the issue with federal holidays too. Do you have any written record of the agency promising this? That's going to be your best bet. If not and it was some verbal promise and they never came through with a contract, that's going to be really hard to prove/make happen. It may have even been on purpose. Some agencies like to lure in nannies with promises of bigger checks and better hours and benefits and then they just don't deliver. It's shitty, but it happens. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, don't let your parents opinions dictate how you plan YOUR wedding. Different people have very different opinions. FH and I both have divorced and remarried parents, so we have four sets to deal with. Three of the four of them have OPINIONS (My dad and step mom want some kind of backyard rager with too much alcohol and not enough food, like theirs was. My mom thinks I'm crazy for getting married in the mountains and is very picky about accommodations. FMIL wanted us to get married in a park next to a freeway, lol.) 

FH and I got financial contributions from his mom (who, when we were firm about having a nicer wedding, had a ton of CBF but stopped pushing), my mom (who is now trying to kiss up and saying she loved everything from the beginning lol) and HIS dad and stepmom (who are contributing the most out of all the parents but their only big opinions so far have been "it's your wedding, do what you want" and "sounds cool!") 

I'm rambling at this point but basically put it this way - the whole traditional "parents make big choices" thing is waaaay outdated even if your parents were helping to pay for your wedding. Since YOU TWO are the sole financial contributors, it's up to you. 

What does your fianc say about this whole thing? Does he agree with you or with parents? It can be hard to fight a partner on it (mine initially wanted something very small and simple) but if you're both in agreement, it's easier to be firm with parents. I basically told FH the same thing - we only get to have one wedding. I don't want to regret anything about it or make any decisions I don't like just because one set of parents didn't like it. I'm not willing to compromise on a once in a lifetime event that's about US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'm hoping to do exactly what you did, I'm saving this post for inspiration when I need it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got really lucky with mine, I finally got help for my depression/anxiety/etc and my first request was that I be put on something that would NOT make me hungrier/gain weight, because I had emotional binge eating issues. My doc said "let's try Wellbutrin first, it can help curb cravings instead" and holy crap, I don't feel like a zombie anymore, I feel like I can do things and get up and shower and I bought a recumbent bike for my living room. And I don't feel those awful impulses, I'm eating healthy... all of the sudden I'm down 20 lbs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I know. She only does it at night and she dumps it in the morning, but nooooo. And everyone kind of chuckles at it a little but it's just normal for her. So nasty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, this. And it will only get worse when it's her graaaandbaby instead of a dog. She can claim ignorance or think she's bringing treats to a dog, dog gets sick, she keeps doing it. With a baby? Yeah, no. This kind of behavior will be amplified. She'll think she's got a right to give baby whatever she wants to/do things against parent's wishes! And why? Because nobody ever told her to stop with the puppy! 

Personally, I think you should handle this, but not in a "fine I'll do it" sort of way. Sit down with your husband and ask how he would feel if she fed something to your child that made kiddo sick. Would he just not say anything, even when it was bad enough that you have to take baby to the hospital? (If he says it's different somehow because it's a dog, that's a whole different ballgame of disregard for animals, but I digress!) Let him know that NOT putting your foot down now will just pave the way for future rule breaking, and that you would be uncomfortable with MIL around baby if she's just going to ignore your rules and do whatever she wants. 

Let him know that you will not let his mother trash your decisions with no repercussions at the expense of the suffering of a living thing. There are two ways this can go: he can talk to her and let her know that the dog is no longer allowed table food, and let her know about the vet visit, explain that he understands she feels like it's a treat but it's actually making him very sick. Or YOU can talk to her - in the form of handing her the vet bill for the treatment of your dog that is HER fault, and maybe not being as gentle with her as he's being. He can let this go either way. She'd feel less attacked hearing it gently from him than aggressively from you. It's his mom. If he'd rather spare her feelings than spare actual suffering of a living being, do not have children with this man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know other people feel this way... I'm in the process of losing 80ish pounds and I am avoiding seeing people who haven't seen me since it started, until my wedding in September. I'm 25ish pounds down now but I had really gotten uncomfortably big for my frame and didn't see any friends during that time. I'm hoping to just avoid everyone else for the next 5ish months and then... bam! It will have to be noticeable. Haha. Irrational, but I feel the same way. I think you and I both might benefit from finding a little more confidence in the MIDDLE of our journeys, not just the end! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao, I feel you. My FMIL spent the entirety of a weeklong family camping trip making it seem like I was a total idiot. First of all... I've been in Girl Scouts/literally leading camp workshops for troops for 14 years. I have been camping several times a year since my birth. I am not new to camping. And her "camping" is hardly camping. She liked to point out that I didn't know where things were. (for reference, she brings like fifteen buckets of shit, sets up two different stations for... things? And also brings herself a five gallon bucket with a toilet seat so she can pee in her tent in the middle of the night. The last one isn't super relevant but it's gross, lol) 

Then, when I spent the first three days firmly reminding her that I am feeling just fine, I just don't do breakfast on vacation because I take forever to fall asleep so I like to sleep in... then she says "oh! Are you drinking enough water? You're drinking plenty of everything else..." assuming I'm some kind of dehydrated idiotic alcoholic who hasn't been chugging water (and yeah, okay, vodka crans too... but they were necessary.) 

Ugggghhhhhh. This is the woman who asked me to help her clean out her massive horrible crap filled spare bedroom and make sure she threw stuff away. When I tried, she made it seem like I was asking her to throw away her most prized possessions. Over shit like a pair of shoes she bought ten years ago and literally never wore. And then complained to everyone that I was making her throw stuff away, but also that I wasn't helping (??!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine they photoshop your old photo pass pictures of yourself into something like this... in really bad and obvious ways. "This could be you, but..."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's about emotional maturity. Some people you can deeply connect with almost immediately. Some people just don't feel that same level of comfort or connectedness. I have some friends that I've had for 10+ years that I consider good friends, but nothing else. I have very few close friends because I don't like wasting time with people who don't genuinely want to help and love others as I do. But the couple of close friends I have are gold. The others... well, it's nice to have a beer with them now and then but I don't think I'll still be talking to them fifteen years from now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is basically what happened with my fianc and I. We'd been dating about a month, spending a LOT of time together (like, I was staying at his place 6 nights a week, we went out all the time, blah blah) and hadn't put a name to it. Then randomly one night at a friend group Christmas party, one of his friends called me "FH's girlfriend" and then we got quiet and he was like "oh shit, have you guys not had that talk yet? Whoops!" Later that night he was like "soooo Paul called you my girlfriend..." and I said "well, yeah, I think that's kind of what we're heading for here" and now like five and a half years later we're getting married! At one point we told Paul that his comment is kind of what made us talk about it and he was like "well I mean you're both pretty awkward so I did you both a favor."  Bless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we went last weekend, they kept sending too many people to the levels at the structure. There were zero spots for sixty cars. When a spot opened up, someone took it, but by that time ten more cars had slooooowly made their way up to the level and were waiting on the next spot. We finally bailed after trying for over a half hour, went to Toy Story, tons of parking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents split when I was 20ish, basically they were both terrible together and neither of them have all of their marbles to begin with, so when accusations of cheating started flying from both sides I immediately just cut myself out of the whole situation. Mom and dad want to crash and burn? Fine. I don't care about what kind of ass you're chasing. You're adults. Handle that shit on your own time. But don't expect me to fall at your feet and forgive you for destroying this family. 

And that was the day my spine was born.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 09:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to go kid music, there are TONS of great kid music bands! Sirius radio has a whole kid's channel, and tbh it's not bad, I get so many of these songs stuck in my head lol. Recess Monkey, Caspar Babypants, Andrew and Polly, They Might be Giants did some fun kids stuff, my kiddos loooove the Okee Dokee Brothers, Tim Kubart, Secret Agent 23 Skidoo, Brady Rymer, Frances England, Gustafer Yellowgold, Lori Henriquez, Justin Roberts, The Pop Ups have some suuuuper cute stuff, Lori Henriques... those are my kiddos favorites off the top of my head. Disney stuff also works, Hamilton, they'll even listen to Kidz Bop stuff now and then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel you. I'm on month 3, few weeks now with a double dose. Like night and day. Suddenly, I am human again! Wellbutrin is a helluva drug.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you like the diamond crushers? I'm soooo on the fence, I love glitter but I am worried that these have glittery fallout. How do they perform over the course of a day?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls complimenting girls makes the world a better place. Cases in point: at the Women's March LA, I made an all out fun sign with tons of cool stuff on it. I had so many people stop me and say how cool it was and how they loved this or that about it. 

Also, whenever I'm at a festival and... chemically inebriated, as it were, I am a compliment MACHINE. I will yell "YOU LOOK SO PRETTY!" and call everyone gorgeous and compliment hair/makeup/outfits all day. Fianc chuckles and says "you're just in this for the lady smiles" and I'm like "yup, feels good!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe both!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bupropion. Generic Wellbutrin. It's a different class of antidepressant than most, an uncommon one, which I'm super lucky was prescribed to me and has worked so well so fast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Binge Eating was somehow harder for me to talk about than abuse and anxiety and depression and night terrors. It sucked to finally admit it because it's such a loss of control on it's own. I don't remember what post I was reading the other day, but the poster said the part of them that binged was just some small primal part of their mind that wanted to consume everything and protect itself. So they gave it a name. And whenever they wanted to binge, they said "oh, I don't really want to eat all of that, that's (insert name here) talking." And honestly it was a big step for me in realizing that my bingeing seemed to come from an entirely separate sector of myself, and that's why I had had such a hard time with it. Our instincts are sometimes wrong. It's actually been freeing to talk about it. I almost didn't want to post but it's good to get out there and it seems a lot of people relate. 

Have you tried writing it out? I came forward about some abuse by writing a single sentence on a post it and basically chucking at my therapist. Bit of a crude method, throwing things at a therapist, but gets the point across.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love corny! And the moment itself felt corny to me. I feel like since my emotions have turned back on, I am one big cheesy antidepressant ad, I'm a few bits short of running through a field of flowers on a sunny day, but whatever, works for me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one I like best is by HypnotherapyByKris on youtube. Something about her voice works for me. The video is "Achieving Your Goals - Removing Blocks and Barriers!" And I don't know if it's because it's the first one I ever did like that or what, but it really stuck with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, Texas, land of humid horrors and lots of food, as far as I remember. I have some family I used to visit in Texas, now they're here and I'm free from your home state's weirdness. I kid. Sort of. But seriously, next time you're in the area, hit me up! It will be good times! I feel like there should be some kind of THING for this. All like-minded internet twins should have some kind of conference every once in a while. Take turns hosting. "Hey I have no friends and you have no friends but I know where good food is and also we can have wine, just find a way to my state of residence and we're golden."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, kind internet stranger. 3 I will look back on this time with "wow remember when I was terrible at life and now I'm not? Cool, who wants a beer?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I am you. And we just don't know it. Shhhhh. It's gonna be okay. I promise! We are gonna rock this. It's settled. (Live anywhere near Southern California? You can have the super sweet benefit of being friends with me! My depression made me lose almost all of my friends, so there are positions open. Yay?) 

For real though, be upfront with your doctor about upping your meds. Mine thought it was a great idea, but she wasn't sure how I was feeling until I told her. I figured I might as well share my experience. I see so much about mental health and so much about weight loss, but I don't see nearly enough about how one affects the other and how sometimes, taking care of your brain can help you take care of your body. I wish I had read something like this a year or two ago and thought of getting help sooner. (Not to toot my own horn, but... actually, yeah, toot away, I am proud of myself for putting this out there because it was hard, but here it is!)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, depression is the fucking pleb bitch in the back row now. Banished! By love! (And chemicals!) But yeah, I feel like having a good understanding of depression and saying "hey, this fucking blew for like several years, but I did the good thing and now I'm awesome" is a thing I'm going to be proud of for a long time. Huh. I have not been proud of myself in several years. And now I am. This is weird. Shut up. Shut uuuuuuuuuuuup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it was quite the roadblock and now it's not. So different. Yay!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick it out, I promise you, it is a world of difference. I was frustrated at first too because I had hoped to feel a dramatic difference instantly, despite my dr telling me that was not likely to happen. I went through the first two months just saying "well, it's not making it WORSE, and I am noticing SLIGHT improvements." The doubling of my dosage was the big one. Now I know why people are on antidepressants. Holy crap. Night. And. Day. And if this med doesn't work for you, try another! It can take a while to find what works for YOU. I got really lucky that my first med worked with no unbearable side effects. Stick with it. I'm proud of you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just turned 26 too, and it was very much this feeling of "oh, I'm closer to 30 than I am to 20. I don't want to waste my life away watching these milestones pass while I'm miserable. I can't be working this hard just to function. Let's do something about it."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually just recently got into meditation too, I think that's honestly part of what drove me to get help. I felt awful all the time and stressed when I wasn't completely depressed. I started with like 15 minute guided meditations, and then I found a 30 minute one that completely blew my mind. Totally changed my meditation game. This is the one that helped me realize that my mental health was a major road block on the way to my goals. And then I kept digging and found different methods of meditation and the other day I just zoned out and did my thing and looked up and, whoops, there went an hour and fifteen minutes. I normally can't sit still for more than ten minutes so that was amazing. Revelatory. And Yoga and I might get along better when I've gotten a little lighter/stronger, as currently all that happens is I fall on my ass, so...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take the generic too, and I know that's supposed to help so I'm super glad I didn't get stuck with the name brand and all the problems that go along with that. I have a weak stomach with or without medication, and I figure it's more diet AND med change than anything, but it's still... ugggghhhh. I take mine in the AM with a little food, should probably be drinking more water with it in the morning though! Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! That first revelatory moment of "holy shit! Hey! I'm not totally fucking miserable! This is fucking awesome! AHHHHHH!!111!!" is hilarious. I basically started crying and then I was like "Why am I crying, I am happy?" But emotions are tricky bitches. The wave of emotions coming in at any time is usually !!!! but sometimes it's more like ???? 

And I totally get what you mean about a crutch. I got to the point where I was just like "whelp, without this I will probably just slowly get heavier and heavier and be miserable and ruin my younger years with self hate, so... might as well try it!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS exactly. I hated myself for so long before I realized it was more "I hate what I do to myself" than anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then partner, I know where you are, I've been there, and I'm telling you - it CAN get better. It is HARD and you have to accept some crappy truths about yourself, but it helps. I decided to skip straight into dual therapy and medication mostly because I know that in the past when dealing with my anxiety in high school, I was not always 100% truthful with my therapists. I can't get the help I need if I'm lying because I don't want them to think I'm weird or 100 other things. My family history with mental illness has shown both positive and negative interactions with therapy, medication, and hospitalization, and I decided the benefits far outweighed the risks and that it was worth a shot! And I'm so glad I did it! You can always go back OFF meds, but the decision to start meds ASAP rather than wait was a necessary one for me. And don't hate YOU. Feel free to be unhappy with your choices, but if you've already made the decision to work on yourself, you're worth it and you're awesome!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! It took me so long to really accept the fact that I could not function anymore without a little help. My family has a long history of mental illness of many kinds, so I was a little wary going into it having seen the negatives of improper care, but I took the plunge anyway. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WILD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol well it works! I can't get a line that straight to save my life so I'm jealous of your accident haha!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reeeeeally love how you lifted and extended the end of the cut - so many people do the cut crease business on the lid, but the outer 1/3 is blended. This is a super sharp look and I loooooove it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Filipina moms are the real MVPs in the kitchen. My best friend growing up... it's a good thing it was a loooong walk to his house, I never left that door without at least one big container of food, haha. Meanwhile my boring ass white mom finds a way to burn everything from bread to fish to literally everything else. I learned to cook from a young age. My mom offered to help make desserts for my wedding and I immediately booked a baker. Whoops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had warts on my hands and knees as a kid, and once when I was 12 I tripped and landed right on a medium sized one on my knee. It bled like crazy and then it spread out to over an inch wide in either direction. My doc was like "what did you do???" And then laughed at me. I used to get the liquid nitrogen treatments and they helped quite a bit, but they hurt so bad I cried. He'd always take the little bit of leftover liquid and throw it on the ground and say it was magic. Poof! Which made me roll my eyes because I was 12 but secretly I thought it was pretty cool and he knew it, haha. 

The tape thing, I had totally forgotten about until you posted it. Duct tape mostly. Sometimes medical tape. Hurt like a bitch if it pulled stuff. 

You know how they finally went away? I stopped trying. I figured "oh well, I guess I just have them forever." I would tape it now and then (like once a month) and pull stuff off and it hurt, and at one point they just healed up. Haven't had one since. Weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did pretty much exactly what I want to do. I started at 206 and just hit 188, so I'm still working, but I'm hoping I can at least get close to this awesome by my wedding in September. Great excuse to work my ass off. Also, I browsed your old post and I love that weight loss simulator! I hate mirrors and don't have a full length one in my apartment at ALL, so it was uncomfortable seeing how big I had been but encouraging to see the bit of progress I've already made. Looking at my goal weight/old stats from when I was that weight is like... yep, I wanna be there again. Pretty much RIGHT where you are. Congrats and thanks, too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 4F is soooo like this. I'm trying to lose weight but every time we hit Starbucks she says "we could just get a little snack, if you wanted..." luckily I know what she's up to and I'm used to telling her no because she asks for something every twelve seconds. Lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents are the same, but I'm mostly VLC with my dad and stepmom and stepsisters. My parents try to get along but if we're being real for a second, they hate each other and they're like petty teenagers so I had to basically sit them both down (separately) and say "you don't get second chances. There will be no drama surrounding this wedding or you will be asked to not attend. I am not afraid to kick you out in the middle of my reception. Do not test me." But then, I've spent the last five years forging myself a pair of giant steel lady balls in the fire of my annoyance and fury, so I know it's not easy for everyone. 

Next time your mom talks about traveling in, or the time around your wedding, mention how crazy things are and how grateful you'll be for the week of alone time during your staycation, and how you and FH will be so glad to have some peace and quiet. If she insinuates that she wants to visit for longer than you want, remind her of the staycation and alone time, and how it's basically your honeymoon at home and you'll be busy being together. 

As far as the days before go, same deal. Mention how busy you'll be, bring up appointments or errands you have to do and how you'll barely be at home or have time to rest. If she presses, tell her that because of all the family drama, you organized to do everything yourself so that there wouldn't be any claims that you picked sides and wanted one parent's help or presence more than the other. There's a middle ground here - save boring monotonous stuff for them to do the day before, if they want to come in a day earlier. Make it clear that this won't really be time to hang out and rest, that if they're here early they're going to have to bear some of the burden of preparation because you can't not do the prep. 

Good luck. Ours is September too and I've already realized I'm waaaay behind on planning. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt like this for the first year or two with my fianc. Actually, I still sometimes feel like that, but not nearly to the degree I used to. 

If he didn't see something special in you, he wouldn't be with you. Simple enough. He's obviously very into you and likes to treat you nicely. That's it! It doesn't have to be more complicated than that. Worrying too much about it is going to ruin your perception of the relationship. Take it easy. Let him treat you well. Show him appreciation whenever you can in whatever way you are comfortable with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thiiiiis so much. My childhood was filled with so many happy memories with them, and even as I got older and the abuse became more frequent, I still loved them. They still did a lot for me. It doesn't erase the abuse, but it does make it harder to heal. It took me until I was 25 and had been out of the house for 6 years to actually call it abuse, because there was no way my parents were abusive, right? I mean their punishments were way over the line and both of them hit me several times, were intimidating and threatened me, used to gaslight me, would openly mock me and encourage others to mock me, but... oh, yeah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, doing Ritalin you don't really need when you have sleep problems is bound to fuck with your mood, I'm guessing. I have night terrors and if I even drink too much my whole night is weird. Tell her to lay off the pills and see her doctor. That kind of behavior is a little bizarre and there are some things that can be done for night terrors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hashtagjustpornhubthings  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, don't let squealing teenage girls in high school talk for the grown women you'll encounter now. In high school I probably would have also said it was "weird", but I'd never even seen one in person. Teen girls are also very hive-mind-y, if one of them says "that's gross!", they're all going to agree even if they have no clue about the reality of things. 

As a woman who has seen a decent selection of dicks in her years, I'm gonna spit a little truth. Two of the best lovers I ever had were the two guys who were uncut. Because of anatomy? No. Because they both had confidence. Both of them basically gave a small disclaimer before things got sexy and said "hey, I'm uncut, I don't want it to be a surprise but it's just how I am. Everything works exactly like it should." And oh man, did it. 

It's not an easy 180 to magically become comfortable with some part of yourself that you're nervous about, but you have two options - build confidence and learn to own it, or just avoid having sex for the rest of your life. Easy choice. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
