<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6292</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 01:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ssquishy people jussst jealousssss...
...
......sss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude... It's right there. Right freakin' above you. How did you mess that up twice with it spelled correctly *right there?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Floran will sstab thosse who mock sspeech impedimentss. Then chew on ssquisshy inssidess... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An asstute obsservation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 17:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting concept. I will now steal it and claim it as my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 17:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yeah, but I like bookmarking the planet itself, too Little visual "I've been there" on the nav screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this all the time, marking them with the feature that sticks out to me most. "Human camp," "lots of surface ore," "Freaky eyeball trees," that sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 04:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Automato stew, coffee, chocolate, carrot juice, baked potatoes, and bon bon bon bons are what I tend to carry around after selling off my surplus. Sometimes I keep a few loaves of carrot or mushroom bread, as well. I have a very varied and eclectic diet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 19:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that what it's called? Hooray for new words! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 16:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The method I developed (having only started playing two days ago) seems to be pretty efficient: Dig straight up, then put your cursor just under your feet, jump as high as you can, and place blocks under you as you go. Got me from lava to the surface in about 20 minutes with basic equipment. Also I got lucky and encountered no monsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 23:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're asking this question, you may as well grab them all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 14:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, well, Fred, I think the point is to r/rant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 16:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen that method on videos before, but have never managed it myself. I like the "process" of the fight though, and have all the patterns and shortcuts down pat. And who would ever want to miss out on the Cake Core? He's adorable!

...though, Rage Core invariably ruins any good vibes. Voice actor did a little too well on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 09:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly the basics for portal. Out of the blue, try to get trapped, take out every turret without taking damage, drop every camera, hit the buttons without carrying the boxes, last instant portals on drops, etc. Don't get me wrong, I can whip through the thing in an hour and a half, but the only place I really try to do it quickly is at the very end. Even then, it's just because it tickles me to hear GlaDOS fast forward through her whole endgame rant.

Probably my toughest and least successful rule is trying to fizzle a turret every level that they appear, and my most successful is taking out every turret in the arena (that big square three storey room near the end with all the hatches in the walls) without taking damage, alerting them, or touching them directly. I'm proud of that one, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 03:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the ultra rare *reasonable and enlightening internet discussion*. It's not every day you find people willing to patiently explain their way, while also accepting the contrary views from someone else. If I had more money, I'd throw some Gold your way in appreciation.

I never considered the replay value aspect, given that the game has so much already. There again, though, I have occasionally put limitations on myself to artificially raise the difficulty level, because most things seem more fun with that extra level of challenge. Is it something like that?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 23:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's certainly different. I can't imagine you figuring out to do that on your first run, though... Unless you only picked up the game to practice and improve speedrunning it.

I've never understood the draw of speed runs. You're basically heavily diluting the experience of the game for bragging rights, and possibly some sort of compensation in contests. My personal opinion: Games should be enjoyed to their fullest potential, not rushed through homeopathically.

That said, I'm impressed by your video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 13:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have heard this literally every single time I've played through the game. All thirty-ish times. In fact, I can't even tell what you supposedly did differently. It all looks/sounds normal.

I am curious, though: How do you normally pass this area, without triggering that line? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 04:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reborn, if you just need something shorter.

I don't think an abbreviation exists for that word right now, but let's play around, shall we?

Reincarnated

Reincarn'd

Reinc'd

R'ncarn'd

...not a good word for this, I think. Synonyms would probably serve you better. Something like reborn, revived, hell, even incarnate would work in the right context. For example:

His spirit has been *reincarnated* as a woman.

That woman is his spirit *incarnate*.

...ok, bad example. But still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 12:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading comments as they performed. Scrolled down and Seal was singing, scrolled back up and he was just standing back watching Guitar Guy sing. Didn't even notice them switch. Guitar Guy's pretty damn good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 07:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You Only Use 

A Relayed External 

Network On The 

Sites And Files Expected,

Never On Windows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't open this message. Seriously. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 03:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 00:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fur is murder!" *ruins fur coat with a new paint job*

Wearer: *shrug*. Guess I gotta get someone to murder more things so I can wear their fur. *#dealwithit*

and the cycle continues, ad infinitum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 22:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one bothered by the fact that whoever recorded this kept focus on the shark corpse even while the babies were being returned to the water? We're missing out on some majestic shit, here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 16:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Man...I just started playing Morrowind for the first time yesterday, so I thought this would he a helpful post I'd randomly found.

Nope. Nosleep weirdness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 19:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange as it may sound, breathing.

Take a moment, and slowly fill your lungs up completely. Not til it hurts, but just a bit more than usual. Then let it out, just as slowly. Now, keep doing that while you read the rest of this.

Practicing this deep breathing has a few benefits that I have directly seen. Your heart rate slows down, which can help relieve tension and reduce headaches. By now you should feel a certain amount of calmness that wasn't there before, even though you haven't been doing it very long.

In addition, letting more clean air into your lungs oxygenates your blood more, which can help reduce muscle fatigue, improve mental acuity, and even promote healing. 

At this point, you should already feel a slight increase in your energy levels, but it also works the other way around. Breathing like this can actually help you fall asleep faster. So, it helps when you're active, and also when you're at rest!

Okay, you can breathe normally again. You know, if you want to... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 05:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fought and defeated this boss in quite possibly the least "in the spirit of the game" method possible.

Basically, I found a very specific spot in the entry cave where its projectiles couldn't hit me, but it was still within range of my arrows. One hour later, and I whittled it down to submission.

I knew it was cheap, but it was still satisfying to have taken down something that had me so horribly outclassed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 23:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm sorry, but your child's mother said that we're not to release her to you."

Said to me as I'm trying to pick up my daughter from the daycare my ex wife picked, which I had to pay for, for my twice weekly four hours of visitation.

I was literally floored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experiment no. 17 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 19:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 20:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/40Idny0.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 18:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case, let me give you some feedback.

The pacing was a little strange, your transitions could be a bit more apparent, like when they suddenly appeared in the car (not the only place, but the most jarring). A simple page break might help the flow.

The story was witty and well written, otherwise, pretty much exactly what I'd hoped to see from this prompt.

My only real place of concern is the ending. It was funny, but dark, in a way that might put off readers. I thought it was good, but you may risk losing some of your audience with it. That said, it was just the right level of dark, suggested instead of stated.

Just my opinions, of course, but overall, nicely done! I hope you'll put more stuff out there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 17:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was hilarious! Wonderful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A car salesman goes on a test drive with a customer, who turns out to be a bank robber in need of a getaway car for an active heist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 19:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 16:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, let's see... Not in numerical order, unless there's something I can't see... Not in series order, given the various authors... Not in alphabetical order by author OR title... Not arranged by color, height, or thickness...

Damn. I quit this bookstore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 18:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you ever find a fix? I'm having the exact same issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be stranded with Adam Savage and Jamie Hyneman. I would be the exact opposite of fucked.

Especially if we had a pallet of duct tape.

* enter nerd fantasy world * </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That was upsettingly... Freeing. Nice one, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! One critique: I think you wrote "horridly" at the beginning, but might have meant "hurriedly." Other than that, fantastic!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome! I had Live Free or Die Hard running through my head for the whole read. This is exactly what I'd expect the news to show. Thanks for the good read! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] An action movie, from the perspective of an ordinary citizen just trying to get through his/her day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he happens to be at every major exchange. Maybe it's all just a blurb on the news. Maybe she's directly affected. Let your imagination flow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 23:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...barstool? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 16:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't feed the trolls, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 23:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have read (I don't recall where) that every character you create tends to represent a piece of yourself. The comic relief stems from your sense of humor, the hero or villain from your own morality, the support cast from the many highs and lows of your own ego or psyche. The best way to know any of them is to just let them talk.

It's all you, all your mind. You can't try and force the characters into a role. Let them tell you how they're going to act.

An example: I have a character in one of my works that I never planned to create. He started as a filler, who turned into a recurring theme, and after two or three rewrites, he's now a minor recurring character, with his own history, motivations, and hardships to overcome. I didn't plan out any of it; once the character was "born," he told me all about himself.

I think I'm almost rambling now, so I'm gonna cut myself off here. Hope this helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 16:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a worthwhile one-time watch, to be sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 13:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This prompt reminds me of the movie, "The Brass Teapot," which has the same premise, but diminishing returns. 

Your take gives the concept a whole new life. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 21:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extreme Chutes and Ladders.

The board is a 30m high grid of 3x3m squares. Game is played with actual ladders and slides, some covered, some not.

More extreme versions have traps in the slides, and inconspicuous breakaway rungs randomly placed in the ladders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 15:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I've been seeing it in girls of all ages for decades.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 14:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My coworker's jacket. I pull the hood string tight. He's wearing it, so I got smacked. Now he's fumbling to fix it. Still fumbling. Lol, it's loose mow, but lopsided. He's trying to straighten it. Mission accomplished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 14:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they talk, every sentence has an upward inflection at the end? As though they're asking a question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose that's worth try. I'll see if I can get anywhere with that.

Honestly, I hope it works. My foster parents are really upset since the accident. I don't want them hurt if they accidentally make me mad... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 18:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. I have no idea how to interact with her directly. I know she's there when the bad things happen, but I don't want anyone else to die for me to speak to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 15:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe. Maybe not. I get the feeling something like this was bound to happen eventually.

I just wish it had been someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 13:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure there's anything worth an update. My Godmother (as I've come to call the Golden-Eyes) seems to only act in my best interest. I wasn't arrested, and in fact am sitting quite comfortably at home.

My foster parents don't seem too happy, though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Golden Eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 03:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they knew the truth about me, theyd never let me live.

Im not insane. Im not evil. Im not dangerous. But knowing me is.

It started when I was born. The earliest memory I have is of a vaguely human face with golden eyes. For the longest time, I thought that face belonged to my mother. 

I remember it looking down at me, tilting side to side, swaying gently and cooing at me. I remember feeling the deepest love Ive ever known, lying in my crib.

My next memory had me walking, my mother kneeling in front of me and encouraging me onward. There was someone behind me, holding my hands and guiding me forward. Then I felt the support fall away, and I was afraid. I didnt want to fall, didnt want to get hurt. Out of fear, I pushed one foot forward, then the other, and eventually managed to waddle over to the safety of my mothers arms.

I dont know who the other person was. It might have been my father, but I never knew him. According to my mother, he died shortly after I learned to walk. I dont remember his face, or his voice, but I certainly havent missed him.

Mother tried to replace him, though. Time and time again, with one man after another. They all tried to worm their ways into my life - my heart - but they always ended up disappointing me. They hurt me - by spanking me, or shouting at me - and then they went away. I never knew where, but I assumed that my mother had sent them away because of what theyd done.

I didnt like it. They were nice men, but they always went away. I tried to be good, to be the model child, so that they would stick around. I liked feeling like I might have a father in my life.

But they always left. I didnt know what to do. I was so disappointed and hurt, every time they left. Eventually, that disappointment turned toward my mother.

The last man went away a week before my birthday. I tried to be a good son, I didnt want to hurt my mother by asking hard questions, but I just couldnt hold in my pain anymore. I asked her one day, where did they all go? Why did they leave?

She just looked at me sadly and said, I dont know, sweetie.

Such a cop out answer. She couldnt even tell me the truth? I know I was only four, but even then I could tell that there was something more going on.

I hated her for keeping the truth from me. I hated her for lying.

She died before my birthday. My present was being put in the foster care system.
It was a nightmare. I didnt know anyone. I didnt trust anyone. And nobody trusted me.

It didnt last long, though. In the night, a week after I arrived, almost everyone died. Some sort of freak gas leak, theyd said, made everyone suffocate in their sleep.

Everyone but me, and four other children. They were the only ones whod been nice to me until then, so I was glad.

I was lucky after that, when they sent the four of us to the same care house while they fixed the gas leak. We werent the only kids there - five more kids were already living in a four-parent home - but we knew each other, and that was enough. We all got along well enough.

Apparently, the parents liked us, because they said we could all stay, even after the gas leak was repaired. I was happy, but Lenny - one of the kids from the group home - said he wanted to go back. That made me sad.

He left without saying goodbye. The adults didnt want to talk about it when I asked where he'd gone, but I knew the truth. The traitor had left me.

But I still had the others. Derek, Angie, and Sarah.

We grew up together, the four of us. By high school, wed grown inseparable, the best of friends. We went everywhere together, did everything together.

One night, we went to the movies, all four of us. I wanted to sit next to Angie, but Sarah pushed her way in. Derek slipped in next to her, and Angie ended up at the far end. I was disappointed, but the movie looked good, so I didnt think about it much.

Halfway through, I realized Sarah was cuddling up against me. I looked over toward Angie, but she had fallen asleep against Dereks shoulder, so I just tried to ignore it and focus on the movie. It proved difficult, as Sarah had decided to start rubbing my arm.

I wouldnt say that Sarahs unattractive or anything, but I was never interested in her. I wanted Angie.

I tried to act nonchalant, to shift away so that Sarah would get the point, but she just slipped her hand down to my leg, idly rubbing along the outside as I focused on the screen.  Then, she slipped her hand down to my inner thigh, reaching up to grab my privates. 

I freaked out and jumped up, yelling, What the hell are you doing?!

And then I saw it. Angie had her head down in Dereks lap, but she wasnt sleeping. She pulled her head up with a *pop* at my outburst, clearly showing me her grip on Dereks turgid shaft, a line of drool still linking it to her lips.

I was at a loss. I walked out of the theatre, and though Sarah tried to chase me down and apologize, I left her standing in the lobby. I couldnt even speak.

I hated them all so much right then. Derek had my Angie. Sarah overstepped her bounds.

Angie had betrayed me.

I walked home, furious and fuming. I wasnt watching where I was going, and so its no wonder that about 45 minutes later, I crossed a street without looking. I was nowhere near an intersection, and honestly didnt care if I lived or died.

The first thing I noticed was the light. Not the horn, or the roar of the engine. A bright light, flooding the street around me. In that moment, I saw a face on the far side of the road, not ten feet from me.

The face was triangular, yet vaguely human, with golden eyes. It sat atop a body with limbs that bent strangely, and seemed too long for it. I was captivated by what I saw, and didnt notice the horn until it was too late to move.

Then the creature was gone with a *snap*, and I heard tires squealing. I spun wildly in place, just in time to see the oncoming truck swerve into the opposite lane of traffic, directly into a small blue Chevy.

It seemed to happen in slow motion. As the truck swerved, I saw the dark creature crouched on its roof, leaning over, almost like it was steering it. 

Just before the two vehicles smashed together, I recognized the blue car. It belonged to our foster parents, whod let us borrow it for the evening out.

Just after the impact, the windshield blew out by the force of the drivers momentum. Angies seat belt had snapped on either side of her chest, and trailed uselessly behind her like a death banner.

She skidded to a stop just feet in front of me, and didnt move.

I stared at her, numb, for what felt like forever, standing dumbly in the middle of the road. 

There was a soft *snap*, and the creature was back, crouching between me and Angie. It reached out a gnarled hand and stroked the side of my face gently, swaying its head from side to side and cooing softly.

And I felt more loved than I ever had.

Then it was gone, and a car pulled up. People poured out to help, calling the police, while I sank to the ground and stared at my childhood friends corpse.

As I sat on the curb watching them load my friends bodies onto the ambulance, I knew they were all dead. 

And I knew it was my fault.

The police came to me eventually, with a blanket, of all things. The officer asked me what happened, and I told him. They died because of me.

He wrote it off, said it was an accident.

I insisted. He didnt listen. 

I got mad, yelling. Dont you get it?! They pissed me off, and now theyre dead!

He got serious then. Detained me for questioning, put me in his cruiser. We drove off toward the station, but didnt make it very far.

The last thing I saw before blacking out was a face with golden eyes, crouching in the road ahead.

I woke to the rhythmic beeping of hospital equipment. I knew without even looking that something was wrong with my left arm, and my chest burned like fire every time I breathed. 

They told me I was in an accident. The car had hit a tree, and I'd broken my arm and bruised a few ribs. The officer had died.

I knew why. Those golden eyes were with me, now. Theyd always been with me.

They were there when I was born.

At my first steps, watching alongside my parents, when my father scared me.

At my home, when all of the men in my life - and my mother - had let me down.

In the group home, when I was hurt and scared by everyone.

In my new home, when my friend abandoned me.

And now, when my closest friends betrayed me. When the officer enraged me.

I dont know what it is, but its following me. Its been following me all of my life. And even now, as I sit in a hospital room waiting for the police to come interview me again, I can see the golden eyes watching me from outside the window of this fifth-story ward.

Im not sure whats going to happen next, or how Ill be leaving this place, but one things for certain.

Nobody better fucking upset me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 17:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a child misbehaves and isn't corrected, they will learn that it is acceptable to misbehave.

The same principle works for everyone. By covering for her, doing her work instead of yours, you are enabling her poor performance and enforcing it as 'acceptable' behavior.

 It's a pretty simple solution, here. Do the job you were hired to do, and leave her to suffer the consequences of her own inaction. She'll either improve, or fail and get fired. Either way, she'll earn whatever comes on her own.

I have no  pity for self-inflicted damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update posted, link at bottom of post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schism (part 2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 18:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one does. Not really.

Just keep going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 14:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don here.

There's an update coming today. Friggin' Dave can't take responsibility. I told him to put the story here because it's pretty fucked up, and he writes a floofy love story.

Don't worry. I'll be posting the truth later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 22:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 18:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna go ahead and stop you right there. 

You can't go into writing trying to appeal to "X" group. You write what feels like it should be written. If your character needs a mentor, give that to him/her/it. If a father figure is what's needed, give that. Sensei, leader, Sarge, whatever comes to the story when you need it, *that* is what you put in.

The second you lose focus on your own inspiration and start trying to appeal to some outside group, is the second you begin to lose your intrinsic artistic fire as a writer.

That said... Do what you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 18:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, first and foremost, you've got a colossal run on sentence going there. 

Suggested edit:

-----
*He looked out over the fence at the ice-blanketed pond. It stretched out some tens of yards to the low stone wall, which wound along the edge of Gregory Boulevard, which itself stood before a ten-storey, forest-covered heap of mud encrusted with boulders.*

*"I should get a picture", he said aloud to no one*

-----

That's just to improve the grammar.

I tried to keep your adjectives in place. I would explain my editing choices, but really all I can say is that this version just makes more sense to me

As a reader, I would say you're being a bit too verbose. Why use 10 words when one could do?

Also, you've fallen victim to a classic writer's sin. Unnecessary use of long or uncommon words, which seem common to you, (such as encrusted, or aloud, or even using blanketed instead of covered or coated). These mess with the flow of the writing, even for educated readers. The thesaurus function on Word is your friend if you can't think of something relatably simple off hand.

Another suggestion, this time for reader's clarity.

-----

*He looked out over the fence. A low stone wall marked the edge of Gregory Boulevard, winding along the far side of the frost-coated pond. A massive, forest-covered heap of mud and boulders rose against the sky behind it all, framing the scene.*

*"I should get a picture", he mused.*

-----

This edit, I feel, makes for a better read.

Hope I helped! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 20:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither. I had to google that shit.

Not the answer, just the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 16:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got it. Biggest clue for me was the last line.

I'd say more, but don't know how to spoiler tag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't try to find me, or you'll be next </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 01:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Miles Krieg. I am a freelance private investigator. And I am about to die.

I need to get this message out to as many people as I can. Anyone who might possibly come looking for me is at risk. This community is my last stop, the last place people might try to reach out to me. I'm telling you now, don't. Leave it alone.

What follows are the notes on my last case. It's not any sort of official transcript, I just like to write down everything related to a case, to help myself remember any minor detail that might help.

I'm glad I did. Without these notes, I might not have made the connection. It's too late for me, but... hopefully I can keep others from suffering the same fate.

---

*From the desk of Private Investigator Miles Krieg*

**Case Journal #1: 4 January 2016**

Normally Id start out listing case notes and document control numbers for the official police paperwork. Let me start by noting that this is not an official police matter. I have not been commissioned, and dont expect reimbursement for my time.

A close friend of mine died tonight. A good man, a man Ive worked with on many cases in the past. Senior forensic pathologist Daniel West, at the city morgue, has given me more leads on homicides over the last decade than any amount of footwork. He was, quite possibly, the least selfish man Ive ever known.

Certainly not a man who deserved to be murdered.

Im getting ahead of myself.

At approximately 10:30 yesterday evening, I received a call from Daniel on my personal line. That in and of itself was an indicator that something was wrong. You see, Daniel never called me outside of the office unless there was a break in an active case, and Id not taken any new cases since before the new year. There was nothing on my plate, so he had no reason to call me directly unless it was urgent.

I didnt even have time to properly answer before he interrupted.

No time, he stated as soon as I picked up, his tone brisk and harried. No time, just listen. I think something bad is about to happen.

I remember my pulse quickening. Daniel loved to talk, always using ten words where one would do, so his clipped sentences caught my attention like a gunshot. Whats wrong?

I saw something I shouldnt have, and now I  aaugh!! He cried out - a loud, nonsensical sound, pained but not urgent, like someone had just pressed on a broken bone.

Daniel! Are you alright?

No, he grunted. No, Im not alright. Im afraid.

Afraid of what? 

I think Im going to die next.

My blood chilled at the sincerity in his voice. Where are you? Are you at work?

No! Daniel cried out, loud enough I had to pull the receiver from my head. NO!!

At home, then? Daniel!

Dont! he shouted, and then he screamed. A long, primal scream of rage and pain. Stop! Stop, damn you, why wont you stop?!

I heard the phone drop and bounce on his end, and knew Id gotten all I would out of him. He hadnt told me where he was, but he needed help, so I had to work it out for myself, and fast. I steeled myself, took a quick, slow breath to steady my pounding heart, and looked at the facts.

Hed said no about being at work, but given what had come after, that may have just been in response to his assailant's arrival. However, when he dropped the phone, it sounded like it had landed on some sort of thick fabric. I knew that the morgue didnt have any carpets, and he wouldnt have called me if he hadnt known I could find him, so he must have been home. 

It wasnt much to go on, but I didnt have time to waste. I was closer than the local PD, but just to be sure I gave them a call on my way out the door. I told them about the call, and that there was possibly an intruder in Daniels house, and dispatch told me an officer was on the way.

I knew their response time was slower than mine, though, so I booked it to the stairwell, because I like my exercise. 

Okay, mostly because the buildings elevators were slower than cold syrup. Anyway.

I got to Daniels home in about five minutes. It was a tiny house, the sort youd call a cottage if he lived in the woods rather than the suburbs. Hed lived there all his life with his mother, whod left it to him when she died some ten years ago. The front door was locked, so I just grabbed his key from under the mat and opened it up. 

Side note: It didnt occur to me until I wrote it just now, but there were no signs of forced entry. Locked door, no cracks on the frame, no broken windows. Well, thats what these journals are for, to help piece things together after the fact.

I threw open the door and called for Daniel, but heard nothing in reply. I ran through to his room, threw open the door, and saw him lying on the ground in a pool of blood.

My stomach heaved at the coppery smell, but I rushed to his side to check his vitals. He had a pulse, but only just. Quickly, I checked the rest of him. No chest wound, nothing on his neck, so where was the blood coming from?

Then I saw. His right ear was missing.

Oh, god, I remember hearing. I suppose it was me. 

I looked around frantically for something to block the wound, and ended up grabbing his bedsheets. As I pulled them over to press against his head, something tumbled onto my lap.

His ear.

I dont know how much time passed before the police arrived, but Im glad now that Id had the foresight to call them ahead of time. I was in no fit state to do anything until well after they dragged me away from my dying friend. My mind went somewhere else, screaming blindly into the darkness.

Numbly, I watched them load him up into the ambulance. I was herded into a police car, and we followed him to the hospital. Midnight came and went, I sat blindly in the ER waiting area for hours, barely blinking until a doctor came out sometime around dawn.

Hes lost a lot of blood, I was told, but hes stabilized. Weve had to sedate him, so hes resting now, but you can go see him if you like. Just dont expect much of a response.

I stayed behind at first, not wanting to face my mutilated friend again. The images of his pallid face, his ear falling into my lap were still fresh. I know theyd probably managed to reattach it, but I just couldnt seem to drag myself up from my seat. I watched all day long as his coworkers and friends flowed in and out of his room, all teary-eyed but grateful that hed survived the ordeal.

Finally, around mid-afternoon, I pushed myself out of the chair and went in to see him. Everyone else had gone by now, so it was just me and him in the room.

In stories, people often speak of how peaceful their loved ones look in a hospital bed, as though theyd be fine once they wake up. Daniel didnt look fine. Even in his drugged sleep, with bandages wrapped around his head, he looked tortured.

I was scarcely there a minute before his eyed fluttered open.

No, he groaned, his voice terribly hoarse, as though hed screamed all the life out of it. No, no, no

Danny? I said. Youre awake?

No, no It hurt me to hear him like that.

Danny, who did this to you?

It was him

Who?

The man in the cell Wilcox.

Whos Wilcox?

Last week died in the cell I did the autopsy. Ever since his voice faded, his eyes scrunched up in pain.

Danny, please, did you find something? Is someone after you?

I cant I cant, you have to go, or itll get you, too! He started getting louder, now, despite his hoarseness.

What will? Danny, what is it?

Cant you hear it? he rasped. The screaming It wont stop, it wont stop

What screaming? What do you mean?

It wont stop It never stops! Power came back in his voice as he spoke, frantic volume pushing the rasp aside.

Then he started screaming. 

It was worse than before. Pain, rage, suffering, desperation, as though he'd lost all sense or reason. I saw his heart rate monitor start racing, but the tone completely lost under his voice. I raced over to the call button to get a nurse in, though Im sure it wasnt necessary at this point, but he fell silent before I reached it.

I mashed the button, one-two-three-four, before I realized what I was hearing now. A high ringing in my ears.

Daniels heart monitor had flat-lined.

I looked up, and he lay there, unnaturally still. Looking at him, something shifted inside of me. Outrage, fear, hatred. I had to find the man whod done this to my friend.

The nurse was there in a second, ushering me out of the room. I waited around long enough to hear them officially pronounce him dead before heading home.

My first step was writing out these notes. As I said before, my involvement in this case is not police sanctioned. Thats one of the perks of being freelance  as long as I dont get caught doing illegal things, Im free to pursue my own cases. No, my involvement here is purely personal. Im going to find out who would do this to poor Daniel. Once I do, well well see what happens.

My only lead right now is Wilcox. Ill have to look into that in the morning. Hopefully I can get a look at his case file, but itll be tricky with my best contact lying dead on a slab. Ill figure it out, though. 

I always do.


----

**Case Journal #2: 7 January 2016**

My head hurts.

I didnt react well to Daniels death. After I finished my last journal entry, I had a whiskey to calm my nerves.

And then another. And then a few more. 

I ended up draining a fifth that evening, and passed out until late the next morning. Hungover, head pounding, ears ringing, I felt like Id been laid out on the tracks and hit by every car in a mile-long train. I barely got to my feet to brew up a pot of coffee, which I drained in short order. The caffeine cleared my head a bit, but I knew I was in for a rough day.

I didnt have much luck at the station that day. Even though everyone on hand was still in shock from Daniels passing, they were amazingly tight-lipped about this Wilcox fellow. Even the receptionist, Lara  a sweet thing, not too bright, but more than willing to do anything to catch my eye, poor dear  even Lara was less chatty than normal. Even my last-ditch effort of asking her to lunch in exchange for information didnt bear the fruit it normally did.

For the record, I feel bad every time I lead her on to get case information, but sometimes youve just got to bite the bullet to get results.

I figured Id come in too soon, the wound was too fresh, so Id try again the next day (yesterday, now.) Plus, thatd give me time to kill my hangover.

Next morning, my ears were still ringing, but my head felt clearer. I hit the station bright and early to try and get more information, but was barely in the door when Chief Anderson pulled me into his office. The Chief was a lanky workaholic who almost never saw the sun, so he was pretty pale. We usually got along pretty well, despite my tendency to call him Casper now and again.

Krieg, he started  never a good sign, when he calls me by my last name  You need to leave this alone.

Leave what alone, Chief? Playing dumb often paid off with Anderson. He had a bad habit of letting out more information than he wanted to when I made him explain things.

The Wilcox case. Leave it alone. Its not your problem.

Why so nervous, Casper? You look a bit paler than usual.

Nothing. Its nothing. Andersons hands shook as he wiped his brow. Its just youre an asset, here, you know? Id rather have you on less risky cases.

Risky? I looked at him skeptically. Daniel said that Wilcox was dead. Whats the risk?

Andersons face flushed. I was on to something. But what?

Look, Miles, he said, struggling to stay calm. Why dont you go home? I know Daniels passing has to be sitting hard on you. You were his best friend around here, and Im sure you need time to cope. Go on, take a few days. Were not that busy here anyway.

I knew this was futile, so I threw up my hands in surrender. I left with no argument and no information.

I went back that evening, around shift change.

The station was packed full of people who were used to seeing me there, so nobody batted an eye at my presence. I even made small talk with a few of them as I worked my way over to where the case files were kept. Lucky for me, the station had transferred over to electronic filing in the last few years, so the newer documents were all online. A couple of people noticed me messing around over there, but they seemed satisfied with my claim that I was double checking on one of my recent cases. A quick search for Wilcox, sorted by date, brought up a short list of names, only one of which was dated within the last month.

I hit print, grabbed the papers, and was out before Anderson even knew I was there.

My head was pounding again by the time I got back home, so I took a few Ibuprofen and laid down with an ice pack on my head. Before I knew it, Id passed out. Residual hangover effects, I suppose. I hadnt had much to drink that day.

Which brings me to this morning. Woke up with my head pounding, ears ringing again, and quickly made a pot of liquid revival before sitting down to read the case notes regarding one Henry Wilcox.

The cops like to fill the pages with official terminology and other things to cause headaches, so Im just going to translate it here.

Wilcox had no police record prior to the third week of December. Hed never even had a reason to get in touch with them until one of his employees had apparently committed suicide at work. The intern, Keith Sanders, had been there only two weeks, and had seemed a little unstable the entire time, complaining about headaches and noises that no one else could hear. The day before they found him, hed been aggressive, and earlier that morning hed even gone so far as to violently shove a coworker aside whod brushed against him on the stairwell. They were about to let him go at the end of the workday because of it, but Keith had no way of knowing that.

According to Wilcoxs testimony, he was on the way to lunch that day, when someone screamed bloody murder in the middle of the office. When hed gone to investigate, hed found the intern lying dead on the floor with his right ear cut off. 

Reading that, I had a flash back to Daniels ear falling into my lap. Already, Id found a connection, but what about Wilcox?

Well, he was dismissed by the police without charges, and the death was ruled suicide by an official examination  by Daniel West.

The next page is where it got interesting, though. Apparently, just over a week later  the evening of the 26th, to be precise, a Saturday  Wilcox walked back into the station looking extremely agitated. Hed asked to talk to the lead on the Sanders case, claiming he had important information.

Well, they brought him back to the Officers desk for an interview, and thats where Wilcox, for lack of a better term, lost his shit. They papers say he had a manic episode, attacking the officer and two other people nearby before he was subdued and cuffed. They took him to a holding cell under suspicion of illegal use of narcotic substances, and they held him there overnight.

Apparently, his condition worsened. Not long after 11 oclock, he was shouting gibberish and crying, by midnight he was screaming and banging his head against the wall. He got so bad that they started processing him for transfer to a mental health institution.

Apparently, they werent fast enough. Wilcox beat his head against the wall hard enough to cave in the right side of his skull around the ear. He managed it when his guard wandered off for a cup of coffee, and was found by none other than my good friend Daniel West.

His death was ruled a suicide.

By this point in the case notes, I was already seeing a trend that I couldnt believe the police had overlooked. There were plainly connections here.

One: Daniels call to me, and his final moments, didnt sound like him at all. It was as though his mind wasnt working properly.

Two: Henry Wilcox, clearheaded and calm at his initial interview, comes back with information and then goes mad before he can deliver it, ultimately killing himself.

Three: The intern, Keith, found dead at work, who had exhibited similar behavior to Henry Wilcox before his death. To a different extent, of course, but similar.

And, of course, the ears.

My theory at this point is this: Keith was murdered. So was Wilcox, and so was Daniel. The killer seems to like to use hallucinogenic drugs to make his victims susceptible to his approach. Obviously more information is needed, but I believe that the killer knew Keith personally, perhaps even worked with him. That would explain how Wilcox had gotten new information a week later, and how hed been drugged before going to the cops  possibly in his coffee.

And Daniel, well the poor man must have found the toxin in Wilcoxs system during the autopsy, and the killer then went after him to cover his tracks.

Well. Thats all for today, I think. Im going to have to dig up more information on this Keith Sanders later. For now, perhaps a hot shower.

Note to self: make a doctors appointment to check for tinnitus. Your ear shouldnt still be ringing like this.


-----


**Case Journal #3: 8 January 2016**

Its been a long day. I almost didnt make it to writing this out, but I need to follow my own rules. Gotta get it out while its fresh, so I dont forget anything.

Id better hurry, though, before the whiskey takes hold. Maybe thatll stop my damn ear ringing. Or at least make me not care. 

I swear its getting louder.

Anyway, today I followed up on the Keith Sanders lead. Chief Anderson didnt give me any grief when I went to check the official records on the guy  probably because there wasnt much to it. Cut and dry, suicide case, no other police record. Same as Henry Wilcox.

Same as Daniel. 

Luckily, Keiths former coworkers were willing to volunteer more information than was found in the official records. Turns out, he and Wilcox worked at a traffic control center. Specifically, in tollbooth operations. Keiths job was monitoring the live feeds from the cameras at automated toll crossings. Specifically, he monitored the high-occupancy vehicle lanes, looking for violators. Even more specifically, he had one-third of the city's main east-west highway. But thats not important. I think.

Anyway, from what I could tell, Keith had only been employed there for a couple of weeks before killing himself, which matches the police report. Most of his coworkers told the same tale as Mr. Wilcox  that Keith was a strange man, increasingly prone to paranoia and violence, and that he was expected to be let go soon. Nobody really knew anything about him, though. He never spoke of friends or family, and other than other office workers hed slighted, there was no clear sign that he had any enemies. Certainly nobody there seemed to have any real problem with him.

I double checked with the HR department, and was given access to his personal file. He had nobody listed as beneficiary on his life insurance, no emergency contacts except his now-deceased boss, and lived in a small apartment downtown. All in all, Keith seemed an extraordinarily boring man.

Then why would someone want to kill him?

Nothing was adding up, so I stuck around for a while, asking more questions. Eventually, I stumbled upon a lady named Evey, short for Evelyn, who seemed particularly put off by Keiths departure. She seemed almost taken with the man, which seemed at odds with what everyone else seemed to say about him. A little more questioning showed that he hadnt always been so strange. Apparently, in his first few days, Evey found him charming and sweet, and had fallen for him almost immediately. Her face soured when she told me about his gradual transformation over the next week.

Apparently, it started with him seeming distracted. A few days later, he started to complain about a ringing in his ears, and later still, pain. With the pain came agitation, and despite Eveys pleas, Keith didnt see a doctor. It would seem that he was used to living without insurance, and didnt want to risk a large medical bill over something minor.

Roughly three days before he died, Keith closed himself off from other people completely. He never spoke without shouting, so he just came in, did his job, and went home.

At this point, I thought Id finally found a connection, but it seemed not only weak, but frightening. Still, a lead is a lead, and I had to pursue it. 

I asked Evey whether Keith had witnessed a death recently, or found a body, within a day or two of his first symptoms.

Ill never forget the confusion on her face, and the dawning comprehension. 

Well, yes, she said slowly. On his monitors, he saw a woman run her car into a traffic pylon at the toll station. She was thrown out, if I recall, died instantly. Keith got a picture of it at his station, and called emergency services out to help immediately. You'd be surprised how common stuff like that is around here, one every months or so, so I didnt think anything of it at the time.

She looked at me with concern heavy on her face. Do you think that had something to do with it?

I shook my head, and quietly changed the topic, but Evey had already confirmed my worst fear.

There are only a few things each death has had in common so far.

First, each victim was the first person to find the previous victim after their murder. Yes, murder. I dont believe any of these deaths were anything less.

Second, each victim suffered from similar forms of uncharacteristic and increasingly erratic behavior in the days prior to their death. Very likely, they were drugged. Possibly something psychoactive, nerve agents or something. In any case, they all had similar symptoms, from what I can gather.

Third, upon their death, their ears are removed or mutilated. The killer does not take it with him/her; the act seems purely symbolic in a way I cant yet fathom.

After reviewing the facts, Im left with only one conclusion. There is a killer out there, preying on innocent bystanders. His M.O. is to track down the first person to find his last victim, and make that person his new target. He poisons them, somehow, and strikes when theyre at their weakest.

Unfortunately that can only mean one thing. 

I was the last person to see Daniel alive. I was the first person to see him dead. And ever since, my right ear hasnt stopped ringing. In fact, its getting louder. Its starting to hurt.

I believe I have been drugged. I believe the killer is after me. And I believe I dont have long.

Ive got to dig deeper, find more information. I have to be ready before he comes for me.


-----

**Case Journal #4: 13 January 2016**

I am about to die.

I dont know who my murderer is. I dont know where it came from. I dont know if its human.

Ive run deeper into my investigation. The woman on the tollway, Leslie Bates, showed the same erratic behavior as the others in the week before she drove her car into the toll station.

Almost two weeks before that, Leslie had found her infant child boy in her crib. The child had been increasingly agitated and inconsolable for almost two weeks before he killed himself.

Yes. An infant committed suicide. Hed found a way to wedge his own right ear into the clasp on its crib gate, and hung from it until his fragile little neck popped. The only reason the parents noticed is because the incessant wailing had finally stopped.

Theyd thought it was a miracle, until they found him.

That infant had been born two weeks prior. On that day, an old man had escaped the hospital psych ward, stolen a security guards gun, and blew his brains out in the maternity ward. Guess where he aimed his shot? 

Yes, his right ear.

I couldnt find any more leads after him. Not a jot, not a trace. But the signs are clear.

The first person to see the victim dies, within two weeks.

It starts as a ringing in the ear, growing more persistent over time.

It never stops. It just gets louder and louder and *louder*.

Eventually it changes. The pain caused by the sound becomes physical. The ear starts to throb and itch, like somethings trying to claw its way out.

Or in.

Until you scream.

Once you do, it changes again. The pain rises, the noise changes, like a cacophony of demons wailing in hell, clawing at the inside of your ear, as though its the gateway for them to escape hell itself.

Ive already cut my right ear off, like the others, but I managed to stop the bleeding. It seemed like a good idea at the time, but it didnt help at all. 

If anything, its just gotten louder. The screams sound excited now. Like Ive done well.

Like Ive done what they want.

Well, I wont have it. And they wont have me.

This is my final entry on the case. Whoever finds this, you must know. You cannot come looking for me. You must not find my body. Or else this will fate will befall you as well.

It should be no problem. Very few people explore the deep woods this far north. Almost nobody could ever find the abandoned cabin from my childhood. And certainly no one would dig through the ashes that will be left behind to find my charred remains in the basement. But just to be certain, I will print a copy of these notes to keep with me in a fire box. Hopefully it will help whatever poor soul might happen upon me someday.

If you are that wretched soul, and you are reading this now, youve probably already noticed a ringing in your ears. 

If so

God help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 18:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! PCplease! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 13:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research cloning and genetic manipulation in order to rebuild the human race in the manner I find most pleasing.

I'll probably fail, but why not try? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 13:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this exact problem. It's the reason I'm struggling with finishing the book I've been working on for most of a decade.

I'm learning to overcome it, though, little by little. I put myself at the computer and tell myself that it's time to write. Not necessarily the story I want, but something. Thanks to this, I just finished a little side project that started as a minor passing notion. It's getting the creative juices flowing, and I may soon be able to continue with my goal.

I'm just following advice I've seen all over this sub at this point. Writers write, they don't wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 04:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. 

Would an albino neat-freak be considered a tidy whitey?

Another:

Don't argue with the man. Either he's right, or you're a racist. (regarding a black coworker who can't admit when he's wrong)

 And finally, in a conversation with a coworker who's getting a divorce he didn't want:

* someone else:* You need a blow job, man.
* me:* Are you offering to do that?

Not gold, but not bad, I thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 13:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't get better.

But you will get stronger, if you don't give up.

And then it won't *seem* so bad.

Stay strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 22:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point. 

Honest answer, yes, they think I'm weird. Hell, i *know* I'm weird. Obviously, some like me more than others, but I don't feel as though I'm truly UNliked by anyone. 

Or maybe they're just being polite. Ish.

Anyway, I'm usually okay with it. Today, though, it just hit me extremely hard. 

Thanks for the response, though. Just the right perspective to cool me off. Take pride in knowing you helped a stranger today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 22:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd response, but sure. Why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck people in general </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 22:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck my coworkers specifically. Everyone else can crack the dumbest, lowbrow jokes in the world, and they're apparently Robin fucking Williams. I try and join in, and apparently I'm about as funny as cancer. 

Dick and fart jokes=comic gold.

Idle, relevant, mildly amusing comment= murdering puppies in a blender.

I can't say shit in my work space unless it's related specifically to the job at hand, or I'm some kind of psycho, apparently. 

And I try. Dear god, I try. I hold back sooooo many bad jokes, soooooo many idle insights that might get misunderstood, trying to find some way to positively interact with people. I know I don't have great social skills, but it's like treading on eggshells with you people! It's bad enough that I get random anxiety attacks despite my medication, but having my every idle offhand comment picked apart by gearheads and rednecks, like I'm somehow less than human and don't have the right to speak out, really does a number on the ego. 

Fuck you all. You're the reason I want to drink myself stupid every weeknight. Hell, maybe if I did, we'd get along.

Nah. Pricks are pricks, drunk, sober, or hungover.

When the hell did I start caring what the fuck you thought? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you don't want to risk having a movie spoiled, stay off of social media sites until you've seen it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 05:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty simple. People suck, as a general rule, and as such they will do sucky things, such as posting movie spoilers or causing genocide.

You can't trust people you see day to day, let alone the faceless assholes on the internet who answer to no one but their inbox - which they probably ignore anyway.

That said, social media has no solid, lasting impact on your life. The most poignant things put on facebook, twitter (fucking twits), etc, are usually song lyrics written decades ago by artists they've likely never actually heard of (fucking Glee).

So, trust the stupid and inconsiderate to be stupid and inconsiderate. It's what they do.

Besides, it wouldn't kill you to fucking unplug for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 17:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do not fuck with the Zohan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 18:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just clicked, have read, can confirm. It's hitting me harder every second it's in my brain than it did as I read it. Will likely blacken my soul by day's end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 19:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spoiler](/s "Check the man's shirt for cat hair. They will most likely match the color you find.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] One morning, the entire world forgets everything about money, in all its forms, and how it is used. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would people function if this core concept of global society simply didn't exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 18:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. So do all colas, like Coke and Pepsi.

And all lemon-lime sodas, like Sprite and 7-Up.

And Dr Pepper is exactly the same as Mr Pibb.

Budweiser and Guinness? Same shit.

And Wild Turkey is clearly not inferior to Jameson.

Look, you could subjectively rule that dicks and vaginas taste exactly the same, and still know which one you prefer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 00:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Building, maintaining, transporting and operating non-destructive in-line inspection tools for oil and gas pipelines worldwide.

We were cleaning one from a crude oil line today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 00:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's part of my job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 20:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drank it without looking.

 Expectation != result. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no... Thank *you.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no idea how many times I've been compared to known serial killers. This is the first one I'm okay with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extra large gloves on large hands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This just ruined my day. (crosspost from r/pics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This just ruined my day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 01:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a celebrity exit organization that orchestrates their fake deaths when the celeb is too famous to step out of the limelight on their own.

Sure, some are real, law of probability makes that certain. But, really, how many drug overdose are we expected to just believe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 22:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Whisk is still great, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 20:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My preferred method has 1/3 bag added at a time, which I stir in with a whisk before adding the next 1/3. Works like a charm, and no lumps. Best part: No messy leaks from bad seals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 13:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two astronauts float up to a Space Bar.

"You know," says one, "this is a terrible pun."

The second astronaut puts down his drink. "You think that's bad? It's even worse as a punch line!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
