<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8754</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the flies. They're everywhere and are seriously disgusting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh fuck right off. Why don't you try to mix with them and see where that'll get you. Recognising gypsies and North Africans as non-friendlies the first thing that the locals will tell you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well as usual, was in a room at Schnbrunn with a lot of PRC tourists and the guards were complaining about 'stupid Chinese'. Kind of true though, I don't blame them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 11:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's way too hot there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 11:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I speak French so the language issue isn't that much of a concern. People suddenly become friendly when you do speak French with them. Cost of living seems lower than Singapore based on my 1 month living there. Had no problems with racism (unlike in Vienna) if you avoid those North Africans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paris. The sights, the food and the culture are so exciting. 

What's wrong with Reddit? Downvoted for answering OP's question? WTF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you actually can? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Android should be easier to use and perform better without the need to tweak every single thing. When I had an Android phone, all I could think of was rooting the phone, installing root tweaks and trying out different ROMs just to see if any one of them would run as smooth as iOS. It's such a frustrating and time consuming ownership experience. 

Oh, and also the nice bounce overscroll effect rather than the sudden halt when you reach the end of a page in Android.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They put the VIP in quotation marks, so I guess they knew that it would generate some controversy, but it's nice of them to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play on Assetto Corsa with my G29 but not with other people. Just against the AI.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, that makes sense based on my limited understanding of quantum physics. Alright, into the LHC I go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't time slow down as I approach light speed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time should pass faster... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was wrong with the R63? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's big and slow and will never see snow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me more things to test! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 13:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 12:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the same basic PSA engine. Mine comes with a DCT. No manual option on mine haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha what a rare car we have, but mine's right hand drive. Is yours a manual or an automatic? Diesels are great where I live since it's so much cheaper than petrol (~US$0.70 vs US$1.70).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. Waze is how I've avoided speeding tickets for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now put that engine in an A/B Class. Or the Vito van. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I have the same car with 5 more HP. 3.9L/100km is the best I ever did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The exception doesn't make the rule.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always Wilmar when it's something to do with plantations and clearing of forests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Indian IT 'Professionals' are in the same league as Pinoy IT 'Professionals'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling the dealer's not fixing the problems correctly if the same parts keep failing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think one improvement I'd like to see in the old parts of the map is simply to make curves less jagged. That alone makes Germany and other parts look really old, when you look at the broken curves on the highway lane markings. Shouldn't be too complex to fix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Questionable rim choice and really disappointing engine note for a Ferrari. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a local racetrack for track days. This will definitely reduce the prevalence of street racing. Anyone can recall why the one at Changi never materialized? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chiron

Rolls-Royce Phantom EWB

Mercedes G63 6x6

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 08:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say one of the worst for me is NEX. Too cluttered, too crowded and the carpark design is terrible and far away from the mall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 08:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an irrational hatred for Giant. Their yellow, green and orange theme is just revolting to look at. And the whole place feels like Malaysia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in an Asian university and most of the smokers I see are Caucasian professors and exchange students from Sweden.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because a car to many signifies freedom? You can be stuck in traffic, but you have privacy, unlike being stuck on a bus or a train.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the soundproofing on the Mercedes truck is too good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? Not everyone values life the same way. It might be sad and depressing, but it's still entertaining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't know window ledges were no longer allowed to be counted. No wonder new projects don't use them anymore. My condo's air-con ledge is quite reasonably sized, but I used to stay in another where the planter was huge and mostly inaccessible, and more importantly, not visible enough to warrant putting plants in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know why but McDonald's Classic Cheese burger. I think I just love Garlic Aioli.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 04:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $500 a week in rental? I think you can get a new car with a monthly installment of less than $2000 a month. And in the end you own a car and can sell it, although there's depreciation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those were the turning lights. Since the driver decided to go straight (from the wrong lame), it was still technically legal for him/her to do so since the lights for straight-away is still green.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically the driver didn't run a red light; it was green for vehicles going straight-ahead. The driver was in the wrong lane though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's passenger cars that are always the target of such investigations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't authorities target truck and bus manufacturers too since their vehicles rarely comply with emission standards once they've left the factory floor? I see buses marketed as Euro 5/6 spewing ridiculous amounts of soot continuously, even when they've just been on the roads for a few days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be nice to have some loud radiator sounds, which I hear a lot on YouTube videos but not in-game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't know it was that cheap. No wonder it's taking off with cab companies everywhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a ride in one and honestly it wasn't a very good car at all. The plastics were hard and nasty, and it's by far the loudest EV I've seen. The whine from the motor's quite noticeable and the range's not really sufficient as a taxi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sustainability Prof boasted about her $1 water bill. She lives in a landed property, which makes it even more incredulous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does everyone find this offensive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the company also makes a truck called Ant and a motorbike called Motochimp. Why have we never heard of them before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not again. There's so much congestion because of the road diversions. It's been years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup I use SingTel for home fibre and on my mobile phone. Both have been extremely solid other than very occasional outages.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 07:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I make a joke here?

Because you look like an ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Singapore. We have massive taxes on cars, that's why it was about 100k for a base model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 09:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Volvo S80. Bought for $168k new in May '15, now worth $105k. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 11:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how he called out Middle Eastern countries on their human rights issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spoke Cantonese at home since young. As a result, I do not have a natural Singaporean accent when speaking English or Mandarin. It's awkward when speaking either (BBC or CCTV style) since I have to purposely slip in some 'Singaporean' intonations to make it sound more natural.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 15:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12.8 seconds. Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine a Cadillac Escalade with a turbocharged 2.0L inline-4 being sold in Europe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 02:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The front grille looks out of place on such a classy car as this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually cheaper now unless you use more than 2000L of diesel annually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone out there using the iPhone but can't be damned about the rest of Apple's products? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our McDonald's burgers seem really well put together when compared to what people are complaining about in the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halal pork.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $1500 for bank internship

Edit: what's with the downvotes? This is from personal experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to go hunting with a gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit a Trabant?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't take either often, but almost all taxi drivers I've encountered have no concept of smooth driving. Apparently the accelerator only has an on/off function.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I knew him. Not personally, but I was managing his performance (HR function).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 08:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds amazing but I doubt it will be commercially available within the next 10 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I do try to avoid establishments with a Halal certification. I don't like the fact that I have to bend over backwards and change my food choices to fit someone else's dietary restrictions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xenophobic is when I'm afraid of/dislike Malaysians. It's more racist since I don't want their majority to prosper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I avoid products that are Made in Malaysia. 


Edit: I don't know why I'm being downvoted for this. OP asked a question and I gave a valid answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 09:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a condo and don't want random strangers coming into what's supposed to be private property. I think most Singaporeans don't want random strangers coming and going around their sanctuaries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Volvo has the same DCT gearbox. You've got to learn to drive it like a manual. If you want it to upshift, let go of the accelerator for a brief moment. To make it downshift, 'blip' the accelerator once (more than you need to) and return to your desired throttle position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems underwhelming when they could have based this off the 6x6. If I were rich enough to afford this, I'll feel inadequate knowing that there's a bigger G Class out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most autistic people have some kind of learning disability. Learning disability = retarded when not bothering to be politically correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 10:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like she's retarded too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should be both touch and rotary dial controls for the infotainment system. I like touch screens and hate my BMW's iDrive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only they made such soft cars today. I just want a car that floats and glides over bumps without having to buy an S-Class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learnt to drive in a RHD manual car, rented a LHD manual car and it was much easier. I think it's strange that lower gears are away from you. Probably depends on whether you're right or left handed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's what happens when you sell extremely outdated Lancers and trash like the Mirage. The Outlander PHEV is doing great in the UK but Mitsubishi's reluctant to expand their market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drove home when my mum came to pick me up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 11:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least the meetup location was at my home. I wouldn't have bothered with the deal otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buyer came 4.5 hours late. How can someone be so useless at being a person? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Stop sharing the folder on your network.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 09:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you please upload the Blizzard Mountain folder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 08:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drive with your headlights on even in the day to get other drivers to get out of the way. Bonus: drive around with high beams.

Unethical, but be aggressive when dealing with service staff. Usually you'll get things more things done sooner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What other comment? The only other comment is about Sharia Law and that's another pile of shit altogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Researching more of what? Violent verses? Aren't those above sufficient to prove my point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quran (2:216) - "Fighting is prescribed for you, and ye dislike it. But it is possible that ye dislike a thing which is good for you, and that ye love a thing which is bad for you. But Allah knoweth, and ye know not." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh come on. Those that deny god's revelations = infidels = non-believers. You can't be that thick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 05:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter when these were written. And there are many more of such verses. The fact of the matter is that such verses remain in the Quran today and is used by overtly-devout followers to justify Jihad. Try explaining these:

Those that deny Gods revelations shall be sternly punished; God is mighty and capable of revenge (3:5)

Those that deny Our revelation We will burn in fire. No sooner will their skins be consumed than We shall give them other skins, so that they may truly taste the scourge. God is mighty and wise (4:5556).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Islam perpetrates beliefs that are incompatible with modern society. It's genuinely worrying to see Wahhabism's spread in the recent decade or two. And you can't claim that the Quran doesn't encourage violence when there are verses like these:

Quran (3:56) - "As to those who reject faith, I will punish them with terrible agony in this world and in the Hereafter, nor will they have anyone to help."

Quran (8:12) - "I will cast terror into the hearts of those who disbelieve. Therefore strike off their heads and strike off every fingertip of them" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat. That's super cheap. Even after discount I'm paying like $1.10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if it helps, when you get back you can euthanize it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must be a terrible Chinese. I've never heard of these practices.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I have never seen such queues before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many people queue at the petrol stations during CNY? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone knows why there are such long queues at every petrol station during this period? There was a record-length snaking queue around my area's Caltex. It can't be that everyone's running out of petrol at the same time right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best: PES E, watching movies like Braveheart

Worst: It's still NS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the PSA D2. Max it'll go with ECU tuning is ~136HP. Not really worth it. It's illegal here too since the 'tax band' restricts it to 120HP and below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 06:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I feel inadequate about my 115HP D2 :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if I tried pushing such barriers with my car's bumper, would it scratch the paint? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 04:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A rental Toyota Camry. It was just a car with no real redeeming features. It did nothing exceptionally well nor did it do anything notably poorly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate yellow noodles. Looks and tastes disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 04:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come at me bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 14:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prawn noodle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 19:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do I hate dogs then? Is this hormone not secreted when I stare into a dog's eyes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
