<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Wish My Roommate Was Here (Part 3) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 2 Here] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/69ga76/i_wish_my_roommate_was_here_part_2/?st=J2F58WVX sh=76333e8f)

With more context from my previous post, maybe you guys now understand why running into my dad was so terrifying to me. I wish I could say he talked to me and made amends and apologized and all that, but that most certainly did not happen (though thats what I told my mom). No, what happened was a lot worse

What are you doing here? I ask, short of breath. Is that any way to greet your father? He chuckles a little. I dont respond. Instead, I look around hoping people are still out and about. A sinking feeling takes over my stomach as I realize the campus has hit a dead period, where everyone is either in class, the library, or dorms. A person here or there crossed my eyeliner, but they were very far off. I look back at him and say, Sorry, I cant right now. Ive got studying and homework. I turn to walk away, but he grabs my arm  harshly and spins me back around. School can wait, he says, all grins and chuckles gone from his disposition. I pull my arm free. I have to work, I say with as much aggression as I can muster into my voice. His face twists slightly in anger. My dad always had an issue with people who refused to acknowledge him and what he wanted. I knew I was lighting a fuse as soon as I told him I wasnt going with him, but for once in my life I didnt care. 

Dont you fucking walk away from me, he said in a harsh whisper. I wish I had the courage to stand up to him, but I freeze. What do you want, Dad? I ask shakily. Ive protected you, kept you safe, done everything I could for you, and this is how you talk to me? He steps forward. I step backwards. Protected me? Protected me from what? I ask, anger flaring up inside of me. The fact that he not only saw nothing wrong with the way he treated me all those years, but that he actually thought he was helping me and being a good parent appalled me. The world, he says. All the shit in the world. I made sure you never once had to deal with any kind of  hardship in your life. You had it easy, he raises his voice. I cant believe what he is saying to me. My anger continues to boil. Easy? Easy?! You fucking raped and beat me! I exclaim. He grabs my arm again. All I ever did was show you I loved you. At this point, my anger gets the best of me. I shrug my arm out hot his grip, rear back, and punch him directly in the jaw.

I smirk a bit and turn around, heading towards my dorm. He cant do anything to me, Im on a college campus, I think to myself. Next thing I know, I hear him grunt with exertion and a crushing pain emanate from the back of my head, as if someone nailed me with a cinder block. Before I even have the opportunity to think I guess he can do something to me here, my world went black.

The next thing I remember, I open my eyes. They take some time to adjust, but I come to realize that Im in a car. Theres a terrible smell, as if every fast food restaurant in the US had stored food in this car and left it sitting out in the sun. At that point, the back of my head surges with pain, and I close my eyes again. Shouldve just fucking came with me, a voice calls out. I look again and discover Im in the back seat, my dads in the driver seat, and were moving. Where are you taking me? I try to sound assertive, but I fail to mask the tremble in my voice. I look out the window to see that were still on-campus, headed towards the main highway. Cut the shit, son. We both know youre not cut out for college. Youre not supposed to be here. Youre better off staying with me and helping me in the shop. I silently undo my seatbelt and reach towards the car door. Its locked, but I silently unlock it. I take a deep breath as the car picks up speed. We were hitting the main highway and I didnt have much time now. Yeah, fuck that, I respond to him. Simultaneously, I rip the door handle and shove the door open, leaping from the car onto the blacktop below.

The next 30 seconds or so are blurry to me. The car hadnt been going that fast, so I managed to jump out with minimal damage. The problem was, the other cars werent all exactly aware I was going to jump out of a moving vehicle in front of them and a chorus of honking horns ensued. Lights were flashing everywhere and I developed an overwhelming deer-in-the-headlights feeling. I ran back in the direction we had been driving from, passing the University sign at the very edge of campus. I never looked back to see what my dad had done, but I knew he wasnt going to just let me go. 

I sprint through the lower half of campus. Since there arent really any dorms or Greek life houses down here, I dont expect run in to anyone. I begin to wonder what I should do. Should I run to the upper part of campus and seek help, or should I continue searching the lower half for quicker help. Just then a thought occurred to me. My roommate worked down here in the football facility as an equipment manager. Its Friday, they should be practicing around this time. A small amount of hope glimmers in my heart.

I run to the building my roommate worked in and bang on the door. No one responded. I looked through the windows to see that all of the lights were off. At that moment I realized my roommate was gone for the weekend with his work. It was game weekend. Shit, I whisper to myself. You really shouldnt have done that, a voice echoes in the alley. Through the steam rising from the vents beside the building, a shadowy figure emerges. As the light hits him, I can see a massive sinister grin on my dads face. Thats okay though, I dont need you at home to have my way with you. Immediately after saying that, he charged at me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get where you're coming from man, this initial part makes me seem kinda like a spoiled brat or something. I share more in part 2 that I think will answer your question a bit better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Wish My Roommate Was Here (Part 1) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot even begin to explain this past year. Not fully anyways. Coming to college was a surreal experience to me. I mean, with my grades it was never in doubt, I just always felt like time would prevent me from ever getting there. Now I wish it had. 


The most exciting part of coming to college, at least in my head, was moving into the dorm. Co-ed, free Internet, restaurants on campus, with the potential for some of your future best friends to live just a few doors down? Yes, please! I was stoked. The biggest thing though was getting out of my house. My parents had spent the previous 2 years fighting and had finally decided to separate during my senior year. I hated my dad for cheating on my mom, I hated my mom for not leaving my dad sooner. Once my dad left, I thought that was it and that my life could roll on without him in it. Boy, was I wrong.


It all started about a month in to the semester. Classes were going well, I was enjoying my independence, and certainly enjoying the girls on campus (for those of you who dont know, there is a drastic difference between college girls and high school girls). Anyways, my mom called me one day to check up on me. We talked for about an hour and it was nice, until I was just about to hang up. Have you seen your dad at all recently? My mom asked. I attend college over 3 hours away from my hometown, so I was confused. No, should I have? I respond. My mom mentions that she and he had gotten into another argument in which she shouted at him that I wanted nothing to do with him, which was (and is) true. Apparently, he shouted back at her that he would come ask me that himself. Dread began to creep in my chest, that sort of heavy feeling falling over me. They were feelings I had not felt in a while. I dont want to see him, Mom. I try to sound as calm as possible, but a tremble snakes through my voice. I know hun, but I cant control what he does. If he comes up there and tries to get you to talk to him, just tell him you dont want to, my mom says. Yeah, that has worked so well in the past, I say immediately before hanging up with her. It was harsh, I know, but the dread that crept in had settled onto the top of my shoulders, sitting on my chest and weighing me down. It greeted me as if an old friend, which, I guess, is not entirely inaccurate. It was feeling I had never hoped to feel again. The rest of the night I was quiet. My roommate asked me what was wrong, but I simply told him I was just tired. The next day, things got exponentially worse.


I was walking from my first class to my second, when I had a disturbing feeling that someones eyes were following me across campus. I looked around and saw nothing but the hustle and bustle of students moving from building to building. As I re-focused my gaze forward, I saw a shadow dart behind a building. Its just a student getting to class, I mutter to myself. I worried that I was faking myself out, but I took another look at the building only to realize it was the building I was headed to. I shook myself of the worry because the shadow couldve been anyone, even though it moved suspiciously quickly. I walk into the building and make my way to my second lecture of the day.


As the day goes on, the dread lessens only slightly. I cannot shake the feeling that Im being watched. As I leave my final class for the day around 2 pm, I get another strong sense that Im being watched or followed as I walk across campus. I immediately stop and look around, startling classmates walking behind me but I dont care. As my eyes cross the iconic building of Old Main in the center of campus, my eyes latch onto something. There. By the fountain. A large figure, arguably masculine, stands shrouded in shadow by a tree. Hes too far away for me to see his face, but I can tell that hes facing me. I turn around, ducking my head and continue walking towards my dorm at a brisk pace. No, no, no, no, I whisper to myself. It cant be him, I think to myself. Why would it be him? Just because he and Mom got into a fight? My thoughts get cut short as I slam headfirst into someone. Oh, Im so sorry! I exclaim. As I look up though, my apologetic behavior is replaced with sheer terror. Thats okay. Its been a while, I was hoping to run into you anyway, the man smiles, but not a sincere smile. More of a wicked grin. The man I ran into was my dad.

I'll post more later, it's been a tremendously difficult time for me as of late. This story needs to get out there, but to do that I have to condition myself to tell it.

[Part 2 Here] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/69ga76/i_wish_my_roommate_was_here_part_2/?st=J2C5DX8U sh=5b8c2f8d) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
