<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7426</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some good food for thought. I haven't decided yet if I want the desert to be a "living" thing that is continuing to expand (creeping corruption) or if it is stagnant yet hella permanent. As far as a centralized location for where the magic occurred, I don't really feel there was one. See the updates I made above, but the magic was cast on multiple battlefronts in a collective effort to push the Manous theocracy back. This resulted in several meteors colliding with the planet and a dramatic reshaping of the terrain (things looked waaaaaay different prior to the end of the war). What is left of the desert once things settle down only represents maybe a third of the region where that final battle was waged against the God-Emperor's forces.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback. I should have mentioned this earlier - don't know why I forgot. The desert is not a naturally forming feature. It was the result of a large amount of magic being performed as well as the sacrificing of a few quasi-godlike entities. Otherwise I totally agree - it's super out of place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, I have a few races that could use some male and female depictions at your leisure! Feel free to go wild. Like real wild.

A mountain and crags dwelling race that I envision as about 75% humanoid and 25% elk. Not really centaurian, more satyr. Real tall - talking between 8 and 9 ft.

Fallen angels. Well, not really angels. But if a humanoid race was generally viewed of/thought of themselves as fallen angels. Again, go wild. Also, most other races generally hate these guys because they are dicks.

Albino, crippled cave slaves. Bred over multiple generations into their current state - used to be regular ol' humans. The more twisted, the better.

God bless your bored-ness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 16:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy world builders! I'm looking for either general feedback on my map but would love specific criticism on river, mountain and forest location. Feel free to pepper me with questions.

A little background information: There are four nations represented on the map, though it was not a goal of mine to have this map represent the political boundaries. The two main nations represented are the Manous and Vorcae. To the east reside the Trellen and to the west reside the Ageis.

**Manous Democracy**
The Manous Democracy occupies most of the region to the east of the Blackmirror Mountains that form a spine down the peninsula. Its capitol, New Union, represents the second iteration of the Manous people. The old capitol, Ash Throne, is one of the few remaining vestiges of the heretical Manous Theocracy. The theogracy once spanned the entire region depicted in the map, as well as most of the Ageis and Trellen regions, enslaving the other nations as it conquered them. The Manous have made reparations with the Trellen nation and have began naval trading with them across the semi land-locked sea. The Ageis are still openly hostile to the Manous and hold an uneasy peace enforced by the desert they border.

**Vorcae Clanholds**
The Vorcae Clanholds are the result of the young race slowly transitioning into a loose form of centralize governance. The two regional centers of governance are Four Winds and First Cave. The Vorcae are a much younger race than the other three, having formed after the God-Emperor War that shattered the Manous theocracy. The Manous helped lead the Vorcae into the modern world and the two nations hold each other in very high regard. Because of this, the Vorcae act as a watchful eye on the desert to monitor any Ageis activity.

**Trellen City-States**
The Trellen City-States are a collection of self-governed hubs of commerce and industry. This nation is a leader in invention and the arts and is quick to adapt to changing circumstances. The city of Reach is the center of their northwestern most city state and is the port-of-call for the newly created naval trade routes with the Manous nation.

**Ageis Empire**
The Ageis Empire clings to the vestiges that remain of their culture from before the God-Emperor War. As a result of their enslavement and subsequent genocide, they seek violent reparations against the Manous empire and their Vorcae allies. The only thing stopping them, ironically, is the desert they created during the God-Emperor War. The desert was created as a result of a large consumption of magic that killed thousands of spell casters as well as ruthlessly sacrificed several quasi-godlike beings in order to put an end to the Manous Theocracy's regime of war and genocide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for map feedback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 16:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 18:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question - I am currently registered to vote at a past address in WI and just need to update my address which I plan to do at my new polling station today. Will I be fine with just my WI driver's license or do I need to bring additional documentation? My driver's license has my new address on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 18:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be taken with a grain of salt because I'm only partway through tCG right now on my first read-through:

* TtH

* MoI

* tCG

* MT

* DG

* RG

* BH

* GotM

* HoC

* DoD

But if we are being honest - I love them all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 19:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great! My only complaint is that I wish the bill summary section were put into layman's terms. Most of the ones I read were just pulled directly from the bill's text itself. Which is fine...but most are worded so that a simple person such as myself gets all wrapped up and twisted around! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 18:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I left off DoD and tCG because I am still working through the former (so I don't want to make any preemptive assumptions). I am curious how this will change with me during a reread. I suspect MoI is ranked so highly for me because it was my first moment of "holy shit...SE is just going to kill everyone I've ever cared about". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 17:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom is currently on her first read-through of the series and she is spacing each book out with a lighter, less dense stand-alone novel. I know she has had a little trouble remember who is who and where everyone is going/ended up in previous novels. If you take this approach, I would recommend glancing at the Tor reread of the prior books should you have a foggy memory when picking up the next volume after a break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 17:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth, here's a list the Malazan books (through TtH) ranked from least amount of crying to most amount of crying (done by me, so this is purely subjective ;p):

* GotM

* MT

* BH/HoC

* DG

* TtH

* RG

* MoI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 16:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hopefully TtH will be less emotionally straining.

Mweheheheheheheh....*breaks down crying* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't worry about *how* to read the books. Like The_Chrononaut said, they are just books. Just take your time with them and trust in the author. Sure, you won't understand a lot as you start the series. Hell, it was only by Mo! (book 3) that I started to feel like I was really getting my footing in the world. But also remember that SE has dedicated 10,000 pages to developing the world, its characters, and the tangled skein of plots and subplots. As long as you don't rush through and skip large parts of the narrative, you should do just fine.

As an aside, my mom has been spacing each of the Malazan books with a smaller, lighter read. She's had a bit more trouble keeping track of the characters and plots than I have, but I've been reading them one after another. The Tor re-read is invaluable and I read it after every chapter or after a group of chapters (if I plow through a bunch in one sitting). I would stay off the wiki and come here with questions - we are far less likely to spoil something for you than the wiki is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 14:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I own all the mmpb versions for the series and I've only had an issue with one of the books (BH). One of the blank pages in the front fell out almost as soon as I picked it up, so I think I just got a dud and it was unrelated to book thickness/rough handling. I carry these to work and they are in and out of my work bag every day, as well as travelling with me on trips. All the other books, especially the thick ones towards the end of the series have held up really, really well despite constant flipping back and forth to the maps and dramatis personae. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 22:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I was kind of assuming they would be picked back up on later, but I'm getting close to the end of the book and was still very confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 22:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...try this one on for size. I got my mom to start reading the series and she calls Anomander "Mandy". She has yet to meet Nimander, so we will see how this nickname holds water then. But talk about a nickname... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 22:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep reading for that one. I think you'll get answers to all that in RG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DoD - What the hell was going on with the thuderstorms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Draconus just got brought back into the wonderful world of Wu. And that was tied to a magnificent storm brewing over the Akrynaii and Barghast battle. But I'm still hella confused over what was just slaughtering people in the previous thunderstorms earlier in the book. Some non-spoiler enlightenment would be much appreciated.

Also can we talk about Draconus' entrance? And the ensuing conversation between the Errant, Killy and SL, as well as the one between Mael and Killy? So many things are being set up right now.....my brain is on fire! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree about her not being a "core" member. When they do refer to her involvement, it is defs in a more auxiliary role. God, now I'm thinking about the core BBs and getting all sad inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's such a testament to SE's writing and the payoffs of his stories that until someone mentions these sections I find I have totally forgotten about them. My brain has just created an "alright, this will be touched on later...moving on" filter thanks to this series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, and I don't think this is a spoiler, but when members of the remaining Bridgeburners refer to Apsalar in the capacity that she was a Bridgeburner, they refer to her as Sorry. From what I recall, she served in the unit for a number of years (3ish? am I making that number up?) so I would say she was one of them, just for a very brief period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm glad someone who has done a reread is tuning in. I felt like Heboric's vaguebooking was similar in style and effect to all the other crazy foreshadowing but it's nice to hear it confirmed. We should just have a thread or sticky of all the aspects of the series first time readers shouldn't get hung up on because they are foreshadowing/there for the reread, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though I'm not done, read ahead for answers. You have four more books left - literally anything and everything can and will happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you there - Heboric is the King of the Vaguebooking Warren when it comes to actually articulating what's going on. I'm on DoD right now and there a section where [DoD Spoiler](/s "he's sailing across the wasteland like some god damn ghostly apparition while communicating with Kalyth in her dreams. Wtf Heboric...I only understood about 0.015% of what was going on with his monologuing but it was interesting nonetheless.") I do think Heboric is a bit of a cypher - I'd be interested if that feeling is lessened in a reread as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 20:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just scedule once-daily five hour energy shot sessions to follow each book as you finish them.
They. Get. Worse! (Spoiler alert - it's awesome) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
