<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7661</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 00:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was scrolling through comments just to find this video. Brilliant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mate if corgis don't have tails then fine. I was wrong. But no way is tail docking fine in my books. 
Wrong on every level. 
Banned here in uk for good reason.  https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Docking_(dog)

As for circumcision. That's down to your beliefs. You can cut off half your dick if you want. Just cause someone don't remember doesn't mean it didn't hurt at the time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huge risk of getting downvoted. His tail has been docked. There's a few methods of how this is done but none of which are humane. Basically tie string or band really tight around base off tail when they are puppy. This cuts off blood supply and after tail will not grow   kind of die. It's then cut off. There are other methods, I'm not sure I'm 100% correct myself. Docking tails is common for working dogs in past when tails could get injured, while dog is working usually done for larger breeds of dogs.  Docking tails now are just so dogs look better   you can post pics/gifs of cute dog butts. The puppy suffered for this so make sure everyone upvotes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 01:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that you jay?

https://49.media.tumblr.com/4b74470f3b936007f4be048c04ee3c19/tumblr_n5enmjTs6o1qb39w1o1_500.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Name suggests quality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 20:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what you call a rock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much that cost? Must've been expensive with all the different strains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 00:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toad was the best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 23:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good reply.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 20:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the correct term is "nails on fleek". 
Not sure what that means tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 02:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always read comments. Someone else has thought it before you did. 
This guy would've been stabbed not his neighbour but was saved by his amazing headphones   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 20:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the toothbrush for?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 18:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You evil bastard. I'm going to tell the queen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 18:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care about that. Mods removed it. Reddit is basically everyone reposting. Good luck making it too top post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 18:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this pic before too. But mods didn't like my choice of wording. 

Looks just like a fag! Rolling papers https://www.reddit.com/r/trees/comments/3uet9w/looks_just_like_a_fag_rolling_papers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 20:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not loud but you definitely notice it. Noise is only bad thing about the lighter that you could think of as negative  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 20:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't but someone has posted a video of it somewhere in the comments  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 19:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the only reason to do it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 19:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only read about it from comments. Sure links been posted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 19:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.elementiumlighter.com/collections/plazmatic-x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 19:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very Easy to use, there is a button on the side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 18:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pics or it didn't happen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 18:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U wot m8

http://www.elementiumlighter.com/collections/plazmatic-x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 17:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.elementiumlighter.com/collections/plazmatic-x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 17:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My life is complete </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 17:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plazmatic X from elmentium lighters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 17:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a long list mate. Rather just stick my tongue in it lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 17:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much apparently cheaper to buy Chinese. 
From elementium lighters. It's called plazmatic X about $50 with shipping.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 17:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just saw it. Plus I don't have to burn my tongue or dick now either. Win win  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 16:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plazmatic X from elmentium lighters. Can get cheaper from China apparently. This was probably made there, just paying extra for branding I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 16:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plazmatic X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 16:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one killed me! Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 15:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had thought that if I was to stick my tongue into it and make video. I'd surely make the front page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 15:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What cartoon? I'm trying to see it but can't. I have been called brown cartman before but sure that's cause I'm just fat nothing to do with thumbnail lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 15:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not good. Just got it then leaned that could've got it like 4 times cheaper if I bought it from China.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new lighter uses electricity. Looks cool. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 13:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 20:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Karma is the only reason anyone would plasmerize their tongue   maybe get shocked to death! Nothing else would be worth it. 
Will see how this goes, might be getting a farm out of it;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 18:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just how close are you to dankruptcy?lol But If you happen to be the owner of one of them fine weed growing establishments with lots of trees freshly budding then your on!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 17:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I'm too high for all that lol. 
Although sticking my tongue into the lighter   filming it would surely get me to front page of Reddit. Ahh The dream   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 17:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading comments. Realised made amateur mistake, paying as much as I did. Why buy American when cheap Chinese knock off is available. This was probably made in China anyway. Just paid extra for it travelling to USA   branding 1st.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 17:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lot of reviews, but no video of anyone touching it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 16:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly. It's just so tempting to touch but will wait for someone else to do it 1st. Can't be that bad can it? Only one way to find out lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 15:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting video. Seems to work well but just looks a bit awkward using it. At least you don't get your fingers burnt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 12:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battery! Only just got it. Well report back on how long it last but that would depend on how much a person smokes. Think website said 1000 sparks per charge. Have to check tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 11:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smoke joints! Don't do bongs. probably wouldn't work well for a bong. Sparks my spliffs up nicely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 11:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plazmatic X </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 10:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shame about the weed. Looks like crap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New lighter! I think it's cool. Works well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 10:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 13:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should've been at the house of the guy who took it. Before they got there. You know where the people involved live. So go there beat them up. Even if you don't get weed back. They need a lesson that they can't do it again. Put word out they are lowlife thieves. And will be getting what's coming to them. Pick them off one by one. 

Like I said everyone's reaction would be different   situation is always different. Only you can decide what best course of action is. Obviously by coming on Reddit your not some psychopath who will go shot them all. So be smart. Plan your move. Sit back watch them get fucked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 17:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This kind of makes situation worse because there's always been "honour among thieves" that clearly these guys don't follow. If they got caught   weren't expecting too then they should've held their hands up   returned what's yours. Imagine this. You leave it alone but next party you guys are all at a party, drink   drugs   guns don't mix. You could end up doing something much worse than confronting these assholes now. 
Generally in groups some people are in the middle. You need to find someone both sides respect or fear. That can sort this out without a war because that's your only other option. Start cracking heads. They won't try it again. But this could alienate some of your friends in this group. Don't play the victim be the bigger man. Let all friends know what's happened. If you are in good group of "friends"  others in this group should be able to pressure the scumbags into knowing they done wrong   have to make it right. I'm sure most of your friends won't want to be friends with this lot knowing that they would steal from you. 
You hustle in silence from now on or you do something about it. 
I'd let everyone know what happened   let people know that shit will go down. Speak to friends who you know will go and tell them everything. That way they will get message. Honestly don't go into this half hearted. They already robbed you   probably won't have issues beating your ass. If your not the type of person who is willing to fight. Then don't get into the fight. You can live happily   peacefully being the nice guy. Sometimes the war will cause you more trouble than the theft. Just comes down to how you want to react.  I'm at(0) just Incase my ramblings sound like I'm high. Weed is not worth killing over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
