<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2724</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy activists to gather at Apple stores in solidarity against FBI demands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 23:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy activists to gather at Apple stores in solidarity against FBI demands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 22:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy activists to gather at Apple stores in solidarity against FBI demands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 22:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digital Rights Group Organizes Rallies Outside Apple Stores to Support Apple Against iPhone Court Order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Queer activist musician Evan Greer plays two shows at Wandering Goat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 01:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyonce and Jennifer Lopez urged to boycott Israel. As reports of concert dates swirl on social media, activists ask stars to stand in solidarity with Palestinian people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 17:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyonce and Jennifer Lopez urged to boycott Israel. As reports of concert dates swirl on social media, activists ask stars to stand in solidarity with Palestinian people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 16:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyonce and Jennifer Lopez urged to boycott Israel. As reports of concert dates swirl on social media, activists ask stars to stand in solidarity with Palestinian people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 16:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Would Ban State Efforts to Weaken Encryption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 23:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 20:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary previously supported the TPP, saying she hoped it would be the "gold standard" of trade agreements. She announced late last year that she can no longer support it as written. That said, a Chamber of Commerce lobbyist has said that he expects she would support it after the election. http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/statements/2015/oct/13/hillary-clinton/what-hillary-clinton-really-said-about-tpp-and-gol/

Bernie Sanders opposes it outright, as does Donald Trump and Ted Cruz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 20:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have the numbers on the expected vote splits right now, I think it's still very early to know. We definitely know that it's not DOA, and we definitely know that it's not a sure bet. This is very much a live fight and we need to be vigilant and fight hard.

Your question about which arguments are most convincing is really good and one we all need to consider. There are so many things wrong with the TPP that it provides a good opportunity to figure out which of those things the lawmaker you're contacting is likely to care most about and highlight it.

I think there are more resources out there on the left hand side of things, so here are some resources for why GOP should oppose the TPP (note I don't agree particularly with all of these framings personally, but I think they are helpful depending on our audience):

6 reasons free traders should oppose Obamatrade: https://www.conservativereview.com/commentary/2015/05/6-reasons-free-traders-should-oppose-obamatrade

Democrats working with Tea Party against Obama's Trade Deal: http://www.slate.com/articles/news_and_politics/politics/2015/02/democrats_working_with_tea_party_against_obama_s_trade_deal_the_president.html

10 Reasons Why You Should Oppose TPP and TTIP: http://www.thenewamerican.com/usnews/constitution/item/21010-10-reasons-why-you-should-oppose-obamatrade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 20:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think there are better uses for dildos. (!!!)

But the people here who have the power to stop this are U.S. congress. That's the theory of change for how we can still stop this deal. It's deeply controversial in Congress and faces opposition from both left and right. We need to get really creative and organized and put concerted pressure on lawmakers to make sure they oppose this deal when it comes to a vote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 20:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there's this, but it might not be the best thing for your mom ;-) http://www.fuckthetpp.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will New York Ban Smartphones With Security Protections? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not totally sure what you're referring to. There have been a number of major moments around the TPP in the past, including the fight over Fast Track legislation here in the U.S., but there hasn't been a vote in Congress on the agreement yet. That's our moment to stop it. Now's the time to be [contacting your lawmakers](https://www.fightthetpp.org) and demanding they vote no on the TPP. The vote could come anytime in the next several months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are planning a major "TPP Roadshow" in 12 strategic cities that will bring together high profile performers, musicians, speakers, celebrities, etc. to help spark large educational events but also targeted actions. I think there is a huge need for escalated action on the TPP -- the way to win this is in Congress, so people in local communities organizing creative protests and civil disobedience focused on their Senators and Representatives would be a very good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool. Will check that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, to answer the second part of your question -- the TPP will be the largest agreement of its kind in history. If it fails -- and Senator Wyden could have played a major role in helping stop it if he hadn't chosen to champion it instead -- it will be a long, long time before governments attempt something like this again. Any lawmaker claiming to support the TPP because it's the "best we're going to get" is just trying to save face while they support an agreement that's incredibly popular with large, incumbent, corporations, but harmful for everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full disclosure, I once [flew a 30' blimp](https://cms.fightforthefuture.org/wydenblimp/) over all of Senator Wyden's town hall meetings for a week protesting his position on TPP. 

I think unfortunately, in this case, Wyden's excuses are a bit vapid. He is the Senator of a state that has a big export economy, and some of the largest companies there, like Nike, are very keen on getting the TPP passed. Wyden is a bit of an ideological supporter of so-called "free trade" (there's lots of writing out there about how these to-down, secretive, and bureaucratic trade deals are anything but free trade or free market capitalism, but I'll let you google that). 

I think in this case Senator Wyden is turning his back on his Internet freedom values in order to appease powerful interests in his state. It's a shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The section on "Trade Secrets" is dangerously vague and broad and could be used to harshen penalties for whistleblowers who expose corporate abuse, or even journalists who report on the materials they provide. Source: http://www.crikey.com.au/2015/10/14/trade-deal-will-provide-new-weapon-against-whistleblowers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there are other serious issues that [EFF outlines here](https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2015/10/final-leaked-tpp-text-all-we-feared), but I also wouldn't gloss over the serious danger of codifying the U.S. copyright law like DMCA and exporting it to other countries. Our copyright system is already fundamentally broken and deeply unbalanced in favor of large copyright holders (like record companies, hollywood, etc.) as opposed to user' rights and free speech. There are [many examples](https://lumendatabase.org/) of how copyright has led to censorship and the removal of legitimate content from the Internet. As the Web expands and becomes more crucial in our lives, we desperately need copyright reform here in the U.S. The TPP would not only prevent that, it would lock other countries into the same broken system, and prevent them from making their own decisions about how to balance copyright and freedom of expression. The TPP specifically enshrines all the parts of U.S. copyright law that protect large rightsholders, while paying only lipservice to fair use and other protections for free speech. Exporting the bad parts of U.S. policy without the protections is dangerous, and could lead to widespread Internet censorship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whew! Love your passion.

I'll answer one of your questions and maybe others can answer others. 

Calling your representatives DOES HELP, but not all by itself. Hearing from constituents is definitely a huge part of how members of Congress make decisions on votes, but unfortunately there are lots of other factors, like who their campaign contributors are, what they're hearing from lobbyists and "experts" (sometimes real experts, sometimes "experts" paid by special interest groups, etc.)

The good thing is that organizations like the ones running this AMA are always using a variety of tactics to pressure lawmakers and make change. Bombarding Congress with phone calls is definitely one important piece of almost every legislative victory, so when you get an email from one of us asking you to make a call, please do! Sometimes even just a few dozen phone calls can sway a legislators vote.

Tweets are also a really good way to pressure lawmakers, so tweet at your reps too! 3

Fight for the Future has an easy tool for taking action on the TPP here: https://www.fightthetpp.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time to stop mincing words about the TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 19:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India says yes to net neutrality, no to Facebook's Free Basics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 16:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India says yes to net neutrality, no to Facebook's Free Basics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 15:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 14:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India Blocks Facebooks Free Basics, Other Zero-Rated Mobile Services Over Net Neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 14:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning has released her own podcast from prison  in which she opens up about her life, from being the victim of homophobic bullying to her transition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 18:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Downtown Boys headline Break the Chains in Boston tonight, dismantling the system one dance party at a time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 17:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 17:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks for the info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning releases podcast telling her story in her own words </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 15:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Listen: Chelsea Manning speaks to Amnesty International's podcast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 15:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The TPP was signed in Auckland, New Zealand Wednesday, but anti-TPP campaigners say the fight against the controversial trade pact is far from over. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The TPP was signed in Auckland, New Zealand Wednesday, but anti-TPP campaigners say the fight against the controversial trade pact is far from over. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikimedia foundation explains how TPP threatens online freedom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats TPP? The Problematic Partnership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 22:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'America's Most Exciting Punk Band' Is From Providence, They Aim To Change The World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 22:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TPP Protesters Alarmed by Corruption, Urge Leaders Not to Sign. Bribery allegations against Japan's lead TPP negotiator have sparked public concerns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 17:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 22:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! You weren't rude :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 21:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These issues certainly affect every PC user, and honestly this is one of the few subreddits that is not so heavily over-moderated that there can be a real free flow of discussions and ideas about things that affect Internet users. I hope for the sake of all of us that it stays that way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A top official negotiating the Trans-Pacific Partnership (TPP) has RESIGNED over bribery charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 21:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chamber of Commerce Lobbyist Tom Donohue: Clinton Will Support TPP After Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 15:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top official in charge of negotiating Trans-Pacific Partnership quits over bribery claims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 19:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be like Ed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 15:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top official in charge of negotiating the TPP accused of accepting bribes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 19:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Japanese official in charge of negotiating TPP accused of accepting bribe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 22:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Japanese official in charge of negotiating TPP agreement accused of accepting bribe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 22:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Taina Asili  The Singer Who Just Wrote a Black Lives Matter Anthem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 01:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Taina Asili  The Singer Who Just Wrote a Black Lives Matter Anthem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 01:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Downtown Boys to headline Break the Chains dance party in Boston on Feb 5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New BlackLivesMatter music video, "Freedom" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 16:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrorism Act incompatible with human rights, court rules in David Miranda case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 16:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 18:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah data caps are totally BS. One fight at a time though. We have to stop them from eroding the net neutrality rights we already have, then we can go on the offensive. Honestly the end goal should breaking up these monopolies so we have actual choice 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 18:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intentionally slowing down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 18:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally true. One good thing is that T-Mobile is really worried about customer opinion right now, so if we can stop them from doing this early it will send a message to other companies to not fuck with our internet
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile is violating net neutrality. They're throttling all your video, and their CEO won't stop lying about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 18:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile is violating net neutrality. They're throttling all your videos, and their CEO won't stop lying about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 18:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whitesboro Residents Vote to Keep the Towns Racist Logo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 17:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whitesboro Residents Vote to Keep the Towns Racist Logo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 14:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile CEO John Legere is a douche </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 17:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile's CEO got caught lying about net neutrality by EFF so he insulted them on twitter. Then we made him a new website. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 15:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile CEO John Legere got caught lying by the EFF, and now hes totally losing it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 23:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TransCanada launches legal action over Keystone pipeline rejection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 23:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TransCanada launches legal action over Keystone pipeline rejection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 23:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got my money's worth with this one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 00:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Reversal, Twitter to Let Politwoops Collect Politicians Deleted Tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 23:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Reversal, Twitter to Let Politwoops Collect Politicians Deleted Tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 23:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 23:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes indeed! Feeling pumped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Reversal, Twitter to Let Politwoops Collect Politicians Deleted Tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 23:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Reversal, Twitter to Let Politwoops Collect Politicians Deleted Tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 23:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is why the Internet matters so much to me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 15:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indian Regulators Suspend Facebooks Free Basic Services </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 21:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Telecommunications regulators in India have ordered the suspension of Facebooks controversial program to bring free basic Internet services to mobile phone users in the country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 21:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indian Regulators Suspend Facebooks Free Basic Services </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 21:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 17:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pretty good commentary on the state of cybersecurity today, using humor, but can post elsewhere if folks don't agree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa Claus confirms NSA attack on naughty or nice database </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 17:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa Claus confirms NSA attack on naughty or nice database </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 17:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pete Seeger's FBI file shows they first started surveilling him when he was an Army Private and wrote a letter protesting Japanese internment camps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 16:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 01:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for being a voice of reason in this thread, and thank you for donating to help cover the cost of sending the cards. We ended up sending more than 5,000, and all the costs were covered! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last-Minute Budget Bill Allows New Privacy-Invading Surveillance in the Name of Cybersecurity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 18:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imprisoned whistleblower Chelsea Manning is going to get more than 5,000 birthday cards this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 17:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last-Minute Budget Bill Allows New, Privacy-Invading Surveillance in the Name of Cybersecurity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 16:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning's 28th birthday. She's been in prison since she was 22. Let's make sure she gets more birthday wishes this year than ever before in her life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 21:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning's 28th birthday. She's been in prison since she was 22. Let's make sure she gets more birthday wishes this year than ever before in her life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 21:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning's 28th birthday. She's been in prison since she was 22. Let's make sure she gets more birthday wishes this year than ever before in her life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 17:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning's 28th birthday. She's been in prison since she was 22. You can send her a card, here's how </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 16:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Chelsea Manning's birthday and you can send her a card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 16:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is WikiLeaks whistleblower Chelsea Manning's 28th birthday. She's been in prison since she was 22. Let's make sure she get's more birthday cards this year than ever before in her life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 08:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Slips CISA Into Omnibus Bill Thats Sure to Pass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 18:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress adds contested cybersecurity measures to 'must-pass' spending bill. ACLU criticizes inclusion of Cisa information-sharing rules in year-end omnibus spending package amid concerns over privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 17:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress snuck a surveillance bill into the federal budget last night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 17:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress adds contested cybersecurity measures to 'must-pass' spending bill. ACLU criticizes inclusion of Cisa information-sharing rules in year-end omnibus spending package amid concerns over privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 17:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress snuck a surveillance bill into the federal budget last night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 17:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress adds contested cybersecurity measures to 'must-pass' spending bill. ACLU criticizes inclusion of Cisa information-sharing rules in year-end omnibus spending package amid concerns over privacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 17:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyber bill reportedly included in omnibus deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 16:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Drops All Pretense: Quietly Turns CISA Into A Full On Surveillance Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 23:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Drops All Pretense: Quietly Turns CISA Into A Full On Surveillance Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 23:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's what you can do right now to save net neutrality and limit mass surveillance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 21:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Ryan is trying to use riders on the must-pass budget bill to block the FCC from enforcing its net neutrality rules. He's also trying to package in a much worse version of CISA, a mass surveillance and incarceration bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 21:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mobile Is Likely Violating Net Neutrality by throttling all video for its subscribers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 19:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Adds 'CISA' To 'Omnibus' Budget Bill, Up To President Obama To Veto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 16:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opponents launch 11th-hour campaign to kill cyber bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 23:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy advocates have launched a last-ditch campaign to block a major piece of cybersecurity legislation that could soon be added to an expected omnibus spending deal. The bill would encourage companies to share more data on hackers with the government. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 23:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy advocates have launched a last-ditch campaign to block a major piece of cybersecurity legislation that could soon be added to an expected omnibus spending deal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 22:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING: Media reports indicate that Congress has cut a deal to put the final version of CISA  a bill that gives corporations legal immunity to share your private data with the Federal government  into the "omnibus" must-pass budget bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Media reports indicate that Congress has cut a deal to put the final version of CISA  a bill that gives corporations legal immunity to share your private data with the Federal government  into the "omnibus" must-pass budget bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama stood up for net neutrality and claimed to support Internet freedom. But now hes poised to sign CISA, a bill that tech experts, major companies, and civil liberties groups agree would destroy our basic rights to security and freedom of expression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 20:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 20:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's](https://www.congress.gov/bill/114th-congress/senate-bill/754) the last public version of the bill text. And [here's](http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/134856244738/breaking-19-civil-liberties-organizations-oppose) a letter from a bunch of leading civil liberties organizations about how it's gotten worse since then. Unless you are the CEO of a major retail or technology company, and you're counting potential liability protection when you abuse your own privacy policy as a form of future profit, I'd love to see which section you think entitles you to a "fast stack of gold by law?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 19:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a fascist, and Obama is not the devil, but it doesn't do anyone any good to gloss over the deep flaws in this administrations policies, particularly on issues of free speech, surveillance, whistleblowers, copyright/TPP, etc. 

The goal of the post linked is to hold Obama accountable, not demonize or heroize him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama stood up for net neutrality and claimed to support Internet freedom. But now hes poised to sign CISA, a bill that tech experts, major companies, and civil liberties groups agree would destroy our basic rights to security and freedom of expression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 19:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 19:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's rough. I think in this case it's about getting past what we think of him personally and recognizing that, particularly on issues of government surveillance, this administration has been really unresponsive to the public's concerns. Important that we speak out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Obama stood up for net neutrality and claimed to support Internet freedom. But now hes poised to sign CISA, a bill that tech experts, major companies, and civil liberties groups agree would destroy our basic rights to security and freedom of expression. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 18:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weigh Less, Pay Less: Whole Foods Offers Discount Based On BMI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that since 2010 Whole Foods has had "weigh less pay less" policy of offering better discounts to employees with lower BMI's </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 16:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France looking at banning Tor, blocking public Wi-Fi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 16:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 01:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "under-educated fools"

Advocacy for Principled Action in Government
Amicus
American Library Association
Bill of Rights Defense Committee
Campaign for Liberty
Constitutional Alliance
Defending Dissent Foundation
Demand Progress
DownsizeDC.org, Inc.
Fight for the Future
Free Press Action Fund
FreedomWorks
Media Alliance
Niskanen Center
OpenMedia
OpenTheGovernment.org
Restore the Fourth
R-Street Institute
X-Lab </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 00:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. They have been awesome since even before the PATRIOT Act fighting for privacy and free speech rights </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US librarians have joined with a host of civil liberties groups to condemn a cybersecurity bill now passing through Congress they claim will be both unhelpful and dangerous to Americans civil liberties. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Librarians and privacy advocates ally to condemn cybersecurity bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were amazing after the PATRIOT Act refusing to hand over people's borrowing records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Librarians and privacy advocates ally to condemn cybersecurity bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 00:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah -- it's particularly disturbing though when the institution conducting the poll has so much perceived legitimacy like the NYT and CBS. If it were, say, a political organization conducting it, more people would be likely to be skeptical, but these news outlets convey objectivity even though that's clearly not the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers still at impasse over cyber bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 22:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Is the New York Times Misleading the Public About a Carbon Tax? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 22:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Is the New York Times Misleading the Public About a Carbon Tax? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Is the New York Times Misleading the Public About a Carbon Tax? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 21:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final version of CISA "cybersecurity" bill appears to strip out key privacy protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 18:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final version of CISA is even worse, could go to vote this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 18:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyber bill's final language likely to anger privacy advocates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 18:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 19:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing to notice is that tons of the organizations that have fought really hard for net neutrality are also the leading groups opposed to more government surveillance. Strong net neutrality protections don't really make the FCC "bigger" or give them any power to regulate CONTENT on the Internet. It gives them power to  *prevent* Internet Service Providers from regulating your online experience. 

I share your general skepticism about government agencies like the FCC, but in this case, these rules were demanded by the public and they're a good thing for free speech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 19:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an awesome list! Can you share source? 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Or are there none and it really is just a bunch of old greedy bastards letting Comcast and other ISPs fill their pockets with disgusting amounts of money?"

Yep, that'd be it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  SNEAK ATTACK ON NET NEUTRALITY  Congress is trying to sneak language into a budget bill that would take away the FCC's ability to enforce the net neutrality rules we worked hard to pass, undermining everything we did to protect the open Internet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 17:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These budget bills are really scary opportunities for special interests to push their agenda. Definitely worth making a call today -- Congress hasn't been hearing much about net neutrality lately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sneak attack on net neutrality. Congress is trying to sneak language into a budget bill that would take away the FCC's ability to enforce the net neutrality rules we worked hard to pass, undermining everything we did to protect the open Internet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Carbon Tax Center has rounded up 32 signatories, including four economics Nobelists and three former cabinet secretaries  George Shultz, Robert Reich and Steven Chu  for a letter to Paris climate negotiators pressing the case for taxing carbon dioxide emissions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 15:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As World Leaders Kick off Paris Climate Talks, Prescriptions Abound, from a Carbon Tax to a New Nuclear Push </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 15:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Carbon Tax Center has rounded up 32 signatories, including four economics Nobelists and three former cabinet secretaries  George Shultz, Robert Reich and Steven Chu  for a letter to Paris climate negotiators pressing the case for taxing carbon dioxide emissions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 14:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
