<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9525</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if Eternal Envy has an aura that makes all the players around him worse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 08:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fata went from clown9 to epicenter champion and one of the strongest mids. Universe went from one of the best play making offlaner to an average mediocre player </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 14:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clock, Riki, skywrath good against all of them. And she has zero mobility so, that helps too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hurricane pike on Luna? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 11:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great value for money, mobility, longer attack range. Are there any negative points?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 06:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Higher mmr doesn't always mean a better player. There are plenty of good players in the sub 5k pool. This policy would just hinder discussion and growth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 20:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope he doesn't play with ee ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was gonna happen. He's a legit rags to riches story. And he got to the riches way to early in life. That's bound to make him too full of himself. You can see it from how he said storm spirit should be renamed sumail spirit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's not gonna happen any time soon. He's a pretty introvert guy who prefers being by himself watching anime/smoking in his free time. He smokes like a chimney, moon said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 07:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, yeah. That build from hell. Extremely irritating early to mid game. But then you'll have to be prepared for "Noob support no wards only ks report"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 07:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Tucker has absolutely no experience in the pro scene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 07:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abyssal is waaaay costlier than euls since you won't have a lot of farm the way I'm suggesting you play. Sure, you want stats. But utility also does not mean you need to be tanky. Most prevalent supports aren't tanky. They survive because they're on the back line. Same can be done for this build  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 07:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay okay. Chill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 06:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infernal blade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 06:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an unofficial youtube channel called OG Dota 2 Team that uploads daily vods of the entire team playing pubs. Check miracle's games out there. Pretty sublime  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 06:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has calmed down because of the state EG is in since artour and universe left </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 06:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, it's nice. Killing the said enemy core is even nicer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 06:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I'm talking about a support, utility bloodseeker here. There are much more effective heroes that can be played as cores.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 22:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seems like it could work
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, euls isn't necessary. I agree. But the silence is too good to be wasted as something that can easily be side stepped, isn't it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think of euls for the mana regen or MS. It's mostly my reasoning that since you can just tp out of rupture with no damage taken, people tend to waste rupture often. So, why not give him a disable that can also act as a set up for his silence which is easily avoided without disables. 

Also, who says you can't build blade mail along with aura items like pipe or gg boots? 
Go right ahead and do that, my friend. Throw in a midas if you like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 18:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I agree with you on the coordination factor. People just aren't ready to try out new stuff in pubs. At least not sub 3k people (Yeah, I'm a 2k scrub)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Utility bloodseeker? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 16:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Q for damage output amp (Yeah, I know incoming damage is also amped) , thirst for global vision/ true sight, rupture to hold people in place. 
Yeah I know people just tp out. So build euls, Rupture, as they start tp'ing out, use euls (also easy set up for silence). Thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 16:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Echo thingy on Riki also quite good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 09:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can't be interrupted by force staff. But stuff like spirit breaker charge, or any other single target stuns, euls, etc. interrupts it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 07:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carry venge is good in those line-ups that can group up very early and just run all over the enemy team. Early team fighting potential heroes and pushing heroes. 
But carry venge line ups should aim at ending the game around the 20 minute mark if the entire team is an early game line up. Another alternative is getting a good strong late game carry at mid, let vengeful safelane and then turn her into an aura providing utility carry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 07:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phoenix is definitely tier 1 right now. Then there are some supports that at ALWAYS viable like enigma, ancient apparition. Then there are the situational armlet counters that are basically heroes that deal damage over time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 07:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, aghs costs 4.2k for a 900 distance jump that can be interrupted like tiny's toss. Blink is half the cost and even more distance. Get a blink - force if you need more mobility. 
Aaaand supports for new players: lion, shadow shaman, lich, vengeful spirit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes it even more special, because I did </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
