<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3642</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do! Mine's "UnsettlingStories.com." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! Count me in, then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that's allowed? I thought it was only for a novel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because those all have such happy endings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I certainly write enough to be able to technically go through with it, but I have such a hard time sticking to one piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I remembered... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'll probably get sucked into it in a few days. I really don't want to, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bubbles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bubbles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was getting my hand stitched up in the ER last night when a series of rapid beeps sounded on the intercom, followed by an announcement of ABD, code A, bay 1. Every doctor and nurse in the area stopped what they were doing and rushed to the main ER entrance. They got there just in time to meet the ambulances.


I couldnt see anything, so I waited. I figured there had to have been a serious accident. My phone rang. It was my Lucy, my wife. She asked how my hand was. I told her they were still stitching it up. I apologized for getting blood all over her bagel, and she laughed and said she told me not to cut it that way. 


There was a pause while Lucy answered one of the kids questions in the background. Then she came back on the line and asked if I saw that really bright light about a half hour ago. I didnt know what she was talking about, so she went on.


It was crazy bright - the whole sky was this weird, pastel pink color. Then it turned white. It almost hurt to look at it was so bright.


Huh, I replied. Maybe it was a UFO. I craned my neck to see over the mass of people still huddled by the ambulance bay. Still nothing.


Lucy laughed. Yeah, mustve been aliens. She said something to one of the kids again, then came back on the line. Ok, Im gonna go. Joey said hes about to throw up.


I said goodbye and ended the call. The commotion on the other end of the ER was growing as more people from other parts of the hospital had gotten there. Something smelled terrible.


I covered my nose and mouth with my shirt and stood up. I walked over to the window so I could get a better look at what was happening. The crowd had thinned slightly. I saw a few nurses running off, probably to pick up supplies. At the end of the hall were two gurneys with medical personnel hovering over them.


The smell got worse and I gagged inside my shirt. One of the gurneys began to move as someone pushed it down the hall.


I stood in the doorway and watched. As the victim came into view, my eyes widened. It was a young woman, covered from head to toe in what I could only describe as bubbles. Some were as small as a pea, others were the size of a grapefruit. They all throbbed and pulsated from some pressure inside them, and every so often, one would tear open and weep yellow fluid onto the gurney. The smell was overwhelming.


They pushed her into the room next to mine. I could see everything from the window in the wall. They didnt bother closing the curtains. I heard the other gurney being pushed by and glanced over at it. A girl, maybe 12 or 13. I shuddered.


I directed my gaze back at the person in the adjacent room. The doctors were popping bubbles to insert an IV. Fluid oozed onto the floor and I used every bit of self-control I could muster to avoid throwing up.


The womans eyes were wide and darting back and forth. It was an expression of terror. Terror and agony. As if sensing my stare, a thin stalk slid from the center of her left eye. The doctors shouted and backed up. The stalk elongated a little over a foot, and its tip grew a bubble of its own. The bubble expanded and the weight caused the stalk to droop. When it was the size of an orange, it stopped growing. It hung like an obscene fruit.


There was a yell from the room where theyd brought the other victim. I assumed it was for the same reason. On the other side of the window, more stalks emerged in a cluster from the womans other eye. All of them produced bubbles like a bunch of grapes.


My phone beeped. It was a text from Lucy. Can you go look outside? Its that light again!


As if on cue, every light in the hospital went out. The emergency lights clicked on for half a second, then they went dead. There was nothing - nothing but the stream of pink light coming in from the open ambulance bay doors.


I stepped in the hall and asked, to no one in particular, what was happening. I doubt anyone heard me, because the light shifted from pink to white, accompanied by a blast of noise I can only describe as static. It caused me to clasp my hands to my ears and retreat backward into the room, where I cowered in the corner.


I saw shadows passing in front of the white light reflecting off the floor. Bizarrely-shaped shadows. They moved in a way that was both jerky and fluid, like jelly suspended on bone. The shadows darkened as whatever was making them got closer. Doctors and nurses in the next room shrieked, and there was a flash which silenced them. Then, two feet away in the hall, harshly illuminated from the back by the piercing, white light, I saw it.


My initial thought of jelly suspended on bone wasnt very far off. Six ossified tubes carried heavy, segmented portions of sloshing, semi-transparent sacks. The first thing that came to mind was the body of a jellyfish. Bubbles and waving stalks decorated the entirety of its trunk and it walked by, either not noticing me or not caring about my presence. It reached the room of the other victim. Just like before, there was a scream, a flash of light, and then silence.


The light outside went dark. The sound stopped. The emergency lights in the hospital clicked on.


I scrambled to my feet and looked through the window at the room next to me. The doctors were writhing on the ground with burns on their exposed skin. The burns didnt look life threatening. But the woman on the gurney was gone. Nothing was left but the sticky, yellow fluid on the floor.


What the fuck was that?!, I yelled, and banged on the window. The person whod been stitching me up got off the floor, came back into the room, and asked me to sit down so he could finish. A nasty burn on the bridge of his nose wept tears of lymphatic fluid down his mouth and chin.


ABD code, he said. Abduction. Weve trained for them, but it was the first one I ever saw. Theyre not supposed to come back for the abductees, though. I wonder why they did that.


I sputtered and asked, You..you people have dealt with this? How isnt this going to be on the front page of every paper?


Well, youll forget about it in a couple hours. Everyone will. Better write down what you remember so you can tell your friends. Youll recall something happening, but you wont remember what it was.


I looked at him, stupefied. So how could you train for something like that? And how do you know it was your first one if you cant remember?


He shrugged. Its just what I was told. And good point about that other thing. He paused and I saw a series of nearly invisible, faded scars around his hairline. He smiled and nodded. Very good [point.](http://unsettlingstories.com)
















 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 13:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just crawl inside with me. There's room for two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I emailed them last year when they first posted it and asked if they could properly credit me. They didn't. Oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so cool! Thanks for putting it together :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 years ago today, my neighbor's son disappeared. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 years ago today, my neighbor's son disappeared. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 15:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 years ago, my neighbors across the street, Mr. and Mrs. Stein, endured a terrible loss. Their son, Adam, disappeared on Halloween. It was assumed he was kidnapped, as there was a rash of kidnappings in the area at the time. The kidnapper was never found, though. Neither was Adam.


Todays the 30th anniversary of his disappearance. To the Steins, the wounds are still fresh. They refuse to decorate their yard, despite all the houses on the street going out of their way to be as festive as possible. They dont give out candy, despite the rest of the houses on the street trying to one-up each other by giving out better loot than their neighbors. 


The Steins mourn quietly in their dark house; the television being the only light emanating from their window. Kids are advised by their parents not to knock. 


Ive always felt bad for them. Ive lived here for 40 years. I remember the frantic search and rescue efforts that swept through our town. Even though I was barely 20 years old and living with my unemployed father while working double shifts to pay our mortgage, I did my part and joined the search. It was the least I could do.


Like all futile searches, it ended after a while. Adam was presumed dead. The Steins grew old and the neighborhood changed around us. New families moved in and old ones either died off or moved out. Aside from me and the Steins, Id say the average age of the homeowners here is 35. And they all have lots of kids.


A terrible rumor started to spread a couple years ago. I know who started it - an older kid named Chuck Demopoulos. He told his younger brothers and neighborhood friends that Adams ghost haunts the woods behind our street. He said Mr. Stein killed him and chopped him up into little bits. 


When I learned about the rumor, I was disgusted. The disrespect was so vulgar and uncalled for. I prayed the Steins wouldnt hear about it, but Im sure they must have. It was pervasive. I called Chucks father and told him what I heard, and I suspect Chuck caught a beating for it. Still, Im afraid the damage had already been done.


Despite pitying the Steins, I dont express my sympathy by refusing to decorate my house and yard. I love Halloween. Always have. I like to see parents beaming from the street while their kids nervously ring doorbells and collect piles of candy. The spirit of the season keeps me feeling young, despite being well past my prime and having to deal with high blood-pressure.


Being an old timer has its perks sometimes. I have Halloween decorations they dont sell anymore. Ghoulish stuff like hangmans nooses - things that are too politically incorrect for stores to sell. I firmly believe Halloween shouldnt be sanitized. It should be scary and unsettling.


That said, there needs to be an emotional component, too. Not just blood and guts for the sake of blood and guts. There needs to be poignancy. Something thatll stick with you after you see it. 


Thats why Adam helps me decorate.


After Dad died in 1989, I emptied out his safety deposit box. There was an envelope with note a note and a Polaroid photograph. All the note said was, I caught him snooping around the cellar. I had to teach him a lesson. The photograph was of fresh cement drying on the basement wall.


In the middle of the night, I went into the cellar and opened the wall. Adams body was inside. My instinctive reaction was to call the police, but I was terrified Id be arrested. Theyd never believe the note.


So I sealed the wall. After a while, I stopped thinking about the dead boy in the bowels of my house. Many years later, after talking with Mrs. Stein about Adam on a Halloween afternoon, I knew what I had to do. 


I took his remains out of the wall in 2014. He was only a skeleton. I separated the bones, splashed them with fake blood, and incorporated them into my Halloween decorations. At first, I was worried. As the days went by, though, I realized I didnt need to be concerned. The bones blended in with the rest of my decorations. Just more festive material in a neighborhood chock full of it.


This morning, when I went out to get the paper, Mr. Stein was doing the same. We met in the street and chatted for a while. We talked about the Cowboys game from last night and he mentioned his wife made a spectacular coffee cake that hed bring me a piece of later. I smiled and told him that would be real nice.


Before we parted ways, Mr. Stein said, I never told you how much Shannon and I appreciated all the help you gave us back when we lost Adam. We knew how busy you were. Its been 30 years today, you know. 30 years.


I felt guilt and sadness wash over me. Im sure hes in a better place, I told him.


He nodded, and I saw tears in his eyes. He was a good boy. I know wherever he is, hes watching over us.


We hugged briefly, then went back to our respective homes. I walked up the driveway, past the ghosts dangling from my trees by their nooses, and headed up my front steps. I looked at the skull hanging above the doorway. It was pointed at the Steins house. [Watching.](http://unsettlingstories.com)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 21:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing such a great job. Keep it up :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My throat's pretty sore... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Bet-he's-packing-lots-of-meat)

Oompa Loompa... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 23:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it true Jill Stein tried to censor a movie because there was a part where the hero used a shop vac to save another character, but Stein said, no way, people shouldnt be lied to about good vac scenes.? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god what a perfect smol pupper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha fucking Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks /u/chrisinpbc! Yeah, I'm pretty prolific and surprised it's working as well as it has, since I've only been at it a little over a year.  What type of things do you write? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit, cool...that's not *too* far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, that's quite a move. Can you estimate how much of a difference in revenue that would make? Or is it too dependent on the quality of traffic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I haven't even heard of those. Thanks for bringing them to my attention! The issue is that since I'm hosted by Wordpress, I'm stuck using their WordAds platform and nothing else. I'm guessing those things you just mentioned fall under the category of "else?" Or are they separate services that serve a different function? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 19:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the original pic and the blog it came from. C'mon, OP. Give credit. It's a really good blog.](http://skookumthesamoyed.tumblr.com/post/152430357163/skookumthesamoyed-little-boy-big-boy-this) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just hit a new record of 250,000 monthly pageviews. I have no idea what I'm doing, and I'd like to know where to go from here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 19:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. I run [UnsettlingStories.com](http://unsettlingstories.com), a blog that features original horror stories that I've written. It started as a Tumblr blog, which is where the majority of my traffic still comes from, but I also get a decent bump from Reddit sometimes if one of my stories does well on /r/nosleep. 

When I was still on Tumblr, I had AdWords set up. My traffic was lower then, and I was getting between $100 and $200 per month. Since I started with WordAds on Wordpress, I have no idea what I've made yet, as I was approved for WordAds right in the beginning of September and they're slow to release numbers.

I've read online that the amount of traffic I get is decent enough, and I'm wondering if there's a better way to go about monetizing the thing so I can make more than the low hundreds of dollars, assuming the traffic stays around the same.

Any help or advice would be really appreciated.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The perks of working in a funeral home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 17:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The perks of working in a funeral home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 17:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working in a funeral home doesnt have many perks, so when one presents itself, its important to jump on it. Thats why closed-casket funerals are the best. You know the ones Im talking about. People who died in car accidents. Fires. Shotgun suicides. Anything that destroys the face and head of the deceased. No one wants to look at hamburger meat in a suit.


I was in charge of preparing the carcass of a middle-aged woman whod gotten half her head blown off in a gas explosion. We didnt even offer her family the option of an open casket. She was really fucked up.


The family gave us the dead ladys favorite dress and some of her jewelry. This is where the perks I mentioned come in. The bereaved are always so trusting. Over the course of the three years Ive had that job, I must have pawned $10,000 worth of necklaces and engagement rings and all sorts of other sentimental crap.


I figure its a victimless crime. The families think its in the coffin with their busted-up relative, so theyre happy, and the dead persons dead, so they dont care. Theyre in a better place, right? 


Anyway, you shouldve seen my face when I got the jewelry to bury with the gas-explosion lady. One locket caught my attention immediately. It was huge and looked like solid gold. I opened it up and saw pictures of the dead woman and others who looked like her mother, grandmother, and maybe even great grandmother, all smiling happily for the camera. The locket had space for five or six pictures. I figured itd be perfect for my girlfriend. She loves big and gaudy shit. We live three towns over, so there wasnt a chance shed get caught wearing it.


I pocketed the locket after everyone had left and I finished working on the dead chick. I wheeled the coffin into the fridge and headed out.


Liz was making dinner when I got home. I figured Id wait until bedtime to give her the present. We ate, watched a movie, and got ready to turn in.


After Liz got out of the shower, I surprised her with the locket. As Id expected, she loved the thing. It looked comically large on her tiny frame; the golden heart full of pictures was the size of a deck of cards against her chest. I thought she looked ridiculous, but she couldnt get enough. She opened it up and flipped through the photographs. Then she closed it, sat me down at her desk chair, and unzipped my pants.


Toward the end of one of the greatest blowjobs of my life, the sound of the dangling locket banging against the hardwood floor was starting to break my concentration. But then Liz did something shed never done and went all the way down. And I mean all the way. And that was all it took. 


When the world had unblurred and I could move my body again, I patted Lizs head and told her I didnt want to know where shed learned to do that, but if she wanted to do it every time she should feel free. Liz remained with her head between my legs. She didnt move.


Ok Liz, I said, starting to feel over sensitive and uncomfortable. Still, no response.


Liz?, I asked, starting to worry. I realized she wasnt breathing. Oh my God, what the fuck!, I yelled, and pushed her back. She separated from me and collapsed on the floor. Her eyes and nose were bleeding. Panic filled me as I stared at her motionless body.


Her bloody face was horrifying, but that wasnt what I was focusing on. It was the locket on her chest. The bright gold locket that now glowed dull red. It opened on its own. My eyes widened as I saw that the oldest picture, the one of the great grandmother, had changed. Her smile had become a scowl of rage. Page after page turned and I saw the once-smiling women were all frowning with hatred and indignity.


The photo of the women Id stolen the locket from was next. Her expression was one of seething animosity. My paralyzing terror kept me rooted to the chair, and I wondered how it could possibly get any worse. Then the page turned again. There was another picture. One that hadnt been there until right that very moment.


The photograph was of Liz, with blood streaming from her eyes and nose. In the picture, carved across her forehead with vicious precision, was the word THIEF. Only once the word started to appear on her forehead in real life, invisibly etched by some malevolent, ghostly hand, did I begin to scream.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

[F_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[R_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I traded him for Marvin Jones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 14:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, that one's mine! I have a bunch on the podcast under the name "Max Aaron." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about your balls, bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tongues of the universe, in *The Bleakness Before Our Old Eyes*. It, and maybe the man with the soft teeth from *Soft Teeth.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There you go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wooooo! Your part's coming soon :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just need another 18 yards and he can go rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 01:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a big-ass table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 23:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate you 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm less me than one might think ;)

It's more of an eldritch story and less of a batteries-up-the-dickhole story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's something very wrong with my parrot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only a matter of time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's something very wrong with my parrot. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an African grey parrot named Perry. Hes been part of the family for 25 years. Ive known him my whole life. When my parents were alive, they taught him a bunch of words and phrases and hed always make us laugh. 


Lately, though, hes been saying things we never taught him. Certainly not things wed ever say, either. Nancy, my wife, was in the kitchen with her friends the other day when they all heard Perry squawk, it bathes in tears and reigns beneath our feet.


They all laughed and wondered what the hell I couldve been watching on TV for the bird to pick up a phrase like that. They continued their lunch, but ten minutes later, Perry started again:


It reigns beneath our feet. It reigns beneath our feet. It reigns beneath our feet. 


Then he squawked and screamed and rattled his cage so hard that he almost fell off the table. Nancy checked to see if he was okay, and he chirped and allowed her to stroke his head with her finger. He seemed no worse for wear.


That night, after Id gotten home and Nancy had told me about Perrys weirdness, I let him out of his cage to fly around the house. He was always well behaved and never knocked anything off shelves or shit on things we cared about. He stepped out of the cage and onto the table, but he didnt take off. He just stood there, looking around.


Go ahead, Perry, I coaxed. Go get some exercise.


He remained stationary, but he watched me; the pupils wide in his beige eyes.


You okay buddy?, I asked. I was concerned for the little guy. Hed always been in great health and never acted weird. This was entirely unlike him.


Perry cocked his head and stared into my eyes. For some reason, I felt a chill run down my spine even before he spoke - almost like I knew he was about to frighten me.


In a deep tone Id never heard from him in all my years, he uttered, beneath your feet.


Something knocked on the floor directly below where I was standing. I jumped about a mile and stepped away from the bird, who hadnt moved. Still beneath your feet, he said. 


The knock came again. It was a hundred times louder and so powerful my ankle twisted under me and I fell sideways onto the couch. The floorboards where Id been standing bulged upward. One had cracked. Nancy came running downstairs asking, what the hell was that? I told her to go in the kitchen and call the police - someone was in the cellar.


Nancy and I waited by the door for the police to arrive. They got there quickly. We let them in and they went into the basement. A couple minutes later, they came back up. No ones there, they told us.


Wait, then what --


The older cop cut us off. Can you come look at something with us?


Okay, Nancy said, but what is it?


Just come downstairs.


We followed the cops into the basement. Neither Nancy nor I go down there very often. I was a little embarrassed by how gross and dusty it was until I saw marks in the dust-covered floor and countertops. 


Are those footprints?, I asked, more to myself than to anyone around.


Thats what we thought, said the younger officer. But they look pretty weird for footprints.


We got to the part of the cellar that was under where Id been standing. The cops aimed their flashlights at the wood above our heads. An indentation was clearly visible. It almost looked like a punch, but the shape wasnt of any hand wed ever seen. It looked like it had too many knuckles; too many bones.


What the hell? I traced my finger over the indentations. I shivered.


Upstairs, Perry squawked. The floorboards around the indentation began to leak. Liquid dripped into my mouth and I sputtered. It was salty and reminded me of the taste you get after crying for a long time.


Did something spill upstairs?, the older cop asked. 


Yeah, maybe the bird knocked something over.


Is that him making all that noise?


I nodded. Hes been weird all day.


We headed back upstairs and the cops told us to call if we have any other concerns about someone being in our house. Nancy and I thanked them, and they left.


I stared at the damage to the living room floor. Perry hadnt knocked anything over, but there was a small puddle on the wood. Hed gone back into his cage and sat in the corner, quietly clucking. I approached the cage. There were little, wet footprints around it. They were his prints. It looked like he mightve lapped up some of the water thatd been on the floor while we were in the cellar.


Whats going on, bud? You having a rough day? I tried not to think about what had happened. There had to be a reason for it. Maybe the wood had warped. The basements always been damp and gross. That had to have been it. The wood warped and trapped moisture was dripping out of the fracture point. But then there was Perry.


Perry stared at the bottom of the cage, still clucking. He didnt look up. I reached out to pet his head, but he struck my finger with his beak. Not hard enough to do any damage, but with enough force to let me know he wanted none of my affection.


I looked at my pet with sympathy, wondering if he was just getting old and losing his mind. He remained in the corner, trembling slightly. Something caught my eye. There was red on the cage where he was sitting. I looked closer. It was blood.


What happened, Perry?, I asked, and reached inside to pick him up, knowing I was in for a pecking. Before I could grab him, he spoke in that same, chilling voice:


It will bathe in blood and claim the sky. He paused, then slowly spoke. Twenty.... seven days.


I picked up my bird to see how badly he was hurt. But before I could assess his wound, I saw what was in the corner where he was sitting. Something entirely unexpected.


Perry, my male, African grey parrot, had been sitting on a bloody, black egg.


Its been 24 hours since all this started. Perry seems no worse for wear, but he fights whenever we try to pick him up. He does everything he can to remain by the egg. I dont know whats happening to him and I have no idea what he means with any of the stuff hes saying. Whenever he talks now, its just 26 days followed by the word hours. The number of hours keeps going down. And I havent heard it, but Nancy swears she hears soft knocking coming from the basement each time Perry makes his announcements.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

[F_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[R_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 16:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, true. They're a voracious bunch. Here are some things:

* Final part of "A Glimpse is Never Enough"

* Another piece of my "Runners" series (the mushroom one)

* The next part of "Psalms of Savagery"

* Something about a woman with Alzheimers recalling unsettling events

* Something about snow in July

* Toothpaste

* A guy who moves into a very bad apartment

* A kid who discovers a bunch of weird batteries in his neighbor's garage

* Something very wrong with a parrot (which will be today's piece)  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 14:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I've finally put out enough Halloween stuff to satisfy the ravenous appetite of my Tumblr followers, so I'm excited to start moving on to more creative pieces. Not sure if today's will be one of those, since I'm in the middle of about 10 things, but that's the goal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 14:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 01:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/r3YggpY.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most beautiful pieces of hardware I've ever seen.... running Windows 10. It's like a model getting cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's my cousin. He lives in the hood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Maybe we should change our name to Gambles because the Broketalentlesscunt family hasn't won anything in a long, long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wholeheartedly support being involved in this, lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 18:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .
.
o sh wdp
.
. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rotting Pumpkins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely loved Xenocide (and the entire Ender series), but no, it's just the name of my Night Elf rogue from when I played WoW ten years ago :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rotting Pumpkins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The farm near our house had a jack-o-lantern pumpkin patch on Halloween. It was pretty cool to look at; a whole field filled with meticulously-carved pumpkins with their grotesque faces glowing from the candlelight within. There was candy strewn about in little baggies, and kids of all ages visited either before or after they trick-or-treated to get some extra loot.

We moved in across the street from that field a couple years ago. At first, we loved the idea of the jack-o-lantern patch. It looked quite haunting and really spoke to the Halloween spirit in me and my wife. But when Halloween was over, the farmer didnt take the jack-o-lanterns away. He left them to rot.

I assumed it was to fertilize the ground for whatever crop hed plant in the spring. It made sense he wouldnt want all that organic material to go to waste. The problem was, theyd attract animals. Animals and bugs. In the unseasonably-warm November we had last year, the smell of the rotting gourds brought critters from far and wide to the field, and when they were done eating, theyd wander the neighborhood.

Being a small town, there was little anyone could do to stop the farmer, whose name was Ruben, from doing what he wanted on his property. We had to deal with the deer and skunks and coyotes and foxes and flies and bees and bats all eating and shitting and fucking their way across the town until no more pumpkins were left.

Last year, I approached Ruben while he was setting up the jack-o-lanterns. He was a friendly guy, there was never any doubting that. I explained the issue and he listened and nodded. He said a few other people had told him the same thing, and hed fixed the fences over the summer so that wouldnt be a problem anymore.

Besides, he told me with a smile, last year was just a test run. This Halloween, everythings going to be just perfect.

On Halloween, the jack-o-lantern field looked even better than it had the year before. Even though the arrangement was the same, Ruben had hired some artists to collaborate and create truly monstrous designs for the pumpkins. They were awesome. I even did a walk through by myself in the early afternoon before the candles were lit just to take it all in. I felt like a kid again.

As the evening was coming to a close and wed given out the majority of our candy to the neighborhood children, we were getting ready to turn off the light and lock up when we heard sirens approaching. I looked outside and saw a procession of police cars and fire engines and ambulances heading toward us. I stepped out on the porch and watched as they passed our house and took the sharp left into the driveway of Rubens farmhouse.

I sat on the steps with my wife and watched as lights were flipped on and the field was partially illuminated. Oh my God, I whispered.

In the harsh, overhead lights, I saw bodies on the ground among the glowing jack-o-lanterns. Small ones. Small, costumed ones. Kids. Oh my God, I repeated, louder.

Paramedics and rescue officials descended on the field and worked to resuscitate the still bodies. One by one, they gave up. Parents were arriving in droves and the sound of wailing and hysteria filled the air. My wife and I held one another as little bodies with sheets over them were loaded into ambulances.

The next morning, it was all over the news. 32 children dead in an apparent poisoning. Ruben was arrested and questioned. He refused to speak to the investigators and he was held without bail.

Funerals were held and pumpkins began to rot. It was another unseasonably-warm November, and on cue, insects began to discover the field. Clouds of flies drifted in and out, blanketing the field in a gray haze as they left their eggs in the pumpkins softening flesh.

In the following days, toxicology reports on the autopsied children came back. Whatever had poisoned them was still unknown. Theyd exhibited all the outward signs of a poisoning: cyanosis, hemorrhage, paralysis, etc.  but no toxins were found in their bodies. Tissue samples were held for further testing, but the corpses were released to the families.

Two weeks later, the air was still thick with flies and bees. We still hadnt had a frost, and things that crawled and flew feasted on the pulpy remains of the jack-o-lanterns. From the house, I could see their deformed, hideous faces; faces which no longer evoked a feeling of holiday fun. They were faces that mocked the dead.

The incredibly warm autumn continued. 20 degrees above average, according to the weather man. Flowers were blooming and the cherry trees had blossomed a full five months ahead of time. The pumpkins were still there, but mostly formless, having succumbed to rot and the ravenousness of vermin. As the hot November slouched into December, the luckiest of us had started to forget about the tragedy that had befallen the town. But we still got reminders  especially on December 2nd, when Ruben broke his silence.

My cousin, Ron, works for the police department as a mechanic. He doesnt have any access to criminals or official information, but he talks to cops a lot. And the cops like to talk.

Ron came over on the 2nd before any news had gotten out about what Ruben was saying. It was clear he was uncomfortable. Lillian and I sat and listened while Ron relayed what his buddy had learned from the detective.

The Ruben I knew was nothing like the man being described by my cousin. Hed blanketed himself with cuts and scars of indecipherable symbols and words. Every inch of his flesh was carved or mutilated in one way or another  something hed done with his fingernails over the course of the time he was in jail.

The detectives learned that Ruben was ready to talk when he began to scream the names of each dead child. Just after midnight on the 2nd, he shouted each first, middle, and last name until his voice was hoarse. Detectives stood on the other side of his cell and transcribed what he said. They didnt understand most of it, but it was better than nothing. The main takeaway was a date and time. December 5th, 11:00 pm.

No one could figure out what he meant by it, so there was a lot of speculation. All the police could do was park a unit over by the farm overnight just in case he had something planned. On the 5th, I sat with Lillian and Ron on the front porch and stared at the black field in front of us. 11:00 came, and nothing happened. We waited for a few minutes. I saw the cop across the street standing next to his car, smoking a cigarette.

As we were getting ready to go inside, I saw something flicker in the field. A tiny flame. Look, I told the others, and pointed. They saw it too. More flickers came into view.

Hey!, I yelled to the cop, and kept pointing at the field. The cop snuffed out his cigarette and walked around the barn to take a look. He got to the side of the field, then raised his radio to call for backup.

As we watched, the flickers intensified, as if they were from new candles thatd finally started properly burning their wicks after sputtering and threatening to go out. After only a couple minutes, more police cars arrived. I got up started to cross the street. I needed to see what was going on.

Dont, said Lillian as she grabbed my hand, but I shrugged her off and headed toward the fence. I heard Ron walking behind me.

The police arrived and lit the field up with their search lights. We could see the rotten pumpkins sitting in the field, all with single candles sticking out of them. They were shaking. One by one, candles fell and hit the dry straw. The straw ignited. Police officers called for emergency assistance from the fire department, but there was no chance theyd get there in time. The fire began to rage.

Entombed in flame, the rotten pumpkins started to burst. Only after their pulpy bodies had disintegrated did we see what was inside. Oh my fucking God, Ron half whispered, half prayed.

In the place of each pumpkin, there was a small, human-shaped thing sitting with its head down and its knees clutched to its chest. The heat intensified further and I backed up, but I still saw it all. One by one, the things rose on sturdy legs and stood erect. They were growing, and soon they reached the size of the children whod died.

Their skin began to char, and they walked out of the flames toward the crowd of police officers. Without any idea what to do, but terrified out of their minds, some began to shoot. The bullets did not stop them. Round after round tore through the fire-spawned children, exiting their backs and legs and heads in a geyser of gore, but they walked ever forward.

Soon, the officers whod fired fell to the ground. They didnt move for a second, but then they started to rot. Just like the pumpkins. Other officers backed away. Id backed all the way up to my house, and I watched from the doorway with my wife and cousin. We were horrified.

A procession of children walked down the street, followed by the police cars. Firefighters worked to put out the blazing field, and after a little while, theyd succeeded.

Ron turned on his police scanner and we sat in the living room, listening with horror as news of dead cops and other officials came in:

*The children have reached the prison.*

*The children have burned through the cell of Ruben Rendell.*

*The children are carrying Rendell back the way they came.*

Oh fuck, I said, and opened the front door. They were coming back down the street  a procession of blackened, smoldering kids carrying a burning man. Ruben. And he was screaming.

ITS ALMOST DONE! ITS ALMOST FINISHED!

He screamed with peals of hysterical laughter as he burned. The children carried him to the field and placed him in the center. They then placed themselves in the same spots as the pumpkins from which theyd emerged. Most had gone out, while some still glowed with dull, red fire.

Before Ruben burned to death, he unleashed one final scream:

PLEASE ACCEPT THIS OFFERING! IS THIS ENOUGH? IS THIS WHAT YOU NEEDED? SEE ME THROUGH! SEE! ME! THROUGH!

There was no sound from him after that final word. Nothing but the crackling of dying flames.

The following days were a whirlwind of investigations, media visits, and speculation. No one knew what happened. No one knew what Ruben had done. And for a while, it was still a mystery how the kids had been poisoned in the first place.

A mystery, that is, until Jasmine McCray, the mother of a child who was fortunate enough to have been too sick to trick-or-treat, found a small letter in her sons toy chest. It read:

For a special night of Halloween fun, draw this little picture on a piece of paper and swallow it, then come to Farmer Rubens pumpkin patch to trick-or-treat. You will never, ever want to leave.

The picture was of an inverted star. A pentagram.

Jasmines son told her Ruben had given them to kids at recess one day after he talked to the classes about what it was like to be a farmer. He came to them individually and made them promise to throw it away after they read it and not to tell their parents.

Jasmine gave the letter to the police, and then told the media. While the superstitious residents of the town took that as an answer to what had happened, skeptics like myself couldnt believe it. Even after what Id seen, I couldnt believe something supernatural had occurred.

But then the photographs came in. The aerial photographs from the news helicopter the day after the holocaust at the field. Clearly marked in carbon and ash was the shape of a pentagram  the exact shape the pumpkins had been arranged in. No one had noticed it from the ground.

And at the center of the pentagram, where Ruben had screamed his final, pleading prayer, four words were burnt into the dirt. The answer to the old farmers prayers.

[NOT ENOUGH. NEVER ENOUGH.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

[F_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[R_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ::shudder::

I'm out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did in January when I was stuck in jury duty. Fucking hated it. I revise as I go, rather than draft, and it's a god damn nightmare to do that by hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last of the Trick-or-Treaters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Last of the Trick-or-Treaters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 16:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last Halloween at 11:25 pm, the doorbell rang. Id just gotten into bed. Thinking I could ignore it and go to sleep, I clicked off the TV and pulled the covers up. The doorbell sounded again. And again. And again.


I threw off the covers, put on my bathrobe, and stormed out of the bedroom. If it was a group of kids playing a prank, I told myself, even their parents wouldnt be able to identify their bodies. I unlocked and opened the front door.


On the doorstep was a young boy wearing a Native American headdress and an ornately-beaded leather vest and pants. He was clutching a bag of candy to his chest. No one else was around.


It was unseasonably cold that night, and without any adults around, I couldnt let the kid stay out there and freeze. He looked miserable. I held him by his shoulder and guided him inside, then I picked him up and placed him on the couch. I didnt know what to do. Calling the police seemed like the only safe bet, so I dialed the non-emergency number. While I waited on hold, I heated up some water to make the kid a mug of hot chocolate.


The kid stared at me while I stood in the kitchen. He didnt say a word. I felt bad for the little guy.


The receptionist at the police station answered and I told her what was going on. She said she hadnt heard about any missing kids, but as soon as a car was free, one would be sent over. She cautioned it might be a while, though. Apparently Halloweens a busy time for them over there.


With the water boiled and the instant hot chocolate made, I went over to the kid and sat down next to him on the couch. I placed the mug on the table across from us. After cautioning him that it was hot, I figured I needed to talk to him.


Nice costume, I told him. It wasnt really that nice. Pretty culturally insensitive nowadays. But whatever.


Thanks, he replied.


So, um, did you lose your parents?, I asked. 


The kid shook his head.


How about your brothers or sisters? Or friends?


Again, no.


Want to try the hot chocolate? Its really good.


I dont like chocolate.


Oh, okay. I picked up the mug and started drinking, wondering if the kid was slow or something. Who doesnt like chocolate?


We sat in silence for a little while. He kept his eyes on the unpowered television while I did everything in my power to not appear creepy. I never know how to act around kids.


Did you have a good time trick-or-treating?, I asked, then realized it was a stupid question. Hed gotten separated from his family or friends, for fucks sake. How good could it have been?


The kid, to my surprise, nodded. I got what I wanted, he said.


Oh? And what was that?


The doorbell rang and I hopped off the couch and answered it. Two officers. I invited them in and they saw the boy on the sofa. They greeted him and asked the same questions I had. He had nothing to say to them, though. In fact, he looked angry - almost like he hated them.


After a few minutes of getting nowhere, the officers said they were going to bring him back to the station. There still hadnt been any reports of a missing child.


As they were about to leave, there was a call on the police radio. Something about a murder on 113 Chestnut Place. The three of us stood very still for a moment. I live at 115 Chestnut. My neighbors, Paul and Lynn Chesney, had lived there for decades and were the curators at the local museum. 


The officers answered the call on their radio said they were nearby. They were told backup would be there shortly.


Wait here, the cops ordered, and the kid and I just looked at each other while the two men left the house and headed next door.


Dont worry, its okay, I promised the boy. He looked flat. Unaffected. Then he turned and looked straight at me.


Bring this to the MTIC. It all belongs to them. He handed me his bag. I was extremely confused for a second, wondering why the local Mohegan tribe would want Halloween candy. I opened the bag and gasped. 


A bloody, stone knife sat atop a pile of beautiful, beaded vestments, ornate carvings, and other, old-looking artifacts.


Your neighbors have been keeping these from us. We tried to get them back, but they just laughed and mocked our efforts. But theyre too important to give up - especially after weve been forced to give up so much.


I stood like an idiot, holding the bag as sirens approached and the commotion outside grew. 


Give it to them, the kid shouted with a deep, adult voice that was entirely out of place coming from his small body. And with that, he vanished. The headdress and pants and vest dropped in a pile on the rug. I spent a good 45 minutes convincing myself I hadnt gone nuts.


Hours later, an officer came back for the boy. What happened over there?, I asked the cop. I already knew, but I needed confirmation. 


Looks like the couple got killed in a robbery attempt, he told me. Their daughter came home from a Halloween party and found them with their throats cut. Im sorry.


I let out a long sigh and nodded.


Wheres the kid?, the officer asked.


I had an answer ready. There was a family going door to door with a picture of him. I guess hed run away. But hes back with them now.


The cop shook his head. And they didnt even call us? Christ. He paused. Well, okay. Goodnight. Im sorry about your neighbors - well have officers in the area until whoever did it is found.


I thanked him and closed the door. It was almost 5:00 am. It was too late to go to bed; I had work in a couple hours. So I sat down at my computer, and with the kids bag on the desk next to me, I mapped out directions for my drive to the MTIC.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

[F_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[R_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 03:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't hurt those broad shoulders. 

You can only feel their hardness against your warm hands. 

So broad; so hard --

soft stubble brushes your lips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 03:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's on the sidelines in his helmet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Big Scary House in the Woods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Big Scary House in the Woods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took two days to hike to the spot wed heard about: a strange house standing alone in the middle of the woods. And if it couldnt possibly sound any more cliche, the rumors were that the former owners of the house haunted it and killed anyone who dared to enter.

From the outside, it looked unremarkable. Had it not been in the middle of the forest with nothing around but trees and rocks, the house wouldve looked like any other run-down home in a bad area. But the fact remained: it was the only man-made structure for miles. Why, let alone how, anyone would haul construction materials through the inhospitable wilderness to build the place was beyond my or my boyfriends understanding.

Being journalists for the high school paper, we came armed with our notebooks and tablets. John tried to peer through the windows, but there was nothing to see. The windows were smoked out - it looked like thered been a minor fire inside at some point.

The front door was locked, but around the back there was a rusted-out hole in the cellar door. It was just wide enough for John to fit through. No way my boobs were getting through that hole unless I did way more squashing than I was in the mood to do. No, it was okay; John would go through and open the front door for me.

After a bit of squeezing and cursing, John made his way into the cellar. Looking at the ragged, rusty metal hed just forced himself through, I wondered when hed last gotten a tetanus booster. With a shudder, I made my way over to the front of the house and waited for him to let me inside.

I waited. And waited. After a couple minutes, I heard John banging on the door from behind to get it open.

It doesnt want to move, he shouted from the other side.

Can you find something to break it open?, I called back. A crowbar or something?

The banging stopped as he looked around. More waiting. Out of the corner of my eye, I saw a doe and her fawn. I was spellbound. Growing up in the city, this had been my first trip into the woods since I was a little girl. Id never gotten to see deer in real life. 

I carefully moved in the direction of the animals, crouching low so I didnt frighten them, and held out my hand. The ears of the deer perked up and they watched me intently, trying to determine if I was a threat. In my head, I was pleading with them to come over.

Its okay guys, I whispered sweetly. Its okay.

I held my breath as the fawn stepped toward me. It was so close. The mother wasnt stopping it as it got nearer and nearer - so close that I could see my reflection in its wide, inquisitive eyes.

A massive bang sounded from behind me, making me jump and sending the deer running for their lives. God damn it, John!, I yelled, turning around. You scared them aw--.

I stopped talking and froze. The door had flown off its hinges onto the front steps. In the doorway stood a thick, bulbous, corpse-like man. He was swollen and burned, almost like hed been soaked in gasoline for months then set on fire. And in his hand he held the severed head of John, whose eyes stared straight ahead with confused shock.

I screamed and began to run. Stay away from our home!, came a voice so loud and powerful it caused me to stumble and fall. I righted myself and looked over my shoulder, tears streaming down my eyes. There was another thing now - a woman - standing shoulder to shoulder with Johns murderer. Her mouth opened and she bellowed, and dont fucking come back!

She lumbered down the steps and picked up the door. She carried it back up, and before she set it back in the remains of its frame, the husband took Johns head and threw in my direction. I heard it hit the ground behind me as I ran, but I never saw his face again. Never, except in my nightmares.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

[F_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[R_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 20:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I don't know...a few of them end up pretty happy. The main character of the one I wrote today did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, I might actually use my Twitter now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time Enough at Last. One of the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah yesterday was dead as fuck - OOC and NoSleep proper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Topical </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 18:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There once was a man, Donald Trump,  
whose polling had taken a slump.  
Should he lose the election,  
hed still have the erection  
of Putin stuffed deep in his rump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bend it like Beckham Jr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 02:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basic bronchoscope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 01:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This deserves more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Triscuits are just salty Shredded Wheat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all might have to soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 17:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be a fun challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Job I Couldn't Leave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Job I Couldn't Leave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 16:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In February of 2004, I was employed as a housekeeper for a wealthy real-estate developer. Id been gone for a few days; my uncle had died and Id traveled from New York to Florida on short notice to help with the arrangements. I came back one day earlier than Id planned. My boss was quite irate when I told him I was leaving in the first place, so I thought an early return might help put me back in good graces.

I got to the penthouse around 3am, ready to get a jump on the days work. According to the schedule my boss had given me, hed be home later the following day and expected the place to be spotless. I dont care if youre still in your funeral clothes while you scrub the toilet, were his final words to me before I left for Florida.

When the private elevator reached the residence, I was surprised to see all the lights were on. Like I said, he wasnt supposed to be back for almost 30 hours. None of the other staff were scheduled, either. 

A strange sound caused me to jerk my head in the direction of the dining room. I couldnt identify the noise at all. It was like a mewl and a groan and a gasp all at once. Whatever it was, it was very unsettling. I waited and listened. There was a voice. A familiar one. My bosss adult son.

I couldnt make out what he was saying, but I felt a little better. At least it hadnt been a burglar. I put my supplies on the counter and headed toward the dining room.

The doors were shut. Almost shut. One was slightly ajar, and I could see movement on the other side. That strange sound came again, this time quieter. More like a sigh. Gooseflesh rose on my arms and neck. I tiptoed over to the doors and peered inside. Had the son not coughed the moment I stifled a gasp, they wouldve heard me.

My boss sat at the head of the table with his face between the legs of a dying girl. Her throat had been cut. The sounds Id heard were her pained, gurgling breaths. The son, whose back was to me, held the girl down as her flailing tapered off. Her head came to rest with her eyes fixed in my direction; eyes that locked onto mine. Eyes that screamed help with silent desperation.

She didnt move after that. I swallowed a scream.

I heard my boss grunt, bring her mother out to clean it up.

His son crossed the room and unlocked the gold and black-glass cabinet thatd stood in the corner for as long as Id worked there. I couldnt see him opening the door, but I heard a terrible, howling wail as the woman trapped inside was released and saw the remains of her daughter.

Oh shut up, my boss yelled at her. Then he chuckled. My boys going to put another one in you soon enough.

The whole scene had lasted less than two minutes, but those minutes were indelibly etched on my consciousness. On my psyche. On my soul.

I left the residence as quietly as Id entered. In the lobby, I saw the lone, overnight security officer who'd let me in. Abdullah. He'd always been kind to me. "Please, please, please don't mention I was here," I begged. He looked bewildered, but then he nodded. He hated our boss as much as anyone.

The moment I exited the building, I called 911 from one of the few remaining pay phones and told the dispatcher what Id seen. I didnt give my name and I disguised my voice as best as I could. Then I waited by the subway entrance until the police cars and ambulances arrived.

I got home where I tossed and turned and cried for sleepless hours as I pictured the poor girl, who couldnt have been older than nine or ten, bleeding out as she was so hideously violated. Even now, 12 years later, the scene is as sharp in my mind as it had been that night.

The next day, I got the newspaper, ready to see his awful, smirking face on the cover with a headline declaring him a murderer. But there was no such thing. I flipped through each page, poring over the stories and looking for his name. Nothing. I rushed to my computer and searched online. Headlines about his TV show and his business dealings were all over, but nothing about an arrest; nothing that even hinted at an investigation.

Sickness washed over me as I realized his money and influence had certainly kept his crime quiet. I sobbed at home all day.

The following morning, after Id somehow slept for a couple hours, my phone rang. Why the fuck arent you at work, a voice screamed. It was him. I couldnt speak at first. My mind was blank. After nearly a full minute, I stuttered, I...Im sorry. Ill be in as soon as I can. He hung up.

Everything went gray as I realized I couldnt leave the job. If I did, hed know itd been me who called the police. If I even momentarily showed fear or uncertainty, he would figure it out. I had to go to work. I had to do what he told me until I was absolutely sure hed never learn Id discovered his secret.

So I went to work. I went like nothing was wrong at all, aside from how I claimed I was still mourning the death of my uncle. It was an excuse, but it was one he bought. Get your shit together, he demanded. And I did. My first order of business was to clean a stain on the dining-room table that he said had shown up out of nowhere.

As I scrubbed and held back a scream of indignant anguish, I did everything I could to pretend I was somewhere else. Anywhere but where I stood. And, for the most part, it worked. All I had to do was lie to myself and pretend I didnt hear the nearly-inaudible sound of muffled crying coming from from the gold and black-glass cabinet in the corner.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

[F_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[R_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *really* like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 15:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://vine.co/v/5ZnMFwjVW3Y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 14:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've learned to accept it, haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My stuff isn't even that gory, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 03:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. They were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone is good at using google. Don't feel bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I wish I hadn't read those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 00:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks like The Onion's AvClub picked up on my Double Dare story. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty cool.

http://www.avclub.com/article/marc-summers-robot-eerie-piece-double-dare-creepyp-244463 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [They incubated and hatched in the lungs.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/58an2x/tainted_candy/d8yyjm9?st=iuhessde sh=e6821fe5) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all over the place when it comes to shapes. It'll be interesting to think about, though, when I look at the shapes of my more successful ones and compare them to the ones that didn't do as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no stomach acid in the respiratory system unless you have a *major* problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem was the cocoa powder finish on the chocolate. Ever eat a powdered-sugar donut and accidentally inhale the sugar and cough? Well this was the same thing, but with unprocessed, unfiltered, unwashed Honduran cocoa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tainted Candy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tainted Candy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wont let my kids trick-or-treat this Halloween. Not after what happened last year. Not when half the towns parents are still in mourning and every other week you see cribs and twin-sized beds by the curb for anyone to come by and pick up. Theyre stark reminders that the losses cut deep around here. The pains still there. And even if those wounds have started to heal for some, theyll always, always itch.

Last year, kids received tainted candy. 55 got sick, 31 died. It was all over the news, so I dont need to go into a background story that you already know. My girls were lucky; theyre both allergic to peanuts so they just gave the candies to their friends. Friends they dont have anymore.

I remember my shift in the ER when the kids started trickling in. It took a few days. The first one was on November 3rd - a four-year old named Regina. She was having trouble breathing. At first, we thought it was an allergic reaction, but none of the treatments seemed to work. As she got worse, it was only after wed scoped her to get a look inside her lungs that we realized what was happening. By then, though, it was too late. She died on the table.

Three more young kids came in that night. They all died.

The next day, the trickle became a flood. Older kids joined the younger ones with trouble breathing. These seemed worse off than the kids from the night before. The initial symptoms had given way to the secondary ones before death, so we had to deal with the shock and terror they were experiencing as their condition progressed.

The CDC representatives arrived not long after ten more had died, and they were able to quickly trace the source to contaminated candy. The local chocolate producer was determined to be at fault, and a speedy investigation revealed exactly how the candies were contaminated. The business was shut down. The owners are still tied up in court cases for their negligence and refusal to comply with proper importation safeguards.

Like I said, after a year, its all still fresh in the minds of so many families. Theyll go their whole lives associating the holiday with death and devastation, rather than fun and excitement. Out of respect for that, few yards are decorated for Halloween nowadays. There are some pumpkins on front steps, but no real displays. Well, thered been one.

A Japanese family whod moved to town in August had been mostly unaware of the circumstances surrounding the tragedy. Theyd bought the house across the street from me. Excited to celebrate Halloween in America for the first time, they decorated their front lawn with skeletons, pumpkins, monsters, and spiders. A couple neighbors visited the next day and carefully explained to them what had happened the year before. The decorations were down within an hour.

It wasnt that anyone was truly angry that the decorations were there. Most of them were fine. Had they just left three of the four things up, no one wouldve complained. Hell, some people who were lucky enough to not have been touched by the tragedies might have appreciated a little Halloween spirit. But for some, seeing that one thing was just too much. Even I, who hadnt lost anyone, cringed a little when I saw the setup.

It made me think back to that night on November 3rd when Regina came in. I remembered the scope going down into her lungs. I remembered how we stared at the screen in a combination of horror and fascination. 

It wasnt a skeleton or a pumpkin or a monster that had killed those children. It was the spiders. The millions of tiny, black spiders whose eggs had been in the cocoa powder decorating the finished chocolate and peanut-butter candies. 

The kids whod suffocated before the spiders had exited their lungs were the lucky ones. It was those in the waiting room or car or ambulance who hacked and coughed up clouds of them as they died who had it worst. 

The Japanese family apologized profusely as they removed all the decorations. It was obvious they were mortified. As I watched them out the window, I saw Giichi wave his wife, Ai, over to get a close look at the lawn. Her eyes widened and she put her hand over her mouth. I couldnt see what they were looking at, but I knew what it was.

Ever since last November, thereve been webs all over the place. Theyre small - only the size of a quarter - but immediately recognizable as being from the same Honduran spider thatd been accidentally imported by the chocolate shop owners. The towns infested with them. I try not to get too close to the corners and eaves of my house because I know theyre there. Harmless, but there. Just another cruel reminder. One of many.

I havent touched a piece of chocolate in over 350 days. I dread having to use the scope when Im at work in the ER. And nearly every night I dream about how it all happened, only to jolt awake with the feeling of spiders squirming through my lungs and sinuses.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

[F_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[R_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 03:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mine from today](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5845mp/the_pilot/?st=iug9m1vo sh=34d9b73a) is a little like that, but not quite supernatural. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 01:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, go back far enough and you can watch the Old Gods first visit the Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put your head out the window and wait. You'll have an update before you know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medical-related things aren't allowed to be the sole driver of horror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh absolutely. If someone's making more than advertising revenue from something, you need to be getting paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just know I've gotten a lot of new readers from people discovering my site through YouTube narrators. As long as they credit my work the way I want, I'm happy for them to make a few bucks off it. It's a win-win.

And if they refuse to credit you, you can submit a DMCA takedown request pretty easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've fucked around with wormholes and extra dimensions and shit and just used some heavy sciencey stuff to back it up and give it moderate plausibility. I can't think of a reason why you can't do the same thing with time travel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost wish I wasn't allowed to start new series.

"OMG this series is the best idea ever I'm gonna do 100 parts!"

*The next day...*

"Jesus I'm sick of this fucking series." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pilot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pilot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like so many things, it started with a bright spot in the night sky. As I watched, it grew brighter. Closer. Before long, I could hear it. It was loud and constant; a freight train riding a persistent thunderclap. Birds were roused from their sleep and they took to the sky, soaring away from the threatening light and sound. I didnt move, though. I had to see.

It struck the ground in the woods outside my property, perhaps a quarter mile away. A second later, a searing blast of heat and pressure singed my eyebrows and threw me to the ground. My daze, while not insubstantial, was pushed to the side by excitement and wonder. 

I scrambled to my feet and ran toward the impact site. The woods were alive with fire; orange plasma licking the evergreens as the sap within boiled and hissed. I passed the charred bodies of squirrels and deer as I darted around the hottest spots of quickly-dying flames. Before long, I was there.

The crater was about as wide and as deep as a backyard swimming pool. At its center was a red rock. Bright red. Fire-engine red. Its color wasnt from heat, I noticed with some surprise, as feathery rime crept with fractalic persistence over its exposed surface. 

For a moment, there was no sound.

I peered into the crater and watched the rime crawl up the rock, wondering how ice could form so close to the still-smoldering brush and dirt alongside it. On the other side of the object, out of my view, a sliver of yellow light flashed. Before I could go around to investigate, a crack spread on the surface of the rock. Dazzling, hypnotic sparkles of yellow and green filled my eyes.

I woke up on the forest floor at some point in the morning. The fires were out. Whatever had been in the crater had crumbled to dust. Without any knowledge of how Id lost consciousness, I felt fear tickle the back of my neck. Almost as quickly as it started, though, the feeling evaporated. All my concern evaporated. For the first time in my 40 years of life, I felt wonderful. At peace.

I followed the trail that had been left for me. It led to my garage. Impelled to write something to let the world know what had and would be happening to me, I took my phone from my pocket and started to type.

And here I am.

Here we are.

I hadnt noticed the gossamer-thin tendril stretching from my forehead to the pilot until wed officially met. Its eyestalks perked up upon seeing me enter the garage, and it extruded newer, thicker filaments from its bulk to greet me. They stopped at my clothes, slapping weakly and wetly against the fabric until I got the message and stripped them off. Unhindered, the finger-thick filaments, now perhaps tendrils, pushed into me.

I tasted the cosmos with my skin, and every exposed surface of my body sang in an electric choir of caressed nerves. 

Let them know how it feels, the Pilot whispered in me.

The sensation was that of being licked by ten thousand tongues, if ten thousand tongues were the emissaries of ten billion galaxies. I felt stars blink into existence on my chest and detonate in supernovae chaos upon my hands and feet. Pulsars fondled my shoulders while civilizations discovered fire and tamed the atom on my cheeks and under my scalp. 

Have them come to us so we can let them feel, the Pilot breathed throughout me.

I dialed 911 and sighed the words, officer down at 133 Rural Route 5.

It didnt take long.

The Pilot kissed each one with its tendrils the moment they arrived. The stellar choir of skin and taste grew by nine. 

The Pilot, too, had grown. It filled the entirety of the garage; its filaments and tendrils and tentacles poking and pouring out of windows and doorways. The ground grew slick with its excretions. We stood - we stand - inside, all connected. All consumed and all consuming. All feeling.

More calls have been made and our network of flesh will only increase. The Pilot is gifting us with poetry to swallow; concepts that can only be understood once theyve been tasted. Once theyve been digested. Once theyve been incorporated.

It is with a fleeting sense of loss that I recall the man who Id once been. A man who, just last night, succumbed to his fervid curiosity and ran toward the fire. Never once did he care about being burnt; never once did he worry about what may happen. And now he is here. Now I am here. Now we are here. It was his desire to learn - and now he knows everything.

The Pilot has broken through the roof of the garage and is towering above the forest. It tells me if I were to measure, it would be a mile. One mile of the Pilot stretching like a gray-green obelisk toward the cosmos which birthed it.

More sirens puncture the tranquility of our home on the outskirts of the forest. Soon, they will stop. The Pilot can now reach aircraft with its tendrils, which have grown strong enough to break through. And those bodies inside are now with us. We all taste stars - we all bathe in radiation and fling ourselves toward the expanding borders of the universe in simultaneous orgasm. 

The Pilot whispers he is 20 miles tall now. Depending where you are, if you look outside, you might see it. If you do, dont be afraid. Dont be anxious. Just feel the one, final moment of your loneliness. Of your solitude. Then open your windows, smile, and wait.

Its time for you to meet the universe.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

[f_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[r_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 02:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even read that one anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny, an alt-right reactionary was one of the victims. It wasn't even investigated because no one was upset they'd died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 21:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God you people are adorable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Objective: see how many women you can sexually assault in a 40-year period. Bonus points if you can blame it on Mexicans or Muslims.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm most into transformational and seductive body horror. I don't write much of it, [aside from this one](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4v815k/it_all_started_when_i_realized_my_iphone_was/?st=iuec5v3b sh=8b3b349c) from over the summer. Something about completely changing or disfiguring oneself for the purpose of pleasure and/or escape really speaks to me. I can't explain why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will post all parts here, as well as on the site I've linked. The goal is to reach as many people as possible. I am terrified of what will happen next if people don't learn about what's going on. Everyone needs to be vigilant.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psalms of Savagery, part 1: Lisette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psalms of Savagery, part 1: Lisette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im an IT contractor for the FBI. I learned about a serial killer whose crimes are being actively hidden the by the Bureau and by state and local police departments. I believe it is my duty to bring these crimes to light. The files Ive taken detail the criminal acts and the evidence associated with them. I will share portions of the files over the course of the next week or so, starting with this one today. People cant live under a false impression of safety.

On May 3rd, 2016, Lisette Jan Aronowitz, 43, was found dead by her husband at their home in Bethesda, MD. She had been crucified. Nails had been driven through her hands and feet, anchoring her to the brick wall above the fireplace. It is assumed Lisette was alive during the crucifixion.

The victims eyes and teeth had been removed. Her eye sockets were filled with the excised teeth; top teeth in the left socket, bottom teeth in the right. These injuries are also assumed to have been inflicted while the Lisette was alive.

Death appears to have been the result of internal injuries from repeated blunt-force trauma to the abdomen. Bruising patterns suggest a cross-shaped object.

There was no indication that Lisette had been sexually assaulted. However, blood, hair, and semen were found at the crime scene. Each sample was contained in small, individual ramekins on the floor below the victim. The victims left eye was in the ramekin containing hair while the right eye was in the ramekin containing blood.

Federal databases have no record of the DNA found at the scene. Fingerprints, while numerous, were also not on record.

The autopsy of Lisette yielded a great deal of evidence with little-to-no clues about who the murderer may have been. In the place of each tooth, small pieces of frankincense resin had been inserted below the gum line. The interior of the eye sockets were coated in myrrh oil. A cut had been made in the soft palate, where a gold coin was found. The obvious biblical connection was not overlooked.

While the killers general motive remains a mystery, a small amount of illumination was gleaned from the contents of 83 small incisions in the flesh of Lisettes back and buttocks. Inside each incision was a plastic-wrapped piece of paper, on which one word, number, or punctuation mark was written.

A cursory examination of the words suggested another biblical connection, and when they were fed into a pattern-matching database, their source was revealed.

**Psalms 64: 1-2, 9-10**

***1*** *Hear me, my God, as I voice my complaint; protect my life from the threat of the enemy.* ***2*** *Hide me from the conspiracy of the wicked, from the plots of evildoers.* ***9*** *All people will fear; they will proclaim the works of God and ponder what he has done.* ***10*** *The righteous will rejoice in the LORD and take refuge in him; all the upright in heart will glory in him!*

The case is still under investigation, but the official report made no mention of the ritualistic nature of the murder. All inquiries into the case are being denied. Further, the lack of details released have prevented any connections being made between Lisettes murder and the murder of at least four others.

But I have the details. And in the coming days, so will you. 

[Will be continued.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

[f_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[r_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 13:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Demarco gets to feast on them next week :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 04:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [UnsettlingStories.com](http://unsettlingstories.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 22:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was writing gross vignettes on /r/wtf and someone said I should write for NoSleep. And here I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 03:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You truly are a great asset, Butler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 03:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/V34khzb.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 02:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehh I didn't make that one up. It was in a joke book I read like 25 years ago. I think it's actually how I first learned what a vas deferens was, because I looked it up after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 02:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 02:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, here's five:

[The Tomb of the Builders](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4zde6y/the_tomb_of_the_builders/)

[Pebbles](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/53icnv/pebbles/?st=iuafs99s sh=cee32dea)

[The Bleakness Before Our Old Eyes](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4y161k/the_bleakness_before_our_old_eyes/?st=iuafsjxz sh=8047a526)

[The Least Satisfying Explanation](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4413pt/the_least_satisfying_explanation/?st=iuafswrj sh=4a08d614)

[Teeny-Tiny](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/2xcvgt/teenytiny/?st=iuaft952 sh=c7dee4ad) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 01:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My story gracing the top of NoSleep at the moment is predictable and unoriginal. But I had fun writing it, and I knew it would do well. I have a few stories with 2k+ that I'd give a C- to that only got noticed because they're shocking and/or gross. 

Bugs in my stories are certainly a cliche, but I'll be damned if they're not popular. The stories I've written that I actually like and consider original barely break 1k, and it's not because they're qualitatively worse, but because it's not the type of thing NoSleep reinforces with upvotes.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 23:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck else do you do with a carpet, though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 23:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so obviously part of all my characters that I should be singing Jewel's "Pieces of You" while I write. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned "stationary" and "stationery" were separate spellings, like, four days ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 21:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I shall storm the citadel of her womanhood!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 20:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the same thing, then I noticed how popular the stories were so I wrote one. I'm a hack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The reason why I dont pick up hitchhikers anymore is also the reason why I need a new car. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The reason why I dont pick up hitchhikers anymore is also the reason why I need a new car. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 19:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind, Id never even considered giving a ride to a stranger before. All my life, Id been told thats how you get killed. Only crazies hitchhike, theyd say. Theyll cut your throat and steal your car and youll be dead in a ditch.

I didnt want to die in a ditch. And I liked my car. But after Id left the gas station and I saw the poor guy sitting in the gutter on the I-95 onramp, feebly holding out his thumb, I made my choice. Id be a good samaritan.

The storm in the distance looked pretty threatening. If I let that guy sit there, hed have to bear the brunt of it. From the looks of him, he didnt appear to be able to bear much at all. I pulled over to the side and rolled down the window.

Where you looking to go?, I asked him.

Baltimore, he replied. His voice was stronger than his sickly body had suggested, and that gave me pause. I looked him over again. Dirty jeans, baggy red t-shirt. No bag, no bulges in his pockets. I sighed.

I can get you as far as Philly. He nodded. Hop in, I told him, unlocking the door.

In he hopped.

Im Colin, I said.

Frank.

We didnt talk much for the first few miles, aside from me asking if he wanted some of the Fritos I had left from my lunch stop in Rhode Island. He took them and crunched away as I drove. He caught me studying him out of the corner of my eye a few times, but he didnt say anything.

As the miles ticked away and rain started hitting the windshield, Frank fell asleep. The open bag of Fritos was on his lap. I wanted a couple, but didnt want him to wake up thinking I was trying to grab his dick. I had absolutely no interest in his dick.

Frank snored like an orgasming Pratt and Whitney jet engine. In the confines of the car, since I had to close the windows once the rain had started, I noticed Frank had an unpleasant odor. Nothing overwhelming, but still obvious.

Over his snore, his stomach growled and burbled. Gross, I thought. Lightning flashed and wind buffeted the side of the car. The traffic ahead of us slowed to a crawl.

One of the annoying things about my car is the climate control only works properly when the car is moving. God knows why. The air conditioning we were enjoying up to that point cut out, and hot air started to blow out of the vents. The windshield began to fog up.

I cracked my window, hoping the outside air might clear the windshield. It did a bit, but visibility was terrible. The rain was heavy and my wipers werent doing a good job. All I could see was fog and the brake lights of the cars stopped in front of me. Franks stomach kept gurgling. I looked over. He was awake, staring straight ahead.

You okay buddy,? I asked. No response. He just stared at the fog-shrouded glass of the windshield. The smell Id noticed before had intensified.

Hey, Frank, whats going on? You sick?

Still nothing. Thick, humid air poured from the cars vents despite the AC being set to max. Rain and small chunks of hail pelted the choked highway.

Frank retched. Shit, I said, and I frantically reached in the backseat for a bag or bucket or anything that might catch what I thought was about to come blasting out of my companion. My hand settled on one of the canvas shopping bags I used at Whole Foods. God damn it, I mumbled, as I placed my favorite shopping bag on Franks lap.

He moaned and turned to look at me, his eyes swimming back and forth with what I knew had to be intense nausea.

Frank, please open the door and puke on the road or at least use the bag. Im begging you.

More silence punctuated by gurgling and retching. A boom of thunder caused us both to jump. For Frank, that was all it took. He didnt open the door. And he didnt aim for the bag.

A heavy wave of yellow vomit exploded out of his mouth and splashed against the windshield. I screamed. Another projectile torrent erupted from the man, dousing the ceiling, the dashboard, and the center console.

Get out!, I shrieked, the smell of the stomach contents invading my nose and threatening to force my own contribution to the mess. Frank sat back with his head down, pasty slime drooling from his mouth into the Fritos bag in his lap.

Cars behind me were leaning on their horns. The traffic in front of us had cleared. I poked at the hideousness on the console to turn on my emergency blinkers, then steered onto the median. On my right, I heard Frank choking. I got out of the car and stood in the rain, watching him. If you told me the following 30 seconds actually lasted 3 hours, I wouldve told you you were way off. It felt like a day.

Franks throat bulged as something was forced upward and into his mouth. I saw the something a second later. A colossal, writhing centipede as thick as my wrist began sliding out, its passage eased by the vile lubrication from minutes before. Inch after inch, foot after foot crawled out until it was free. It skittered under the passenger seat.

Id already dialed the 9 in 911 when the solid matter entombed in his vomit began to move. Frank groaned and I distinctly heard him mutter, not again. As the rain soaked me, I watched as small centipedes crawled through the sludge all over the car, leaving trails as they went.

My dialing complete, I waited through seven rings before a dispatcher answered. As I told her about the medical emergency and tried to estimate where we were on the interstate, Frank abruptly opened the passenger-side door and stood on the side of the highway. He was gripping another massive centipede and pulling it out of his throat. I watched it bite his hand over and over until its two-foot length was exposed. Frank flung it into the dirt.

Sorry about your car, man, Frank called over the sound of rain and traffic. I havent had an episode since I was a kid.

I was speechless. I just looked at him as he walked down the side of the median, the torrential rain washing his clothes of the filth and bugs. And as centipedes crawled throughout my car and ropes of stomach contents dripped from its ceiling, Frank stuck out his thumb to flag down another potential ride to Baltimore.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[f_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[r_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 15:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just sounded really familiar, and then I remembered a scene at the very end when Ray pulled a scrap of wood with a hole in it out of his pocket and a tiny ghost tumbled out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your great story idea was the exact plot from an episode of The Real Ghostbusters that you saw in 1987. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fill me with cement and fuck me into the Marianas trench. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 countries in the world that can properly make a 10-gallon hat, thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 20:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciated the attempt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but the first piece of body horror I ever wrote, which wasn't really a story, had the same bifurcating stuff happening. I thought it was cool enough to deserve a place in a real story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's something alien at the cemetery in Norwalk, CT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theres something alien at the cemetery in Norwalk, CT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 19:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> []()I bought a house across the street over the summer, and now that the leaves have started to fall, I have a clear view of the graveyard from my living-room window. A week and a half ago, I saw something tall and white moving among the headstones. Something that glowed with dim light, even when it was pitch black out.

I told Denise, who said, and I quote, well thats pretty fuckin cool. We started staying up late to see if it would come back. On Thursday night, it did. Through the binoculars, I could see it was shaped more-or-less like an upside-down tree. It didnt have feet, but rather hundreds of small tendrils that shuffled it through the rows of headstones. Its body was erect and unremarkable, save for an opening at the top where different, longer tendrils hung.

It moved silently and ceaselessly for almost 20 minutes before disappearing into thin air.

When I got to work on Friday, I told a couple guys about it. They said I was full of shit, so I invited them over to see it for themselves. Dan was the only one who took me up on my offer, so I told him to come for dinner. We could eat and wait for the thing to show up.

Around 1am on Saturday morning, it came back. Dan was speechless. He took out his phone and started recording. I told him there was no point; it hadnt shown up on anything Denise and I had tried to record with, but he insisted on trying anyway.

We were out on the front porch, so the thing was about 100 feet away. Maybe more. Dan wasnt having much luck getting it in focus, so he crossed the street and stood on the edge of the cemetery property.

I wouldnt go near it, Dan, Denise advised. Part of me agreed with her, but another part wanted to join him and get a better look.

Its cool, Dan replied over his shoulder. He kept walking in its direction.

I stayed on the porch with Denise and watched Dan get closer.

Can you hear that?, Dan called. It sounds like its singing or something.

Neither of us could hear what Dan heard, but I was growing increasingly uneasy at his cavalier attitude in the face of something completely unknown.

Before any of us could react, one of the tendrils from the top of the creature shot across the cemetery and whipped Dan in the face. He stumbled and fell on his back. Denise gasped and I started running toward my friend. The thing evaporated. I reached Dan, whod already gotten up. He looked no worse for wear.

As we headed back for the house, Dan began to limp. He started to complain about a weird feeling in his feet. I helped him across the street and back into the house. He immediately took off his shoes and started to rub his heels and arches and toes. It was obvious he was in pain.

Without warning, with a series of sickening, wet cracks, Dans feet split in half. He and Denise screamed. They split again. And again. Denise fumbled with her phone to call 911 and I could just watch, horrified, as Dans feet continue to bifurcate until there was nothing left but bleeding tendrils that jerked and twitched, flinging blood across the living room.

Dan passed out as further bifurcations turned his feet into noodle-thin, then hair-thin, filaments. I heard an ambulance approaching. We live only a quarter-mile away from the hospital. The filaments knotted and unknotted as the EMTs entered the house. They gazed, wide-eyed, at Dans injuries.

As they loaded him onto the gurney and began exiting the house, two cracks like gunshots rang out, making everyone jump. His shins, knees, and femurs had split. Blood poured down the sides of the gurney and cascaded down our front steps. Denise and I heard more cracks after the ambulance doors had closed. Then, with sirens blaring, they were gone.

Dan died not long after. I attended his funeral this morning. Theres no explanation for what had happened to him, and the news report on his death simply called it an accident. I want to come forward and tell the police whats going on in the cemetery, but the thing hasnt shown up at all since that night. If anyone else lives in Norwalk and can claim theyd seen something like what I described, please do so. I dont want anyone else to get hurt. Dan didnt deserve what happened to him.

Edit: I asked [Denise](https://www.reddit.com/user/TheBakercist) to paint a picture of it. [She got it exactly right.](http://i.imgur.com/31R9pmU.jpg)

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[f_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[r_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stealing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 03:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The threat of one to oneself. 

Skypupper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She felt bad for the little shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Balls. I haven't been to a show since I saw Skinny Puppy in, like, 2004. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I wish I would've known they were playing there. I would've gone in a heartbeat. Next time they're in NYC, I'm all over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 22:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.giphy.com/media/JVqeFxl3Qo8/200.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Date Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 21:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I courted the lass from afar,  
so she trotted up to my car.  
A grin like Bells Palsy  
and breath that smelled ballsy  
for only a thousand dinar.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jill-O-Lanterns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jill-O-Lanterns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1987, a plastic surgeon named Harris Wilhelm Tristemon killed his wife, Jill Texana-Tristemon. Harris was never caught, but it was widely assumed it had to have been him. Only Harris had such expertise. Only Harris had such meticulous attention to detail. Only Harris had such devastating psychopathy.

I know.

Im his brother.

I shared with the investigators every incident I remembered from our childhood and adolescence: All the animals Harris had killed. All the classmates he had assaulted. Every punch, every slap, every grope. By late 1989, the investigation had yielded nothing. Harris was gone.

Last month, in the small town of Zermatt, Switzerland, an American expatriate named Jill Pepo was found murdered. While Zermatt is small, crime is not alien to them. Neither is murder, although it is exceedingly rare. That said, the circumstances surrounding Pepos murder were hideous enough for officials to demand silence during the investigation. There was concern the growing immigrant population would be blamed. Despite the lockdown, some details leaked. I found them online. 

Three weeks ago, a Canadian businesswoman, Jill Moschata, was found dead in her hotel room in Dsseldorf. Again, the hideous details were kept bottled up to avoid sparking a xenophobic panic. Again, those details were leaked. 

Again, I found them online. That time, I wasnt the only one.

A few true-crime aficionados had noticed the similarities between the Zermatt and Dsseldorf murders, and one old-timer made the connection between them and the killing of my sister-in-law. The fact the victims were all named Jill was not overlooked.

Once Jill Cucurbita, a Mexican national in upstate New York, was found murdered, all the cases were officially connected. International investigators descended on all the crime scenes. They were looking for evidence to connect my missing brother to the crimes. All they could find were the same wounds. The same cuts. The same disfigurations. 

According to an ICPO and FBI estimation, 11,225 people could have made the same travel arrangements to put them at the scenes of the crimes in Zermatt, Dsseldorf, and New York. That number ballooned to unknown hundreds of thousands if the suspect drove, rather than flew, from Switzerland to Germany. This all meant they had no suspect. No one aside from Harris, who everyone assumed had changed his identity decades ago.

Last Friday, I received a piece of mail containing 13 photographs. There were three from each murder scene. They detailed the incomprehensible brutality of the Jill-killers process. The skinning. The scooping. The carving. The candle burning inside empty, grinning skulls. 

The 13th photograph was of my daughter, whod been named in memory of my beloved sister-in-law. It was a very recent picture, which appeared to have been taken when she was playing in the backyard. Our fenced-in backyard.

All the pictures were given to the FBI, and weve had round-the-clock surveillance of our home ever since. The police presence has done little to allay the fear my wife and I are experiencing. Jill, despite being only four, knows something bad is going on. Something involving her. We cant tell her, though. We cant even hint.

Still, its hard to keep it a secret from our daughter. She sees the police officers outside. She sees the expressions of anxiety on her parents faces. Worst of all, it was she who found the jack-o-lantern that appeared on our kitchen table in the middle of the night. One that was carved with artistic, surgical precision, to look exactly like her.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[_f](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[_r](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 23:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fortunate enough to have been featured five or six times, credited as Max Aaron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I gotta stop killing kids. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, every fucking story. I get it, they're renewable, but have some god damn creativity. Story about a monster? Better kill a kid. Story about an elf? Better kill a kid. Story about a clown? Better kill a bunch of kids.

Stop killing kids, Max.  
.  
.  
.  
Starting next month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He fell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the best black metal band and why is it Behemoth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a pair of cool velcro sneakers, a rubber ball, and a Christmas sweater! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh Grandma died years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says you're nice and feeling the Christmas spirit :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 19:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you cold? You should put on your Christmas sweater! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Language! Don't you have an elf listening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Language! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it wasn't too bad. I turned out ok :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I always thought because his eyes were so smol he couldn't see too great so I'm glad I fooled him. Hope he's not too mad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have my presents :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I would've raged over something like that too. I hate bullying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing like a wave pool filled with lutefisk vomit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elf on the Shelf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elf on the Shelf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 17:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grandma would always warn me that the elf on the shelf was watching to make sure I wasnt bad. Growing up, even when it was nowhere near Christmas, the elf would observe me. The elf would judge me.

With my brother and cousins around all the time, it wasnt easy to be good. But I tried. I tried really hard. When Id make a mistake and be mean to one of them, I felt the elf staring at me. It would remember that moment. Id picture it waiting until I was in bed, then running and tattling to Santa. No matter how much I screamed and sobbed to it, the elf wouldnt answer. It would just watch and wait for me to do something bad again. It knew me too well.

On the fourth of July, I burned Marisa with a sparkler. I didnt do it on purpose. I mean, I meant to burn Marisa, but I didnt want to hurt her. I just wanted to see what would happen. Unfortunately, she got hurt pretty bad. Grandma had to take her to the hospital, but not before she got out the belt and whipped me until I couldnt sit down. 

After Marisas mom came over to give me a beating of her own, I was left watching Neil, my little brother. Grandma was still at the hospital. Neil watched TV while I tried to walk off the pain from the beatings. Before Dad died, thats what hed tell me to do. Walk it off, you little faggot. 

I walked a lot. 

When I got to the living room, the elf was watching me. It knew. Its wooden mouth was open, almost like it was screaming accusations. 

Youre a bad kid. 

No one likes you.

Santa thinks youre terrible.

Youll be a bad man when you grow up.

It didnt actually speak, of course, but it was obvious thats what it meant. It was the same stuff Grandma said to me, day in, day out. And somehow, I always made sure to live up to it. Try as I might, I couldnt be good. At the age of eight, I was already certain I was rotten to the core. 

Months went by and my best efforts yielded punishment. If I wasnt accidentally knocking over a vase in the kitchen, I was tracking mud into the hallway. It invariably ended with my pants around my ankles and my grandfathers old leather belt smashing into me as I tried not to scream. Screaming would only make the beatings last longer. 

When it was finally over and I inched my jeans and underwear back up, I told myself Id be better; that Id be a good kid from here on out. And for a while - for the entire month of November and into December - I was.

Grandma, Neil, and I went to get our Christmas tree on December 4th. We came home and decorated it while cookies baked in the oven. I remember Grandma lifting me with her strong, solid arms so I could put the star on top. The star had been her daughters. My mothers. It was one of the only things left that had belonged to her.

On December 5th, after Neil and I had gotten home from school, we were playing around. Like all brothers, we played rough. With him being six and me being eight, I was quite a bit bigger. When we were wrestling and I was spinning him by his arm, I made a mistake. I let him go and send him right into the Christmas tree. It fell onto the hardwood floor. Ornaments broke. Lights went out.

The star shattered.

In an instant, I was panicking. I knew Neil would tell Grandma. I knew the elf in the other room would learn what Id done. Id been good for so long that Id started hoping I might get Christmas presents. After this, though; after breaking the one thing Grandma had left after her daughter was killed by Dad, Id be doomed. Grandma would beat me senseless. The elf would tell Santa. Id get nothing. And Neil would taunt me with his presents.

Something sparked inside me. What if the elf hadnt seen what happened? What if Neil didnt tell Grandma? 

I was very busy for about an hour. By the time I was done, Grandma would be back from work any minute. I knew I might not fool her, but Id fool the elf. That was most important; it was he who talked to Santa. Not Grandma.

I wore Neils face into the living room and looked at the elf on the shelf. He stared back with his blue, judgmental eyes. 

Im sorry I knocked over the tree and broke the ornament, I said, doing my best impression of Neils high voice. I thought about his body cooling on the kitchen floor and his blood making a mess everywhere. Maybe Grandma would believe he fell on a knife if I cried hard enough.

Under the mask of my brothers skin, I peered at the elf through the eye holes. The skin tasted awful, but I had to breathe through my mouth because the nose holes line up right. I wondered if the elf believed me.

Im sorry, elf, I squeaked again. I heard the garage door rising and a car pulling inside. Grandma was home. I felt a new rush of panic. I glared through the cold mask at the arbiter of my Christmas fortune. The door connecting the garage to the kitchen opened and I heard my grandmothers shrill, hysterical shriek.

Elf, I whispered, as tears mixed with my brothers blood and cascaded down my face.

The elf on the shelf turned its head 360 degrees as its mouth opened and closed. When it faced me again, it spoke: Youve been very bad, Neil.

I fell to my knees in fervid, incomprehensible relief. Some part of me heard Grandma still screaming, somehow even louder when she came into the room and saw me. Again, the elf spoke, Youve been terrible Neil. 

Grandma whirled around and looked at the elf, but then shook her head back and forth like she was trying to get ahold of herself. I stood up. Not wanting to ruin the illusion for the elf, I held the mask to my face until I left the room and sat down in the kitchen. Grandma didnt try to hit me. She didnt touch me at all. I piled the skin back on Neils head and told Grandma he fell. She didnt answer. 

It didnt matter, though.

20 days later, in my own, warm room at the hospital, I got some very nice Christmas presents. The doctors and nurses were so kind and gentle with me. One even hugged me after Id opened my gifts. The gifts werent exactly what Id hoped for, but they were better than nothing. So much better. I giggled to myself as we hugged. When the nurse asked what I was laughing at, I lied and told her I remembered a funny joke. She smiled, and I was surprised to see a tear running down her cheek. I didnt think much of it, though. All that mattered was Id won. Id finally fooled the elf on the shelf.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[f_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[r_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 15:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been "featured" by SRS and the alt-right shitbags quite a few times over the years. I've learned to shrug it off. They're as impotent as they are obnoxious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 14:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they're a hazard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 04:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey thanks! Loved your administration :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 02:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sitting at home and not giving out candy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welcome, new fans from /r/CringeAnarchy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daycare Massacre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daycare Massacre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to get swept under the rug because of the Hurricane Matthew coverage. Even if it isnt, whatevers mentioned in the news will be sanitized for public consumption. People arent supposed to hear about this kind of thing  especially when you consider how frightened they are already.

Theres a daycare in Charleston, SC. Its in an awful neighborhood. I was patrolling the area before dawn this morning when the owner ran out in the street and flagged me down. She was covered in blood. I got out of the car and called for backup. Officers Fitzgerald and Ndoma were a block away and got there a minute later. Ndoma stayed with the inconsolable, trembling owner while Fitz and I drew our weapons and entered the building.

There were six children inside. Unclothed. Dead.

I called for paramedics and a supervisor. Amid the chaos of hurricane preparations, by the time theyd arrived, Fitz and I had cleared the small building. If the owner of the daycare hadnt killed the kids, whoever had was gone.

The news media, who wouldve been all over something like this, hadnt even noticed our radio chatter. They were too busy reporting on the storm. To be honest, I couldnt have been more relieved. The city didnt need to know about this yet.

The daycare owner still hasnt said a word. We have her in custody and its obvious she needs a psychiatric evaluation, but thats off the table until at least tomorrow. We pulled the records of the children from the daycare files and are beginning to notify parents. The last two of the six bodies are being examined as I write this.

The hospital is being prepared for an influx of storm-related injuries, so the deceased were brought directly to the city coroner. The examinations are cursory and unofficial. I know the main guy down there. My father was the best man at his wedding. Whenever I wanted to know something about a case that was above my paygrade, hed usually fill me in. Today was no different. I know what I saw, but were a lot of unanswered questions.

When Fitz and I entered the building and saw the victims, we knew the cause of death right away. The wounds were gaping and obvious. In fact, I dont think Ive blinked today without seeing them in that split second of darkness. To me, it was clear the owner couldnt have done it. Shes 51, and if you told me she was 90 pounds, Id be surprised. Her mouths small, too. Yes, thats relevant.  

Heres the thing: at first glance, I assumed the kids had to have been killed by some kind of animal. The bites which prompted the massive blood loss mustve come from something with large, powerful jaws. After we cleared the building, though, and Fitz was outside with Ndoma trying to get the owner to say what happened, I took a closer look at the wounds. They were too uniform. Too precise.

What I mean by that is the children were all bitten in the same spot. Everything between their legs, from navel to lower back, was gone. There were smudges on their thighs. Something white. It more obvious on the darker-skinned victims, but nonetheless present on all of them. I was about to examine the fibers I saw sticking to the wounds, but I was interrupted by the paramedics and the coroners office. They needed to do their thing, so I left them to it.

Ive spent the whole morning at my desk, filling out reports, and writing this account to help clear my mind. About an hour ago, I called my contact at the coroners office. He told me, like I mentioned above, that theyd looked over four of the six. It was, certainly, the bites which had killed them. They bled out in a matter of seconds.

I asked him what he thought could have done it, and he paused. To me, that meant he still didnt know for sure. After a few seconds of silence, I asked about the fibers Id seen.

Red hairs, he told me. Wiry, red hairs. John thought they couldve been from a chimpanzee, since theyve been known to attack the genital area, but they usually do damage to other places too.

What about the white stuff?, I asked.

Were not sure yet. The lab will have to do an analysis after the storm, but from what everyone over here can determine, its some kind of makeup.

I thanked him and was about to hang up, but he told me to hold on.

Theres one more thing. Something we found stuffed up around what was left of the caucasian boys bladder.

I shuddered, but told him to continue.

Well, its foam. When we pulled it out, it was just kind of a blobby thing. But then John washed it off.

My friend trailed off and I heard him sighing deeply into the phones receiver. I gave him a second, but urged him on. He sighed again.

Max, it was one of those red foam noses. The same ones clowns wear.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[f_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[r_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ethan's Halloween Mask </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ethan's Halloween Mask </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cousin Ethan and I grew up together, but I never liked him very much. His family was rich, so he always had the best stuff. Mine wasnt. I didnt.

On Halloween, 1985, we were going trick-or-treating together. I was the Terminator, he was Freddy Krueger. His mask cost almost a hundred dollars and it looked exactly like Freddys face. The scars, the sneer; everything was just right.

I didnt have a mask. My parents couldnt afford one. I had torn aluminum foil taped to the side of my face. It was meant to look like the Terminator after some of its skin had been ripped off. A few splotches of ketchup on the foil were supposed to look like blood. As soon as it dried, it looked very little like dried blood and very much like dried ketchup.

Despite my terrible costume, I was still excited to trick-or-treat. We didnt have candy very often at home, except maybe on Easter. My parents encouraged me to go to as many houses as I wanted to get all the candy Id be able to eat. It felt good to know they wanted me to be happy.

Ethan and I went out at sundown and visited house after house. Every time, the homeowners would gush over Ethans mask. Theyd tell him how scary it was. How realistic. Then theyd turn to me and ask who I was supposed to be. Id answer, then theyd say something like, oh of course, how could I have missed it! I could tell they felt sorry for me. One even handed me an extra few pieces of candy.

When we were done, our pillowcases stuffed with treats of every sort, we began the long walk home. As we went, Ethan rooted around in his bag of loot. I could hear him grumbling and complaining through his mask. Then he started throwing candy on the street. Stuff he didnt like.

Go ahead and pick it up if you want it, Bill, he called out, heaving handful after handful into the gutter. I know you cant afford to let anything go to waste.

I didnt say anything, but I reached into my pocket and pulled out the lighter and one of the two cigarettes Id stolen from my dad. Id been smoking on-and-off for the last few months, and even at 13, I knew it was bad for me. I just didnt care. It made me feel good.

I stayed a few steps behind Ethan as he tossed more candy away, and as much as I hated myself for it, I ended up picking a few pieces off the ground and putting them in my bag. Ethan caught me once and laughed. Youre going to be as fat as your mom if you eat all that. I kept my mouth shut.

Is that why she got fired from the restaurant? Did she eat a customers food?

I knew Ethan was joking. He did it often. Im sure in his mind, he thought he was being harmless and playful. Still, Id told him more than a few times to leave Mom out of the jokes. She had diabetes. And she hadnt mentioned it to anyone other than my dad and me, but the doctor told her she might end up losing her foot. Thats why the restaurant let her go. She couldnt walk around and wait tables anymore.

Change the subject, Ethan, I said. I knew he heard me, and he didnt talk for another minute or so. Until he did again.

You think her and your dad still fuck? I wonder how he manages to get it in there. He cackled, then insisted, ok, ok, ok, Im sorry, Im done. Promise.

I seethed as we took a shortcut through the elementary school soccer field.

Lets stop here for a minute, Ethan said. Wed gotten to the schools playground. I bet I could scare the shit out of some kids if they come by.

He sat on one of the swings with his pillowcase on his lap. He kicked his legs and the swing moved back and forth. I stood there, hating him.

I think I see some kids coming over the hill, I told Ethan. Im going to hide behind the slide and sneak up on them if they come over to you.

Go for it, Ethan told me, his voice deep and distorted through the mask.

I left Ethan on the swing set and walked over to the slide. I watched him swing as his hateful words rang in my ears. Tears came to my eyes as I remembered Mom smiling from her spot on the couch as she encouraged me to go out and have fun. She was such a good person. So, so good. Shed never said anything negative about Ethan. In fact, shed always complimented him on his grades and his wins in basketball and even his looks. Youre going to be a handsome man, Ethan, she told him. I bet well see your face in a magazine someday.

Even after her kindnesses, Ethan still felt it was okay to trash her.

I heard him laughing to himself from across the playground. I didnt know why, exactly, but I had a pretty good idea. I reached in my jacket for the other cigarette, knowing the smoke would calm me down. But it had come apart. My pocket was full of loose tobacco and paper. Loose tobacco, paper, and the lighter.

Ethan was still laughing as I fingered the lighter in my pocket for a second, then pulled it out. I walked up behind him. He didnt know I was there as he shouted out, ok, one more thing and Ill never say anything about her again - but unless your dads got a big dick, hell never manage to --

I flicked the lighter near the back of Ethans neck, right where his hair and mask met. The hair went up quickly, using his hairspray as an accelerant. Then something happened that I didnt expect. The mask burst into flames.

Ethan jumped off the swing and ran in a loose circle, trying to pull the mask off his head. I saw it ripping under his fingers. He couldnt get a grip. The material bubbled. His screams, barely muffled as the molten chemicals clung to his skin, echoed off the brick walls of the elementary school.

After a few seconds, he fell and rolled around on playground, pushing his head into the sand to put out the fire. And he succeeded. But the damage was done.

He turned over on his back, no longer screaming, but gasping in shallow, hyperventilated breaths. In the moonlight, I saw the mask was completely fused to what remained of his skin. One of his eyes had apparently burst, but his other darted around almost like he was confused and wondering where he was.

I saw something moving on the other side of the field. Kids were coming. I yelled to them to call an ambulance, and I waited, unsure of how I felt, until the paramedics got there.

I took complete responsibility for setting Ethan on fire. I said Id been sneaking up to scare him by flicking the lighter near his face. And yes, I got in a lot of trouble. But everyone believed it was an accident.

Ethans face was destroyed. He had skin grafts and bone grafts and all sorts of reconstructive surgery. He never recovered. Not physically, not emotionally. He killed himself in 1990. His parents held a very expensive funeral. I was invited. Theyd forgiven me for my part in his accident years before. In fact, their subsequent lawsuit against the mask company is the reason why Halloween masks are now made of flame-retardant materials.

Mom died a few years before Ethan, but not before complications from her diabetes took her left leg. Dad and I were with her in the hospital at the same time Ethans parents were there to see him through another round of reconstructive surgery. They visited Mom, Dad, and I while Ethan was still under, recovering after a successful set of grafts.

We chatted for a little while about Moms hopes for recovery, and then the topic moved to Ethan. Ethans mom was gushing about a plastic surgeon that had recently joined the hospital after working in Switzerland. He was the best, apparently. Hed taken on Ethans case earlier in the year, albeit remotely, and wrote a substantial article about the new techniques hed be employing. In the world of plastic surgery, it made a big splash, if only for its ambition.

Ethans mom reached into her purse and pulled out the publication. She flipped it open to the page that showed various photographs of Ethans burns and the notes and explanations the surgeon had written to accompany the article. I could tell Mom was holding back tears. I knew why, too. Her eyes met mine, and she couldnt hold back any longer. She began to weep. Dad and Ethans mother held her while she cried. I just watched.

Mom was thinking that shed been right all those years ago. Shed been right for all the wrong reasons, but right nonetheless. Just like shed predicted, Ethans face had finally made it into a magazine.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[f_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[r_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikileaks rejected a State Department document and demanded that I destroy it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wikileaks rejected a State Department document and demanded that I destroy it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 20:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My uncle worked for the State Department. He died a couple weeks ago. As per State Department policy, whenever one of their higher-ranking employees dies, the Department sends a small team to the home of the deceased to ensure they had no sensitive documents in their possession. Its not that they distrust their dead colleague - they just dont trust his family.

The Department team came to my uncles house one morning, spent a few hours rifling through his closets and drawers, and left with a small pile of papers. They expressed their condolences for my loss, then left. I never saw them again. Not even at the funeral.

On the night I visited and found him on the floor, dying of a heart attack, he told me something. Its something I wouldve preferred to have never heard; something that made me wish Id gotten to his house 20 minutes later to find him dead. 

Rockville Bank. Rangeley, ME. Deposit box 4426. The key was on the ring between his car and house keys.

I pocketed the key before the paramedics arrived. He was dead by then. I went through the motions, arranged what needed to be arranged, and let the State Department do their thing. Last week, I drove from DC up to Rangely. I showed the bank the documents proving I was in charge of my uncles estate and owner of the contents of the box. The bank manager unlocked the main lock on top, then left me to unlock the other one on the bottom. Inside was an envelope containing a single sheet of paper dated August 4, 2016, that looked like it had been pulled out of a fire. I took it from the box, left the bank, and read it in my car.

I have to preface this by saying Ive never been one for conspiracy theories. In fact, I think theyre all a bunch of bullshit. We landed on the moon. Oswald killed Kennedy. Islamic terrorists brought down the twin towers. Vaccines are safe and important. None of the major conspiracy theories have been able to hold up under scrutiny, and all the exponents of the theories are, in one way or another, unhinged. But.

But.

Theres nothing inside me that can adequately explain away what I read on that sheet of paper. Yes, it might be a hoax. During the long drive back to DC, Id almost convinced myself that it was. But my uncle wouldnt do something like that. He took his work seriously. He was passionate and moral. All the evidence pointed to the fact the document was real. And if that were the case, people needed to know about it. That had to have been why my uncle had hidden the file away. He wanted me, or someone else, to disseminate it after his death. I made up my mind, and when I got home, I submitted it to Wikileaks.

Five minutes later, I received a phone call. Destroy the scan you sent us. It is not real. Destroy the file and the physical document. Do not attempt to submit it again. We know who you are.

I hadnt provided any personal information to Wikileaks. They dont even ask for it. And hardly anyone has my phone number. Plus, no one else knew I had that document in my possession. 

If anything could have proven the document was authentic and important, that was it.

That all happened last Friday. Every day since then, Ive gotten calls from different numbers, all asking the same questions. Is it gone? Is it destroyed?

Each time, I hung up without saying anything. This morning, though, the voice on the other end said something different. You will die if that document is leaked.

I hung up and called the police, who said they would send a car over. But Im still worried. I am going to destroy the document, but not before I transcribe it. Not before I put it online. Even if they get me - even if they kill me - Im not sure I want to continue living in a world where the contents of that document are real.

Ive replaced the burn marks with dashes. The content is still discernible. The context is still available. Whatever happens with this, once its out in the open, my conscience can be clear. If this is my last day alive, maybe Ill be rewarded for bringing this to light. God knows if I live through today, I may never sleep again.

***U.S. Department of State: Wikileaks   JA documentation --- --- summary***

*JA ordered multiple attempts on the --- of BO JB HC according to --- sources in --- of Ecuador, London. Electronic surveillance of the --- is ongoing, although human intelligence ---. Following --- offer of funding, most attempts linked to JA have stopped. Tactical reversion to JA --- Embassy of Ecuador, London --- budget to silence sexual assault --- and smear accusers in tabloid --- as promiscuous or drug users.*

*JA has accepted the --- GBP sum in exchange for keeping secret US UK BZ IT --- for refugee experimentation. (See cable ---) --- experimentation via biological, chemical, radiological, ---*

*--- --- refugee populations in SY being moved --- --- ---, though Ciprofloxacin shortage makes it difficult to keep enough alive before reaching BZ and IT labs. JA accepting variable sums to hold back information --- to sick and dying refugees.*

*JA received cables --- from RU re: US initial success in UK lab --- Zika manipulation. Zika reengineering and subsequent failure --- reanimation of dead tissue.* 

*Loss of containment in FL, US, GA, US, LON, UK --- some bodies regaining movement and autonomy --- --- following brain death. In some cases, full recovery. --- motivation altered. Wikileaks and JA rejecting --- reports for GBP 1M per. Google, Yahoo, Microsoft, and others complying --- ---.*

*Final note:*

*JA assassination attempt on --- --- 2016 reported successful by --- Ecuador, London and US team --- via gunshot wound to head. Body --- reanimated likely --- dormant Zika --- accidental exposure to lost mosquito --- LON, UK lab. JA new motivation unknown. Gunshot --- covered by hair styled --- over wounds. Still responsive to --- and communication.*

*Internet in general still unaware of bioengineered --- outbreak. --- and family of citizens in US and UK --- --- reanimated dead without anyone knowing it. Monitor cables from --- and RU. Avoid mosquito exposure.* 

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[f_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[r_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Empty Cribs on Hawthorn Lane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Empty Cribs on Hawthorn Lane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 20:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bloody pacifier I found hanging from my tree belonged to Alyssa Harris, who went missing from her crib two nights ago. I figured it had to have been Alyssas when I saw it, but while I waited for the police to arrive, I realized it couldve belonged to Matthew Roman. Or Muhammad Ahad. Or maybe even Hailey Davis. Over the last four years, theyd all vanished.

Hawthorn Lane developed quite a bit of notoriety in 2015 after Matthew and Muhammad disappeared on the same night. The Romans and the Ahads lived four houses apart, and as far as the detectives were able to tell, the infants were abducted within minutes of each other. Both houses were securely locked and there was no sign of a forced entry.

As far as Im concerned, though, the notoriety and rush of attention from the national news wouldnt have happened if their disappearance hadnt been on the anniversary of the 2012 abduction of Hailey Davis. 

Haileys case was special, if it could be called such a thing. Thats because on October 1st, 2013, exactly a year after she went missing, pieces of her were found stuffed in the mailboxes of every family on the street who had, or were expecting, children. A swarm of investigators, both local and federal, descended on our quiet, suburban lane, and worked around the clock for months before admitting defeat. There was no evidence. 

No fingerprints. No hairs. No mysterious DNA.

When the media came to town in 2015 after Matthew and Muhammad went missing, the rumors started. Rumors and threats. People from all over the country decided to get involved. They felt it was their duty. They began sending harassing letters and making threatening phone calls to the single adults who lived on Hawthorn Lane. These were people whod lived here for years; people who had grieved alongside the parents and families whod lost their children. But that didnt matter to the crazies, whod been thoroughly brainwashed by cable news into believing the abductor had to be someone from the neighborhood.

In December of 2015, a Georgia man named Alvin Stovall drove 300 miles up the coast, parked in front of Jose Partidas house, and shot him to death when he came home from work. Alvin was certain Jose was the murderer of Hailey Davis and the abductor of Matthew Roman and Muhammad Ahad. Hed heard from a cable news anchor that Jose had a criminal record. That, as well as Joses name, was all Alvin needed to justify his action. 

What the anchor had neglected to mention was Joses record was from 1977. And it was for nothing worse than being a passenger in a stolen car. Jose did his three months, got out on his 22nd birthday, and had been a model citizen ever since. He was my friend.

After Joses murder, the local police were ordered to keep a tight lid on any information pertaining to the disappearances. When Alyssa Harris was reported missing two days ago, it was printed on page four of the local newspaper. So far, there hadnt been anyone from the major media outlets poking around. I know its only a matter of time, though. Yesterday morning, someone who looked like a reporter was tailing the police cars when they came to investigate the bloody pacifier. For the rest of the day, my phone rang and rang. When I answered, whoever was on the other line just hung up.

That alone was enough to make me worried. My name is Luis Goncalves. Ive been on Hawthorn Lane for 40 years. Ive lived by myself since Robert passed away in 1999. Jose Partida was my next-door neighbor. While I appreciate the efforts of our law enforcement officials, they werent able to stop Alvin Stovall from murdering my friend. They arent able to stop whoever is taking the neighborhood children. Ive resorted to keeping my pistol holstered to my side all day, every day; even in my house.

I know that may sound paranoid, but look at it from my perspective. Someone is abducting and killing children on my street. An innocent man was gunned down because the news media has convinced a large group of people that Latinos are dangerous criminals. And yesterday morning, hanging from a small branch on a tree in my front yard, was a pacifier dripping with a childs blood. I cant take my chances.

All that said, theres one more thing. Im reluctant to talk about it, because its something I saw when I was experiencing a dizzy spell from my blood pressure medication. Id blacked out from the medication before, so this couldve been nothing but a hallucination. Still, these days, with everything thats going on, I think it bears mentioning.

Last night, I was washing up after a midnight snack. The sink is in front of a picture window that overlooks the front yard. Since it was dark out, I couldnt see anything but the reflection of myself and the kitchen behind me. I was already feeling dizzy from my medication, but it wasnt severe enough for me to have to sit, so I kept cleaning. 

As I washed the last dish, the overhead light blew. The kitchen went dark. It took a moment for my eyes to acclimate, but I could soon see the neighborhood outside. And there was something across the street, opening the Richter familys mailbox. 

A wave of dizziness went through me and I gripped the edge of the counter to steady myself, but Im certain what I saw was really there. It was a pale, nude man with freakishly long legs and even longer arms that protruded from his hips, rather than his shoulders. Despite him being bent down, it was obvious he was tall enough to peer through a second-story window. 

He paused with the mailbox half open, then abruptly stepped away and turned around. In two, long strides, he crossed the street into my yard. He gazed through my kitchen window with large, gray eyes. I stared back. A toothless mouth opened, stretching wide enough to fit a basketball. I reached for my pistol. Through the glass, I heard the sound of infants screaming from deep inside his throat. His mouth shut, then twisted into a grin. Then his long, spindly legs carried him away, down the street, and into the woods.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[f_](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[r_](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In our quest to drill for more and more oil, I think we finally went too deep. Part 2. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In our quest to drill for more and more oil, I think we finally went too deep. Part 2. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4q5n77/in_our_quest_to_drill_for_more_and_more_oil_i/)

The following hours passed in a blur of frantic calls to corporate, systems checks, and a near riot when the divers refused to collect the rapidly-dispersing grease slick that used to be John Edmundson. 

The tension broke when Gervaso Zaragoza, whose headache had returned with a vengeance, grabbed a wrench that weighed almost as much as he did, hoisted it over his head like he was going to hit someone, and then toppled backward and fell on his ass. Its amazing how the humor of someone falling down can diffuse a volatile situation. After a few minutes, the divers stopped complaining and did their part while the rest of the crew shut up and went back to work.

I hadnt told anyone what Id seen in the water. As far as corporate was concerned, a catastrophic failure in the hydraulics system was what had pulped their employee. Yes, people with knowledge of the systems involved would be able to dispute it, but at the moment, which was what mattered, no one did. Id be able to talk with corporate later in the week, once I knew what was going on, and theyd appreciate me keeping it from the rest of the crew. A plausible lie is always better than a disruptive truth. 

During the commotion, when I was trying to get everyone to calm down, the tentacles, or whatever they were, had fallen back to the floor of the plain. They sat in straight lines at the bottom. I dumped all the data showing their movement to a pair of USB sticks, pocketed them, and purged the storage array of the evidence.

For the rest of the day, I sat at the console and did my best to work without interruption. While the calls to and from corporate had slowed, every 45-or-so minutes, Id be forced to respond to another board members secretary asking the same questions Id already answered a dozen times. Thankfully, as the day came to an end, even those calls died down. It was quiet.

My direct supervisors left via helicopter in the early evening. I was in charge for the weekend. It wasnt a new experience; the upper management of the platform had the freedom to go back to the mainland and visit their families a few times a month, and they did so as frequently as possible. I was used to being in charge. In fact, I enjoyed not having anyone breathing down my neck.

In the morning, more of the crew were reporting headaches. Gervaso was not one of them. He said he felt a lot better, and even volunteered to take the shifts of a few of his colleagues who were under the weather. His supervisor, Quan Williams, who felt like shit, told him to do whatever he wanted. I found out about that much later.

Id been busy since early in the morning, working remotely from my dorm, and using my laptop to control one of the drones. I was studying the tentacles. Overnight, one had moved. Not much, but enough to warrant my investigation - especially because it was touching one of the platforms support beams.

To make matters worse, the bottom was exceptionally murky. Sediment was floating in a thick cloud. Visibility was awful. While I could see the tentacle touching the platform through a visual/sonar composite, the resolution was low. It was obvious there was movement on the floor of the plain, but its source was invisible. Part of me was certain something was being intentionally hidden. 

Around noon, Anand, the head medic, knocked on my door. I met him in the hallway. He informed me that 34 of the 66 crew members were sick with debilitating headaches. I told him to keep me abreast of what was going on, and if anyone took a turn for a worse, to keep it quiet and come to me immediately. He nodded. I think he understood the importance of avoiding another commotion. 

I didnt have to wait long. Anand came back at 2pm. He looked upset. When I asked whod gotten worse, he looked around, then put his finger to his lips, shushing me. I nodded and he beckoned me to follow him. I did.

We traversed the labyrinthine staircases of the platform. We were heading toward the mechanical room. I hated the mechanical room.

The mechanical room was where all the heaviest equipment was located. It was always loud, always filthy, and always dangerous. Pumps and engines rattled and expelled noxious fumes while hydraulic cables transported fluids under pressures so high that a leak no wider than a human hair could cut a man in half. The crew who worked down there were a mixture of brave and insane. Theyd been putting in double time over the last few weeks as they tested and prepared the platform to begin its main drilling cycle.

Anand and I reached the room and found five crewmembers being kept at bay by their supervisor, Karen Vant. When they saw me, they started asking questions - all relating to Gervaso Zaragoza, whod volunteered to work there for the day, and Frank Panagakos. Id never met Frank before, but I knew he was one of the newer mechanics on the platform. Karen told her guys to shut up and let us through. To their credit, they did.

Karen, Anand, and I walked down the main corridor between two massive generators. Karen told us how all the holes in the platform from the accident with Edmundson had been patched. All but one. The one we were coming up on. 

The mechanical room was essentially the basement of the platform. Below it was nothing but pipes, cables, and water. I saw the hole ahead of us. As we got closer, I saw there was something coming out of it. Something bright red and glinting in the harsh, overhead fluorescent light. My breath caught in my throat.

We approached the hole. A hundred feet below, greenish-gray waves heaved against one another. I got on my knees and peered down, making sure not to touch the thing coming out. On the northern support beam, a thin line of red rose out of the Gulf, all the way to the underside of the platform and over to the hole. Once inside, it stretched down the corridor. Karen asked me if I had any idea what it was. I lied and told her I had no idea. Anand urged us forward, and we continued down the corridor, following the red tube.

We turned corners and ducked under cables and piping until we reached one of the hottest, noisiest, and filthiest corners of the room. Gervaso was there, facing Frank. They stood, motionless and open mouthed, staring at one another as we walked toward them. They didnt move or acknowledge our approach.

The closer we got, it became obvious something was very, very wrong with them. The red thing had grown up Gervasos leg and chest and appeared to have entered his face under his chin. But that was the least disconcerting part. 

The light was dim over here; blocked by the piping and machinery. I had to get in close to see exactly what was happening. Karen produced a flashlight without my knowledge and as soon as I was within a foot of their faces, she flicked on the light. I gasped.

Gervaso and Frank were joined by thin, red veins. They appeared to have sprouted from Gervasos eyes, and they entered Franks face at various spots in his mouth, eyes, and forehead. They trembled slightly, almost like they were shivering. As I watched, another cilia-like vein pushed from the center of Gervasos eye and twirled outward, searching for purchase, before settling on Franks temple and slipping inside.

What is it?, Karen asked. I looked at Anand. He shook his head. A string of drool oozed out of Franks mouth.

We cant leave them here, Anand said. They need to get to a hospital.

Can we move them?, I asked.

I dont know, Anand told me. They might move on their own if we ask.

Gervaso, estas bien?, I asked. He didnt answer. He didnt move. Frank? Nothing.

I took the flashlight from Karen and touched it to the veins. They stretched under the pressure, but didnt react. I pressed harder.

Maybe you shouldnt -- started Anand, but Id already pressed hard enough to detach one of the veins from under Franks tongue. Frank exhaled heavily and his left eye turned to look at me. Before any of us could react, the entire platform shook. 

What the fuck was that?, Anand practically shouted.

I have no idea, Karen answered, wide eyed. It felt like something just crashed into one of the support beams.

**Will be concluded.**

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[_f](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[_r](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh pasta; beautiful at any shape, beautiful at any size. [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 22:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My erection lasted longer than four hours - and I didn't call a doctor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 20:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My erection lasted longer than four hours - and I didn't call a doctor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 20:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theres something dangerous living near the power plant in Bridgeport, CT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theres something dangerous living near the power plant in Bridgeport, CT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 19:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know if any of you are familiar with the area, but the people who live over here have been talking about it for the last couple weeks. No one can agree on what it is, but the one thing they know is a lot of pets have gone missing. Birds, too. The power plants on Long Island Sound, and there used to be seagulls and herons all over the place. Not anymore.

The Connecticut Posts main office is only a few blocks away on State Street, but they havent published stories about anything out of the ordinary. Same with News 12. That doesnt mean they havent heard rumors, though. A guy I work with, Dion Hargrove, called up the Post last week to tell them about something he saw over by the old Remington building.

The Remington building is right across from a walking park that runs parallel to the University of Bridgeport campus. The parks beautiful during the day, but at night, like the rest of the area, its sketchy as all hell. If what Dion saw was after dark, he wouldnt have thought much of it. He wouldnt have stayed to watch. But at 11am on a sunny day, he knew what he was seeing was very out of place.

While Dion walked, he noticed a person crouching by the front door of the Remington building. He wasnt too close, but it was a clear shot across the street through the chainlink fence. The person was wearing a heavy, green NY Jets coat, despite it being almost 80 degrees out and humid. In his hands was a cat. And he was eating it. Now, Bridgeport has its share of homeless people, many of whom are mentally ill. If you remember that story from Florida about the homeless guy who ate his friends face, well, he was originally from Bridgeport. But I digress.

As Dion watched, the guy buried his face into the poor cats belly and gnawed away. Then he looked up and saw Dion watching him. He dropped the cat and ran, but not before Dion could see something was very wrong with him. First off, he looked extremely overweight. That alone isnt worthy of mention, of course, but there was something deeply unsettling about his bulk. It shifted under the heavy coat as he ran, but not with his steps. It moved on its own.

Right before the man turned the corner into the rear of the building, something fell from his coat. It was like a reddish-gray slab of skin. It trailed behind him as he turned, but then lifted on its own and disappeared behind the building.

Dion didnt know what the hell hed just seen, but he figured he probably had to call the cops. Bridgeport cops have an unpleasant reputation, but considering the guy was so close to the University, Dion was worried the he might try to hurt a student. The cops came and took his statement, but he never heard anything back. His call didnt show up in the Posts police log.

Dions report is the most detailed, but its not the only one. Not by a long shot. Boaters in Long Island Sound have complained about their motors getting snagged and ruined as they passed by the power plant. Nearby residents, aside from losing their pets, have made noise complaints about a low, screaming howl coming primarily from the area surrounding the plant, but sometimes as close as the street outside. And then theres David Chung.

David was a student at the University of Bridgeport. Hed just moved into his dorm in August, and the security cameras showed him walking around the campus and heading off down the street to the beach.

The next morning, Davids body was found in the water near the power plants dock. There was a brief investigation, and it was determined he drowned while swimming and the damage to his body was the result of being struck by a barge delivering coal to the plant.

My friend in the police department, though, told me hed seen floaters hit by those barges. David didnt look anything them. To make matters worse, the official report didnt mention the kids wounds. The holes. Holes all over his body that looked like theyd been sucked out, rather than punctured. And the report also neglected to mention the fact that David had been found wrapped in a heavy, green, NY Jets coat. The same one Dion Hargrove had described to the police.

To anyone who thinks this warrants more of an investigation, I implore you to spread this around. I want people to see whats happening here and not let the violence get swept under the rug like in every other urban community. Because I know something very wrong is living near that power plant. Something thats now moved on from birds and cats to people. And every night, as I shiver behind locked doors with my rifle, I can hear it howling.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[_f](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[_r](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is the last day of my "no body horror for a month" experiment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 14:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All in all, I'd say it was really successful. I posted 15 stories (~~probably~~ 16 by the time today comes to a close), and most of them did pretty well.

The ones that performed below average, according only to upvotes, not how I feel about their quality, did so mostly because they were on the fringe of what NoSleep allows (and a big thank you to the mods for giving them the benefit of the doubt).

It felt good to get out of my comfort zone. Even though the months before September didn't feature *that much* body horror, it was still absolutely a crutch I used on days when I couldn't figure out what to write. 

Forcing myself away from that whole sub-genre and still keeping my output at the level I've grown to demand definitely stressed my creativity, but I'm better for having done so. I'd recommend it to anyone struggling to get out of a rut.

All that said, I can't wait for you guys to see the disgusting and depraved stuff I have in mind for October.

Toothpaste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vanessa felt a familiar tingle between her legs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 13:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spiders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making Faces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making Faces </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 19:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was torn from my sleep by the sound of my daughters screams. I rushed across the hall and saw Jessie standing in front of her bedroom window. When I wrapped my arms around her, I noticed her pajamas were soaked with sweat. The screams tapered off and gasping sobs replaced them; her tiny body heaving as it attempted to take in more air than her lungs would allow.

I picked her up and carried her into my room. We sat on the bed and I held her until shed calmed enough for me to ask what happened. She shook her head. Hot tears spilled down her cheeks.

Please, sweetheart - I promise its okay. What happened?

Jessies wide, blue eyes stared into mine, still leaking away the memory of whatever trauma shed endured. She pulled my nightgown, beckoning me to come down to her level so she could whisper something in my ear. I obliged.

There was a big girl in my window making faces at me.

I lifted my head again to look at Jessie, still feeling the hot condensation from her breath in my ear.

A big girl?, I asked, puzzled. Jessie nodded and wiped her eyes on her sweaty pajamas.

Come on, I told her, forcing a smile. Lets get you in the tub. Ill let you use my bath bomb. 

For the first time since the ordeal began, a smile flashed across her face. Finally.

As we waited for the tub to fill, Jessie held me around my waist. Her crying had stopped, but she still trembled. I stroked her hair and told her it was okay, over and over, while wondering what could have possibly scared her so badly. This type of episode was entirely unlike her. Quite the contrary; Id always walk in on her sneaking peeks of scary movies on TV even though Id told her, in no uncertain terms, that she wasnt to watch them. But still, even though shed seen some creepy monsters and murderers, theyd never given her nightmares.

When the tub was filled and the bath bomb was releasing bubbles and glitter and scents that delighted and relaxed Jessie, I helped her out of her pajamas and into the water. She sat there peacefully as her tiredness caught up with her again. Her eyes closed. I continued stroking her hair.

After a little while, knowing she needed to go back to bed, I shook her awake. She opened her eyes and saw me, prompting a smile. But then she stiffened, her eyes widening, and screamed again. I reached into the tub and grabbed her, trying to hold her close, but she pushed and clawed at me, trying to get away.

I cried out to her, Jessie, what is hap -- and I stopped. Out of the corner of my eye, I saw something behind me. Something at the window.

I whirled around, yanking Jessie against my back as I shielded her from something I hadnt even properly seen. But soon I had. And my own panicked shriek drowned out that of my daughter.

Peering in through the bathroom window was a round, wide face. Pale white with small, jaundiced eyes, it pushed against the window screen until it fell out and clattered on the floor. The face moved toward us on a dowel-thin, articulated neck connected directly to its chin.

Get out!, I shouted, mustering up as much violence in my voice as possible. 

The neck was blocking our path to the door, and the hideous face turned and stared directly at me before opening its mouth and saying one word: Jessie.

A paralyzing wave of incomprehensible terror bloomed inside me. The voice was low and droning, like a normal womans voice slowed and pitched down an octave. I felt Jessie stiffen against my back and she pressed her face against my spine, as if trying to hide inside me.

More neck came through the window, the vertebrae bulging against its tight skin as it swayed in the space around us like a long finger with a hundred knuckles. 

Jess...ie. The voice was even deeper now; I felt it in my chest and bowels.

The face moved toward me and I struck it with my fist. My hand thudded uselessly against its forehead. Before my eyes, the face began to change. Its features elongated, then contracted. Its mouth stretched to its earlobes, then shrank down to a pinhole. The entire topography of its cheekbones and chin and jaw shattered, then reformed. A second later, I was looking at a terribly deformed version of my daughter.

Jessie. It exhaled heavily. Hot, stinking breath filled my nostrils.

The strength in my arms vanished. The stability in my legs evaporated. I dropped to the floor, helpless. Jessie was exposed.

Jess...ie. The serpentine neck wrapped around my daughter and pulled her toward the window. Jessie, no longer screaming, struggled to breathe against its constricting grasp. Her face reddened. The terrible thing drooled black fluid onto the top of her head. Jessie went limp. She, and the creature, disappeared into the night.

My body regained its strength and I bolted to the window. In the dim light of the crescent moon, I watched the long legs of the thing carry my daughter away into the woods.

I called 911. The police came. They investigated for days. I was the only suspect in her disappearance, but as days turned into weeks and weeks stretched into months, the trail had gone cold. Even if I was still a suspect, they had nothing to even hint at me being the reason for her disappearance. And, in fact, there was evidence to the contrary.

During the initial investigation, when every nook and cranny of the house was looked at, when every piece of furniture was upended, and when every inch of the property was examined, there were only two pieces of evidence; neither of which had anything to do with me, other than to help corroborate my story.

The first morning of the investigation, officers noticed a trail of glitter from the bath bomb stretching from the bathroom window all the way through the yard and high into the trees at the mouth of the forest. When an officer scaled one of the trees, he found glitter stuck to leaves 25 feet up. It was strange, they admitted, but in their words glitter gets everywhere. 

While they were quick to dismiss that as direct evidence, they couldnt explain the other thing they found. Smeared across the window in Jessies room was the greasy, distorted shape of a womans enormous face. When the lab analyzed the cells thatd been left behind, the results were inconclusive. The samples were deemed non-viable. To me, that meant they wanted to hide what theyd discovered. After a long while, the active investigation was closed.

Its been six years since Jessie was taken. I live alone in the same house, and every night, I go to bed wishing my daughter would come back to me. Recently, I noticed my bedroom windows had started getting dirty faster than they usually did. I washed them and didnt think much of it. Not until this morning. 

This morning, I woke up to find the outside-facing side of every window covered in grayish, translucent grease. For a while, I struggled to understand what had happened. Then I got to the picture window in the living room. It, too, was filthy. But there was something in that filth. Outlined against the wide piece of glass was the impression of a large face and a thin, articulated neck. The same face Id seen that night. And next to it, clear as day, was the print of another, smaller face. 

Jessies face. 

Supported by the same, terrible neck.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[_f](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[_r](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ::grumble grumble:: 24 hour limit ::grumble grumble:: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 17:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the scariest thing(s) you guys have ever seen outside your window? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your uncle just loves to up the ante. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 00:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My only experience with ASMR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My only experience with ASMR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 19:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been dealing with anxiety my entire life. Whether in social situations, work situations, or even at home by myself, feelings of panic rise to the surface and consume me. Medications dont work. Therapy doesnt work. Each day, I wake up knowing at some point before I go back to bed, I will feel like the world is about to collapse around me.

I heard about ASMR online. For those who dont know, its short for Autonomous Sensory Meridian Response. Basically, its an induced euphoric response that supposedly causes deep relaxation and a sense of wellbeing. Ive never been relaxed. Ive never been well.

Like all natural products designed to elicit a positive biological response, the ASMR space on the Internet is full of bullshit. Countless fraudsters and faux-experts tout extraordinary claims, and while scientists have found no direct correlation between ASMR and health, mental or otherwise, those who sell ASMR-related products will tell you its the next big thing. The thing doctors dont want you to know about. Needless to say, I was skeptical.

Skepticism, however, in the face of daily panic, can often upshift into something resembling hope. I did my research. I sifted through claims and medical information with my untrained, but nonetheless determined, mind. 

Another problem with something like ASMR is that people claim they know what theyre doing, when, in fact, theyre just trying to get hits on their website. YouTube, for example, is full of kids talking seductively into their microphones while dull synthpop plays in the background. Those are the top hits for ASMR. You need to dig deep before you find something you think is legit. 

And I did.

Last year, I found an ASMR site run by a university in Ukraine. The cursory listen I gave seemed relaxing enough; a soft voice over gentle electronic pulses and the certain sounds from nature, like running water. The associated imagery was abstract and colorful, reminding me of Easter palates and springtime flowers. The samples were only five minutes long. To access the rest, they needed credit card and shipping information. At least the subscription came with a free Blu-Ray copy 8-10 weeks later.

I plugged in my payment information, name, and address, knowing American Express would cancel any fraudulent charges in the event the Ukrainians wanted to scam me. I wasnt particularly concerned about that, though. The payment went through, and I was greeted by a Members Only page and libraries filled with various ASMR videos. I put on my noise-cancelling headphones, clicked the first video, and set it to fullscreen. 

The world melted away. For the first time in my life, I felt relaxation overtake the omnipresent anxiety. Peace washed through my mind and passed in a wave down to my chest and throughout my limbs. My sensation of self vanished. Whatever this university had developed, it was a miracle. Enraptured by the sights and sounds and sensations, I remained in my chair for two straight days.

I awoke to the feeling of my headphones being torn off and a rough hand shaking my shoulder. Panic bloomed within my chest, but agony quickly overtook it. My legs and lower back were searing with hideous pain and I screamed, only to have the same hand clasp over my mouth.

Shut up, came a voice with a thick accent. A Ukrainian accent. Scream again and well take even more. Do you have any money in the house? Any jewelery?

I tried to shake my head, which was pinned back against the computer chair from the mans brute strength. No, I grumbled behind his hand, tears streaming down my face from the overwhelming pain.

Good. Now sleep for another hour or so. He strapped the headphones back on my ears and straightened me up so I was facing the monitor again. Before slipping back beneath the waves of bliss, I realized Id been strapped in my chair. I didnt know why.

After an hour, the video ended. The audio cut out. The pain returned. I screamed again, this time alone in my apartment. I was still strapped to the chair. I looked down at my legs, certain they were broken or slashed by the intruders. But my legs were gone. My screaming stopped and everything blurred. I reached for the phone on my desk and managed to dial 911 before passing out, my hand groping at the pain in my back where my left kidney had been.

[More.](http://unsettlingstories.com/index)

[_f](http://facebook.com/unsettlingstories)

[_r](http://www.reddit.com/r/subject3642)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dancing Plant of Questionable Whims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 16:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dancing Plant of Questionable Whims stood calmly, as if in sullen defiance of its name. Looking like a combination of a ficus and a cuttlefish, a slow, undulating pattern of bioluminescence ran along its exterior. I watched, frustrated, as the blobs of light settled at the base of its trunk, near where its tendrils met the dirt. It wanted nothing to do with me.

Recalling earlier, unrelated successes with a particular technique, I poked it with a stick. No response. My frustration grew into annoyance. If I couldnt get this thing to move, Id be in deep shit.

Plant, I said, doing my best to sound encouraging, rather than irritated. No response. I prodded it again with the stick. The chromatophores Id perturbed shifted into yellow momentarily, but then turned back to the uniform dark green of the rest of its bulk.

Plant, please, I sighed. I slumped onto the mossy ground wondering why my luck always had to be so awful.

My professor, Dr. Rogerworthy Meatus, had tasked me with finding a Dancing Plant of Questionable Whims and cajoling it back to the university for further study. The plant was a newer breed of hybrids following the Realm Integration. Most hybrids never developed beyond a cluster of cells. This particular plant, though, a hybrid of flora and fauna from both the Earth Realm and the Other, appears to have thrived - albeit in small numbers.

Plaaaaaaaaant, I whined. I jumped to my feet in frustration and pulled on one of its tendrils. Color and light shot across its body. It rustled.

With new enthusiasm, I pulled another tendril. Same effect. It rustled for a little longer and shifted its weight back and forth. This had to be the ticket. With both hands, I grasped handfuls of its tendrils and pulled. The Dancing Plant of Questionable Whims began to dance with me.

Round and round, back and forth - I held the plants tendrils and we twirled around the small clearing. More color and light streamed across its trunk and its tendrils thickened and gripped my hands. I began to laugh. Id never danced like this before.

Our pace reached a fevered pitch and I held on for dear life while we spun and stepped over logs and rocks and roots while squnnies and butterfoxes ran and hid. The scenery blurred and the lights and colors on the plant all converged in one spot and shot downward. Everything stopped. The plant froze in place, the light and color bright and brilliant on the trunk behind the tentacles. It shuddered violently. 

I never saw it coming.

An eruption of sticky, white sap exploded from the tendrils, covering and soaking me from neck to knees. I fell backward in horror and disgust as the plant shimmied in a way I can only describe as coquettish before rooting itself back into the mossy ground.

Two hours later, after Id given up trying to get all the sap off me, I attempted to get the plant to move with me again. It didnt. I thought of my professor. Theres no way Id be able to complete his task. I began the long walk back to the university, realizing Id just been outwitted by a plant; a plant whose whims were no longer in question.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
