<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4602</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY SHIT I WASN'T LOOKING AT THE USER AT ALL! Yeah, again, thank you so much for that! You have a great taste in music, dude! What'd you think of The Theater Equation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a I'm heavily bias, but not in my opinion, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you heard Ayreon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I know you! Probably 2. The variety is so great. But 3 is great too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you count down the seconds until you leave, I count down the days until I have to go. 11. Summer went fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU! They're so great! Their name made them sound almost like a Primus wannabe. I was just blown away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gordon Ramsay. I'm one for dirty talk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey you're an hour to leaving now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done two in a row for the same reason. Because school is. Like, in a week and a half, I'm going to wade out today and take some stuff to knock me out tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 20:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Don't know them
2. Shit I don't know. Maybeeee Jacob's Ladder, Heathers, and Scott Pilgrim?
3. Yeah! I mainly play bass, but also sing and do a little guitar and piano.
4. Lots. Currently playing LA Noire for the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 19:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may be cheaper and a better start to play SH2 first. It's phenomenal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that show too. Auburn Hills. So awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None. None. Totally none ever. In case my dad finds my account, I feel that I need to *specifically* say that I have NEVER done drugs EVER. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When TA leaked somebody made a stream where we all collaborated to figure out the lyrics. In ANB when Arabelle says "Remember, Bug?" We couldn't believe that's what was said. Then someone came in with confirmation and everyone flipped their shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Feels like it's 4 even though it's noon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comics: nope but I'm intrigued

Game: Silent Hill series, I'm not sure which one. Maybe 4? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I'm not at the most wonderful spot for my brain to function good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Sakamoto I listened to Marry Christmas Mr Lawrence and immediately added him on Spotify. So beautiful and relaxing.

For Alva Noto I listened to Uni C and it's...certainly interesting. It has the sound effects and bizarreness I love from the SH soundtracks, but not the melodies that keep me hooked and returning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watched House, browsed creepy subreddits, listened to music, had a mild anxiety attack, and once people I knew started waking up I talked to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mean, mean soup](https://i.imgur.com/7rZBOsn.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 15:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now? Probably Hemispheres. But I've been *in the mood* for Clockwork Angels as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 15:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By using poor wording </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was fucking crazy though. I wish that I could relive it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 14:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are awesome! Where do you get them from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 12:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's alright, but honestly I'd prefer to have the one remote from the Goosebumps episode. I think it's the one where the kid freezes time and fucks with stuff, but then the remote breaks (ala-Pleasantville) and he's just kinda stuck there forever. Those stories are pretty fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 12:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple albums were left off:

* Power Windows
* Hold Your Fire
* Presto
* Test For Echo
* Feedback (technically) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never forget what we promised </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 12:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just prior to TA's release, after it leaked, some people on a stream made a promise. We promised to always remember...

 #rememberbug2k16 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - The Stars Look Down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 12:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is one of the songs that will divide us between great and bad. Being maybe a little bit *too* open and loving, I think this is a great song, but I'd love to hear your thoughts!

___

 This is based on a 1935 novel of the same name by A. J. Cronin, which was also made into a film in 1939. The book tells of an English mining town pre-WWI following families and their trials and triumphs, particularly a young man who is a miner and tries to change the conditions for which miners work, but in the end looses his battle for change in parliament and also his wife. He gained nothing and returned to be a miner.

 Neil Peart had lost his wife to cancer and penned this song about his experience. In theVapor Trailstour book, he wrote: "This seemed to express a fitting view of an uncaring universe."

[Source](http://www.songfacts.com/detail.php?id=3795)

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/qZ0vQ_r6ghU)

[(Should be the) remix](https://youtu.be/yAWW4NALQ8I) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 12:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marillion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 07:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Very, very, very relevant](https://youtu.be/sodthxK1z44) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 00:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are the last three episodes of this show's seasons always so goddamn painful. Seeing this immediately made me 10x sadder than I was before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roughly 24mph </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep going </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new kitten Gabriel has taken to sleeping in my room. I woke up to this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 09:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not joking or being pretentious, as a huge fan of prog I think II is in their top 3 best albums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rush fans are pretty open from what I've seen, but they're still the best band ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look so horrified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude no. Sorry, but no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Peaceable Kingdom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about terrorism and the forces of destructive people against those that long for a a time of peace. Specifically, it's a response to the attacks by terrorist on September 11, 2001 against the United States. It also refers to the response of hate against hate and the hope that those who desire peace can have a positive effect on others ^^[source](http://www.songfacts.com/detail.php?id=3412)

It used to be an instrumental prior to the terrorist attacks on 9/11. Do you think it would have been better that way or not?

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/edMiJF-IMEU)

[Remix](https://youtu.be/RsPW7y4Xc0I) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to Spotify. He has an album/playlist called Timeline. That+lyrics should help. It's great stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Coheed were to make a compilation album for the Amory Wars universe like Ayreon's Timeline, what would you want the tracklist to be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The long ass title says it all. Try to keep it at a maximum of 2 discs (90 minutes per disc) and tell all the plot possible. Also, make it in chronological order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. As a bass player you either need to improv on boring songs or shut up about how bored you are.

On boring songs I tend to listen to the drums for energy which is, as I've recently learned, a method that Flea uses. It can make dull parts 10x as fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget shitting with the door open and extra long showers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true but okay.

I mainly play Rush, Dream Theater, stuff like that. It's only 90% of bass parts that suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 17:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a joke tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 02:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaah, le pain. I love le pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like Rush, Dream Theater, etc then definitely [Oktopus](https://youtu.be/nLN_ANG2AAU). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 23:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love THE, probably one of my all time favorite albums, but honestly TTE was a pretty big let down for me. Just didn't quite work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 21:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Ghost Rider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 20:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first song on VT that I heard. It's really, *really* good.

___
This is a song based on the chronicles of Neil Peart's adventures on a motorcycle journey documented in his bookGhost Rider: Travels on the Healing Road. Peart, who is the bands drummer and lyricist, set out on a 14-month, 55,000 mile motorcycle journey around America after losing his 19-year-old daughter in an auto accident in August 1997, and his wife to cancer just 10 months later.

[Source](http://www.songfacts.com/detail.php?id=3155)

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/3SomjthIXTI)

[Vapor Trails tour](https://youtu.be/su3zwzmUrxo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genesis fans are never chill. One of my top rated posts is an in depth analysis of why post-Pete Genesis doesnt sucj </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have exact sources, but I read it in one of a few Rush books and probably in some random article. The books I'd recommend (that I have) are Contents Under Pressure and Rush FAQ as well as Neil's books </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair enough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude really? I constantly see them hailed as one of the best prog bands of all time. I have friends that only dabble in prog who preordered Affinity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried many times, but I can't stand that album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too obviously a troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 08:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's my favorite doctor. Such a shame everything behind set happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 07:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #[STOP](https://youtu.be/l5xTReubUro) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 07:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay but I actually like the song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 07:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize that all the songs on Feedback are songs they used to play as a bar band, right? Plus it definitely sounded like they had fun, especially when playing these songs live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 07:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick fact: It was released just prior to the R30 tour and the songs on it were ones that they used to cover as a bar band. Figured that's worth mentioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure others agree with you and I have nothing wrong with Alive 1997, but I'll never be able to agree. I think Alive 2007 is a masterpiece and their all around best album. It was the first Daft Punk album I heard and has been on every device I use for music since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 03:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about half the sub tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 22:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IS HE ACTUALLY CALLED J-ROC? THAT'S CRAZY, KNOW WHAT I'M SAAIIIIIIIIIN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 21:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol sure whatever you want </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 20:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might take that trade. Especially because Limelight by Rush is one of my favorite songs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 07:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's leaving out a huge part. It was more along the lines of: at first it will be familiar to people who have played a lot of action games, but will end up being something very different as it goes on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [For those who don't know](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dgGJhaCS6WA)

I'm not sure how he feels about it being shared, but something can be said about the most raunchy part of an artists' career being because he was standing up for his son is pretty great. Also the way he handled everything is so badass and mature

Edit:

[An ironic movie appearance by Alex](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u5wm6F4LjjQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily Ghost Of A Chance (at least the chorus) is my favorite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Garden Road </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, CA gets so much love here, it's great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, that's MR Getty Ley to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outcry is so underrated, one of my all time favorite DT songs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you're enjoying it! I've found some great stuff too. I think I may have to put this in the sidebar for newcomers/infrequent visitors to check out. I'll talk to the other mod about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's an adorable post from Geddy's Instagram </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 04:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 02:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 02:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Van Halen and it was clear they were doing it because it was fun. People like Van Halen and Guns And Roses don't need any more money, it's purely a joy thing at this point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought there was something peculiar about the flow between Comfortably Numb and The Show Must Go On </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to farm for some quality posting content by admitting that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always down for more obscure Yes, but how is this relevant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I get to Skype I'm gonna haze you so hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 18:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Working Man
* Beneath, Between, And Behind
* The Fountain Of Lamneth
* 2112
* Xaaanaaaduuuuu
* Hemispheres
* Natural Science
* The Camera Eye
* Digital Man
* Kid Gloves
* Territories
* Prime Mover
* Superconductor
* Ghost Of A Chance
* Cold Fire
* Time And Motion
* Ceiling Unlimited
* Heart Full Of Soul
* Workin' Them Angels
* The Garden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely okay! Variety is key </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 22:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am and thanks, but idk. It's just good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Daft Punk's Random Access Memories will be considered a classic. The production, the songs, the variety, and the timelessness is perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually the most pleasant. Like it guarantees that you'll be happy without spoiling it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna make a YouTube playlist. Too much work. Waaay too much work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes smoke 1 black tar pot rock, sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last tour </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 15:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silent Hill 3 scared me while sober. Dark room+headphones. Try it.

DON'T, I repeat, DON'T watch Jacob's Ladder while high </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's make a favorites playlist on Spotify! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 14:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought, because I've been really busy these past two days, I could maybe make it up by doing a cool project.

The idea is that we all add a few non-Rush songs to a [collaborative Spotify playlist](https://open.spotify.com/user/gamesinabit/playlist/2EQwGXPVAvzOWlvVai9kJO) so we can all get an idea for each other's musical tastes. I've got it started with two of my favorite songs right now and I can't wait to see the variety we get in here!

I also wanted to say thank you so much for sticking with me through inconsistencies. I've been going through some personal shit and have finally started feeling better and will put in a lot more effort to do both the listen through as well as cool stuff like this.

Cheers! ~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's rad as hell, dude. I once got a few records for, like, 50c (Days Of Future Passed by TMB, Abacab by Genesis, and The Long Run by The Eagles) but this is waaay better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yess! I hope it comes into play later in the actual story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the rumors about the set being the same are true, yeah but less so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll believe it when I have it in my hands. Waiting for anything new since just before the release of Dallas, I've learned to not get my hopes up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of Coheed's albums but the newest are part of the Amory Wars's universe. The next one will be too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's cause Eyeball records went under </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine getting drunk with friends and playing it would be great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 11:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do pot and get paranoid while playing Silent Hill and tell me it's not bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 06:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it, I said it's terrifying. But that makes it a bit better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 06:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 06:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Defcon Warning System is a bit unnerving, but the doomsday clock is waaaay scarier. The knowledge that the world is *that* close to ending is just horrifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [serious] What's the closest the world came to ending? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bass player, practice practice PRACTICE!

Learn a song far out of your capabilities slowly bit by bit and don't worry about how good you are. Keep at it daily </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Faces Of Stone by David Gilmour](https://youtu.be/XCOUyFJPed8)

It's about walking in a park with his mother who suffers from dementia and is beautifully depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vocaloid and anime. I don't just mean Death Note/Soul Eater/whatever, I mean shit like K-On. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting high and playing Silent Hill.

Hahahahano </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really care about them much either, but their cover of The Man Who Sold The World is really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened recently for me but apparently the girl sent nudes to various people anyway so nobody cared </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 03:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm one of three pretty active mods there. They both have similarly chill communities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - Ceiling Unlimited </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 12:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personal story time! I didn't care for this song until it popped up on shuffle while I was biking to school on the last day of my Freshman year of high school. Immediately made me 100x more pumped to fail my finals and has been one of my all time favorite Rush songs since.

___

The title is a condition of weather. It is the height ascribed to the lowest layer of clouds or obscuring phenomena when it is reported as broken, overcast, or obscuration and not classified as "thin" or "partial." The ceiling is termed unlimited when these conditions are not satisfied.

[Source](http://www.songfacts.com/detail.php?id=3156)

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/X4RVBGcMWnY)

[Vapor Trails tour](https://youtu.be/eKKXXcPbops) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 12:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, when she recovers and if she's up for an AMA, please shoot me a message so we can get stuff planned out. This would be awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 11:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And around them will play Available Light </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 07:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's awesome, dude! Thanks for contributing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 05:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do remember that name, but my has it been a long time since I've seen it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 04:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I want back to /r/rush and it's going much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 04:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a JoJo fan, but a HUGE Yes fan, and I agree! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 03:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like BoJack Horseman's intro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 02:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not enjoying life nearly as much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 01:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, shout out to Jay from Rushcast for pointing it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 00:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aimee Mann's vocals from the chorus and reversed and put quietly in the background </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 00:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghost Rider is a book I recommend to anybody dealing with grief. It's helped me as well no matter how minuscule my problems are. As for his writing, I doubt he'll stop even if it's only on his blog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 23:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I think it's better now that the huge surge of fans has lowered. It allows for better, more unique discussions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 23:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and girl

Don't be silly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. In my time as mod I have only had a couple people that I've had to actually deal with. Where as on the other sub I mod, /r/TWRP, in our first few months we already had two </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a motif and oh my god. I've listened to these songs a million times and know all of Book 1 and some of 2 on bass, but have never realized this. Great catch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LISTEN THROUGH - One Little Victory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Neil:**

 "I'd been working on that tune and came up with that double bass part. I thought it worked perfectly for the end of the song. But Geddy said, 'That's a great part. You ought to open the song with it. That would just kill.' Frankly, I wouldn't have done it that way-I don't think I would have been so assertive-but Geddy suggested it and I said, 'Okay, I'll try it.'"

**Geddy:**

 "One Little Victory was kind of a triumphant song for us, in the lyrics and the message that the song is about. There was something about that song that seemed just so darned appropriate for opening the record, and also being the first release for us in such a long time. That song started as a collection of jams that Alex had done late at night, just a collection of guitar riffs all linked together in a really kind of a typically-Alex-nonsensical way. I came in the next day after he'd done these things, and just kind of scratched my head but really liked a lot of it. At the same time, there were some lyrics there that Neil had written, which were one of the few lyrics that immediately I just loved, I didn't want to touch a word, it was all great. And so I played with it for a couple of days, started using the digital equipment to manipulate the riffs and add my bass to it, and start writing some vocal melodies. And before I know it I had a song, or what seemed like a song. And then I ran it by Mr. Lerxst here, and he seemed to really dig it. So that kind of became a song and it didn't change much after that."

[Sources from here](http://www.songfacts.com/detail.php?id=3044)

___
[Lyrics](https://youtu.be/iDp_wEKiVE4)

[Vapor Trails tour](https://youtu.be/eKdpbpQpHbk)

[Snakes And Arrows tour](https://youtu.be/rLEFPFWVoIA)

[R40 tour](https://youtu.be/xVjGlM0VojU)

___
Seeing this live made me finally appreciate this song as much as I should. Now I get unbelievably hyped whenever I hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm I actually quite like that idea. I'll strongly consider it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 15:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Message In A Bottle! Simple but fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 15:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Dream Theater fan, I snagged MetropolisPt1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 10:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the sheer amount of damage the event caused and the overall eeriness of a seemingly stable man snapping, killing people and then bombing a school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 10:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. But something about the bomber's backstory, the way he planned and executed it, and just literally everything surrounding this story seems like it would fit perfectly in one of the games. I think it's just because it's a really fucked up story though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 08:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can 100% agree! Especially the Score version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 08:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote that while listening to Dream Theater as well. For their stuff I've only got down 90% of Octavarium, about 60% of Erotomania, and 80% of The Ytse Jam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 08:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOW DARE YOU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 08:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Dream And Day Unite - The Ones Who Set The Sun

Images And Words - Metropolis

Awake - A Mind Beside Itself

Falling Into Infinity - Lines In The Sand

Scenes From A Memory - The Dance Of Eternity

Six Degrees Of Inner Turbulence - The Great Debate

Train Of Thought - Stream Of Consciousness

Octavarium - The Root Of All Evil

Systematic Chaos - The Ministry Of Lost Souls

Black Clouds And Silver Linings - Rite Of Passage

A Dramatic Turn Of Events - Lost Not Forgotten

Dream Theater - The Bigger Picture

The Astonishing - Astonishing (nailed it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can we do to improve the sub? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 08:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got back from a vacation (hence the missing Listen Throughs during the week) and was thinking, it's been a while since I made a thread asking for your input on the job that /u/Antidote and I do in modding and if there's anything we could do to maybe help out in the community more. We're starting Vapor Trails tomorrow and I'm pumped to see what everybody thinks of it. In case it's gone unnoticed, the schedule for the listen through is simply monday-friday with the weekend being a short break unless something came up in my week.

You guys rule and I couldn't ask for a better community. Seriously, it makes the job of modding 100% easier as well as gives me the joy of reading awesome people talk about Rush and consider it "doing some work". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 07:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Outfield - Your Love

You've heard Under The Covers, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
