<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4900</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course....not replacing Nunes is the most leverage Paul Ryan could possibly have over Trump other than having direct access to whatever the Russians probably have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been rumored his name came up in the FISA wiretapping stuff and may be the cause of Nunes freaking out and trying to warn Trump.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the party of Devin Nunes? The guy who held a press conference to publicly obstruct justice? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say what you want, but this is impressive....

It took Bush 8 years, mismanaging one of the worst natural disasters in US history, starting a disastrous war, and a global economy on the brink of collapse to get similar numbers...

Trump looks like he may beat him within 90 days....

Is anyone tired of the winning yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give Trump/Bannon that much credit. They're only trying to shift the blame now as it's apparent even to these incompetent fools that it's going to fail and they have already run out of political capital. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just the way the federal prosecutions are done. The Feds don't like to bring up charges and lose, it looks bad for everyone. 

The Feds move really slowly and methodically on routine charges...now compound that normal process with trying to take down a President, who has a political party that controls Congress, and as Nunes has so clearly demonstrated....and will do pretty much anything to protect him....add to that an Attorney General who's openly lied about his involvement with the Russians as well.

You're going to see evidence laid out slowly and methodically piece by piece to be vetted and digested by the American public for weeks/months. 

The case will be laid out so plainly and clearly that Billy Joe Bob in rural Arkansas will be like...this mofo'er is guilty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worse than that...he was actually a co-sponsor. Since he knew it would pass he could abstain. https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/03/gop-senators-new-bill-would-let-isps-sell-your-web-browsing-data/

Rand Paul is as dishonest, and despicable as they come, he's just better at manipulating his image and playing the media (like his searching for the healthcare bill stunt).

It's hilarious to see people touting Rand Paul and his dad as "outsiders." Ron was a career politician, and yet he accomplished nothing and passed no meaningful legislation.

The only thing he was concerned with was setting up his son/family as a political dynasty much like the Bush or Clinton families. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
