<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6842</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 12:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're right!](http://gfycat.com/SilverDimpledAoudad) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 19:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Radler, Diesel etc. sind doch Biermischgetrnke?

Die 3 neuen Sorten sind brigens "Amber Ale", "Pale Ale" und "Pils 1873", also keine Mixgetrnke und nur in einem Fall ein Pils. Ich habe lediglich das Pale Ale probiert und fand es etwas... generisch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 09:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Now it is possible to overdose on alcohol, but if your definition of "poisoning yourself" is consuming something it is possible to overdose on [...]

There's so much more to it than that definition. It seems like in your view your only two options are consuming alcohol in "healthy" moderate amounts or overdosing.  That is not the case. There's a lot of evidence that chronic overconsumption\* of alcohol has [numerous detrimental health effects. 
](http://www.cdc.gov/alcohol/fact-sheets/alcohol-use.htm) Overdosing is a real and acute concern but the long-term effects should not be ignored either. "Poisoning" is certainly not the wrong word here - just look into *any* toxicology textbook.


\* More than 1 drink/day for women, more than 2 drinks/day for men seems to be the consensus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 11:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like they don't think they could reliably get to 6MJ for next year with this flywheel system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 23:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> France might [dislike](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franco-Prussian_War) those two digits as well, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 23:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This](http://raumzeit-podcast.de/2011/06/03/rz016-sofia-infrarotteleskop/) is a very interesting German podcast on it, in case you want to know more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 12:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why? Russia is a very 'wet' country

That was the primary reason for them to ban alcohol advertising in 2012 iirc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 12:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing Platt (Low German) it is even more uncanny. Anyway, German seems to have a similar issue with *Pfannkuchen* (which is considered the correct form) and *Pfannekuchen/Pfannenkuchen*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 20:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ebenso!

Fr den Kindle o.. ist es brigens [kostenlos.](http://www.amazon.de/Jugend-ohne-Gott-%C3%96d%C3%B6n-Horv%C3%A1th-ebook/dp/B00ANU9N6E) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 12:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what the UV index is there for: 

 Basically, avoid sunlight when the UV index is three or higher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 13:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get to all(?) of them [here](http://www.sciencemag.org/site/special/rosetta/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 11:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that was Henry Kissinger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China makes football compulsory at school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 11:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 12:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a [mosaic](http://mars.nasa.gov/msl/multimedia/images/?ImageID=4845) of 55 pictures taken by MAHLI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 12:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to be blocked in Germany - probably due to Google automatically flagging it because of music or something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 10:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have constant narration so you probably won't hear a thing as long as nothing's happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 10:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC the translation for "so it goes" in Slaughterhouse Five was "So geht das". Maybe it's something like that? 

That's certainly not the way I'd use the phrase but perhaps it was in use at some point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 11:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  /r/de[1] Mods sind erstens nicht zustndig und zweitens nicht staatlich (auch nicht im weitesten Sinne)

Hast du die Definition selbst nicht gelesen? 

Natrlich sind die Mods "zustndig" - das ist die Existenzberechtigung eines Moderators.
Staatlichkeit ist in keiner Weise eine notwendige Bedingung. Wenn du willst, kannst du zwischen "staatlicher Zensur" und "nicht-staatlicher Zensur" unterscheiden, aber beides fllt immer noch unter den Oberbegriff "Zensur".

 Wo sind die restriktiven Verfahren? / Welche Verfahren? 

Einen Beitrag zu lschen ist kein restriktives Verfahren?

Welche staatliche oder nicht staatliche Gruppe? 

Moderatoren.

Welches Ziel? 

Ziel ist es, die Publikation von bestimmten Inhalten ber das Internet zu kontrollieren. (See what I did there?) Natrlich ist der bergang zwischen Spamschutz und Zensur flieend, aber ich halte diese Diskussion ber archaische Definitionen fr sinnlos. Nebenbei: Was fr einen Begriff wrdest du stattdessen verwenden wollen? 

Wie wird die Publikation von welchen Inhalten kontrolliert oder im eigenen Sinne gesteuert?

Durch lschen von als unpassend deklarierten Beitrgen.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explaining The Flashlight Sessions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 10:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 18:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the source is basically [this.](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/17101527) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plastic bits found floating around in 24 out of 24 samples of German beer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 15:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 14:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This blogpost](http://scienceblogs.com/aetiology/2014/10/21/the-hot-zone-and-the-mythos-of-ebola/) by an actual expert provides a bit of perspective on the accuracy of "The Hot Zone".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 14:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try [this.](http://scienceblogs.com/aetiology/2014/10/21/the-hot-zone-and-the-mythos-of-ebola/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 14:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I contradict myself? 

Very well, then I contradict myself, 

I am large, I contain multi tunes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 16:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["The Search Warrant"](http://www.amazon.de/Search-Warrant-Patrick-Modiano/dp/184655361X/ref=tmm_pap_title_0?ie=UTF8 qid=1412866206 sr=8-2) (aka "Dora Bruder") has been translated. The [LRB review](http://www.lrb.co.uk/v22/n23/michael-wood/j-xx-drancy-13-8-42) of it echoes some points the Nobel committee took into consideration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 10:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like everyone is clueless right now.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 17:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dM4iWbInyt4)

I also remember Hansa winning 3:2 against Dortmund in 95/96 after being down 2:0. Sitting next to the section of Dortmund supporters turned from awful to awesome pretty quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 14:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Tadsch Mahal" is the only different spelling I can think of, but that one comes into use [even later](https://books.google.com/ngrams/graph?content=Taj+Mahal%2C+Tadsch+Mahal case_insensitive=on year_start=1500 year_end=1950 corpus=20 smoothing=3 share= direct_url=t1%3B%2CTaj%20Mahal%3B%2Cc0%3B.t1%3B%2CTadsch%20Mahal%3B%2Cc0). 

Strikingly, in one of the [books that mentions the Taj Mahal](http://books.google.de/books?id=Wh8uAAAAYAAJ pg=PA170 dq=%22taj+mahal%22 hl=en sa=X ei=TaIqVMClC-TiywPgnoDwDA redir_esc=y#v=onepage q=%22taj%20mahal%22 f=false) the author starts by saying (in 1852):

 "Who hasn't heard of the Taj Mahal, a building that is being called one of the first, i.e. greatest, buildings in India by English travellers?" (My quick and rather literal translation.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 18:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember playing the Counter-Strike 1.6 beta first. Steam might have been in beta then as well, I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 13:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't be "good at FIFA" as long as you have to use assistance just as you can't be a good FPS player while requiring an aimbot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-04 10:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some of these the diminutive (e.g. Muschen, Brchen etc) seems at least equally common and without that connotation.

Additionally, "Br" might refer to the teddy kind of bear in this context. (It does for me.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 12:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Tom_Stall could be right with "wa**h**rlich" but that is not something you'll hear very often, I think.

Especially in the context of "zerstrt"  the word you are looking for is probably "vllig". 
"Vllig zerstrt" would mean something like "completely destroyed". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polizei: Die gezckte Waffe soll Routine werden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 12:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 18:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Das letzte Sommerferienwochenende ist aber auch ein klasse Termin fr den Wahltag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 16:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the original German the sentence is:

 Als Gregor Samsa eines Morgens aus unruhigen Trumen erwachte, fand er sich in seinem Bett zu einem **ungeheueren Ungeziefer** verwandelt.

I'd say that "monstrous vermin" is the most faithful translation of those mentioned and I like it for the same reason you do. It leaves something to the reader's imagination which is something Kafka was wont to do anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 16:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die Emprung ber dieses T-Shirt ist (zurecht!) definitiv [kein rein deutsches Phnomen.](http://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2014/aug/27/zara-removes-striped-pyjamas-with-yellow-star-following-online-outrage) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 12:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't even agree on the right sausage to use for Currywurst... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 13:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both variants seem correct to me. Note the colon in the first example, though.

"Wie schon gesagt: Deutsch ist schwer."

or

"Wie schon gesagt, ist Deutsch schwer."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 13:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interessanterweise gibt es in der [Umfrage](http://www.pewglobal.org/2014/07/14/nsa-opinion/table/american-citizens/) auch die Frage

 Is American monitoring of American Citizens acceptable or unacceptable?

Dies halten 61% der Amerikaner (nebenbei: 78% der Deutschen) fr inakzeptabel. Sobald die eigene Privatsphre explizit einbezogen wird, ergibt sich auch fr die Amerikaner ein etwas anderes Bild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 01:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also only use manual controls and I'm actually a bit surprised that it's not the most popular answer. It doesn't feel like I am the one in charge when using assistance. Consequently, I can always tell myself the opponent only hit *that* shot due to shot assistance..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 19:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are dismissing this a bit too quickly. Pumped hydro storage is certainly not the panacea - nothing is - but it is *one* effective way to store energy. Germany, for instance, already has about 40 GWh of storage in place. There are even plans out there to use spoil tips (basically waste dumps from mining) as the hill and/or underground mining as water reservoirs which would somewhat dispel your concerns.

Of course, the efficacy is very dependent on the local geography but that's the case for any energy source/storage solution. In any case, I think we need diversified ways of generating as well as storing energy. Pumped hydro storage can and should play a role in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 00:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Probably this one!](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Barbados_4%E2%80%932_Grenada_\(1994_Caribbean_Cup_qualification\)) Barbados vs. Grenada in 1994.

[Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ThpYsN-4p7w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 22:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That person would probably have answered the same way regardless. The only way to get a straight answer\* would be to ask a more direct question, like "Wo finde ich (bitte) das Postamt?" or "Wo geht es hier zum Postamt?"

This variant might not seem equally polite but I don't think anyone would hold that against you.

\* besides not asking assholes / people who look like they could be high school teachers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 23:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not necessarily the gifs that are sexist, it's the comments that  follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 20:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's very painful to be associated with a "fan" scene like that. Basically every game you are sitting there hoping these morons don't do anything stupid. Most of the time, they do. "Fremdschmen" must have been invented in the context of watching football..

And then they chant "Fuballfans sind keine Verbrecher" ("Football fans are no criminals.") and proceed to walk out of the stadium to throw toilets at people..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 20:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wenn du sagst, deutschsprachige Nutzer seien die grte nicht-englischprachige Nutzergruppe, sprichst du dann von registrierten Nutzern oder basiert die Zahl auf Page Impressions o..?

Ich kann mir jedenfalls gut vorstellen, dass der durchschnittliche deutsche Redditor mittlerweile reddit - wie wohl die meisten - als kurzweilige Quelle fr unterhaltsame Bildchen und Gifs nutzt, nicht zur Diskussion. 
Wer ohne Account auf die Seite stt, wird nicht viel anderes sehen. /r/de besetzt da sicherlich eine relativ enge Nische und wird durch den eigenen Anspruch kaum diese Kurzweil bieten knnen, dafr bruchte es schon subreddits wie /r/lustig oder eine Analogie zu /r/pics. 

Allerdings kann ich mir nicht vorstellen, dass derartige Subs die kritische Masse erreichen knnen. Da in der fr Reddit relevanten Gruppe Englisch sowieso zum Standard geworden ist, sehe ich kaum Mehrwert bei Bilderposts oder hnlichem. (Die Diskussion wird in den originalen Subs immer in grerem Umfang stattfinden.) Letztlich werden dann Bilder mit deutschem Titel reposted (regepostet? gerepostet?). Wenn jeder ohne Hindernisse in allen default Subreddits partizipieren kann, dann ist der Schritt in die deutschsprachige Variante einfach nicht ntig. Die Memes gibt es auf Facebook und Konsorten zur Genge.

Womit die Nutzerzahl hier mglicherweise in kleinem Umfang gendert werden knnte, wre, /r/de (oder eine *kleinster-gemeinsamer-Nenner* Alternative) fr Nutzer mit IP aus dem deutschsprachigen Raum zum Default-Subreddit zu machen. Sichtbarkeit ist wichtig - kommt aber eben nicht ohne Nachteile.


 [W]chentliche Threads ber beliebige Ereignisse der vergangenen Woche.

Das klingt tatschlich interessant - gerade um etwas ber regionale Ereignisse zu erfahren - allerdings wird man damit wohl kaum neue Nutzer anziehen.

 Wettbewerbe, bei denen regelmig neue Snoo-Aliens entworfen werden.

Vielleicht bin ich aus dem Alter raus, aber ich sehe nicht, was das a) bringen soll und b) speziell mit deutschsprachigen Redditoren zu tun hat?!

Finden und Einbinden von Nutzern mit CSS-Kenntissen, die fr Subreddits spezielle und einzigartige Designs erstellen knnen.

Damit das etwas bringt, mssten die Leute doch ersteinmal in die deutschen Subreddits gebracht werden?


Noch eine Abschlussbemerkung: Ich finde an reddit gerade wertvoll, dass es eine so globale Gemeinschaft ist. Eine knstliche Balkanisierung wrde dem imho eher entgegenwirken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 20:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... which is the part of Die Linke that's actually more *far left* (or, perhaps, *less pragmatic*) than the Eastern section of the party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 12:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The blue policecar has a "private" license plate ( DEL - P 9011)

This is **not** a "private" license plate!  Most police cars in Lower Saxony use "civil" license plates denoting their police (district) headquarters (here DEL for Delmenhorst), then something like P, PD or PA and **4** digits - the latter of which is not available to citizens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 20:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I think it's equally funny how certain many players are of these things happening. "Handicapping" in FIFA is basically a prime example for things vulnerable to confirmation bias.

A few points:

1. An *average* player **will** - for simple probabilistic reasons -experience winning or losing streaks. 
2. When losing the second, third, fourth game in a row, isn't it conceivable that you are increasingly susceptible to making unforced errors? At the same time - and especially if you think handicapping is a thing - you are increasingly susceptible to noticing them.
3. I would guess that the majority of people use all kinds of playing assistance, e.g. shot assistance, pass assistance etc. This implies that passes/shots/crosses don't go where you wanted them to, but where the game *thought* you wanted them to go. 
4. 2 + 3 mean that most of the time, if, for instance, a pass goes awry when you are losing you would blame "handicapping". When it's going well - do you thank the game for making it happen?
5. Besides, I'm not really sure a "handicapping engine" would be a useful thing from EA's perspective. It simply adds unnecessary complexity.

In the end, absent any actual evidence I'm not inclined to believe these anecdotes. Granted, in most cases it's nicer to tell yourself it's the game's fault than your own. (Although, when you've gotten used to not using any assistance, the game gets *really* infuriating.)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 17:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right. Compare my flair with the banners in the background. That game was in the old Ostseestadion in Rostock. I was there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 14:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I remember the international/uncensored version of the game is basically illegal in Germany ("Verbreitungsverbot" - distribution ban), so you might get in trouble importing a physical copy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 22:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sowohl Rben- als auch Rohrzucker sind letztlich raffinierte Saccharose, wenn sie in Deutschland als "Haushaltszucker" verkauft werden. Das macht im Geschmack keinen Unterschied. (Andere Formen beider sind verfgbar, aber in industrieller Produktion kaum relevant.) 

Geschmacksunterschiede - primr diesen "eklig sen" Geschmack - wrde ich genau wie /u/kleinelerche eher auf die Verwendung von Fructose-Glucose-Sirup (HFCS) zurckfhren. Fructose ist ~1,73x so s wie normale Saccharose. ([Quelle](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fructose#Relative_sweetness)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 17:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not entirely wrong but I think this is too simplistic a way of looking at things. Generally, better CPU performance can - even though it might mean higher power consumption under load - actually reduce real-life power consumption. 

Getting your task done as quickly as possible means you are idling most (more) of the time. That's where a huge chunk of the power savings happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-10 22:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what way is that not the case in Italy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 10:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is simply part of the payment for that Motorola deal. (emphasis mine)

The purchase price is approximately US$2.91 billion (subject to certain adjustments), including US$1.41 billion paid at close, comprised of US$660 million in cash **and US$750 million in Lenovo ordinary shares (subject to a share cap/floor)**. The remaining US$1.5 billion will be paid in the form of a three-year promissory note.  [source](http://investor.google.com/releases/2014/0129.html)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 16:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scheint [die hier](http://www.hindawi.com/journals/bmri/aip/179691/) zu sein. ("provisional pdf" oben rechts) Ich habe leider gerade keine Zeit nher hineinzuschauen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 19:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-17 17:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? This seems to be a rather long-winded hoax to tell people that there's less gold in the world than they thought. Not that Glenn Beck would do such a thing..

* Yes Germany - or rather some Germans - wanted to see their gold - and they did: ([source](http://www.bundesbank.de/Redaktion/EN/Topics/2013/2013_01_16_gold_reserves.html))

At the end of last year, Executive Board member Thiele visited the Banks partner central banks abroad in person to check whether its bullion was being stored in an appropriate manner and in compliance with the high security standards demanded by the German central bank. As expected, I found everything to be just as it should be, he confirmed. Furthermore, Mr Thiele went on to say that there have never been any irregularities of any kind in the past in connection with the storage of the Bundesbanks gold reserves at its partner central banks.

* The reason for them asking for 300t was of (domestic) political nature, not because they had seen irregularities. (Although, to be fair, a lack of direct oversight over the gold had been lamented by the German equivalent of the GAO.)

* The Bundesbank does indeed plan to get 300t of their reserves currently in NY (and 374t in Paris) back to Frankfurt **by 2020**. That's why they "only" got 37t in 2013. The plan is to store 50% of the German reserves in Frankfurt. (Again: **by 2020**)

* This will still leave 37% of Germany's gold reserves in the hands of the Fed. Why? Because it's there in case the gold has to be exchanged for foreign currencies, i.e. the Dollar. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 12:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die [Dame](http://www.zeit.de/politik/deutschland/2013-12/datenschutz-nachfolge-schaar-vosshoff), die fr den Posten im Gesprch ist, [macht kaum Hoffnung..](http://beta.abgeordnetenwatch.de/blog/2013-12-12/die-neue-datenschutzbeauftragte-fuer-internetsperren-und-vorratsdatenspeicherung) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 14:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably have one of those ["Cloud to butt"](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/cloud-to-butt-plus/apmlngnhgbnjpajelfkmabhkfapgnoai?hl=en) extensions installed?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 19:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously! That was [awesome.](https://twitter.com/ESAstro_trainer/status/407205952795209728/photo/1/large) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polio risk looms over Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 21:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 12:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm longing for the day there's an F1 driver named Burns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 11:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His team told him Vettel is not who he is racing so he should "try not to lose time." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 15:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diouf is a very good candidate for that "What is one instant sign that a person is an idiot?" AskReddit thread.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 01:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has the NSA provided anything of provable value to the people of the United States?

[This](http://www.propublica.org/article/claim-on-attacks-thwarted-by-nsa-spreads-despite-lack-of-evidence) is a nice analysis of the claims that have been made in this regard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 21:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steam already updated for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 00:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Die beiden Antwortmglichkeiten schlieen sich nicht unbedingt aus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-29 18:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.spacex.com/webcast/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 12:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think this is as big of a problem as you make it out to be.

These steps towards newer architectures happen all the time, the hardware will guarantee backwards compatibility and with time more and more developers will adapt their software (which could amount to "compile one more binary" in many cases).

Additionally the fact that armv8 will be 64bit has been known for a while. Do you really think that Google's developers just now started to prepare Android? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 11:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The thing is that no one talked about 64bit processors before Apple announced the new iPhone.

Except the designers of the chip architecture both companies use did talk about 64bit: http://www.arm.com/products/processors/armv8-architecture.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 12:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany is GMT+2 now (CE**S**T) and the game is 20:30 local time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 12:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI: it starts 20:30 GMT+2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 22:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bezos' letter to WaPo employees.](http://www.washingtonpost.com/national/jeff-bezos-on-post-purchase/2013/08/05/e5b293de-fe0d-11e2-9711-3708310f6f4d_story.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 18:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  All browser tests performed in the latest version of Chrome for Android.

[Source.](http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2013/08/performance-preview-the-moto-x-sports-a-great-gpu-respectable-cpu/)

Anyway, does any site not do it that way? Just so I know what to ignore.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-05 16:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10 M ECGC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-30 19:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spirit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 01:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article OP posted:

 The NTSB confirmed the PAPIs runway 28L were available to the approaching aircraft before the accident, however were damaged in the accident and thus went out of service again. The localizer was available, the glideslope was out of service, according NOTAMs were in effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 00:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Third time's a charm, huh? [This should work.](http://www.box.net/shared/static/a6omcl2la0ivlxsn3o8m.jpg)

Otherwise, you can find an interactive version [here.](http://www.sfsignal.com/interactive/npr100.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
