<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9667</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viewport 2.0 issue with MacBook Pro...help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 02:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone here working with a rMBP, Late 2013? I'm having issues...when selecting any object, while my mouse is pressed, the viewport goes black. When I release the button, it is visible again. This only happens in viewport 2.0, and only on the discrete graphics. If I force it to run on the integrated graphics, I don't have this issue.

Is there any way to update the 750m drivers on a MBP? Any suggestions as to what else might be causing this? Thanks!

EDIT: It looks like it is happening with the integrated graphics as well now. Hmm... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [LF] Someone to build a Control Rig in Maya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 15:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good morning reddit. I'm trying to hone my animation skills but don't have any fully rigged/controlled character models. I have a model with a skeleton that I would like to use however it does not have a control rig attached to it and I'm afraid I don't have the skills to make a complete rig. Would anyone be willing to help out and put a complete functional control rig with driven keys, facial controls, etc. onto my model? It would be greatly appreciated. This is unpaid sorry but I'm a broke student.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help building a control rig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 15:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good morning reddit. I'm trying to hone my animation skills but don't have any fully rigged/controlled character models. I have a model with a skeleton that I would like to use however it does not have a control rig attached to it and I'm afraid I don't have the skills to make a complete rig. Would anyone be willing to help out and put a complete functional control rig with driven keys, facial controls, etc. onto my model? It would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 05:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, they're 1/10th Incuse Indians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 03:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is. And yes it was lol. It's so dense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 02:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they're pretty nice. I bought an ounce worth of each size they offer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Provident order came in today. Including my first Gold! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 00:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 18:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too feel like this is a bit high considering the new 2014 ones are being sold by a reputable online dealer for $23 and the proofs at $34.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 03:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice. I'm not looking to spend more than $2,500 at the moment for a portable solution. Seeing as the specs are greatly increased from the 2011 model to the Late 2013 model, I'm guessing that it will probably handle a bit more intensive animating. (the i7 in it is rated only a few points lower than the PC model i7-4770 according to cpubenchmark.net), and having 16 gigs of ram, it should fare quite well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 19:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, I was always under the impression that the GPU is what helped with rendering. With that logic then, I'm assuming I should get decent performance from an i7 in the MBP. I am going to be upgrading my desktop to possibly a Mac Pro (Xeon) in the future, but for now I am looking for something portable that I can get by with for rendering out animations as I need to be able to work on it at home and at work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 18:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has it ever heated up to the point where the laptop has shut down to prevent damage? Mine will be in a well ventilated dock so I'm hoping it will run a bit cooler, however I'm still worried about it overheating. 

Also, you're running it on just integrated graphics?? I'm sure that this 750M will give a huge improvement in render speeds then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maya's performance on a 2013 MacBook Pro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 16:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title states, I'm looking for some reviews of Maya's performance on a MacBook Pro (Retina).

2.3 GHz i7
16 Gb Ram
GT 750M (2 GB)

I'm mostly an animator, so I'm concerned about viewport performance when animating, as well as render time and heat created while rendering. I'm coming from a PC that I put together a few years ago:

AMD Phenom X4 255 (3.2 GHz)
8 Gb Ram
GTX 660 (2 GB)

Anyone with insight as to how they would compare would be greatly appreciated. The reason I am making the switch is because I MUCH prefer the OS X operating system, and I need a portable solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I suppose I should get in on this #SilverSelfie thing. (My carry piece) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 18:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 03:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh the mental images! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Hollywood run out of ideas? Name a movie that has come out in the past few years thay was a completely original idea, not based on a book, story, event, sequel, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 17:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-08 01:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 05:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insert Nokia joke here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 01:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [LOL](http://cdn.makeagif.com/media/4-05-2014/oz85Um.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 04:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have, but I bought all he had. And he said he had just gotten it in that day so I lucked out on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 04:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Including a handful of Proofs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 04:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greatest show ever. EVER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today's LCS Pickup: $7.75 in Junk for 15x!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 04:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 03:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those bars though! *drools* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 23:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PMing you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 20:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be more than happy to take them off your hands ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 04:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they're normally cheap to begin with, at usually .99 over, and I've seen them on sale for .89 over, but I have never seen them go this low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
