<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1320</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=21XE0cGKdmc

Really?  What makes u think so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 02:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Aduke

Everytime I adjust the time stamp it reverts back to this date. I can't explain it.   I try and nothing happens.

Here's another one:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=21XE0cGKdmc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haunted House - EVP's Caught </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 06:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/IvEfxeDy3nI

(IGNORE TIME STAMP DATE ABOVE) this TOOK PLACE April 3rd 2016. This house has under gone several investigations. Most recently yielding powerful results. This house was featured on Ghost Adventures Feb 28th where they left empty handed. The only team to do so. On April 3rd 2016 these EVP's were caught with a cam and mic placed in the hallway. The infamous hallway were Bibles were burned, objects thrown and wall writing on one occasion. IMO its the most active, elusive part in the house. The place where I've seen the grey haired apparition. Whats odd is most of the EVP's caught by other teams who come after GA - the voices have been mostly male. If you compare the voice in this video to the other videos on my channel where EVP's are concerned you'll see its the same voice or very very eerily similar. Same entity? Too hard to tell? No way to be sure. What is known is the best EVP's caught in this house happen simply when cameras and mics are left running or when 1 or two people are having a conversation and the entity's listen in or respond to our dialogue. It seems one of the entities is speaking about the fall I had Jan 2nd 2014, where its admitting it wasn't a fall but more so a push?! Which to this day I still can't 100% say either way. This video is no exception in regards to THEM speaking, underneath us. If you find an EVP on this video or any other video on my channel feel free to reply and time stamp where yo heard. I think there's more on this video as well. But I'll let you decide. NOTES April 2nd 2016
:23 "Yeah"
:52, :53 something blows on the mic and at
:54 EVP voice is heard 
1:32 "Yeah"
"blah blah blah blah "semantics....I didn't fall" ??? begins at 1:47 ends at 1:53. ME AND HOUSE OCCUPANTS ARE DOWN STAIRS. Somethings at :41 but i cant make it out. Sounds like "NO" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 06:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the poor excuse for a pot unsuccessfully trying to call the kettle black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 23:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hurry up. I move out in 3 weeks. The UK team just left. I will share some of their findings soon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 21:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you're in Tacoma come on down.  Whats a 50 minute drive to prove its all a hoax.  I can easily tell you why the investigation GA conducted was not conducive to a Poltergeist haunting. Are you ready? First off timing? Poltergeist dont perform on queue. You cant tell a Poltergeist to do something let alone expect it to do it on queue.  Poltergeist are agent prone something unknown to Zak and GA is driving this activity. Could be the house?  the land underneath or the individuals living there. By asking us to leave during the majority of your investigation your limiting your success rate significantly. Did u know we had activity at the Hotel we stayed in while GA conducted their lock down?   Do you know how many times GA contacted us at the Hotel to see if the activity transferred as a result of us leaving?  Zero. They made no attempt. Neither did they put a researcher on standby just in case. 3rd investigating Poltergeist related cases are extremely hard. Its like waiting for lightening to strike. It takes time and effort. The famous of Poltergeist related cases became famous because the researchers and investigators moved into the house and investigated the home for a matter of days if not weeks and months. GA stayed for a few hours. 10 at best. That's minuscule when trying to ascertain a malevolent haunting.  if there's one thing I've learned through this true ordeal is entity's like this choose to act on their own terms. U say jump they wont jump. You say speak they wont speak. They want to be in control and own the time and when they can appear.  To make us look like fools benefits them and hurts us.  if you watch GA you will see a majority of their shows center around residual hauntings.  This is not a residual haunting. This is an intelligent haunting. The very thing you are chasing has an IQ probably bigger than Einstein. If its a demon in hiding it certainly does.  Like Angels Demons were here when God created the heaven and the earth so to think we can out smart them. out coax them is ludicrous.  The GA investigation was over before it was started.  The native american lady they interviewed for the show doesn't even live within 500 miles of here. More like 800+ across the mountains in eastern Washington. The tribes specific to this area are the snohomish and Skykomish tribes. Google the Puget Sound War and the history of Bothell and you'll see the tribe names documented here are not even the tribes GA mentioned on the show. Shall I go on? if and when you do investigate a possible Poltergeist infestation you your biggest ally is the environment. Be it the people?  the children(we have none) the land or circumstances not yet known.  The Scientific Establishment of Parapsychology interviewed me via phone, via conference call and via video chat for 2 1/2 months before they felt ample enough to visit the site and conduct an investigation. They lived with me for 6 days the 1st go round came back two months later and lived with me for 8 more days. And this time time they bought a skeptic and colleague. There here now matter of fact.

A TV show has 45 minutes to tell a story. Their approach that being Zak and crew in conducive for haunted locations, not residential. They invade urban legends and folklore places and rarely enter a domain that's active and by active I mean malevolent.  Poltergeist and demonic cases are similar in that they are intelligent hauntings. The methods used to discover them are different say the average investigative means. That's where Zak went wrong. The proof is in the puddling. 8 teams have investigated my house. Zak is the only team that left with zilch.

if the info here doesn't sway you. Nothing else will and tons more is coming.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ia6m0zjiLk

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0O_1_vEomBk
Listen 1:11 , 1:14,  1:23 , 1:25 , 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IJdqk8xPKVE
child's voice "3"

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhA-tqf19Es
and
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1lXvS465MbY

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ufix69pMwyY
1st noise is heard. 29:15 2nd noise is heard Alice admits to it "Its not house settling noises. The noises there are referring to that me and GF are accustomed to are the foot steps and walking around

Lets provide u with some Class A EVP
https://app.box.com/s/cqaat2i9edo3iru3czsuoqxm3y0adjcy
and
https://app.box.com/s/xjpaik9ye44p2klb4v8mks5uy6dl664t
and
https://app.box.com/s/944qbngm2hyv066nic65115a7ifg89wi
and
https://app.box.com/s/6ni6ri5b070xr9bb3uuxm0ckgqdzdf1g

SEP Interview
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VY8f_nI6taI
and
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GdSMEL2duYM
and
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u9YVggTNWiA

https://app.box.com/s/h8wyjnqaqav2fijsi1wvzvkizkmorfrl

https://app.box.com/s/93o3vk8o5i52225lpb686rudo9ikwfg3

download for FREE the April edition
http://www.phenomenamagazine.co.uk/

for money? I scoff at that suggestion. Im telling a truth story, sharing a true story to the best of my ability. Some believe. Some dont.

TBD

got free time. come on down



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> personally met? U haven't met me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poltergeist - Investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 15:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 15:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My snipes are derogatory?  Money scheme? Unreal paranormal claims?  What makes it unreal? because a) U wasnt here when it happened or b) GA didnt find the demon Zak was looking for?  U loose on both debates. #1 Our claims are real, every team accept GA found and left with evidence. The claims we made are not far fetched where Poltergeist and demons are concerned. its only far fetched when some people like you reveal how little you know about malevolent hauntings.  Its only far fetched when you actually believe its possible to capture some of the unbelievable feats by Poltergeist on video cam?  Its only far fetched if you havent studied in history the 8,000 reported Poltergeist claims where objects where thrown, objects caught fire, and wall writings. Its only far fetched if you believe every claim has or messenger I should say comes forth because of money. I have money. Lots of it. I earned it.  The only rich paranormal investigators out in the world are the one's with TV shows that sold out.  Not the one experiencing true hauntings. Get real why dont you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poltergeist - Demons In Seattle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 06:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 02:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow derogatory comments. Adds credence to your argument.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b9pVNMyUG58

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 01:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you have is innuendo, false accusation(s) and believe it or not "zero evidence"   Burn Bibles for publicity?  get out of the clitche way of thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DarkThirty Radio - LIVE. Scotland and UK Parapsychologists travel back to the US(Bothell) to begin Round 2 of their investigation. Recent activity coincides with their arrival. Update tonight via Podcast. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 23:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 23:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you are so behind the times its not even fair to discuss this with you. U still arguing GA POV? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Poltergeist Case UK Team returns for Round Two and bring others with them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one has ever believed me?  U must mean idiots like yourself? Racist like yourself.  The UK team is at my house right now for Round 2 and have already captured more evidence.  This time we're going after possible root causes. There here for a week and they bought others with them. LOL  So I'm afraid you're loosing the arugment of no one believing me. My claims are true. You and those like you are just stuck on stupid.  Get past the skin color and accept facts. People in a greater position than you are substantiating my claims and get ready we're just getting started LOL


http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The technique and format used by GAC is not conducive to an Intelligent and Poltergeist type haunting. Plus they weren't here long.  The guys (Steve and Don) talk about this here  http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Demons In Seattle Uncovered - An American Haunting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 23:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poltergeist - Demons In Seattle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 07:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 16:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   casserole of nonsense.

" casserole of nonsense."  Wow thats different. I gotta use that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 16:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you study the GA show and the GA format. Zak and crew are not geared to study Poltergeist related hauntings.  There was very little prepping involved. Steve and Don analyzed evidence I sent them and interviewed previous tenants months before arriving. They became very familiar with the case.  Zak and GA found out about the case in November and where filming in November/Early December.  The GA show does very few episodes on Intelligent Haunting(s) and more so Residual Hauntings or places. In short they were over there heads. And i dont mean that out of malice. If you watch all of Steve and Dons video about this haunting you can clearly see who had respect and sincere interests in all that was going on and who was there just for show.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 22:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can provide a multiple recording yes. Here you go. 

https://app.box.com/s/osxqgu57oybbndx8dp2efyen5amyx054
and
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0O_1_vEomBk
Both men began experiencing, witness and being a part of paranormal weirdness within minutes of being in the home. Listen 1:11 , 1:14, 1:23 , 1:25 
(its a camera, It's a camera), tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, night cam"

EVP REVIEW SESSSION
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yMMqY01bouw
entire video

EVP captured on multiple cameras
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ia6m0zjiLk
taken 2 weeks after Steve and Don left. Its the same voice.
PDF log file
https://app.box.com/s/h8wyjnqaqav2fijsi1wvzvkizkmorfrl


https://app.box.com/s/6ni6ri5b070xr9bb3uuxm0ckgqdzdf1g
"I hear springs"  3 syllabels

https://app.box.com/s/944qbngm2hyv066nic65115a7ifg89wi
"Hello, ....yeah"

Invisible trip Wires go off
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XLBnoKQSVCA

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gbGRj3YU4YM
Invisible Trip Wires go off


EVP's
captured with FOX news present*
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhA-tqf19Es

FOX news spent 3 hours at my house with Steve and Don and heard LIVE REALTIME EVP'S
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhA-tqf19Es


is anyone still debating me?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 22:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Demons In Seattle" is a point of reference to the Ghost Adventures airing Feb 28th 2015 "Demons In Seattle" they named the episode that when they came to the home Nov 2014* 7 teams have investigated the house. 6 have left with evidence. The only team that left with 0 evidence was Ghost Adventures.

those paranormal teams statement and substantiated reports can be made available. some are already on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 17:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Severe difference of opinion. Investigators and institutions alike label this an EVP. I tend to agree. This in conjunction with multiple EVP's caught in real-time when PP and SEP where here

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhA-tqf19Es spfreload=5

but then again that's just me. U guys as in paranormal teams come in and find the 'voice phenomena" we live it. We hear it clear as day sometimes. 

To my GF and I its random phantom noise.

She's asking me if I put the clothes in the dryer. I say no and she's yells from downstairs "who are you talking to?"  i respond "you, Im talking to you?"

she responds "I didnt say anything?"

happens or has happened all the time




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 17:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> find a quote where I said a demon spray painted my office wall. You're confused. The name is this post is Poltergeist WA State.  Malevolent spirit i.e. Poltergeist i.e. Intelligent Haunting. And for the record we're ( as in us ) are narrowing the culprit down Poltergeist infestation. Or as Steve Mera refers to as a LIH. Land locked phenomena, less than 12% of Poltergeist cases fall into this segment of unknown phenomena.  When did I say this was demon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 18:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6:35 "hey" is heard.  Listen without judging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 18:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6:35 "hey" is heard.  Listen without judging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 18:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6:35 "hey" is heard.  Listen without judging. Define the term extraordinary claims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 18:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6:35 "hey" is heard.  Listen without judging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 18:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6:35 "hey" is heard.  Listen without judging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 00:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U dont like witnesses cause you label witnesses hearsay. You dont like EVP because you label them hard to hear. I provide you Class A, Class B and AVP and the critique is still the same. I provide you a picture of the apparition- you say thats doctored. You listen to an interview were two men (not me) admit to seeing objects moving and substantiate my claims about the camera manipulation.  You ignore everything ever written about Poltergeist, Demons and Malevolent haunting and ignore the similarities with those stories and mine.  You ridicule and point to the science community not accepting Parapsychology as a means of true science and yet you come to this forum looking for answers,  a scientist would scoff at you quicker than it would a Steve Mera, a Collin Wilson or Dr Barry Taff. two men by the way looking into my case. One has reached a startling conclusion.  No friend you dont believe in the paranormal, you believe in the ancient old idea. if it doesn't pass your smell test it can't be real.

Its EZ to be dismissive and label something fake. but you ignore your own common sense. Where theirs smoke there's always fire.  if it quacks like a duck odds are its probably a duck not duck Dynasty.

U my friend are a person posing as a paranormal believer but in fact are the purest of skeptics which in short is really a cynic.

https://app.box.com/s/944qbngm2hyv066nic65115a7ifg89wi

https://app.box.com/s/944qbngm2hyv066nic65115a7ifg89wi

https://app.box.com/s/iz927a576mgxlgdx3w9a6jz2g5dk3vh5

https://app.box.com/s/osxqgu57oybbndx8dp2efyen5amyx054

https://app.box.com/s/bfsieg4fraq6534uobe6nd2l36it50sm

https://app.box.com/s/cqaat2i9edo3iru3czsuoqxm3y0adjcy

https://app.box.com/s/93ads9det22at3jxmbszl3tpqmbto0lq

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 00:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everything you've said is relative. U dont like witnesses cause you label witnesses hearsay. You dont like EVP because you label it hard to hear. I provide you Class A, Class B and AVP and the critique is still the same. I provide you a picture of the apparition- you say thats doctored. You listen to an interview were two men (not me) admit to seeing objects moving and substantiate my claims about the camera manipulation.  You ignore everything ever written about Poltergeist, Demons and Malevolent haunting and ignore the similarities with those stories and mine.  You ridicule and point to the science community not accepting Parapsychology as a means of true science and yet you come to this forum looking for answers,  a scientist would scoff at you quicker than it would a Steve Mera, a Collin Wilson or Dr Barry Taff. two men by the way looking into my case. One has reached a startling conclusion.  No friend you dont believe in the paranormal, you believe in the ancient old idea. if it doesn't pass your smell test it can't be real.

Its EZ to be dismissive and label something fake. but you ignore your own common sense. Where theirs smoke there's always fire.  if it quacks like a duck odds are its probably a duck not duck Dynasty.

U my friend are a person posing as a paranormal believer but in fact are the purest of skeptics which in short is really a cynic.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 16:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah the hearsay routine.  Google and YouTube is your friend.  use keyboard and mouse and good luck. I'm done fighting battles with skeptics.  We put the evidence everywhere. The fact that you're not finding it means you're not looking hard enough.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 16:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok what ever. Continue believing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 13:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, why are so dense?  Do you study the paranormal?  Do you study Poltergeist.  Cameras where thrown around. Plants(pottery) did fly. Books did get knocked off book shelves. 3 Bibles got burned. Two are still missing. None of that and more is ever going to be captured by a paranormal team let alone S.E.P or anyone else for that matter. Why? Its called spurt of the moment. Its unpredictable. The entity's doing this are doing it in front of the house occupants.  Just because its not captured on video doesn't mean it didnt happen. A trillion events take place all over this world thats never captured on video.  SEP captured 420 EVP's.  Of course the science community doesn't view parapsychology favorably.   There once was a time when the scientific community didint view the Big Bang favorably. Whats your point? Its called paranormal, para-science because it exists out of the confines of science. Science will never be able to duplicate it because the environment they want to duplicate it in is sterile.

This stuff happens in homes, building, lands, property's throughout the world. Its called para-normal for a reason.

420+ EVP's is not weak evidence. Maybe for you but not for any respected paranormal team. But lets put the EVP thing aside.  You're also ignoring the trip wires going off. you're also ignoring witnessing (my friends) and previous tenants (to whom I met) after I moved in. You're also missing the apparition photo. The shadow photo. The videos of the banging, the knocking, the tapping, the lights going off and on. You're also missing or overlooking I should say individuals outside of your IQ that are respected within their field.  You're no better than Zak Bagans to think just because you personally don't see an object move or object catch fire be it on video or in person its not real.

The only thing I can say to you and others like you is why are you in this community. Everything it out of your grasp of understanding.

Parting FAQ's

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6ia6m0zjiLk

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0O_1_vEomBk

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gbGRj3YU4YM
18:10

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XLBnoKQSVCA
24:10

http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/

instead of guessing about the investigation. Why not listen to entire intervew (above).

Outside of that you being here (in the Paranormal) community is more so as a interference runner.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 08:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you must not be on the right Phenomena Project page.
http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/

Google is your friend.
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zhA-tqf19Es

http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist

and

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1lXvS465MbY

and

http://i299.photobucket.com/albums/mm305/subject1320/Stafford%20Way/SEP-certification2_zpsejh0tu96.jpg

The April Magazine of the Phenomena Project will have my house and the events therein including the evidence ascertained on the front cover and on the magazine.

What am I missing here?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 08:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually Coyotes I move in May. Jan/Feb UK and US Paranormal teams came to and conducted 3 weeks worth of investigative work. I was never going to leave until true, know what they are doing teams came in and substantiated our claims.  That was always my goal. Was it EZ staying while that took place? Nope it wasn't.

When we moved in May 2012, no one told us the house was haunted. People just vacated and left and thats fine. I get it. But me personally. I was not going to leave the next tenant with 0 data, 0 documentation, 0 evidence for the fear that had I left and not said a word a new family coming in would be blind sided and left doing proactive measures we did which made the situation worse.


The Scientific Establishment of Parapsychology is monitoring the house and all the activity therein.

http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 02:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Rag, thats what your hoping will happen. I post when I have something to share. Something to say. Obviously you don't.  

http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 02:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgive them for they know not what they do.

http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 02:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Here) http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/

and

http://www.coasttocoastam.com/pages/parapsychologists-declare-home-has-poltergeist

need more let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poltergeist - WA State - Seattle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 06:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot while living in this house. I've heard a lot. I've come home to discover strange things have occurred in my absence. I've read a lot in my studying of the mechanics of ghosts, poltergeists and demons. if you belong to this channel you know I've captured a lot over the years. This by far is the most profound video I've ever shared. To our knowledge several things are unique in this Universe. Signatures no doubt are one of them. MAXIMIZE YOUR SCREEN when watching this video. Its real. The events here began Oct 2014 and have reached a new chapter of weird come March 2016 

https://youtu.be/u-UTd37duCQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 06:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot while living in this house. I've heard a lot. I've come home to discover strange things have occurred in my absence. I've read a lot in my studying of the mechanics of ghosts, poltergeists and demons. if you belong to this channel you know I've captured a lot over the years. This by far is the most profound video I've ever shared. To our knowledge several things are unique in this Universe. Signatures no doubt are one of them. MAXIMIZE YOUR SCREEN when watching this video. Its real. The events here began Oct 2014 and have reached a new chapter of weird come March 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poltergeist - Demons In Seattle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 06:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 05:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much hate in your tone. What took place between mom and dad that made you a troll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [UPDATE AND TRUTH ON THE DEMONS IN SEATTLE CASE] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 06:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Poltergeist Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 06:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washington Poltergeist Case

http://www.americas-most-haunted.com/2016/03/18/washington-poltergeist-case-psychic-attorney-mark-anthony-hours-amamericas-haunted-radio/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghosts of Bothell: The Demons in Seattle House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 07:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
