<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4287</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 21:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't have to be a foregone conclusion for healthcare to cost as much as it does. However, it's an enormously difficult system to innovate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 20:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what the estimated cost of a military invasion of Canada would be compared to the 17 trillion merger deal the author proposes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 06:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  accompanied by hanging streetlights
 bowed to court her...

My favourite line.  I loved this poem. :)

They say the moon was made from some massive collision with the earth, not unlike a bad break-up.  For some reason that came to mind reading the lines about the moon wanting to 'destroy the tides, and possibly life as we know it'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 04:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worry a little that we're an echo chamber in that regard.  I'd love to see the mods somehow get a dairy/poultry industry rep for an AMA one of these days and see if there are any particularly *good* arguments for maintaining this policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Ivison: Scrapping supply management would the most consumer first thing the Tories could do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-18 02:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 21:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  meh

I'd agree, there are better lectures available on income inequality, but I thought this would be interesting to post since she's running for Toronto Centre.

Her top three ratings on the TED site are "informative", "persuasive" and "unconvincing".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TED Talk] Chrystia Freeland: The rise of the new global super-rich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 18:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 16:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likewise. I feel like they should have done outreach to graduate student associations across Canada to get more people out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ontario politician trying to lure Quebec doctors affected by values charter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-15 17:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 21:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the charter's most viable goal isn't to assimilate Muslims but to quell xenophobia, by suppressing outward signs of otherness.

That can't be a healthy direction for a society to take though. Trying to suppress outward signs of otherness in the short term would just invite new things for expressing prejudice against in the next generations. You can only sweep so much under the rug, and xenophobia isn't helped, only appeased.

I like that multiculturalism in Canada embraces an ever-changing Canadian identity. It's not only just, but realistic, since population-wise Canada is going to depend more and more on immigration to sustain and grow our country in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 19:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the company that produces these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 06:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Happy Accidents](http://youtu.be/6MGgisPH2v4)

This is a hilarious romantic comedy with Marisa Tomei and Vincent D'Onofrio.  It's easily my favourite movie that nobody has seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 07:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one beneficial aspect I've heard tossed around is that at least the cost of production will be lower, so scarcity should diminish, and avg quality of life should improve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 00:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Growing agricultural crisis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 00:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this as a patent-reform concept. The therapeutic biotech sector for instance requires an average of 15 years to get to market (assuming you can pass ph3 clinical trials). Leaving companies 5 years to recoup expenses from all that R D. Makes drug prices exorbitant, and makes it very difficult to have start-ups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 18:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an interesting subject that should be discussed more in Canada.  The economy that Canada will find itself in in 10-20 years is going to look very different.

There are a number of disruptive economic advances on the horizon that will continue to undercut employment.  This comment in /r/futurology notes the example of professional drivers and truckers that will be replaced with automated vehicles.  Think of any distribution centre or warehouse, where automation can replace labour.  This is without even considering creative enterprises like writing and basic journalism which may become increasingly automated. 

What will the average Canadian do for a living in an economy of advanced automation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Cross-post from /r/bestof] An answer to why the general public is oblivious to the staggering science and tech advances that are happening right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 18:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 17:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Dr. Kang, congratulations on your results so far.

Is SAV001-H a strictly prophylactic vaccine?  Will your research eventually lead to a therapeutic vaccine for those already suffering from HIV?

Thanks very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matt Gurney: Albertan Nenshi hits xenophobic Quebec separatists where it hurts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-03 20:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 21:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone down south would really care all that much, frankly.  Probably wouldn't even make the news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 21:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, hopefully we get around to releasing him then.  I can't help thinking if the circumstances were different - if I had grown up in the same environment as him, that I'd most likely be right in his shoes, or dead.  

I would rather see a person punished for their choices rather than their circumstances.

He's turning 27 this year... 12 years in jail. Not even real jail for most of it, some extra-legal fake jail created to avoid humane conditions. Thinking about him reminds me of a character named Leggatt in this Joseph Conrad story I read years ago called [The Secret Sharer](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Secret_Sharer), where one guy helps shelter a murderer because he can't help see himself in the other's place if the circumstances had been reversed.

As Canadians we can't fix the whole Guantanamo Bay fiasco, but we can do what we used to do in situations like this: be an example.  Show the rest of the world that we don't have to lock someone up for the rest of their lives just because politically and legally we don't know what else to do with them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 20:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  US Penal Law, Title XVIII Chapter 118 defines a child soldier as someone under the age of 15.

Now that he's been transferred to Canadian custody, do the US rulings still have to be honoured, or is he subject to whatever sentencing/incarceration that Canada determines is best? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 03:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it can be considered an inevitability that this happened, and nothing to do with the minimum wage as /u/JPShinebox suggests.

We're currently living in an era of unparalleled technological innovation, which leads to economic disruption. Our public education model prepares us for careers and markets that are rapidly disappearing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New fees for international touring musicians threaten smaller clubs and live venues across Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 20:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New [federal] fees for international touring musicians threaten smaller clubs and live venues across Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 20:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 05:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Do we require them to get a doctor to sign off on it?

Yes, a doctor should make the final call.

In this case you've given anecdote for instance, mandatory vaccines are not produced in chicken eggs, just influenza comes to mind actually. They're also moving away from that practice of using eggs to using insect cells because with the H1N1 outbreak, the dose/egg was so low they couldn't produce enough vaccine to meet demand.

(I'll add some links to this later when I'm off my phone, but it's the same idea as how Glaxo makes the HPV vaccine).

Most mandatory vaccines (Measles, mumps, rubella) and polio before that were/are made in cultured embryonic human cells (WI38). (I believe this is still the case) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 01:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm ashamed to say I never gave them a chance before Hot Tub Time Machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 14:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd feel more comfortable if he was also directing the feature. I didn't like Snyder's Man of Steel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 21:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep clicking on this without reading the title for the post (forgetting I've already seen it) because the thumbnail looks like a space station orbiting earth...

It does look delicious though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mandy Patinkin Discusses Playing Inigo Montoya in 'The Princess Bride' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 23:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 01:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not "just a little too long", but [Bleach](/s "should have ended after Ichigo saves Rukia.  I do love the plot-line of Ichigo's Hollow mask, but not enough to make up for Rukia getting ditched as the main love interest.").   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 04:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should Canada's universal healthcare have provisions for:

* Prescription drugs,
* Prosthetics
* Home care services,
* Optical care
* Dental care

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 16:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, pretty sure I voted correctly. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 12:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your opinion is an acceptable level of gov't intervention into markets and the economy and how should the status quo in Canada be altered (if at all)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 20:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true, the Olympics is an enormous communications platform, if Russia has to contend with the possibility of hundreds of celebrated athletes admonishing the host country during their internationally broadcast interviews, I think it's very likely the new legislation could get rescinded well in advance of the opening ceremonies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 15:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Scent of a woman

*"If I were the man I was 5 years ago, I'd take a flame-thrower to this place!"*

Awesome [final speech](http://youtu.be/Xq8CtJSQFL4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 04:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Would love to have half-priced Bento with the Ice Witch
* Mikoto Urabe from Mysterious Girlfriend X seems like actually an awesome gf.
* Crazy monkey-armed Kanbaru from bakemonogatari. I'd probably get killed, but so worth it.
* Princess Mononoke  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 21:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good or bad, I think whatever Snowden has done is irrelevant.  

I don't see Canada having anything to gain by sticking its nose into a squabble between Russia and the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 20:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anything to be gained by parroting the Americans' criticism of foreign countries in cases like this?  

I feel like Canada just comes off as some kind of toadie to American foreign policy; not communicating anything independent or useful to the global dialogue.  Just chirping away ineffectually until no one is listening anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada criticizes Russian asylum for leaker Snowden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 20:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 03:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically Gene Hunt: 

http://youtu.be/D5XnpK5Hzo0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 01:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really didn't expect to like Trigun at first.  It was my first anime (ever). :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 13:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked a lot of things about it, great concept too, but I can understand why it wasn't much of a commercial success as an anime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 04:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Never forget the pride of wolves"
-Wizard, Ben-To </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 02:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Akagi](http://myanimelist.net/anime/658/Akagi)

This anime is basically about a legendary sociopathic mahjong player.  Apart from being suspenseful and exciting, it's good for picking up the rules of Japanese mahjong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 05:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a fascinating read. Ridiculous and selfish of Greyson to do that, but bizarrely I actually like the aesthetics of the blot. It makes the document look so unique, like the various signatures on the American Declaration of Independence. I'm glad he didn't manage to get the blue bottle out though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 00:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me enormously uncomfortable. I've been getting an annual physical ever since a loved one my age suddenly died from cancer 5 years ago that they didn't know they had...

Healthcare should be moving towards preventative care policies, not the 'wait till they get sick' strategy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little accountability for millions spent by riding associations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 22:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 02:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This eps had me laughing out loud several times, really looking forward to this new story arc. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 01:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bang Bang 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 03:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it argued that attempting to teach financial literacy only succeeds in giving people a false sense of "know how":

http://www.freakonomics.com/2008/09/19/is-teaching-financial-literacy-a-waste-of-time/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest batch of post-Confederation debates bring 'acrimonious' Second Parliament to life [1873] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 22:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 03:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm tempted to get a "no code" tattoo... I really would rather die humanely than wake up to torture before I succumb.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 18:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the problem is establishing a market place for venture capital. You go down to California, and it's reached the point where those with the money and inclination are going there to seek out innovators. 

How do you convince all those people to congregate in Canada?

I think the answer, at least to get the ball rolling is to sponsor technology and culture festivals/conferences. Sort of like how SXSW has that partial tech-focus that attracted venture capitalists to Texas.

It's not just money though, proper mentorship apparently is really difficult to come by and a lot of other factors. I read an article by Eric Migicovsky, the CEO of Pebble that noted a lot of points about how more money isn't the solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 14:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really interesting perspective I hadn't considered, allow select adults that like child-rearing to perform that function professionally... 

As a function of how much personal attention a child receives from an adult, I still like my original proposal (which maintains a sense of ownership). However, in terms of specialization in a civilization, I think you're totally correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 06:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep bringing up an idea at parties that I think is funny; basically, to have a kid as a time-share.

Because the cost and time-investment in having children today seems to be the most difficult part of the scenario (apart from real estate), I figured technically you could just have three separate couples mutually adopt a kid together.  Sort of like having the divorce ahead of time.  You get to raise a kid, have a stake in the future, teach them what you know, feel like a parent.  But, it would be like 2 days a week and one holiday in the year.  

I think it could work out, despite how outrageous it sounds. I liken it back to when we all lived in small villages and children would sort of be raised by everyone.  Living in little silo nuclear families seems unhealthy, I remember growing up in the burbs and having no idea who my neighbours were.  We're all losing that sense of 'community' that's important from a psychological perspective. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 02:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try engineering sometime...  Lots of theory, no real choice in courses because it's an accredited program. 

You forget the material after the classes mostly, but they teach the courses in a different way from other programs.  Everything is problem-solving over and over again.  So, when you encounter an open-ended problem in the real world, before you know it you're spinning out potential solutions to it.  It's rare that you remember a lot of the specifics of the courses though.

What I'm suggesting though is that learning at the university level needs to be more of an active process.  Not just sitting in lectures absorbing information.  Students should be taught and encouraged to develop commercial and intellectual products, whether that's art and poetry or robots and rockets.  And, to figure out outlets for that creativity to generate economic stability for themselves.

Most of my friends studied art and music out of high school.  They actually do fairly well selling their wares on Etsy for instance.  

It's a new economy, we need to find new work models rather than relying on corporations to just "make jobs" for people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 02:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this in the /r/Canada thread in response to someone suggesting another person should simply 'move where the work is':

 I don't think people should have to move somewhere for economic opportunity. Continuing to rely on established companies to supply jobs can't be the answer.

 It's a global economy now, opportunity is everywhere. We're just not doing enough as individuals to generate economic opportunities for ourselves. The generation we're following all got jobs that they stayed in for years with the hope of eventually retiring. It's hard to break away from that pattern having grown up observing it as 'the thing to do'.

 Unskilled labour in the new economy is rapidly disappearing. Where it's not disappearing, it's being outsourced to developing countries.

 We're creative people though, there needs to be a revolution in small-scale entrepreneurship. New forms of intellectual and commercial products... Fewer salaried 9to5 jobs, more ownership. Otherwise, we're just going to be another lost generation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 01:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think people should have to move somewhere for economic opportunity.  Continuing to rely on established companies to supply jobs can't be the answer. 

It's a global economy now, opportunity is everywhere.  We're just not doing enough as individuals to generate economic opportunities for ourselves.  The generation we're following all got jobs that they stayed in for years with the hope of eventually retiring.  It's hard to break away from that pattern having grown up observing it as 'the thing to do'.

Unskilled labour in the new economy is rapidly disappearing.  Where it's not disappearing, it's being outsourced to developing countries.

We're creative people though, there needs to be a revolution in small-scale entrepreneurship.  New forms of intellectual and commercial products...  Fewer salaried 9to5 jobs, more ownership.  Otherwise, we're just going to be another lost generation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 00:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, not to defend the LPC, but them and the NDP are opposition right now. So technically it's their job to levy criticisms of the current state of affairs, not necessarily offer policy to affect change.

Purely from a political stand-point, offering policy opens *them* to return criticism. So outside of an election it makes more sense to keep policy ideas under the hat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 23:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think institutions of higher learning need to put more emphasis on entrepreneurship. Degrees where you take a class, write a test, and forget the material after need to be changed. All the way back to K-12.

Students should be spending a large part of their university time building their own organizations. Doesn't have to be commercial products, I think the same model could apply to the arts. However, more applied creativity. More 'doing stuff', less scan-tron multiple choice.

Also, increased subsidies. Education should be the most affordable investment a person can make. Economically, 'return on education' is one of the most proven benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 23:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have thought you could get a vasectomy as long as you're +18... Weird.

I don't mind the idea of having kids but it is an enormous commitment. I've often thought of just going the 'donor' route and then take the bullets out of the gun.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 21:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to have kids, but I don't feel confident in being able to afford them.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 21:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this issue is directly linked to another article I posted in the sub today on how the birthrate in Canada is dropping:

http://www.reddit.com/r/CanadaPolitics/comments/1i0siv/domestic_dream_of_25_children_per_woman_long_gone/

The cost of living for youth today, the absence of opportunities...  This I feel is the real driving force to low birthrate.  Children require a lot of financing, and with the economy the way it is for young people, it's no surprise people don't want to start families.

Add mounting student debt, the cost of owning a home...  I feel like we're cutting our country off at the knees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 20:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think there's anything wrong with that though?  

I feel like my parents weren't especially well off when they got married and started their family... Is it a generational issue?  Do we lack the desire to have a family, or are we coping with more extreme economic considerations than our parents did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 20:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This feels like a natural political issue, since Canada will need to continue having an aggressive immigration policy in order to supplement our aging population.  Aggregate Canadian culture, values, and politics will see a major shift in response to changing voter demographics (which I suppose is the point of [Ibbitson and Bricker's Big Shift book](http://www.cbc.ca/books/2013/03/how-the-political-landscape-is-changing.html))

I have to admit, as my cohort is now entering the encouraged time to start proliferating, I'm really turned off thinking about the cost of having a family.  I like kids, family, etc., not bothered by the idea of being a father, but economically it feels a little untenable...

It might be interesting to do a [meta] poll on this sub regarding how users feel about the traditional life-model of settling down and having a kids.  I don't feel like I'm alone in my generation looking at it this way.  Young people today are probably too concerned with finding a job and keeping it, than taking on the added economic and financial risk of having kids...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domestic dream of 2.5 children per woman long gone as fertility rate declines for third year in row </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 19:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Domestic dream of 2.5 children per woman long gone as fertility rate declines for third year in row </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 19:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberals say youth aren't getting economic opportunities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 17:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harper's cabinet shuffle seen as critical for Conservative renewal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 15:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 17:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is refining capacity in Eastern Canada, however the refineries are not set up to accept the Alberta product.  Apparently, the reason the Keystone is such a big deal, is because the refineries in the Gulf Coast were already upgraded to handle Venezuelan oilsands product...

I think a larger problem with the whole scenario is that the US is rapidly becoming an oil producer again with fracking of shale oil deposits.  This oil is of conventional quality, which means that Alberta product will soon become considerably less valuable in the face of a large supply of American conventional crude.

I really worry about the Canadian economy and Alberta when that happens... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Train disaster triggers political debate on rail regulations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 22:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Train disaster triggers political debate on rail regulations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 22:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 21:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on where the hole in the hull was, it could pull the boat down at an angle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quebec disaster: Oil shipments by rail have increased 28,000 per cent since 2009 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 18:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 16:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  condensing

I have to disagree, she doesn't look a vapour changing phase into a liquid... well, maybe just a little.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Access watchdog wants power to order release of documents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 01:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-07 03:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the lazy: 

 Over the 2003-2012 period, 52 of the 93 accidents (table 5   table 6) resulted in a release of product. Nineteen of these involved a release of natural gas, all with less than 1 cubic metreFootnote 7 of gas released. Fourteen accidents involved a release of crude oil, with 8 less than 1 cubic metre, 2 between 1 and 25 cubic metres, 3 between 26 and 1000 cubic metres, and 1 over 1,000 cubic metre

I couldn't find anything comparing it to releases by rail accidents though...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 21:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're probably right, according to the Transportation Safety Board, [rail accidents in general seem to have a pretty steady number annually (~1100)](http://www.tsb.gc.ca/eng/stats/rail/prelim-2012/), and have been dropping for the past few years (closer to 1000). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 21:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admittedly, the damage and location make this particular case newsworthy, but there seem to be A LOT of derailment stories in the news this year... i.e. [Northern Ontario in April](http://www.theglobeandmail.com/report-on-business/industry-news/energy-and-resources/cp-oil-spill-in-northern-ontario-larger-than-first-reported/article10781522/), [Saskatchewan in May](http://saskatoon.ctvnews.ca/more-than-91-000-litres-of-oil-spilled-from-derailed-sask-train-1.1290062)

I rarely see much of an explanation as to why the derailments occur though.

 pipelines have proportionately less spills than other modes of transport

Fewer spills, but the magnitude of the release ~~is typically~~ may be larger. Edit, I stand corrected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 19:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it my imagination, or have there been an increased number of derailments lately?  Is it just getting reported more, because crude is getting transported by rail instead of pipeline? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Quebec] Fiery explosions rock Quebec town as train carrying crude oil derails; hundreds evacuated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-06 19:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 04:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beat me to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 01:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is clever, but it doesn't seem to let you select from the back-benchers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Cabinet-Shuffle Simulator [Interactive] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-05 01:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 18:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's saying that the roof is leaking, so we need a bigger bucket to hold the drips.

I'm acknowledging it's good to have a roof at all here, imperfect as it is.  You're saying it's only fair to tear it down and let everyone get wet.  Sure a good roof is the ultimate solution, but you're not going to get that if no one will stay in the house long enough to fix it. (this analogy is probably too drawn out, lol).

 It's a current grey area, which is why large, risk-averse companies can try this. The kinds of professional unpaid internships under discussion are not part of the underground, unregulated economy -- they work (like in this thread) in jobs like IT that are otherwise perfectly respectable.

If interns are unpaid, and not part of a "provincially recognized educational institution", then they are effectively part of an unregulated economy and unprotected labour-pool.

 we need to act sooner rather than later to reduce the supply of training for people who will ultimately never get a job in their field

Some internships don't lead to employment, it's true, but they all provide work experience that helps people find new employment and integrate better into their next position.  The training does have value.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 17:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The root problem is one of motivation. Are unpaid internships so desirable that we as a society need to subsidize them, as you would with your EI plan?

I would argue yes.  If between 100,000 and 300,000 Canadians are voluntarily working without compensation in the hopes of getting a full time position, despite knowing it's illegal for a company to let them work without compensation there's a problem. 

 an outright prohibition is far, far simpler than trying to divide virtuous from sinister internships

Technically this prohibition already exists, and clearly it's ineffective since young people continue to work without compensation as unpaid interns, going uncounted.  

Policy-wise, your comment seems to say "do nothing, we've already got this right".  Or institute a crack-down on companies for unpaid internships, which will destroy potential employment opportunities for thousands of Canadians that have no work experience trying to enter the work force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 16:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think trying to regulate internships and force employers to provide minimum wages is too heavy-handed an approach that will disincentivize companies from hiring interns in the first place.  These are positions for training skilled employees, as opposed to unskilled labour and services (i.e. minimum wage).

I've mentioned it [elsewhere](http://www.reddit.com/r/CanadaPolitics/comments/1hisec/unpaid_internships_exploit_vulnerable_generation/cauw0xg) that with the money that would be spent building a bureaucracy to regulate companies on internships and force them to pay a minimum wage, you could probably just give that money to interns in the first place and have them self-regulate the industry.

If they're on EI, they're accounted for (unlike now).  This will improve our unemployment statistics, to say nothing of the fact that you'll be putting money back in the pockets of consumers to help drive the economy.

If internships are free, more companies will hire interns for the prescribed time.  This will generate more employment opportunities.  Companies could be scored on a permanent-hire/internship metric for eligibility for a tax-credit to better incentivize good behaviour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 14:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One could argue that corporations *already* exploit young workers with internships.  At least with EI the more vulnerable new workers would receive some compensation. Furthermore, it would allow for the monitoring and regulation of internships which is currently not possible. (i.e. burger-flipping internships would not meet eligibility). 

This arrangement *is* a subsidy to corporations, that's the point. Where new workers will take greater risks on training and new employment in a changing economy, corporations will take more risks on how many new-hires come in the door, helping drive employment. The number of interns and the length of internships could be easily regulated to make this economical. Further, corporations could be scored based on a permanent-hires/interns metric for eligibility of a tax credit to further incentivize good behaviour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 03:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simply introducing more regulation on to internships will just burden everyone, disincentivize the programs to companies and cost money you could otherwise just give to interns.

I would agree that the purpose of EI is meant to be an insurance fund; however, the whole point of EI is to get people unemployed working again.  Technically, they could NOT take an unpaid internship, continue job-hunting, and on that basis collect EI (which some people may very well be doing).  I think using state funds to subsidize internships could have significant economic benefits.

On one hand, more people will be willing to take chances on new training and internships in a changing economy.  Companies will be more inclined to hire interns.  Income will be transferred to those not otherwise earning any money, all of which will help drive the economy.

I think in terms of incentives, benefits, and the fact that the government infrastructure is already in place it could make for a nimble turn of policy to improve employment figures.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 03:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morally I don't disagree with you, but given the elevated cost of education and the higher average student-debt of a new grad, this generation is technically more vulnerable, just by the numbers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 02:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree it would be a harder sell to have it come out of regular EI, but I think a narrative of investing in a future work force by sponsoring future employment could actually put a more positive spin on EI from some of the perception that it gets today. (On a side note, do companies pay a separate fee into EI? I wouldn't be in favour of increasing corporate tax burdens in Canada.)

After all, interns are generally a youth demographic trying to get experience.  I would actually feel more generous about paying into EI knowing it was going to support them.

The other benefit is that if you're using established infrastructure, then the cost of added of bureaucracy is significantly reduced. i.e. no increase in the size of gov't argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 00:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One option that might work for all stakeholders on this issue is to compensate interns with employment insurance benefits.  That way they receive a basic income, and it's easier to track which companies are hosting interns properly and which may be abusing the system.

I feel like one of the problems with unpaid internships is that to a certain extent they're "off the books", so they're an easy means to violate labour-laws unless there's a complaint: 

 Student organizations and lobbyists estimate between 100,000 and 300,000 Canadians work without bringing home a paycheque. Statistics Canada does not track unpaid internships.

However, getting hired just on a resume can be enormously difficult and having a way to get your foot in the door with an organization can be of pretty significant benefit. So as long as it's in good faith, I feel like internships can be pretty beneficial.

Obviously there would be a tax-burden associated with this, but I think this kind of wealth-redistribution would be very healthy for the country and economy at large. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unpaid internships exploit 'vulnerable generation' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 22:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unpaid internships exploit 'vulnerable generation' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 22:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alberta MP Ted Menzies bowing out of politics in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 19:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 03:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really good point actually. I'd like to see Trudeau bring that up in Question Period. His recent narrative seems to be big on bolstering student employment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 03:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the question then is, what would be the cost (personnel, equipment) of having LAC resume the digitization, vs. the 3rd party option? (This funding won't reappear with this gov't so perhaps the point is moot.)

Also, what was the pace and data-quality of LAC's digitization? Can a 3rd party achieve conversion of everything more rapidly, and are they capable of delivering the content to users more readily? (Online portal)

Finally, did they bid this out or single-source it to Canadiana? (Was this even the best deal offered? All the negotiations are secret afterall...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-01 22:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not crazy about the lack of consultation with stakeholders (i.e. archivists); however, I am interested in the economics behind the digitization of these documents. 

Is this a service that LAC could already provide, or are there benefits to using a private 3rd party? Using exclusive digital rights for 10years to pay for digitization might be worthwhile.

If however, this deal is being made to undercut the future of the archivist unions, that's obviously not appropriate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 18:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised to see the PMO injecting themselves into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PMO says the RCMP should have better things to do than seize guns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-28 01:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand that comment at the end of the article about Harper possibly proroguing parliament again. Why is that a possibility? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Letterman interviewing environmental activist, Tim DeChristopher "Bidder 70", who served 2 years in federal prison for outbidding oil and gas companies for mineral rights at a Bureau of Land Management auction for lands in close proximity to Utah national parks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 05:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tory senators criticize, amend union disclosure bill backed by their own government [Bill C-377] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 21:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calgary Zoo staff risked lives stopping hippo from escaping into Bow River during flood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 17:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Tory says he's considering running for Toronto mayor's office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-26 03:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 22:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title is a little sensationalist, they're just a small web-development group. However, this is an interesting example of regulation for traditional colleges and institutions of learning affecting new small businesses in web-learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Hacker School [TO's Bitmaker] Goes Dark After Government Probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 22:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Hacker School [TO's Bitmaker] Goes Dark After Government Probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 22:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 22:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Balsillie ever worked for Blackberry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada needs a proper census, and its not irresponsible to say so [Editorial] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 19:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RIMs Jim Balsillie to lead federal sustainable technology agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 18:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-25 05:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was an awesome cut!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 18:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching this, I'm reminded weirdly of that TV show Reboot from the 90s.  Only in this case the user is celebrated instead of being characterized as the antagonist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Fed, China: World faces perfect storm as liquidity dries up and China borrowing rates hit record high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 21:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 01:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will the results be posted in a [meta] post after? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Calgary] State of Local Emergency declared, municipal evacuation plan activated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 22:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City of Calgary Activates Municipal Emergency Plan [Flooding] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 19:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 06:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this happens, I hope they make out better than [Harrisburg PA](http://www.nytimes.com/2010/05/21/us/21harrisburg.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rob Ford wants to turn Torontos trash into cash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 06:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obesity now recognized as a disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 06:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obesity now recognized as a disease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 06:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stephen Poloz, Bank Of Canada Governor: Debt-Loving Canadians Saved The Economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 23:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 19:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am indeed going for satirical here. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 04:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like when we reach the point where the electorate is willing to throw slushy-cups at a public figure, regardless of obvious consequences... that's an important threshold to be able to identify.  The throwing of food (rotten or otherwise) at unpopular public figures is an ancient and storied tradition of human civilization that ought not be impeded.

Plus, didn't Chrtien get [pied that one time](http://www.cbc.ca/archives/categories/society/crime-justice/protester-pies-prime-minister-chretien.html) despite the RCMP protecting him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jackie Chan recounts getting hit during a fight-scene by Bruce Lee on Enter the Dragon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 00:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 23:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With constitutional issues like this and senate-reform/abolition cropping up, perhaps it's time to consider reopening the constitution.

The problem is that PM Harper and the CPC probably aren't in a strong enough position in their current state, political capital-wise, to successfully pull off such a bid.

I wonder if constitutional reform could be one of the big 2015 election issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kate Middeltons baby: Law to allow female succession may require constitutional amendment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 23:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 17:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd agree, there's been a rash of it lately that you normally wait till election season to see. I think it will go back to normal soon and the sub will go back to arguing policy instead of scandal. Just have to weather through it till then.

That said, the scandals are symptomatic of real problems that ought to be discussed. I recall admiring Harper and the PMO for their ability to control messaging and keep the party in line. It's looking like it wasn't a sustainable strategy, which will make it interesting to see how PM's in the future work, and whether a government can successfully be transparent and yet forestall criticism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 16:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, they're the government. Governments get criticised. If another party was in power they would receive the criticism for their screw-ups. Case in point, the Ontario Liberals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 04:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I look forward to a reopening of the debate.  

I believe in the sentiment of universal healthcare, but realistically the current delivery of healthcare in Canada is a badly designed system that it needs to be changed.

We gather every sick person into the same building, regardless of acuity, where wait times are extreme and a significant proportion will become sick on top of whatever they came in with, with drug-resistant hospital-associated infections (HAIs), which already kill more people in the united states than HIV, breast cancer and car accidents [combined](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/judith-johnson/hospital-acquired-infections_b_834425.html).

We have population statistics, we know how many of which kinds of procedures need to be conducted annually and where.  We should be completely overhauling the system such that specific offices/clinics treat specific sets of conditions, and meet the level of care that everyone deserves.

Hospitals and Doctors are not unlike centralized government in trying to be everything to everyone.  I don't mean we should throw the baby out with the bath-water, but there's got to be a better way to organize all this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 03:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, I feel like the only party that would go near privatized healthcare reforms would be the CPC, and their political capital has dwindled for 2013.  Furthermore, I believe a lot of the healthcare responsibility has been [discharged to the provinces](http://www.theglobeandmail.com/commentary/health-care-funding-how-harper-views-the-canadian-federation/article4182242/) in Harper's tenure.

Don't get me wrong, I think healthcare reform is important, and I can imagine models where private providers can exist.  However, I just don't think it's realistic to see this topic come up anytime soon. 

There was an interesting article the other day about how the Canadian electorate has been affected by [watching shows like Grey's Anatomy](http://news.nationalpost.com/2013/06/05/greys-anatomy-makes-canadians-grateful-for-public-healthcare-study/) in terms of their perception of public healthcare.  I think at this point reforms would be a hard sell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 02:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to throw me on there.  

* Economic Left/Right: -3.00
* Libertarian/Authoritarian: -5.13
* Liberal
* Ontario </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 04:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think in terms of speculation altacan probably meant that these latest news articles really don't contribute much new information.  No one really knows where the video or its copies are now.  So it really is just speculation beyond that contact with the intermediary was briefly re-established (to no avail), and in this case the bit about a search warrent for a phone.  

I think the question of whether the video existed in the first place is fairly accepted based on the affidavits of multiple journalists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 17:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm of the same mind.  However, maybe the senate could be reformed to stop being a legislative body altogether, but maintain its original purpose of providing "sober second thought".  Treat senators more like Canadian Research Chairs and have them perform policy research and recommendations for the lower house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 16:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> relief Thank you for explaining this scenario to me, that makes a lot more sense. So, specifically regarding cabinet and executive authority there's little to worry about.  

However, the overall power and influence of the office of Prime Minister and the commons would still be reduced with the introduction of an elected senate, since the ease of introducing and passing legislation would be more restricted. So, I suppose the question becomes whether or not that's a good thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 15:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, there would be nothing stopping senators from forming and executing the authority of a cabinet. After all, officially "advising the Queen" doesn't really mean anything with respect to legislation or executive practices in Canada.

What would prevent foreign powers from lobbying trade agreements in the senate rather than the commons to undercut the PM's negotiating power?

It sounds like a lot of this is tradition vs. how the rules are actually written. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 14:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're assuming one party would continue to control both houses for a hypothetical elected senate. 

Likely there would be a second cabinet in the senate if the opposition in the commons held the upper-house. Furthermore, even if both houses of parliament were held by one party, legislation can be introduced in either house. Meaning, policy could simultaneously be dictated by either the PM or the senate leader and their respective cabinets. 

An elected senate would mean the PM giving half of the legislative power of that office away to the senate leader, and with it the de facto executive power.

So, foreign relations, trade, foreign policy... Who negotiates on Canada's behalf? What if there's another terrorism crisis like the FLQ...?

I can't help but feel reforming to an elected senate would inject a lot of instability into our parliamentary model of gov't in the absence of a supreme executive, such as a president.  

Again, I'm not a political scientist though, so if someone can assuage my concerns, I'd appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 08:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Why would that diminish the power of the executive...?

The power of the executive would not be reduced, rather the position of Prime Minister.  Executive power would be split between the PM and the leader in the senate.  These individuals may not even belong to the same party.  In terms of foreign affairs and foreign relations, who would represent Canada?

I'm not an expert on the constitution or parliament, however. If executive powers are explicitly the province of the prime minister, I'd be very interested if someone could point out my misunderstanding (if I'm making one). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
