<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5987</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transsexual people have existed for a very long time and are recognized in certain cultures. "Transracial" people haven't and aren't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I would ever, gotta maintain some sense of mystery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere in the Amazon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boston would dispute that claim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYC is very safe. It's just gross and filled with homeless people so you don't always feel that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really an adult fashion, but when people wear [shirts with this kind of collar](https://dtpmhvbsmffsz.cloudfront.net/posts/2015/05/10/554ffac0fbf6f94990009ff0/m_554ffac0fbf6f94990009ff1.jpg) it always seems to make them look a lot older to me. You have to look really young to pull it off imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gone Baby Gone. I live in Boston so I'm supposed to like it but I thought the characters were crap and the plot line was boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's safe as long as you aren't in one of the worst neighborhoods and aren't part of a gang. Most Chicagoans are just friendly midwesterners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trail, it's addictive and you don't have to pay for shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a decent Cody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything ending in -yden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommend Chicago, because it's one of the only really large cities with reasonable rents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No women are ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Brown bread in a can,](https://newengland.com/today/food/new-england-made/bm-brown-bread-in-a-can/) preferably with baked beans on the side. Popular in New England/ the Boston area. No but seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not illegal in Massachusetts khed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wicked pissah khed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downloaded colorful mouses from one of those click ads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who turned out to be the opposite of what you expected? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you explain Justin Bieber? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What profession is a lot easier than it seems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can drink bathroom water, people just don't because the idea of it grosses them out. You can even drink toilet water if you want, as long as your toilet is clean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whose real age is the most different from the age they look? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dental hygienists don't generally have a huge amount of training, my friend's mom is one and she's a bipolar former crack addict with no degree and 30 cats.

Although bleeding is generally because you don't brush your teeth enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it any good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A remake of Rosemary's Baby would be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is I doubt there is a significant amount of people on Reddit old enough to have voted for him, if any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was afraid of going to Canada, I thought I'd freeze to death if I crossed the border. And I live further north than parts of Canada. My parents planned on taking me on a trip there once and I cried the whole way because I thought we would die and we ended up stopping somewhere in New Hampshire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was born in '61, I would consider that more a toddler or child, but yeah it is pretty similar. I just thought it was kind of interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. My mom was about 35 when I was born. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I'm 19 and my mom was older than yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lyndon B Johnson? I was about negative 34 years old when he became president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess hipsters, although I feel like hipsterism is too mainstream at this point to be considered a subculture. Plus it seems like it can be used to mean anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have girl pockets so it doesn't fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Please* Fuck off. Gotta be polite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an American, join the club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New England beat Atlanta in the Superbowl even though Atlanta was winning 3-28 at one point. Yesterday was 3-28. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New England beat Atlanta in the Superbowl even though Atlanta was winning 3-28 at one point. Yesterday was 3-28. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The City of Boston getting in on the memes yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The City of Boston getting in on the memes yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dunkies on every street corner, people don't look at you weird when you ask for an iced with a hot cup and it's 10 degrees out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I have some junkie friends and I've seen it really fuck up their lives, shit sucks. The heroin epidemic is pretty bad in New England right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL the second amendment is Canadian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time I smoked pot I also ate huge amounts of weed ice cream. I'm a 5'2 100lbs girl, was 16 at the time and had no tolerance. I was hallucinating that everything was bending, felt like gravity was distorted, was twitching constantly, and basically became wicked antisocial and stared off into space for hours at a time. It didn't wear off for about 3 days. Horrible experience 0/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are Blondie songs used in commercials so often? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL only about 1/3 of American colonists supported independence from Britain during the Revolutionary War. About 1/3 were neutral and 1/3 were Tories. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the soonest year that sounds futuristic to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend had a birthday party for her baby recently and fed it a metric ton of cake, like more than I would ever eat and I'm a grown ass adult. I don't understand why you would feed a baby cake at all, it's unhealthy and the baby won't fucking remember it or care if you don't give it cake, so what's the fucking point? That kid is going to end up fat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only heard that from scene kids circa 2009. If someone said that in 2017 I think I would actually die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean yeah it depends on the sub and the context generally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I would be so uncomfortable if my parents made fun of my period, especially as a teenager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some teenagers aren't comfortable using tampons and will only use pads, so that could be why. You can't go swimming with a pad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really subjective, it depends on what speaks to you personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can say anything you want on Reddit as long as you're not threatening to kill someone or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the best year of your life (so far)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should have been convicted of murder because he murdered someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 22:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm neither "pro" or "anti" Islam. People can believe whatever the fuck they want as long as they aren't forcing it on other people. If they are then that sucks. There are people from every religion that do that, not just Islam.

By the way, I know you have some sort of caricature in your head when you think of a feminist. I just consider anyone who believes that women and men are equal and should have the same rights to be a feminist, therefore I would consider myself one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uncle Sam= US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What weight do you think is too thin for a 5'2 woman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tend to assume that if they like country music, we won't get along very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your opinion of very thin women? Do you tend to judge them in some way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How fucking disgusting is it that you can be convicted of murder but if you're a cop you only lose your job at most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! Now I can cross my fingers every time get on a cab that it's the cash cab again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I hated myself and wanted to be as thin as possible both to harm myself and because I wanted to outwardly reflect how depressed and worthless I felt. I thought I was useless and didn't deserve food. Any little bit of fat on myself I saw as evidence of gluttony and that I thought I deserved to eat well, so I wanted to get rid of it as "proof" that I thought I wasn't worthy of food. It was a pretty fucked up way of thinking about things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about a month before I was born. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started at about 110 lbs at 5'2, my lowest weight was 82 lbs and it took me about a year to get there due to occasional binges. I also wasn't on as strict of a diet when I started out, it worsened later on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It changed but I limited myself to 450 calories a day most days with the goal of losing 2 lbs per week. I would do less if I could but that was generally the least I could eat while avoiding binging the next day. I had calculated that I burn 1450 calories a day without exercise so burning 1000 calories per day would equal 2 lbs lost per week. I didn't always stick to it though and would "binge" or eat less occasionally. I say "binge" but a binge would mean eating like 1000 calories that day, and I'd fucking hate myself for it and fast for the next day to make up for it.

A typical example of something I'd eat in a day is black coffee in the morning, a 100-calorie protein shake around 3 PM ish or whenever I could avoid eating until, then I wouldn't eat until it got dark out usually and I'd have something like a 250-calorie TV dinner with turkey and mashed potatoes. I ate a lot of those. If I didn't have that I might have a bowl of bran flakes or some baked cod or beans or something. The extra 100 calories or so I would use for tiny snacks throughout the day (usually after I had eaten "dinner"). I'd eat low-to-zero calorie things like pickles/ vegetables/ chicken broth/ sugar-free jello to hold me over if I got really hungry. I avoided "sugar free" things and diet soda most of the time though because it tended to give me a headache and gave me diarrhea, and would often lead to me eating more. Popsicles were also something I used occasionally, the kind I got were like 25 calories. Sometimes I'd have things like seaweed salad or miso soup as a treat, although they do have calories in them despite being low-calorie. If I was forced to go to a restaurant I'd try to insist on going to a Japanese place and only eating those things or I'd get hot pot and only eat the broth and vegetables. Although those things would usually take up most of my day's calorie budget so I'd avoid it. I wouldn't eat anything else at a restaurant because restaurant food has an extreme amount of calories and you don't know how many calories are in it most of the time. Restaurant food in particular really scared me and it took a long time to be able to eat at one normally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be there to support the person and try to get them to go out and do things. Isolation is one of the most dangerous things for an anorexic in my opinion and lots will isolate themselves given the opportunity. Encourage them to get help or to see a councilor if possible, it helps a lot more than you would think. Remind them that they're valued and important. At the end of the day though, it's really up to them to get help and to change their mindset and there's only so much you can do. Don't blame yourself for what they're going through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I knew it was unhealthy from the start, but I didn't care because I hated myself. It did progress to where I started having heart papiltations and digestive issues though which scared me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my case I started having heart papiltations and it scared me. I also realized that I fucked up my digestive system and couldn't digest things the way I used to. I was pissed off and tired all the time, and had isolated myself because I didn't want people to see me until I lost weight (it was never enough weight) and because it's hard to avoid food in social situations. Basically the situation I was in scared me into gaining weight. I still have issues with self-image but gaining weight somehow helped me snap out of it. It's different for everyone, but I think the lack of food encourages anorexic thought patterns. I also started being around people a lot more and I think the social interaction and support from friends helped a lot. I didn't have that while I was sick. It's always an issue for me though and I have to be careful to avoid slipping back into my old habits, so I think of it kind of like an addiction. It's kind of similar to quitting smoking or drinking in a way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 82 pounds at 5'2. Which isn't as thin as the scare pictures you see of anorexia, especially since I have a very small frame, but it's definitely very thin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest opinion? Short beards can be nice sometimes but long beards just make me think of homeless people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a former anorexic, AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, and I basically asked this question because I wanted to clear up the preconceptions that people have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if you lose an extreme amount of weight. At milder levels it fucks with your digestion and can cause heart issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Low self esteem yes, but we tend to only be superficial regarding ourselves and very non-judgemental when it comes to other people. And anorexia isn't always because the person wants to be thin for aesthetic reasons, it's often times a way of self-harming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of the time yes but not as often as you would think, you lose your appetite to match the amount you eat most of the time. Occasionally you will get really hungry and binge but it's usually not until after you start eating. Getting weak from lack of food always bothered me more than being hungry, you can just ignore hunger and it goes away while weakness just tends to get worse over time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Job-getting strategies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What preconceptions do you tend to have about people with anorexia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that time a bunch of states banned official travel to North Carolina over this bill? I member. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 19 year old girl and can't eat anything without digestive issues, mostly due to fucking up my digestive system from being anorexic. Little-known side effect, anorexics get as constipated as heroin addicts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back in the 1800s, rich people only ate white bread while brown bread was for poors. What "poor person thing" will become a "rich person thing" in the future? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 09:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of how back in the 1800s, rich people only ate white bread and brown bread was for poors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What internet discovery was most groundbreaking for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does "the past" still exist in some form, or is it just gone forever? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this makes any sense, but basically I was thinking that if time travel were possible, there'd have to be "a past" existing somewhere to travel to, wouldn't there? But if the past didn't exist anywhere, there'd never be a way of traveling to it. So that made me wonder if "the past" exists somewhere, in an alternate dimension or something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey now, we're still the ones with legal weed for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We "have to wait" in theory but not in practice, I've never met someone who actually waited to 21 to drink. It still sucks though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Massachusetts! All students are required to have health insurance and can typically get it for free if they for whatever reason aren't on their parents' and can't afford it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say that's closer to being Askreddit if anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old people are real-life time travelers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well actually everyone is, but especially old people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd be about as confused by what we're saying as old people are (who are actual time travelers). I mean there are even people alive today that remember 1917. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What food were you surprised not to find outside of where you grew up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taco Bell, everything I've had there has been disgusting *and* it's extremely unhealthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buzzfeed news is actually a lot better than you would expect. I check it occasionally and to be perfectly honest every time I've seen, when major political events have happened, it's been much less biased and given more info than Reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked something like "why do you lose your appetite when you're sick" and it got a large amount of upvotes in a short time, then a mod deleted it and said it was a repost question and easily googled. I searched for it on the sub and there was only one person who asked it, and it was from 3 years ago and had 1 response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Dick, what are your thoughts from beyond the grave on recent events? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I think about it the only time I've had breaded wings that weren't boneless was KFC one time and I never ate it again. Are breaded wings a lot more popular in other parts of the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't eat more than like half a slice of Chicago pizza at a time though which kind of ruins the experience for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rest of the US is weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanksgiving dinners originated in New England, so anything other parts of the US do differently from us is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to enjoy it when we're stuck in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god that's fucking horrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has the cameraman been unintentionally baptized then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's basically just processed cheese, shit quality meat, and carbs, and loaded with calories. Putting a piece of lettuce on it doesn't make it any healthier. If you want to believe that shitty fast food is healthy go ahead though, you aren't hurting anyone but yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same and also Papa Gino's. I was always confused when people mentioned Dominoes/ Papa Johns/ etc but not Papa Gino's, I thought they were all just bad rip-offs of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still unhealthy. The reason you aren't fat is that you're eating less of other foods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a horrible choice for a type two diabetic. Or anyone really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a common misconception. Type 2 diabetes is caused by being overweight which can be from eating excessive calories of any variety. Taco Bell is very high calorie and thus leads to gaining weight thus diabetes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude that is so unhealthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, my dad is from Chicago and had never heard of it, so I just figured it was regional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're the New England style, which [look like this](http://www.thefreshloaf.com//files/u28841/IMG_3961.jpg). The bread is exposed at the sides instead of being crust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one knows what scrod is really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still live here but fried dough, steak tips, and scrod come to mind. Also that brown bread in a can, although it isn't as popular as it used to be.

I've never heard of chocolate soda though, and I grew up in a town directly neighboring Mansfield.

Edit: I almost forgot hoodsie cups! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stoppies khed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slavery was illegal in Massachusetts. They were probably relatively low down on the totem pole but so were a lot of whites. They'd have to work together to have the ship run efficiently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does that mean redheads have more red-pigmented skin as well as hair? Anecdotally my dad has red hair and his skin is as red as a lobster. I don't have red hair or skin (mostly) but I'm extremely pale and burn within about 30 seconds of being in the sun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The audio is from a different video, the guy in it is from Malden MA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was some of both, but economics are what ultimately motivated the North to take action. Slavery was a very unpopular idea in the North. That's not to say race relations were perfect, there was still a lot of racism, but by the time of the Civil War most Northerners thought slavery at least was evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A huge amount more were imported to Brazil too, since they had high death rates. A relatively very small amount of slaves were imported to the US, and importing slaves was made illegal in 1807, so their numbers increased to the number they did mainly from being healthier than slaves in South America. And even then there were a lot fewer slaves in the Southern US than Brazil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as that's how my grandparents ended up I'd say it's highly likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They held an informal session over Christmas break with very little advance notice, and voted to delay. As long as at least one member of both parties are present (there was one democrat, the rest were republicans), it's allowed, but highly morally questionable. 

If one person objects at an informal session then nothing can be passed, but since no one outside of the little group that voted on it was given enough advance notice, there was no one there to object. Charlie Baker, also a republican, decided not to veto it.

Although what they delayed to mid-2018 was non-medical pot shops opening. it's legal to have/smoke weed, grow plants, and "gift" weed to other people already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if you're serious but slavery ended in the 1860s in the south, and much earlier in the north. It was made illegal in 1783 in Massachusetts specifically, but slavery was never a big thing in MA in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't in 1845. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Massachusetts guaranteed access to all public schools to every child in 1845, after a group of black whalers from Nantucket, accustomed to the relative equality they had on whaling ships, began a boycott and petition campaign. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
