<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject573</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 16:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know who "liberals" are. Show me some and then I can have a conversation with them and might be able to determine their opinion on the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 16:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I don't know what they meant. I would also would not mistake credit unions for banks as they are different by definition.

I'm not being pedantic either. Generalization is a terrible practice and the worst abuses of it result in people dying or suffering.

Why do you feel the need to group people on superficial characteristics such as appearance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 05:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime you are using the word "they" you are likely stereotyping many people that you know nothing about. Who are you referring to as "they" in your comment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 15:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> humble, at least  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 14:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating pie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 14:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.

Why wouldn't you just surrender? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 13:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't encourage people to hide information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 13:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? The gif appears to show rather brutal treatment. The person is basically ripped open and the baby yanked out. I expected more care to be taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 07:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not exclusive to first timers. Both substances tend to lower blood pressure, so there is a chance of briefly passing out if your oxygen demands jump to quickly (eg. if you were sitting for awhile and then quickly stood up).

Nausea is also commonly reported.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 08:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, most probably. Tanks should always be in a ready-to-deploy state. If people are using them then they require more maintenance and there may be a delay in deploying them for their purpose.

If you want to ride one, just go join the Army. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 08:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People with guns will stop you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 08:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same as for Snowden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 08:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there are already uses for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 07:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have already done those things (for some definition of exact) and I didn't consider it stealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 07:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 07:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two entire weeks, during the lowest traffic month?

Do you know if there was a diff of the policies? Or did you manually have to find all the changes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 06:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree there is a vernacular that supports that definition, but as we are talking about violation of law, vernacular is not relevant.

Clinton also released information she didn't have a right to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 06:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stole does imply more, but I only made a claim of what is necessary, not everything that is sufficient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 05:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All US government work product is owned by the people. Further, *stole* implies someone was deprived of a physical item. I am only aware that digital records were copied. I haven't heard anything about Snowden stealing anything. What source can I use to read more about the theft? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 04:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For...what, exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 03:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I said, none of those people were running. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 03:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I wanted to vote in the Republican primary...there was only one candidate. So...not much of a choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 02:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, so then you admit that you had some choice other than Trump.

As I said, they are *party primaries*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 02:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> False. You can still vote for people who are not Donald Trump. If they registered for the ballot, they're still on there. That's why 11.3% of California voted for Kasich.

I can also write in whoever I want. If the person is not running, they are not running, no matter what a piece of paper says.

That doesn't mean you don't get to vote.

Never claimed otherwise.

Pretty sure they all have been counted at this point. 

Voters are claiming otherwise: https://www.reddit.com/r/SandersForPresident/comments/4rv5k5/california_tossed_1054874_votes_not_accounted_to/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 01:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you understand the election. They are party primaries and you only get to vote in one. All Republican candidates had dropped out. So, if you want to vote in the Republican primary, there was only one choice. The Democratic party had two, but one already had an insurmountable lead.

Also, there are just ballots that haven't been counted. So, yeah, I don't know what you or the person I responded to are talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They? I am a US citizen in California. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are describing intent, which the Federal government is impeccable at determining. Intent is different from motive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know they aren't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 08:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit wants to push on native advertising. If it is integrated well enough, as block might not be much use (though reddit might have no users at that point). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 05:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I did.

reddit seems to think this is only worthy of a notice in changelog and a tiny clause in a document almost no one has read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 04:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And everyone can play hours long ads of Trump.

What a shit show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 02:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a [discussion](https://www.reddit.com/r/changelog/comments/4rl5to/outbound_clicks_rollout_complete/d5220li) about this. Still waiting on an answer from reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 00:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will the information be used for any advertising purposes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 22:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't subscribe to this subreddit and I certainly do not check its side bar twice a week.

The [prior policy](https://www.reddit.com/help/privacypolicy?v=0c106264-a5e0-11e5-bc62-0e42c44f0485) stated:

If we do, we will let you know by revising the date at the top of the policy. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to r/announcements, the front page of the Services or *sending you a notification*).

Does reddit not believe this was a change OR does reddit believe that it was not a *material* change? The announcement that you kindly linked to *does not mention that reddit will track out-bound link clicks*.

What is going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 21:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't appear to be. Historical GDP by country, by half-decade: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_countries_by_largest_historical_GDP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 20:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wasn't the new clause mentioned in [the annoucement of the new, "simpler", "functionally very similar" privacy policy](https://www.reddit.com/r/announcements/comments/3tlcil/we_are_updating_our_privacy_policy_effective_jan/)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 20:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is already explicitly mentioned in our privacy policy, which is linked on sign up:


Looks like that clause only went in to effect on Jan 1 of this year and was added to the policy in November 2015. Since my account was created before then, *I would not have seen this in the privacy policy.*

Where is my consent to this new policy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zoos typically keep animals in small cages. Often, too small for an animal to have much/any autonomy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 04:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be a conflict, for sure, but not exactly the same in every way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 04:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does, because they fall into a (extreme) category of what they are studying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 00:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't I just slightly smash (or spin) a rubber (or other sufficient material) ball? Why go through all of those extra steps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOP doesn't have anything to offer, do they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a mistake though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US government can be taken over in 4-6 years (depends on when you start). 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not following you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Accurate and lazy refer to the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pedantic.


[Yes/no?] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is not the same? Transmitting to an insecure server is not exposing? Or, knowingly setting up an insecure server with the intention of not using the approved servers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is inaccurate (incomplete) to what is actually occurring, but I do agree that it does capture some essence of what is happening. But, if you also have the option of showing the actual result along with the logical selection, it would seem preferable to give that explanation. The box diagrams do seem to more accurately capture the essence of joins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did.

You claimed no new information was added in this article over the Fucking white boys article.

That claim was false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those algorithms actually exist and run though. You can't really give it a completely historical context (though some should be given) since it is just a fact that you can write out and run the algorithm yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you have a choice of what explanation to give someone, the accurate explanation would be better than the inaccurate one, wouldn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labeling pedantic is not a proof of pedantry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extremely careless seems to work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are transmitting to/from an insecure server, you *are* exposing. Hillary intentionally set up and transmitted to/from the servers so that she didn't have to use .gov email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One name: Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that the other choice is Donald Trump, who is worse on basically every count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also note, contrary to some claims being made here: the only qualifications are being at least 35 years old, being a natural born Citizen, and having lived in the US for fourteen years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI cannot and should not be able to stop someone charged with a crime from running for office either.

Nor, an actual criminal.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Comey doesn't want to prosecute, he would not use language indicating legal wrong doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That isn't about rank and file. Similar circumstances where a person engaged in that activity means: anyone in the same circumstances.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just fired, most likely:

To be clear, this is not to suggest that in similar circumstances, a person who engaged in this activity would face no consequences. To the contrary, those individuals are often subject to security or administrative sanctions. But that is not what we are deciding now.


Hillary is lucky that Trump is the other choice.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who forced Hillary to setup her own unsecured email that was hacked and used to transmit secrets? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who was CIA?

Clinton was told at the outset she couldn't do what she did, but she intentionally did it of her own free will. It was also against regs. Also she lied about pretty much everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 17:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manning is imprisoned for sending emails or other communications, no?

Snowden is in exile? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 09:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I am exaggerating anything. I wouldn't believe any fMRI results until they are confirmed to not have not been derived using an invalid algorithm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 08:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I appeal the inaccurate tag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low-quality noise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 03:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 02:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling something out as pedantic is either lazy or wrong. If the argument doesn't have merit it should be easy to directly address it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 00:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would guess any intelligence agency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 00:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The primary benefit of open source isn't reuse, but just *being able to know what is going on*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 00:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be done, but no one should be fooled to think that it is sufficient.

You still need to know *what software to write* and sufficiently motivated people to write it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 00:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless a government is outsourcing to foreign nationals, all of the contributions *are* from citizens and code review is a huge problem, socially and technically. Japan recently lost a spacecraft due to poor code oversight, Tesla just lost a customer, and a huge number of US government projects have failed because of poor code being run, even for basic services such as accessing a public insurance market through a web site.

Writing good software in large (or small) teams is not a solved problem and people suffer from it everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 00:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the next editorial will make their position on the article clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 00:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you see the article garnering support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it's normal, but others report the same thing occurring in other places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearing that a company is looking to hire resources makes me give them a wide berth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For making information public that Google later had struck from public records?

Not that great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it does. We are building off work done over the last century+. High level languages are probably the pinnacle of scale. Any program you want can be translated down through many levels to execute on microscopic gates (and, on *billions* of machines around the planet).

I would say that software development operates at the limit of scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 23:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we stop dismissing arguments as being pedantic in the programming sub, at least?

Argue the text on its own merit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No one is claiming we can read his mind 

Well, that is actually why I came into this thread. Someone did make that claim:

There is no strawman here. Its literally that guy in that post showcasing a mindset that is very prevalent and recognizable.


.

But you're arguing semantics and pretending that you just want to have a civil conversation because you want to win.

I don't pretend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we still don't know *what specifically in the article* made you think that.

The article seems to establish its own (but conflicting) racial hierarchy.

On one hand, non-white is upheld as delivering praise to white boys (particularly if they are fuck boys), but on the other, she believes that everyone sees her as inferior to white women, *because a white fuck boy said he felt bad about having sexual contact with her, due to another relationship, and because he was not exciting enough*.

Shouldn't this view weigh into the balance of powers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that is called "projecting".

Commenters have claimed that reading a handful of words gave insight into a very specific mindset of an individual they otherwise know nothing about.

Now, you are saying that the very particular mindset that was described was not accurate?

Either the commenters 'knew' he was afraid, or they didn't.

I argued it is impossible for us to know that. Others say we can know it solely from the words used.

It sounds like you agree? We cannot know the mindset of a person from a short text message on Tumblr, let alone a screenshot of one on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good thing. Statistics is all about computation. Interpretation of results should have occurred *before* measurements began. Statistics just allows us to compute which result is actually the case.

Probability/Experimental Design is probably where interpretation of results should occur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think that would be her thesis?

What is a social tier? How does one measure inherit power balances? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To me, hacker evokes the following image:

A person moving through a jungle with a machete, hacking a path through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: "Default Mode Network" is based in fMRI data, whose validity has recently been challenged due to discovery of a defect in the process that results in very high false positive rates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didnt waste my time trying to be nice anymore because I was aware of what I had become: the irrelevant Asian girl in a budding Scott Pilgrim-esque romance. From the countless times that Ive been rejected for a white girl, Ive been taught that my desirability was only a fleeting moment whereas a white girl was the one worth getting to know, the one worth bringing home to parents and the one worth being treated as a human. I was the sexual object, whereas my housemate was the one who had feelings worth considering.

Eventually, I showed Sam out the door, and he asked for my number, suggesting that maybe we could hang out next semester when our lives were a little bit different.

Fuck that. Im wise enoughor have been fooled enough timesto recognize that this maybe one day trope was a fuckboy specialty. To objectify women like theyre library books, pulling them on and off the shelf whenever its convenientand for women to be OK with thatis a clear example of male privilege.

Its depressing to realize how much women of color compromise in their relationships with white men. I recall the number of times that my non-white girlfriends and I have praised a white guy for having listened to us, for having genuine interest in us, for seeing us as a real people instead of objects. Its fucked up that these are exceptions and not expectations.

When society has made the white person the ultimate pursuit, it teaches non-white women to be OK with feeling inferior, to be OK with being submissive and to be OK with being treated like shit.

Until white boys prove to me theyre worth more than a faded fuck, I refuse to take these fuckboys seriously anymore.
 
-*Fucking white boys*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article pulled in information from Maggie's other columns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you link to a comment related to this article where someone expressed their voice had been silenced? Or a reference to Gamergate or Donald Trump?

Can you list one fair point made in the article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What in the article made you have that understanding when no one else did? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 15:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand your question. Salary is tied to funding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 05:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are multiple conflicts:

1) Professors fall into a category they are studying 

2) Professors fall into an extreme category they are studying

3) Professors are in an extreme category *because* of what they are studying

4) Professors personally benefit (through continued salary) by continuing inequality (ensuring further study)

I think there are probably many more, but maybe those are sufficient? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 05:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how you (or anyone else) can infer that the author is *afraid* that she doesn't know that she was scaring off potential suitors, just based on knowledge of those words.

People tell others things for motivations other than fear, no?

Edit: maybe someone can answer how they could know that just from these words? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 02:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you saying the poster knows more about the person than just those words that they wrote?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 02:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inequality is, at least in part, measured by salary/income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 01:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't you showcasing the disturbing mindset that blows a handful of words that someone writes into an entire assumed (and, often, projected) 'mindset', when, in fact, you know almost nothing about the person who wrote them, or their mindset? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This already exists to some extent.

Check out Code Contracts in .NET: https://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/dd264808(v=vs.110).aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 17:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that non-sequitor, last-gasp comment was some good shit.

Edit: I'll leave this here, too:


Article 1. Section 2 (a)

Every person may freely speak, write and publish his or her sentiments on all subjects, being responsible for the abuse of this right. A law may not restrain or abridge liberty of speech or press.

http://www.leginfo.ca.gov/.const/.article_1

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 17:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The professors have an interest in inequality continuing (or worsening) so that funding is available for them to study it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 17:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The response of a defeated commenter. ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 01:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Conflict of interest

2) Research bias </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 01:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The assumption of a contract is that it is valid. UC might refer to something as a "contract", but that does not make it the case.

UC has a history of violating the CA (and US) Constitution, so it would not be the least bit surprising if it is currently violating either. Cf. Regents v. Bakke

I don't see anything in the policy you pasted that says anything about speech. It seems to be only referring to physical violence/coercion. UC is strictly forbidden from making any contract, rule, policy, or other law that restrains or abridges liberty of speech.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 23:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I claim UC operates within the Constitution? No.

Here is the relevant bit:

Article 1. Section 2 (a)

Every person may freely speak, write and publish his or her sentiments on all subjects, being responsible for the abuse of this right. A law may not restrain or abridge liberty of speech or press.

http://www.leginfo.ca.gov/.const/.article_1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 23:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know who Geoff Marcy is, but the difference between this column and your other examples is that this column is implicitly endorsed by the University, both through licensing agreements and through material, financial, and logistical support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 21:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UC cannot make contracts outside the CA Constitution. The CA Constitution guarantees an absolute right to say anything you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 21:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That more people know about it.

People should know what is being published at the University and what University students are doing and thinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 04:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of its existence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 00:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racist? Sexist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 21:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No stopping means no stopping. Unless your car moves while it is parked, parking is stopping. Don't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The California Constitution guarantees equal protection of law. UC is formed under the CA Constitution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I think the titles "Fucking yellow girls" or "Fucking colored girls" might get you published?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, awesome. I just went out to grab a copy of the latest edition, so that I could have a physical copy of this article, but it looks like it was not printed.

I would love, purely as satire, a version that just swapped the genders and races mentioned, but is otherwise identical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 20:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please let me know where it ends up. I hope you submit it to be published in DC too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
