<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject414</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, that's where Fender got the idea. I've been using the Grolsch ones for 20+ years. I don't drink anymore, so easier to buy the Fender ones now ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, it happens, especially on Les Pauls, as the angle of the strap is pretty severe. Looks like you'll need to replace the whole switch as from your pic it looks like a couple of the threads sheared off. Take it to a qualified repair shop (or Sam Ash or Gtr Center, if that's all there is). Shouldn't be too expensive. If it is and the switch still works, then put it off till you save up the $$. Won't hurt anything.

I'd advise getting some straplocks as well (I'm a touring gtr tech and I use them on all artist's guitars I work with, as it happens to the 'big' boys too). I like these for Les Pauls, as they are relatively cheap and work well without having to remove the original strap button. https://www.sweetwater.com/store/detail/099-0819-000?adpos=1o1 creative=55397627521 device=c matchtype= network=g product_id=099-0819-000 gclid=CIy11On-qNMCFRuBswodoNkOFQ

And, don't be discouraged, keep on playing, we all started out the same way.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like he sheared off a couple of threads, so that plastic tip would not screw back on. Gonna need to replace the whole switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ours doesn't use the standard side screw method, which is the only place I've seen the oxidation on solderless cables. I still use a George L's cable that I've had for close to 30 years in my touring set-up for tuning guitars, it's been all over the world, no oxidation, no problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 13:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure which model you are referring to, but I don't think any of ours has a tranny right next to the input (maybe you are referring to the choke?). Anyway, Ossie the designer uses an electronic stethoscope to position the transformers on the chassis where they are quietest. Our amps are some of the quietest at idle I've ever heard (or not heard). Thanks for checking them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, he loves them and has built many. Just no more room in the house... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's old skool, no cell, no camera, no email. I did get him an iPad to watch YouTube on, he loves watching you guessed it, woodworking videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks guys. He's great at it, unfortunately no more room in the house for big stuff like this. He is working on some bowl turning now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, for some reason it had trouble submitting. will re-submit. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to visit my parents yesterday (an hour away) and my Dad showed me this Walnut Secretary he's almost finished with (he has some interior drawers to go. I thought this was an interesting design with the peaks in the doors (he said it was tough), I also like the curly walnut on the drawer fronts.

FYI My Dad was a mechanical engineer and has been making furniture (mostly Shaker) as a hobby for at least 40 years, he's in his 80's. He mostly uses his ancient Craftsman Table Saw (not even a cabinet saw) and a Craftsman Radial Arm Saw.

Thanks for checking this out. He taught me a bit, I'll post some of my stuff later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
