<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> watching this after watching UFC... you can see a lot of those guys are heavy on PEDs... on the other hand everything looks more explosive.

I wonder if any of those guys with PEDs could beat a UFC clean champ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want Wonderboy to win, but I don't see how he will do it.

He really needs to throw kicks, otherwise he is lost. But then he risks being taken down. Just by punching he won't win. Woodley would land against at least once, and that's all he needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Rory has a very good TDD and better ground game than Woodley, which meant he could kick Woodley at will. This is not the case for Wonderboy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They really need to book a 3rd fight.

I agree but I don't want any of these guys to lose again. Both of them need a win. Weidman needs a "tune up" fight, Silva needs some kind of big fight. It is a pity he couldn't fight in brazil, that was a good fight for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 14:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for this! great video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is not at all what this paper is about. read the link or the paper source. It is about showing them "reminders" of poverty, and analysing their reaction after it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Messi's 25 free kick goals since 2008 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 11:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paper: http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/01/03/1615010113 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study shows that among the affluent people in affluent neighborhoods, a clear reminder of others poverty does not induce a show of generosity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 11:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> afaik it is a listed building. no chance it will get demolished </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember back then OoT was amazing because it was huge, and just riding epona there was incredible. nowadays we have bigger more populated worlds, so I understand what you mean.

I played OoT back in the day in 64...  and I don't want to play it again nowadays just in case it destroys my memories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature20829.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New insights into mechanisms of breast cancer development and resistance to therapy. Researchers have gained new insights into the molecular processes in breast tissue. They identified the tumor suppressor LATS as a key player in the development and treatment of breast cancer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper: http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature20788.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian prostate cancer researchers have discovered the genetic fingerprint that explains why up to 30 per cent of men with potentially curable localized prostate cancer develop aggressive disease that spreads following radiotherapy or surgery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 years of guitar playing is almost nothing. If you plan to be a teacher you won't be able to compete with any of the pros there. If you plan to be a studio player, no chance.

I don't really know what is your objective. Do you have a band? Do you already have something published? Do you gig?

If your answer to all this is no, then what exactly is your plan?

Studying full time and playing the guitar is perfectly compatible. You don't need to play the guitar that much every day to progress. Something like 1 hour or 2 is more than enough. You will have even time to practice with your band (if you have one).

If you expect to practice full time for 3 years and have a "break through", then it is not going to happen, especially because there's no such thing as a break through. The only way to do it is with a band, and you don't seem to have one. Because a band grows very slowly is a progressive way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I knew it was done in 1 year with a lot of content reused from Ocarina's (which is my favourite game ever).

Majora's really feels like a game which is half done. As someone else said the map feels very empty (except the main town, which is amazing, everything else is super empty). Zora's bay is a joke, a huge area with near nothing. The central map is also kind of empty. Same kind be said about the whole snow section, just a house in the middle, and then their main town only has 2 accessible portions as far as I remember. I don't know, some parts look really well done, and some parts look very rushed. 

The dungeons themselves are fantastic, and some of the pre dungeons are really good (like the pirate's one, which is amazing). This is sadly killed by the 3 day cycle, which makes the exploration a pain in the ass.

For me the worse thing is that a lot of content is "there" but there are no hints at all about how to get it. The only way is to get a guide. This is because the game was rushed and probably it didnt have a really good QA. As said, it happened to me a few times that I had literally no idea about what to do. I don't want to be spoon fed, but a lot of times after reading the guide I was kind of annoyed because that was impossible to guess. I spent around 45 hours to finish it, so I did my time.

Also, the very end, if you get all the mask the final boss is a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished it recently for the first time. It took me around 45 hours. Overall I liked it, but:

The 3 day cycle, even with the inverted song, is horrible. It doesn't mesh at all with a Zelda game. It is like playing 2 different game. It happened me twice that I couldn't finish a dungeon in time and had to repeat parts of it and it was horrible. It just doesn't work with a Zelda exploration game. 

Plenty of times got stuck and I didn't know what to do. I'm not talking about puzzle lost, but completely lost. I've never had to check a guide so much before.  Mix this with the 3 day limit for a horrible experience.

A lot of the side stuff is IMO impossible to discover without guide. 

The fairies are a big mess. Horrible with the 3 day limit. 

Overall, it feels like a game rushed in 1 year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 08:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robbed again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 22:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best in the world  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 22:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why ?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> depends on the country. USA rarely. Europe more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I need to buy this before Brexit ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you need also to compare against whom we played, and against who they played. Arguably their best opponent was us, because their CL run was a joke apart from the final against Atletico. We had way tougher opponets in our UCL run (city, PSG, bayern munich and juventus) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why?

Places like Vilaweb are very dangerous, because they are left liberal places (I consider myself a left / social / liberal .../ I have always voted for left parties). The fact that they have a political aligment similar to ours makes us blind to the fact that they are a cesspit. The_donald is in the other side of the spectrum, so we are already ready to dislike it, but with vilaweb, they upload a lot of content that makes you think "oh this is really cool", but then you check a bit more or read other sources and you are like "oh wait".

Similar things can be said about The Guardian. The main different is that the guardian has good journalists, although some other are just the left version of your average the_donald redditor. That's why the guardian is very dangerous... you have excellent columns mixed with horse shit, and you might eat it all at the same time. Vilaweb follows a similar rule, with the different that for each good column they have 9 which are horrible echochamber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> weigh in was 133. it was a non title fight so the weight limit was 136. it doesnt make any sense to cut 3 extra pounds, so we can assume 133 is her walking weight

you can see the weigh in here: http://www.bloodyelbow.com/2016/7/22/12251440/ufc-on-fox-20-holm-vs-shevchenko-weigh-in-results-live-video-stream

she doesnt seem to be cutting any weight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she was 133 against Holly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My problem with Shev is that she is a small 35, she is not even cutting weight. Pea is a big one .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we upvoting a story that starts with "LOL"? What's next ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 12:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More likely it kept the same price in Euros and it went from 36 to 47 pounds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 12:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a Disney toy from their official store. It is from the previous star wars movie so I guess the price tag was set more than a year ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good old times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 10:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan Air planes don't have a 13th row </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 13:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 13:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say worse. Vilaweb is a cesspit, a echochamber. I'd say it is like the_Donald in terms of quality and bias  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 13:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing really. Journalism in Spain is a complete joke. They basically survive with money from the government, because people don't buy newspapers anymore. Best thing you can do is read several sources and make your own opinion.

I read sometime ara.cat and listen to rac1, but they are biased as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 10:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catalan here. Don't trust Vilaweb, they are extremely biased, not real journalism, more like a pamphlet

There was a poll a few weeks ago done by a Spanish company and they said the no would win. But as Spanish they are also biased. 

By the way, I would probably vote no.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 10:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is actually very common. Hormone related I guess. Otherwise some people would be wanking 24/7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will always wonder if Eddie just waited 1 more minute, if Conor would go past his danger 8 minute mark and suddenly drain like against Diaz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People saying Eddie would be aroun 180lbs.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Android app recommendations for learning to drive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 11:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot in the Google store, and I don't trust their ratings. I wonder if any of you have used one and care to recommend it. I don't mind paying a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrested near Barcelona a moroccan man driving a car filled with official uniforms and weapons from the police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 10:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is from a disney costume, bought through the official Disney store. It is a toy from last years Disney star wars movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good old days (7 months ago) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much promo did she do on her own ? 

Conor and Ronda did a lot of promo on her own before being famous. I don't follow Ronda but Conor is still super active. He even do the mac life web log   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking shit about someone you have beaten in a fair fight in 40 seconds is crap. This is not feel, but being a bad person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 10:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> big benefit is that with a new 3ds you can increase the cpu speed. this will drain your battery, but games will load faster and show higher FPS. You can do this when you are at home and have AC connected </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didnt look that good against Valentina though. She gassed, and she just did enough to win  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  when did this huge skill level rise happen in wmma? 

Agree. Nunes was fighting before her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "she was just first" LOL Nunes was fighting before her IDIOT.

Ronda was as good as it was just a year and a half ago. With a proper camp she can be great again. She is not even 30! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is funny hearing Dana speaking in a serious way about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 19:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your "true cost" do you factor all the profits ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 14:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. My only point is that he didn't go to a better team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Or TJ moving to Elevation to continue to train with Duane.

I actually don't think that's a good example of fighter moving camps. AFAIK he moved to elevation because he was getting paid, and because Duane was there. He lost his belt on his first fight there.

Plus TAM is a legit camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://mmadecisions.com/decision/7244/Conor-McGregor-vs-Nate-Diaz

It is pretty much accepted by everyone that Conor won that fight. Only 1 journalist gave it to Diaz, 4 to draw, and 13 to Conor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if Holly wins she fights Nunes next and they kill the division.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 00:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nunes battered Zingano in the 1st

it was GnP though, completely unrelated to stand up striking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 00:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nunes won round 1. Zigano round 2. Zigano TKO round 3. I watched that fight the other day.

Nunes couldn't hit anything against Zigano, and the fight was basically decided on the TDs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 23:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zigano won the striking against Nunes. The only thing she could do was grapple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 23:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that is false. It is like saying that Conor only has a left hand, and disregarding everything else. or that DC can only grapple.

She has 3 wins by TKO/KO, punches or knee. She is not only a "arm bar machine". her problem is not being "uni dimensional", but having a 0 game plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 12:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A woman in her 20s has discovered that her beloved partner has been having online sex with porn stars. Mariella Frostrup says she is right to worry"

Basically the story is a lie because that woman in her 20s doesn't exist. The crappy columnism uses the story to talk about prostituion and the rights of sex workers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 10:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this has been reposted 1000 times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me a year where the winner didn't win any team trophy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 16:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I hate Real Madrid, this is revisionist hipster bullshit.

No way Pele would have won over Di Stefano. Basically on 1959 Di Stefano won the now known as Champions League. Pele won nothing. It was the fourth UCL for Di Stefano in a row. he was arguably the bigger star in Europe. Pele is known for his role with Brazil NT, Di Stefano is known for his role with Brazil, and that year there was no WC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 16:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barcelona had to sell him to inter to pay Camp Nou, and basically we sucked during the 60s for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 16:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bullshit. She is only 29. In a real team, with a real coach and a good camp, and some tune up fights, she can be champion again.

People is now speaking like if Nunes is GSP, or if Ronda just got overtaken by newer fighters. Ronda and nunes are almost the same age, and fought at the same time. Nunes lost against 2 girls ronda won easy.

Ronda can be champ again if she changes camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 23:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emery, Benitez, Cuper, Ranieri,.... all of them fired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 23:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the difference is that Flo has unlimited funds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and go back to what? because the situation before was the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> meanwhile Alcacer in our bench doing nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am using a laptop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only cancel it. no option to upgrade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 month. if you are from the UK 2 days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how do I do it? I dont see the option to upgrade </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biggest thing ever happened to the division is tj vs barao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is already a legend (woman GOAT) and she is rich, plus all the money she will get tomorow. if she loses again, she wont headline a PPV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if she loses again she is done, and we don't have an event like this in a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conor's "you should have killed me when you had chance" was epic.

vid: https://youtu.be/OOVj1Zkj55M?t=1468 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how many times do they actually answer the question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this was instead Nunes vs Pena, it would be at most a FSN1 card and I would care 0.

I dislike Ronda, but she makes this more interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 00:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why? at least she makes the division interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 23:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> by girls ronda beat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are on such a tiny budget good luck sleeping in NYC, unless you go to the cheapest hostel with bed bugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 16:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im surprised. in my experience cex is super expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sage was shooting, he was rocked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he made weight using jeans, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This conversation started because someone before said that "microsoft and sony are legitimate videogame companies, as opposed to Nintendo".

My point is that they are just money investors, while Nintendo does actually produce videogames. The full cycle in - house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 19:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First party because they bought the studio or the IP just because they were making already good games. That's not making games, that's investing money, very different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 19:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kojima was working for Konami, and they were making games like MGS before Sony was around.

Your sentence about Xbox makes no sense, and even then based on what you say they are just porting pc games into xbox. That doesnt make them a "videogame" company.

I am 31 years old, been playing videgames since I am 5. Do you know the last 2 games I have finished? Majora's Mask and Pokemon. Meanwhile I also play Dota2 (where I have around 1000h of game). If you like videogames, you like Nintendo games. The myth about them doing games for kids if false. Majora's mask is an example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hit him in the temple. Sage seems to have a shitty chin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if they hired them, isnt then the game developed by valve? it is basically the only logo you see when you open the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Valve literally don't make games anymore, how'd they prove anything? 

Dota2 7.00 which is basically a new game got released 2 weeks ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sony and Microsoft are legitimate video game companies. 

what? Nintendo makes better videogames than Sony or Microsoft. Mostly everything in those companies are third parties or studios they bought. Sony is an electronic comic, while Microsoft focuses on OS and office software. They are just investors into the videogames world. Nintendo is a real videogame company.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 15:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Sage got dropped by a lucky punch. Gall was not even looking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 22:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes. especially in Europe, alone, 2am. fuck it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 21:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rogan said it. In the canvas only. They use some kind of spray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what they do nowadays ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 minutes for fights no matter what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Continuing with your bro math, Superbowl did 100m viewers with 5m for 30s ads. Because UFC Conor would do 50m virwers, that's 2.5m for 30s. But obviously that'd only be when Donor fights. Just for the four round breaks (8 slots) they'd get 20 millions. Add around 10 more slots for intros, walk in, introducton, post fight. It'd easily go for a total of 50m </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They paint the blood too btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much money a fox McGregor fight would generate ? Like how much would they charge for 10s of ads (plus all the exposure ).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gimp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think another cinema is needed. Cineworld options are sometimes limited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 14:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry don't know why you meant woodley  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 13:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, last 2:30, and Woodley couldn't stand up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 01:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woodley couldn't take rory down. In fact rory took him down instead.

Rory TDD is leagues above wonderboy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 00:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is low in the rankings because he's lost a lot and he has never had a good run. His best run was 3 wins in a row right when he started ages ago.

He is loved by mans because his fights are amazing, and he is a very exciting guy to watch. You know that a fight with him will deliver.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 22:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> basically what Wonderboy could do if he had great take down defense. Rory can pressure and throw without risk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 21:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Including Woodley  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 21:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He could just remove the nose cartilage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were the ufc I'd do the same. How much Amanda has sold the fight ? Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 12:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you hate Android?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 12:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why you don't like Android? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? Do you think it will be any different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to see MM vs Benavidez again. I strongly disagree with triologies when they are 2-0 already, especially considering how the second fight went.

A fighter needs to realiaze about this, and move up (or down when possible) like Dodson did. My interest on seeing MM vs Benavidez again is 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus they don't have total power anymore. So whatever he says is random crap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Jimmy case" (Deportivo fan killed by Atletico supporers) closed without culprits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romario was also there the last year, which was amazing. That team is known in Barcelona as "Dream Team". They won 4 leagues in a row. Before that Barcelona had only won around 10 leagues in 50 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have problems with my elbow. Even when I'm not playing . only the right one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early 90s football was not as global as it is nowadays. 

I'm not saying Pep is better, but if he where to play nowadays he'd be as famous as Xavi or Iniesta  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impossible to compare. Pep played in the same position as Sergio Busquets although he was a bit more offensive. Like a Xavi but playing 20 meters behind. 

No matter how good Busquets is he will never shine as much as someone who plays in the 10 position. 

That said, yeah, Zidane was better. He also played in much better teams. And pep won the first UCL with FCB ever, so that's quite an achievement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Koeman with Barcelona ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Barcelona fans. He is a legend here. He scored the FK that gave us our first UCL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guardiola is also a all time legend. One of the best pure midfielders ever. He won the first FCB champions league. 

He is not as food as Zidane, but anyone who was following football during the 90s knows about him. I'd put him in the same level as Pirlo or Xavi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These maps are really bad. I'm also Spanish. In Aragon you only need Spanish. Only in the border with Catalunya some of them speak Catalan, but mostly Spanish. 

North of Aragon and catalunya is also very green, around the Pyrenees.

You would fail a geography test. The 2 mesetas are really flat and you ignore them. Catalunya is not flat, Barcelona is surrounded by mountains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 11:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been reported from the police themselves. The big red flag is that he tried to go to Siria to join Isis but he was bounced back by Turkey. From that point on he was carefully followed. He got the truck and the route to transport from Germany to Spain, and he got caught the moment he entered Spain. 

He is from Morocco, so he is not a refugee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spanish police stopped a similar terrorist attack as in Nice or Berlin from a suspicious and Interpol reported truck driver who entered Spain driving from Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 10:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 10:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The government already has that db. Id cards don't contain that much information: name , address, dob , POB. If you think your government doesn't already know that ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers demonstrate here that the mere subjective experience of being lower in socioeconomic status relative to others is alone sufficient to causally elicit behaviors that may risk obesity, independent of actual economic deprivation or stress from being subordinated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 12:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers believe that the unique sound of Stradivarius instruments may have arisen from a secret anti-woodworm treatment applied by the master-luthier. Stradivaris use of mineral-treated maples belonged to a forgotten tradition. His maple also appeared to be transformed by aging and vibration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 11:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have found that children with a genetic risk for obesity had greater activity in brain reward centers when watching fast food commercials. The study is the first-of-its kind to examine how a key obesity gene influences brain response to food advertisements. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 11:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers are now able to zap antimatter atoms with a laser, precisely measure the light let off by these anti-atoms. By comparing the light from anti-atoms with the light from regular atoms, they hope to answer one of the big mysteries how antimatter lose out to regular old matter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new protein pathway found in multiple types of cancer has been uncovered, which shows that mitochondria may play an important role in tumor progression. Mitochondria was previously thought to not influence the progression of cancer tumors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 17:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's fault </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 15:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crop spray which can boost farmer's wheat yields by one fifth, without the need for genetic modification, has been developed at Oxford University. They found a molecule which helps plants make the best use of the sugary fuel that they generate during photosynthesis, producing bigger grains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 10:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research team found households in rural Africa that vaccinate their cattle for East Coast fever increased their income and spent the additional money on food and education. They also found that when fewer cattle died from the fever, girls were more likely to attend secondary school. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 10:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police are appealing for information after a 26-year-old woman was kicked down a set of subway stairs by a man in Berlin, Germany, in October. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 13:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU outlines benefits reforms delayed by Brexit vote: Economically inactive (non nationals) people would, however, not be able to claim social security benefits abroad, setting out that freedom of movement of workers is not a full right to reside for everyone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 11:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers demonstrated that fearful imaginings about the future can be inhibited by neural mechanisms that help to suppress the past. Importantly, suppression reduces later apprehensiveness about the feared events, a benefit that was diminished in individuals with greater trait anxiety. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 10:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Childhood poverty in a prospective, longitudinal design is linked to deficits in adult memory; greater psychological distress, including a behavioral marker of helplessness; and elevated levels of chronic physiological stress. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even with maximized yields, sub-Saharan Africa won't grow enough grain in 2050 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experimental drug that blocks the activation of an immune cell component effectively prevented rejection of heart transplants in mice. The findings describe a compound that inhibits cellular structures called immunoproteasomes while sparing closely related structures called constitutive proteasomes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 11:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery molecule is a key to inhibiting colon cancer. Immunologists have discovered that a protein called NLRC3 plays a central role in inhibiting colon cells from becoming cancerous. Researchers found that deleting the protective NLRC3 protein exacerbates colon cancer development. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 11:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aldo vs Conor multicam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 01:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Choi vs Cub was the Fight of the Year, but the first round of Villante vs Safarov on Friday was also amazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A youtuber "pranks" people by insulting them, until one of them slaps him in the face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 13:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study shows how mobile money lifts Kenyan households out of poverty. Greater access to services raises daily spending, especially among female-headed households. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New diabetes treatment could eliminate need for insulin injections: tested in mice, therapy involves a capsule of genetically engineered cells implanted under the skin that release insulin as required </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers report that four distinct populations of killifish, living in four Superfund sites on the East Coast, have separately and rapidly evolved a genetic adaptation that allows them to survive in severely contaminated waters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neuroscientists have discovered that the activity of certain neurons in a deep region of the mouse brain can be manipulated to induce the animal to under- or overestimate the duration of a fixed time interval. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 12:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoolgate with Yoel Romero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pepe and Coentrao sold their image rights for 1 euro to a Panama company </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 12:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research using satellite images shows that syrian rivers are overflowing into Jordan now that syrian people have left its own country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 11:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New discovery shows that paleo diet was heavy plant based and had less meat than what modern cookbooks suggest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 11:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Rangers became Espanyol fans second team </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odegaard's dad didn't want to use the fiscal cheats Real Madrid offered him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 14:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odegaard's dad didn't want to accept the fiscal cheats Real Madrid offered him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 14:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New neighbour chilling out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 12:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who leaked TUF winner months ago? (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 12:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fastest room (cm, stock,...) for a Moto G 4G first gen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running at the moment CM 7.1 and I'm not very happy. The phone lags a lot. I just tried to use google maps and it was quite horrible.

The phone came with 4.4 and as far as I remember it was recently fast. Then it updated to 5.x (the auto update from Motorola) and everything started to go downhill. So I installed CM 6.x which I have been running for a while, but I was not 100% happy, and now with 7.1 I feel it goes even worse.

I don't know if I should just buy a new phone . the phone is 2.5 years old so it is above its 2 years cycle. But I don't know if any room (or even going back to stock 4.4) will make it lag less. That is my priority, speed over features.

Thanks ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anything Christmas-y to do apart from the christmas market? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 14:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering if you know anything. In particular for this Friday. I will go to Glasgow market (I will also go to Edinburgh, in case you know anything there).

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to add text to video, and the ouput only shows the final text, video never plays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a project like this:

http://imgur.com/a/zFS4A

The 3D scene was just created it only contains a 2D text. it should play for 2 seconds, and then the video, but instead the text plays for the whole video. Even if I remove the text, then it will just be a greish video window, and the video I am trying to load never plays.

I need to close Blender, and add the video from fresh, but from the moment I play with a camera, my video is gone.

I am new to blender, so I guess there is something I am missing.

In the preview everything looks fine, and when I move my mouse around, the video looks fine. But when I click render, the output file will only contain the text.

I have also set the background of the text scene to transparent, and same behaviour.

Even If I remove that text scene, and then move the video to the start, then from that point on only that text scene will play. See:

http://imgur.com/a/JWzRE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I copy a video strip from one opened Blender into another? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a meta strip, which is a video, with some text, and speed up. I want to re-use this into another project, but I have no idea how to do it.

thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is Tim Elliot winning the last TUF fight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Left my parents house 6+ years ago. I don't know if I should sell the guitars I have there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been playing the guitar for 15+ years, and I left my parents house more than 6 years ago. While I was living (until my mid twenties) I had a tiny collection of guitars (4, I had some others which I sold). My parents haven't complained about the space, and I don't really need the money (and the guitars don't have much value, apart from the sentimental one to me).

So probably most people would say "don't sell them". The thing is that I live more than 2000km away, in a different country. I only go home for holidays, which is a few days a year, and I rarely play the guitars then. On the other hand, I have with me now a guitar, so I've got that covered. Some might say "bring them with you". I studied this. On one hand it is very expensive to send them or bring them with me in the plane, on the other hand I don't really have space at the moment, and as said, I already have a guitar with me which is the one I play.

The reason why I am thinking about selling them is because I feel bad I haven't use them in 6 years, and I don't foresee using them any time in the future. it can go to maybe 10-15 years, and they will just stay put in a closet.

The guitars I have in my house are:

* My first spanish guitar. I bought it 15 years ago for like 50 euros (back then in pesetas). It has 0 value, I am going to bin it next time I am home.

*  My first electric guitar. The brand is "kohler", which was a spanish brand for electric guitars. Very nice wood body (looks exactly like this one: http://cdn.wallapop.com/shnm-portlet/images?pictureId=83835508 pictureSize=W320) sadly when I was a teenager I put some stickets, and I never managed to fully remove them. I played this guitar to death, so the frets have clear signs of usage. This guitar has a very high sentimental value to me, and it helped me going through those shitty times everyone goes through when you are 16. I bought it for like 100 euros, plus the stickers and frets, probably has a very low value now. The only thing is that I put a bridge DiMarzio X2N, so that is basically the value of the guitar.

*  The first guitar I bought with my own money after working a few months in a call fender. A telecaster MiM from 2005, color daphne blue. The strap did some damage on the side of the guitar, and the jack for the cable gives problems. At most I could sell this guitar for 200 euros, but I put to it Lindy Fralin Blues Special pickups, so that would probably put the value up to like 300 euros.

* A good spanish guitar Alhambra 7Fc (cypress body, this is a flamenco guitar). This is the one in better shape. Google throws prices from 800 to 1200 euros.http://cdn.wallapop.com/shnm-portlet/images?pictureId=83835508 pictureSize=W320

So yeah, most would say "don't sell them, not enough money value". I just feel bad they are never used, and they will probably never be.

I have been thinking about this for a long time, and I need some advice

Thanks for listening!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Left my parents house 6+ years ago. I don't know if I should sell the guitars I have there </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why recently in every popular thread the top comment is a sticky from the moderators patronizing the user base? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How am I supposed to play Majora's Mask? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played Ocarina back in the day on my N64, and it is my favourite game ever. So as soon as I got a 3DS I wanted to get a MM.

I just finished the first temple and I am loving and hating it, but the hate is growing strong. I don't know if I am doing something intrinsically wrong. Maybe I am missing something.

Basically I hate the 3 day limit. I feel it limits a lot my exploration / free roaming (which is something I love in Zelda games), and I am just rushing everything. I am not really enjoying the game, it is more stressful than anything. The first temple, which I just did, was super easy. The only difficult part was doing it on time.

So far 3 times I ran out of time, so I had to play the song to go back in time, which means I lose every item, so collecting stuff seems pointless. Even worse, I need to re-do a lot of stuff, and having to do things twice every time is very annoying.

Second time I was going through the temple (because I ran out of time before, and I didnt want to have to repeat everything again), I had to check a guide (something I had to do) because otherwise I wouldnt be able to finish the game. I killed the boss (very easy) and then there was the cutscene and I got the pricess, but oh well I ran out of time, so I had to play the song to go back, and book, Ive lost everything, including the princess, so I had to go back to the temple, and this time it let me fight direclty with the boss.

So I don't know if I am doing something wrong. I understand you can go back to the start, and you can tp to places where the owl is, but then you seem to lose any progress done. Is this how the game is supposed to be played? Do I have to repeat everything 2-3 times until I memorize the right sequence to do it in time? I really really hope I am doing something wrong and that I am missing some big part of the gameplay.

thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monkey experiments showed low status alters the immune system in a way that raises the risk of heart disease, diabetes and mental health problems. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 11:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man spends a fortune on a horse that is supposed to be an amazing stallion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A man spends a fortune on a horse that is supposed to be an amazing stallion. He is told the horse will impregnate 20-30 fermale horses.

He brings the horse to his farm, but the horse is not doing anything, just sleeping and eating grass all day.

Some time after he meets with an old friend, and explains the story. The friend replies:

- The same happened to me, I bought a horse that was supposed to be an amazing stallion, but he won't do anything, so I bought him a syrup drug that he is drinking every day, and from that day on he is impregnating 20-30 females a day.

So the lazy horse owner asks: 

- Do you remember the name of the syrup?

To which his friend answer:

- I don't remember, but it has a kind of mint taste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone playing Dota2 using Linux/Vulkan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 13:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My CPU is an i5-3740s, and my GPU is an Nvidia GTX 750 TI. My OS is Arch Linux, and I am using the Nvidia drivers.

I have been playing Dota2 in my computer for years using Linux. I stopped playing for a while, and when I came back I set the launch options to Vulkan because people were reporting higher framerates. At the same time, I upgraded from a FX6100 to the i5 as said.

It happened to me then in every game than around the 38-42 minute mark the game would go to hell, and the framerate would drop by a lot. I needed to kill the game and restart it, and everything was then fine.

I asked this before in this subreddit, and some people suggested overheating issues, so I tracked it. The CPU never goes above 40-45 degrees, while the GPU never goes above 45-50 degrees, so nothing is really overheating, and I cannot hear the fans going stronger because the temperatures are always low. Before the games goes to hell the FPS is stable at 60 (I have vsync enabled, otherwise it goes to 100-120). And the drop in FPS is very sudden. It goes instatly from 60 to 5-10.

Yesterday I changed from vulkan to standard (which I think it is OpenGL), and the game went well. So I assume there is some problem with Vulkan that makes the game go crazy around the 40 minutes mark.

I wonder if anyone has any experience to share. So far I will keep the standard launch options. No idea if this is a problem with linux / nvidia / my graphic card
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone playing Dota2 using Vulkan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 13:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My CPU is an i5-3740s, and my GPU is an Nvidia GTX 750 TI. My OS is Arch Linux, and I am using the Nvidia drivers.

I have been playing Dota2 in my computer for years. I stopped playing for a while, and when I came back I set the launch options to Vulkan because people were reporting higher framerates. At the same time, I upgraded from a FX6100 to the i5 as said.

It happened to me then in every game than around the 38-42 minute mark the game would go to hell, and the framerate would drop by a lot. I needed to kill the game and restart it, and everything was then fine.

I asked this before in the Dota2 subreddit, and some people suggested overheating issues, so I tracked it. The CPU never goes above 40-45 degrees, while the GPU never goes above 45-50 degrees, so nothing is really overheating, and I cannot hear the fans going stronger because the temperatures are always low.

Yesterday I changed from vulkan to standard (which I think it is OpenGL), and the game went well. So I assume there is some problem with Vulkan that makes the game go crazy around the 40 minutes mark.

I wonder if anyone has any experience to share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CM 14.1 Notifications wake up screen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to stop the notifications from waking up the screen, but I don't know how to do it. I have disabled everything in "settings notifications", but at the moment when I receive a text or something the screen will flash for a few seconds. It doesnt show anything, just the clock. I also had to stop the white led, which I would like to continue using.

I don't know how I had it set-up in CM13, but I would like a similar set-up, where the screen is never woke up, but the white led flashes, and then once I start the screen I can see the pending notifications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disabled Barcelona fan needs to go to the games in a toddler's pram because from this season the club is not keeping wheelchairs anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 10:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huge fixing scandal in spanish "3 divisin" (4th tier) involving chinese on-line betting websites (e.g 27 corner kicks in 45min) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 12:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthony Randolph amazing block in the spanish league </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 12:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glasgow city council website - constantly getting "Internal server error" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just registered to pay my council tax. I registered to 2 things, one of them a Santander bill payment thing, the other one my profile in the Glasgow Council website. 

The santander thing works fine, but the Glasgow council website fails continously giving me a "500 - Internal server error". Once registered I could go to my profile, set up my council tax and see the amount I need to pay. Then I had to login again, and I was getting that error all the time, only once 10 minutes ago I could see my dashboard again, but it logs out very fast somehow, and then everytime I am seeing the same error. No idea if it is because I am typing my password wrong (I dont think so), or the security question answer. I don't know if this is normal, if their server is going wrong, or if I am doing something wrong.

This happens both in Firefox and Chrome, and in both cases I am trying incognito mode, because my default browser profile goes directly to that 500 error.

Any experience with this? What I am doing wrong?

thanks!

EDIT: The error I am getting all the time looks like this:

Server Error

500 - Internal server error.

There is a problem with the resource you are looking for, and it cannot be displayed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A group of researchers have developed a new material that can be used to turn waste heat into electricity. This technology could allow power plants to recycle their waste heat and save money, while reducing our fossil fuel consumption and helping the environment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 11:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Linux with Nvidia. My game goes to hell every time around the 40 minutes mark. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the last 2-3 months, I cannot really remember, my game goes to hell and the FPS drops to like 5 (otherwise it is stable at 60), always around the 40 minute mark. I don't have the exact time point, but it is between 38-42, and it happens in every game. I need to close the game and join the match again, and then it works fine.

I have archlinux, an Nvidia gti 750, nvidia drivers.

I have always played Dota2 in Linux and it has always been good. I don't know what it going on. I have been ignoring this for a while, but the last game I played we lost because this just happen when we were pushing high ground in a very even game, it was my fault that fight was 4v5, and when I could reconnent we were all dead and they were pushing to win.

The fact that it always happens at the same moment leds me to believe it is some problem with Dota2 and not with my drivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good places for a graduation/Chritmas dinner in Glasgow or outside of it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to organize a graduation dinner for the first week of December. Because everywhere will be doing Christmas dinners, I assume I will book that instead. We will only be 3 people, so it is not for a big group. I don't care much about the budget as long as it is not crazy (like I assume around 30 pounds per person can be decent, and we don't drink alcohol, so there won't be bottles of moet and chandon)

I know most of the common places around the west end, I also know some other plays like the three sisters, or 2 fat ladies. That's why I am more interested in places outside Glasgow. Anywhere as long as it is a 30-40 minute drive. It is usually cheaper and better. I have been for example in the Struther farmhouse which was simply amazing, and I wonder if anyone knows more places like that.

In any case, any recommendation is good! And I don't care much about the style of food. European/british/curry... anything can work.

thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study shows that an experimental drug can reverse the effects of cells that prevent the body's immune system from attacking tumors. This could lift the brakes that the body imposes on the immune system's T cells to unleash an attack on cancer cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study found that the Indian Ocean's Agulhas Current is getting wider rather than strengthening. The findings suggest that intensifying winds in the region may be increasing the turbulence of the current, rather than increasing its flow rate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find that amnesia caused by cannabis use starts in the mitochondria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have developed the world's thinnest photodetector. With a thickness of just 1.3 nanometers - 10 times smaller than the current standard silicon diodes -- this device could be used in the Internet of Things, smart devices, wearable electronics and photoelectronics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grades and achievement tests are generally better predictors of life outcomes than pure measures of intelligence like IQ test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 11:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By 2040 with a 2 C warming more than 90% of coastal areas will experience sea level rise exceeding the global estimate of 0.2 m, with up to 0.4 m expected along the Atlantic coast of North America and Norway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For blacks in America, the gap in neighborhood poverty has declined faster than segregation. This resulted primarily from narrowing differences between blacks and whites as opposed to narrowing differences between blacks and Hispanics or blacks and Asians. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spanish kids (14 and 15 yo) fighting in organized illegal street fights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UFC coming back to Glasgow (31 Jan) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 14:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers have designed and created an electrically controlled ion pump able to deliver neurotransmitters at close to the same speed as live neurons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 11:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers found that Facebook users who accept more friendships have a lower risk of mortality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 16:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next Clasico game between Barcelona and Real Madrid will be this 3rd of December at 4:15pm local time in order to appeal to the chinese viewership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone hack my 3DS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought yesterday a new nintendo 3DS XL (it was a mistake to get the XL, too big for me, but anyway...)

My firmware is 11.0.0.33, as far as I can read, the only way to hack it is using another already hacked 3DS. My problem is that I dont know anyone with 1. I don't mind paying if there's an "specialized" person who can do it.

thanks ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lately I am losing every 5v4 game I am playing (being me the 5 team). Has anything changed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 19:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing this forum people is probably going to make fun of me, "loser how can you lose against 4", but it has happened to me like 3 times in the last 2 weeks (I don't play that much).

In my experience 5v4 was always an easy game. You need to throw very hard to lose it.

Also, I almost always play as support, and in all the games I lost vs 4 I was a support.

The last game I lost this way was yesterday, I was SS. They had meepo, doom, sven. I warded their jungle and our SB destroyed doom and meepo with charges from everything. Around the 25 minute mark the score was something like 20-5 in our favour, and we were destroying their towers and I thought it was going to be a fast an easy game. When the game finished I saw that the exp and gold graph was basically flat.

We lost a fight, I don't remember exactly how, and they came back hardcore. Next time I saw Sven I was level 13 I think, and he was already 19, and killed me in 2-3 attacks. From now on, they just completely destroyed us, all of them had like 5 level advatatge and almost 6 slotted very fast.

Just going through my dotabuff I can see a very similar game, we were destroying them, but the graphs were flat, they manage to get a few kills, get some space, and they steamrolled out of control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has there been TUF this last 2 weeks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 14:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transplanted neurons act like the normal cells lost to brain damage. Researchers discovered that the transplanted neurons matured quickly, achieving adult like densities of dendritic spines and axonal boutons within four to eight weeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 11:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New paper shows how diamonds can be harnessed to store data for the long term. Right now, a tiny diamond can hold a hundred times more information than a DVD. But in the future physicists could access a diamond with storage capacity a million times greater than that of a DVD. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 11:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neonatal isolation augments social dominance by altering actin dynamics in the medial prefrontal cortex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 11:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will handheld consoles every be on par in terms of power with stationary consoles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 13:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racist thug hits man in face with plank of wood after hearing his Spanish accent and screaming 'speak English' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 19:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New research suggests that babies are highly selective in whom they will pay attention to. And even before their first birthdays, this research shows, babies distinguish between people like me and all others. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 19:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
