<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A built in timer would be nice. Also some like a notes list or technique references. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there AMD. I'm not all that keen with tech but this 480 seems like a game changer. How do you guys think it will influence GPU's in the future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Gordon. I am a young culinary student in highschool and I have my heart set on going to either the CIA or Johnson and Wales. What is your opinion on those two schools?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea but I'm looking for more tools then I found. Not so much recipes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 11:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever your planning on doing, you probably shouldn't be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of any good apps for a culinary enthusiast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 11:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 00:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a sata to USB dongle and plug it in. Right click on the windows icon and go to disk manager. Reformat whatever you want there. Then instead of copying the old hdd I would use the dongle and just manualy transfer everything you wanna keep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 08:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it rly matter that much if they die </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [discussion] what are your favorite cooking shows to learn from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 08:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm new to the game. What's the best way to make some money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 07:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 07:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to the game. I don't really understand snitches, can you explain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 07:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solved! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 06:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ thanks that's it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][SONG] please help me find this Slowdance song I'm going crazy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 06:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three chord song with the chord progression of 11-2-333333 11-2-333333 pretty sure it's accoustic. Definetly pretty polular, guessing from the 60's to the 80's. Good song for prom/wedding slowdance. Kinda classic rock kinda folk kinda country idk. From what I remember it reminds me of the way you look tonight by claptopn. Thanks yall! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SONG][TOMT] Slowdance song. Please help I'm going crazy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 06:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 22:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't buy it build your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 07:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea just 6500 not 6500k sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Small question. Planning my first pc. Should I spring for a i56600k with a stock cooler or a 6500k with a aftermarket cooler? Will not be overclocking. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 07:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks yall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 06:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to pc... Is that a joke or does it really come with an upgrade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 05:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea probably. $350 is cutting it a little close though. Save up a little and hop on pcpartpicker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [help] I'm kinda a beginner, but I want to make my own music. Is there any good free software I can use to mix tracks into a song so I can play 2 different parts? Thanks! (pc btw) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 05:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 04:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally would save up a bit first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 04:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeppers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 14:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There might be dust in your port. You can ide compressed air to clean that. You might have also bent the port, inside your pc. That can happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 19:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mod devs or cs devs really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 00:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally the more heavy cream you use the softer it stays. For your purposes ide probably use 1 cup sugar 1+cup cream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do yall get your ROM's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 22:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 19:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1072 thanks op' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best site to download ROMs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 05:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 05:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] I'm new to RetroPie. Where do I go to download all the roms I want safely, and what do I do with them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 05:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love ya bro. Viva la pcmr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 15:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A suction cup dildo on each point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 04:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope I checked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] Been playing for several hundred hours. New city has no people or cars whatsoever. Not a problem with the map (Cars where there for first few minutes and its a popular map). What the hell is going on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 04:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 21:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 562 for mirrors edge. Thanks bud! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 21:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 462 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] I need a portable micro amp under $70. Should I go with the Marshall MS4 or the Blackstar Fly3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 13:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can stream well but I would always stay away from hdmi pass through ports. Unless it's built for streaming, like the benq hdmi passthrough, it will have latency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 06:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for being newb. Just a student in highschool culinary. I just don't understand the coralation between this dark roux you are talking about and gumbo. Is it because you need that flavor for the gumbo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am obsessed with that game. If you don't win just buy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saints row: the third. It's old and its dirty, but it's a damn good game. Hours of laughs and action. It's $5 but I would pay full price for it. My favorite game. I also like advanced warfare :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 06:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 632 thanks OP! Viva la PCMR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 06:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to get Rocket League. Your a true hero OP. Peace and Viva la PCMR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 06:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7:23 in morning. Thanks op. Hope you like your new job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PCMReddiquette(?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 05:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear PCMR, I am fairly new to the masterrace, but I love it and I think the community is great. Many a meme and much news has been shared. We have posted news and ideas and participated in great banter. We are a glorious race, however, I feel we are not being very appreciative towards each other. I think if we are going to be the best technologically, there is no reason we cant exceed socially. Thus I think this issue should be addressed. 

All I am trying to say is our habit of daily giveaways is great, and it would be great if more people said thank you and gave a nice up-vote too, to show our appreciation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] PCMR Family, our upvote to comment ratio on giveaways is horrible! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 05:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love you guys... Have some games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 04:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I had a bad day, and I have a few extra keys. It's about time I give back to you wonderful sons of bitches again and really need a pick me up so woot woot giveaway time. 

Want a key? Great! Pick a number between 0-300 and I'll pm a few of you keys in about an hour or two. 

Viva pcmr. Shalom yall.


[Giveaway Over] I hope the few of you who won ( u/GreedyRichguy u/pnair7 u/MushroomPlanet have a good time with your games. For those of you who wrote a little few words, thank you. Have a good one PCMR. Peace out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 04:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 337 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
