<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8219</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im the UK Spice is fucking up a generation. New psychoactive substances in general. That shit is evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God yeah man. Mitsubishis in 1997. Mind blowing love and visuals to die for. Listening to some deep trance. Eyes rolled. Hearts swelled. Hugs were given! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Methamphetamine addiction. Its about 14 years later and ive never been the same since.

The massive dose of mushrooms that ended a 15 year ride with psychedelics. Id taken plenty of acid, and that year  i had been taking regular and increasingly strong doses of Cubensis. One night I was just reckless and took a large unmeasured dose. It blew my mind. Made a damn lot of changes in my life after it.  But never took psychedelics again. The way I explain it to people is this. I saw what I had always been searching for.

It sounds stupid to people in general. But I saw the light at the centre of the universe. The all seeing all consuming presence. I had left a religion i was raised in. And had pretty much been lost for a long time in constant drug abuse. Im not saying this experience made me religious again, but I felt a presence that was godly. It was beautiful. And it felt safe.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shrooms were always more fun than acid in my experience. Shrooms feel more natural, last for a more enjoyable and manageable amount of time and have less of a head fuck.

With both though it's always the same "set and setting" that make for a safe trip.

Just look after yourself. I did a lot of shrooms a long time ago and ended up a mess! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The strongest i ever had, God knows the dose. All i know was the floor was a rainbow. Musical notes poured out of my mouth and the cosmos hung in the air. After the peak i tried to make a butty but the ham was dancing in the fridge so I gave up and went and led in my bed. For 8 hours i watched things on the ceiling like it was a tv. Visions that were divine and mesmerising and also some dark shit.

I was awake all night. The next morning my mum came in my room and told me my grandad had died. Worst come down ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 08:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic breasts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love dr phil. He is a walrus of love.

What does he smell like ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does help! I am pretty well educated in general, I have a degree and a few other qualifications, there just doesn't seem to be many opportunities around where I live though...


The thing that I feel trapped by is i cant afford to earn less than i do, I'm living month to month as it is, and don't know how to start afresh without starting at the bottom of a new ladder... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats good advice! Thank you!

My problem is I feel trapped. I live on my own i have two kids and a job that I'm enjoying less each day  I feel stressed and depressed. I dont earn a lot of money (15-20k) id just love to do something I enjoy....with the possibility of progressing to earn more in the future.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you go about changing careers when you are mid thirties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a shitty world we live in sometimes. Why couldn't the cunt just kill himself and leave the baby alone. Never mind live streaming his vile act.

I actually object to facebook live for the below reason - 

It encourages narcissistic shit. Seriously i see absolute twats who genuinely believe other people need to see their nights out or boring life events. Its literally always assholes that love themselves using it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the UK. Its been snowing and hailing today in April. There is literally no good time to visit the UK based on weather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My early life progressed like this...

14-18 smoking cannabis daily
18-22 taking amphetamine daily
18-30 taking ecstasy, coke regularly
Sporadically the entire time taking shrooms and acid
Chuck in random sideline addictions of benzo, codeine, nicotine, bouts of alcoholism....

My entire formative years revolved around drugs. It was literally all i surrounded myself with. All the people I was involved with took drugs. I was obsessed with anything drug related. I thought I was some cool counter culture rebel. In truth I was a fucked up drug addict who was masking a million and one issues from my childhood.

Whilst ill talk at length about mind blowing experiences i had on psychedelics and crazy times at festivals and raves. The truth is, inside i was so unhappy and lonely. In the year I was 18 i tried seriously to kill myself twice (thankfully I survived). I am 36 and my arms are full of the scars where I would cut myself just to feel something. 

I left drugs behind. I then turned to abusing alcohol. Getting drunk every night. Id sleep in a stupor. 

Fast forward to now.  I'm mid thirties. I dont take drugs. I drink about twice a year, I smoke cigarettes which I want to quit, but in general I am making it through life sober. I did it all with the help of the woman I love.

I dont regret my past. But I don't like the damage i did to myself mentally. I live in a state of almost permanent anxiety that holds me back.

I still feel depressed most of the time to be honest. I struggle to cope. But I do.

Id advise anyone that is young and starting taking drugs, to just maybe consider pursuing other things. I've seen my best friends turn into fuck ups. People end up in prison and dead. Its real life. And no amount of thinking you are invincible can ever protect you from shit you might carry within.

Im sorry to go on!



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really disappointed with this one. Yes it's free. But like every other long term gamer ive played hundreds of hours and have a right to opinion.

Its just a bit boring to be honest... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to sneak out of parties when I was in my late teens and go home to game (introvert, I hated parties)...

Id get home still wired off ecstasy, cannabis or acid. Id go to my bedroom with drinks and blankets and sit and play silent hill. I swear I lived that terror in the game. Looking at the game now, the graphics are shit. But after an all nighter that game scared me shitless.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose it's rose tinted hindsight. I had some epic experiences when I was young. Like the time i took a large dose of LSD at a festival and had some insane visuals....the first time I took Ecstasy and felt the love, first few times I took crystal amphetamine and stayed awake for days, first time on mushrooms...

I guess it's being young and carefree enough to do those things that I miss. Now, real life, just seems like one long conveyor belt of routines...think I'm a bit depressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex drug users... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It never leaves you...those experiences stay with you forever! Good and bad.

It must be 8 years since I touched a drug. The last experience I had was a mind blowing mushroom trip. And since then its like i just never wanted to again.

But often, like daily i find myself thinking about the old times, endless nights sat up high as a kite, insane trips on acid are my favourite memories from my younger years.

So my question is to ex users of substances....what do you miss the most?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Drove a top of the range car right accross the map to find a group of dicks had blocked the entrance to the garage. I spotted them before they could get a good shot at me. RPG'ed them out the way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How easy is it to dye a beard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had a similar thing earlier.  Diamonds are for trevor mission. Dick head team mate doesn't have any tactics when faced with multiple enemies.
 

I hide behind a wall popping up to take the enemies out one at a time.  He arrived about 5 minutes late. Runs into the middle of about 10 enemies. Dies. Then does it a second time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with considerable personal experience of psychedelics...i am still pretty against their use by most people.

I had some amazing times on acid.really mind blowing experiences that twenty years later I can still remember vividly.

However, I saw too many people damaged by them to think they are all good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought a litre of white lightning. Had a great night, first time socialising and being a teenager. Loved it! Walked home so happy and buzzed. 

The week after thought I'll buy 2 litres and be twice as happy..... i drank two litres and my mum had to pick me up as i couldnt walk and threw up everywhere. She put me to bed. I wet myself in the night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
