<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4427</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gut the State Department while ratcheting up tensions with North Korea and Iran. Sounds like a good way to start a war(s).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ultimately, Trump is failing because he has little knowledge of the world and no guiding star of moral principle. The best of our leaders  think Abraham Lincoln  have been sure about the truth and uncertain about themselves. Trump is the opposite. His mind is uncluttered by creeds. He knows what he wants at any given moment, but it can bear little relation to the moment following. Who really believes that he would be sleepless if the wall were not built or if NAFTA ultimately survived? Who believes he would not be sleepless because of a nasty joke at his expense during a dinner party?"

I think it is pretty clear what Trump stands for- Himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We set a low bar for Trump. He still failed to meet it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secretary of State Tillerson calls for new sanctions on North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China warns situation with North Korea at 'critical point' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US economic growth rate hits three-year low </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's praise for Michael Flynn is coming back to haunt him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China warned North Korea of sanctions after any nuclear test: Tillerson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox host Watters takes sudden leave after Ivanka remark backlash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Check Out the Lexus That Apple's Using to Test Self-Driving Car Technology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DPREVIEW: Sphere of frustration: Nikon KeyMission 360 review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft's cloud business is growing almost twice as fast as Amazon's, with Google far behind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NAFTA: Trump plays a risky game with $1.2 trillion in trade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
