<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8985</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazilian Indigenous People Attacked, Hands Severed in Land Dispute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The upsides to this are minimal, while the downsides are enormous and compound themselves over time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed... we've closed the Head-Ass loop and are now firmly lodged; it's dark in here, and it smells of mushrooms... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still... double-check on that too, it's not not like anyone there did! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that's a perfect example, yeah! In any other situation without the cameras, they'd all be slapping each other on the back and laughing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair relating to #3 and #4, they could confirm the geometry of the Earth, with their own eyes, just by climbing a tall tree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it depends on the kind of investment... after this, I'd be looking to invest on the downswing, and then cash in on the next boom. Long-term though, is a very different proposition. If you want an investment that you can largely sit on and forget about, this seems like a poor choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congress can stick its nose in just about anything, and does so routinely to get free publicity and make themselves look good. There are other plausible reasons why they *would*, but the reason I gave is why they *did*. 

To be clear, United deserves a drubbing, but this is like having someone who screws dogs prosecute someone for screwing a cat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First reaction: "Wow, that's one hell of a claim."
*Glances at source*

Ahhhh... it's bullshit then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GM, Ford and Toyota all post U.S. sales declines in April </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The constant steam losses is sort of what I'm getting at... how many industrial byproducts are safe to just... vent? Or leak? Imagine trying that with a loop of liquid sodium, or Pb-Bi eutectic!

By the way, thanks for keeping the lights on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... Brexit is a tantrum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Antifa"

Sort of like identifying as an attack helicopter, it's something I hear about constantly from a certain breed of asshole complaining about it, but never once have I seen the real deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to zero-in on the critical issue...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denmark bans six 'hate preachers' from entering the country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Very* few people are flat-earthers, who are not simply trolls. The ones who aren't just trolls tend to be general conspiracy theorists; conspiracy ideation leads to more of the same. People who believe in conspiracies are more likely to believe in other conspiracies, even contradictory ones. 

http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/1948550611434786 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Human:...
#EVENT
Human: Formulate heuristic based on past experiences; best fit to current situation. 

Human: No valid heuristic with current data, error, error. 

Human: Reformulate heuristic based on "sounds good to me Jack!" criteria.

Human: Outputting...
`Aliens!` </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too... I'm just trying not to actively hate myself too much right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's like an ADHD 13yr old boy's idea of what a great dad is

I see you've twigged to the YouTube target audience... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The record of the system with older kids (who are bound to have some issues from that jackass of a father) is pretty dismal; hopefully they get lucky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> despite all the rhetoric on all sides (of the n.korea situation), i'm going to guess that peace on the peninsula will win out, save for some spikes of vol here and there. i'm selling a good chunk of my position with the idea of rebuying once the price comes down a fair chunk (probably down to $1100 level)

Definitely a smart move IMO, and I agree about the Korean issue. I think you could reasonably expect more volatility ahead though... I've never seriously considered speculating in this market before, but now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right?! Not "Unmask" not "Expose" not "Block"... *COUNTER*... god fucking damn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No really! I just had chole for lunch! *Sob* Oh my god it's a lie, my name is Kyle and I'm from Birmingham!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about your sentence structure, I found you perfectly understandable. So, to answer your question lets think about life *today*, alright? We know, all of us, that driving a car is dangerous, and that most of us will be in at least one accident. Some of us will be seriously injured, and many thousands die every year. 

BUT...

...We do it anyway. We see cars as a necessary and vital part of life, and are willing to accept a certain amount of reasonable risk to get around faster, and cheaper. 

The risks of travel in the time of the Hindenburg were not much better to be honest, and air travel was especially primitive. If you wanted to move a lot of people a long way, pretty much the only options were overland, or by ship. A giant zeppelin could have changed that, inherent risks and all. 

When you're talking about a cutting-edge technology, it's always a debate, and you have to think about it from the point of view of someone at the time. You could cross an ocean in comfort and relative safety in a dirigible... or go in a boat. It wasn't really understood just *how* dangerous the setup of the Hindenburg was; and Hydrogen is *much* cheaper and easier to get your hands on than similar quantities of something like Helium.

So... bottom line tl;dr to your question?

Hope.
Greed.
Ambition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Deti hai to de varna kat le

So... I'm not going to fuck you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mujhe jaana hai, phir milenge. Main aapko phone karoongi. Lekin sach muuch nahi karoongi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela opposition blocks streets to protest Maduro's power shakeup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From an evolutionary perspective, there is value to novelty, and novelty-seeking behavior, but the safest court is generally to stick with the group. If everyone else is skittish around feeding time, and runs when they think a tiger is coming, but Thag doesn't... well... maybe we're not descended from Thag. More generally, for most of human/hominid history being in the group was a matter of life or death, a matter of being able to enjoy mutual grooming, defense, and sharing food. 

So we have millions of years of that, backed up by thousands of years of social evolution driven by that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost always a (state) constitutional issue, but honestly pro se defense is not the norm, and the courts are *required* to admonish the defendant, but... you know... "State's Rights" and all of that. 

The truth is that most of the people representing themselves are delusional. The bottom line though, is that for whatever reason they have that constitutional right; it may be that it comes from a time when it could have made a bit more sense, I'm not a legal historian, sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not looking into light, they're looking into a relatively dark area, while being lit. You can actually see that in the picture you posted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you say so crazy lady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - According to Gordon, an unnamed marketing exec waived off the multiple warnings and said, Let's just do it and be legends, man.

I mean... that makes me want to die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barbarians... here in the US we elect a Cheeto to do our dirty work for us! That's why we're civilized... 

^^^^^^^^^/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that food coloring is safe in the quantities used, but I wouldn't drink it either, or preservatives, or artificial flavors, Would you?

In any case, you're clearly not able or willing to support your point, so I've lost interest in it, and you; obviously you'll just say any old shit you like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't sweat it. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm not drawing a parallel between oxygen fires, I'm just saying that in terms of sights that are incredibly haunting, even many years later, they all compare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure, thanks for the feedback.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not responding to demands, that's not what the burden of proof is. What it really means is that when you make a positive claim (such as, "Glyphosate is not safe.") people should only take it as seriously as you're willing to support it. 

You're free not to support it, and I'm then free to dismiss it with a wave of a hand; one begets the other. In the same way, citation isn't a game of numbers, but a matter of quality; you're supporting a point you make, that's all. 

In essence, you made a claim which is (to use your word) a "demand" to be believed. Why should anyone simply believe what you say?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most haunting visuals of all time, along with the Hindenburg, and the planes into the twin towers IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glyphosate is not safe, whatever it "appears" to you. We can not know how bad exactly since falsification and deception was employed to muddle the science.

Ok, I'm open to any citations showing that it's unsafe.

Cut the bullshit and cite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always easy to put the burden of prove on the other. Typical corporate trolling tactic you are using there. Maybe you explain me why you would fudge your science if you have all the honest prove that your products are safe and there is nothing to worry about.

...He said, as he tried to Judo reverse the burden of proof. 

*lol*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress' new spending bill includes $100M to counter Russian information operations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/6821ro/verizons_annual_data_breach_report_is_depressing/

...Try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the second person to call me a shill instead of actually doing anything like backing up their point. 

Pathetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you commenting with a theme today or are you always this much of a dismissive cunt?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok crazy lady.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you mean... less an issue of the apprenticeship concept, and more to do with the society around it. Wasn't there a push a while ago to get people working in fast food positions classified as "apprentices" to avoid minimum wage laws? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Whistles*

https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/68s9kv/monsanto_accused_in_court_of_conducting_an_army/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I'm open to any citations showing that it's unsafe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh the UK apprenticeship system is *sick*, and I do not mean that in a good way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not assumed to be capable, but they *are* the one accused.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/kittyportals2 said
If you knew Monsanto like I know Monsanto, you wouldn't be defending them. Oh wait, you do. Shill.

*lol*

This is great. If you go back a week or so in my comment history you can actually see the argument I got into with some Libertarians defending Monsanto with the same fervor you're attacking them. They accused me of being a secret GMO-hating far-leftie. 

It's almost like the two extremes of this debate are full of polarized assholes who can't have a reasonable debate...

Edit: ... I have to add by the way, that if you're accusing me of knowing Monsanto like you "know Monsanto" and *also* accusing me of being a shill... you do understand that you'd be saying you're a shill, right? No? You didn't?

*lol* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Have you *heard* of ADM, Kraft, Nestle, Unilever, etc...? 

What you're saying is laughable bullshit; glyphosate really *does* appear to be pretty safe, meanwhile the food people happily stuff themselves with *is* proven to be terrible for them. You end up in this ridiculous and macabre situation in which people guzzle soda, eat whole pizzas, and then complain about the GMO origin of their corn syrup. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest risk of a 100% oxygenated environment is that *everything* burns. A small static spark can end the life of everyone in that room, faster than you could believe, and even your bones will burn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Work in a PR firm, at the very *lowest* levels, and do it between frantic coffee runs for people who only ever scream at you. That, or be in a really repressive state that can just tap you and say, "Your function now, is to represent the Glorious People's Republic of Horgenstein on the WWW... do a good job or we shoot your family." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitcoin soars above $1,400 to all-time high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There shouldn't be any changes you need to make right away, but a lot of sites will start "broken". The trick then is to open the uMatrix interface (which is point+click!) and "green" (you'll see what that means) the servers you need. It's mostly pretty obvious (you want Reddit.com for example), but sometimes it *is* just a bit of trial and error. 

The good news is that your settings are globally applied, so after a few days of fiddling, it starts to just work in the background. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not doing that either... issues with "feeding the planet" are NOT issues of supply, but logistics, will, and regional conflict getting in the way. Monsanto isn't "feeding the planet" they're turning a profit. 

Mind you, I think that falls somewhat short of, "Unequivocal evil" or at the very least renders the concept of evil meaningless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're delusional.

As strong as that may seem to be as a counterargument, I'm going to have to pass on another round of, "Answer my questions!" while you come back with... that. 

Have a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure, if you need any more help on this topic, just let me know. I'm always glad to help people take back their own web browsing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't misunderstand; China has no more chance of really influencing the DPRK than the USSR or Russia did. The DPRK doesn't particularly respect the Chinese, they just use them. By the same token, China allows this because they are 100% about unity, and the notion of millions of ethnic Koreans flooding their border horrifies them.

Not to mention that a united Korea almost certainly means the US military on their doorstep. 

No... the DPRK has China by the balls, not the other way around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well slow is certainly accurate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NoScript or uMatrix takes care of that; script control is the issue there. Don't forget to turn on user agent spoofing too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but it's already been established what a low bar exists for doubt in your mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.tenor.co/images/1a4b67f9bd15e0dab79aa231968fdafe/raw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not unless they've passed the bar in your state, as I said "you" are a special case, no one else is. That said, representing yourself is *not* the norm in a criminal case, and any judge is going to try hard and repeatedly to get you better representation; up to the point of assigning it to you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing new in that lawsuit, it's just two people alleging what people on Reddit do all of the time, and seemingly with no more evidence. The notion that Monsanto (like any massive company) actively spins, PR's, and goes after online commentary is neither new, or surprising. 

The questions which matter in regards to Monsanto have to do with paid or ghost-written research, concerns that they might have (or might in the future) go down the ADM lysine route, and other issues. 

You can dislike companies like Monsanto without turning them into special cases of bogeymen in your mind. Monsanto is not somehow magically different from ADM, or Pfizer, or Kraft, or Nestle, or Exxon, or Boeing. The issues with one are largely the issues with the other, but people are just so confused, paranoid, or ideologically fucked to have a conversation with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aesthetically not very different, functionally *very* different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you can, but they'd have to agree to represent you, and be qualified to represent you. You don't have to be qualified to represent you, but you're a unique case... mind you a judge can still decide that you *need* representation and assign you a public defender anyway. 

I mean, you *could* ask for Bon Jovi to represent you, but why would he, even if it would be allowed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could teach people online, answer questions, or you could even answer hypothetical questions. That said, you have to be very conservative with "teaching to learn" and keep within the bounds of what you truly *know*; otherwise you're just an agent of spreading bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dude deregulation has always been key.

Yeah, without deregulation how could miracles like the crashes of the late 90's or 2008 have happened? Totally impossible dude!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if China or Russia put a system like this in Cuba.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly, from the mind of a meerkat... 

Because what could be simpler than starting up a war we already fought to a standstill, but now with decades of mining, and tunnels, and nuclear research and artillery... 

Genius! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... anything that hurts her is good, but it's a bit like calling out Hitler for his mustache.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! Now you just have to show that they...

seems to be detrimental to them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't understand that about China for quite a long time... that the people-central government is more of a two way street that it appears on the surface. Sure, an individual person is a speck, but it's amazing how sensitive the central government is to the majority sentiment. They try to guide it, shape it, control it, but above all I think after the 80's, they try not to be swept away or crushed by it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hello, my name is Chadji *cough* my name is Chad." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be one of those, "Everything would change" situations, truly. Water would cease to be an issue overnight, along with recycling, disposal of trash, pollution, transport, etc. The notion of an economy as it exists today wouldn't make much sense after very little time, and poverty as we know it today would eventually end. 

A lot of the hardest living around the world is predicated on power being relatively expensive and difficult to generate and transmit, but this would not be the case. 

Everything... EVERYTHING would change. 

Of course, the odds of such an energy source emerging suddenly like that, which is cheap AND practically unlimited? Unlikely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a policy?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the UK is shooting itself in the foot because of... "attitude" is that it? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The regulations that the EU puts on Britain seems to be detrimental to them.

According to what sources you'd care to cite? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you comparing a country choosing who to allow citizenship to, with a country murdering people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This *is* literally how the system is designed to work; avoid the system at all costs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, pattern-welded... not the same really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uMatrix, uBlock Origin, NoScript.

You're welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, well... unfortunately memory loss *is* a side effect of "Butter" exposure, you should recover in time if you have plenty of local ice cream; don't forget the Flake!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original in Nature: https://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature22045.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butter? Oh my Irish friend... this is America, home of "Spread" such as *I Can't Believe It's Not Butter!*

Well... I fucking can. 

The Cheeto has almost certainly never eaten anything as wholesome as butter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a fair cop! *lol* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is depressing... the parts of your brain which normally inhibit erratic behavior. Given time and a higher dose you'll depress deeper functions, all the way to essential ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Note: some restrictions may apply. Hungary, Poland, The UK, and France may not currently or in the future participating in these sweepstakes. Italy and Spain may disappoint too; in fact, you'd better just stick to the ScandiWegian countries.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey... factor this very large number for me." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gut... gut what do you think? Gut?!"

*"Hummus..."*

This might take a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your username is making this... difficult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. issues travel alert for Europe, citing threat of terrorist attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. issues travel alert for Europe, citing threat of terrorist attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/tbRwbY6.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox News isn't really the heart of conservative viewership anyway, they're mostly for retirees who couldn't *find* Breitbart unaided.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all have assholes, they serve a purpose, and can even give pleasure; Hannity fits none of those criteria.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly, it's the end for that channel, and I think this is what a lot of people expected once Ailes was out; he was the disgusting glue holding that corrupt mess together.

The feeding frenzy of ambition to fill the gap is going to be truly staggering and nauseating; brace yourselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why would they do that? They are already cranking out products at a breakneck pace. what the hell are they gonna do with hundreds of billion extra dumped into more R D?

I honestly hope that you're just the troll you appear to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is philosophy, not science, so prepare for a clusterfuck of equally valid opinions and a total absence of anything like fact. 

The truth is that you can't examine these issues without the technology existing in some form, and it doesn't... at all. Without a grounding in reality, this isn't really science in any form, even science-fiction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he was just pointing out that what Trump said was fatuous and obvious, without weighing into a false dichotomy about the starting a war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in other words, last year the DPRK had slightly less technological capability in that regard than the USSR did... in 1957.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not investing it like a grandmother in retirement... investing in R D. If you worked a bit harder on having a conversation and tried a bit less to score meaningless rhetorical points, that might also help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The distance between where such a suggestion starts, and the person who could make a decision based on it, is truly staggering. Is it impossible? No. Is it unlikely verging on pissing into the wind? Yes. At most you can be one among many making a similar suggestion; that would be the good outcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the anti-science people are a tick on the ass of reasonable debate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How many missiles can a THAAD installation target at once? What kind of situation does this system realistically protect against? A 'few' incoming missiles? 

I'd be shocked if people at the Pentagon could produce an honest answer to that question. The realities of practical countermeasures, multiple launches, etc... who knows really?

Is it effective against missiles only or can it be used against aircraft or artillery as well?

Only ballistic missiles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  so they choose not to piss away money

...Ah yes... investing money is so famously "pissing it away" while sitting on cash hoards of course, is the secret to growth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we're talking past each other, while largely agreeing with each other.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, they've come a long way, and will continue to advance with their nuclear and missile tech. Meanwhile the reasons for not engaging with them haven't changed, and are unlikely to changed. I'd urge you to pick up some good books on the history of the region; knowledge is the antidote to concepts like that "red line" crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Mid... on a window? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article has been updated, greatly expanded, and pictures added. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are some indications that a total nuclear exchange between India and Pakistan would have global consequences on climate, with the potential to cause at least a few years of severe famine in some regions. Even if we ignore every other aspect of two hugely populous nations potentially killing each other off, we'd have to consider broader economic and humanitarian issues. 

I would also say that if you have to spend a paragraph extolling the relative virtues of "track rabbit" you've already conceded something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to consider making more than one visual; have one for vitamins, one for fats, carbs, etc... 

Then you can have some overall rankings, that kind of thing. You could also show each as representations of how much of your daily values of various micro/macro-nutrients they provide, vs. others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From an app they could ask you to fill out forms you might hesitate to fill out on a website, and they can just ask "permissions" to track anything you'll let them, including location data. This ties in with the notifications; lets say McDonalds wants you to use their app and not their site. So their app might vibrate your phone with a notification when you're near a McDonalds, offering you a limited time-only coupon for a free small fries. 

It's not that a site can't do all of the same things (and better in some cases), but for the company they get better engagement when they live in your phone or tablet, rather than waiting for you to come to them. As an app they're also there, in your life, more than they are as one of a million sites you *could* visit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun "fact": It also changes over certain words, so if you type the phrase:

"My father works as a garbage disposal technician and wears the appropriate uniform, and requires a certain degree of financial assistance from the state..."

You might say instead...

"My father is a dustman, he wears a dustman's hat! He wears cor-blimey trousers and he lives in a council flat!"

Simples! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alcohol and many of it's metabolites (byproducts of your body breaking it down) are irritating; you've felt that when you drink it after all, it's harsh stuff. Well, it's irritating on the way out too, promoting inflammation. 

With a UTI you want to *avoid* inflammation. If you want to stimulate the production of urine, iced or regular tea can be a good choice, without packing on the calories of loads of cranberry juice. That, and cranberry juice really has no proven link to helping; it's just a matter of passing enough fluid, avoiding inflammation, good sanitation, and if needed antibiotics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, Apple doesn't need to sit on *cash* to avoid paying tax, as they've shown time and again. They're sitting on cash because they don't have a better idea of what to do with it, which is sad, because a $250bn USD could be working *hard* in an actual economy or functional company.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
