<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans never would have made those promises (other than removing regulations). Trump backed them into an impossible corner. The fool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Dealmaker Trump" eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did it take me until just now to realize that Vlad is our Roose Bolton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty cringeworthy, but nowhere near as bad as when people insisted on calling Mitt Romney "Mittens". Whether it's "libtard" or "cuntservative", these nicknames are fucking stupid people. They aren't funny or clever. They're just. Fucking. Stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Incorrect, when Marduk raised his club to split Tiamut's body and create the earth and the sea from the spoils of battle and the vanquished gods, he spake it unto her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If true I'll puke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine reasoning aside from the fact that more people who voted cast those votes for Trump's opponent. The reality is that Trump had the right message for a few key states and swung a very narrow electoral college victory. If the democrats realign themselves with working people and make it clear what they stand for they'll be just fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was his name, the guy in the article - it was about his building in NYC. It, like this building, was an awesome combination of concrete and glass. I definitely want to look more into his work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read an article in the Atlantic about this architect and his use of concrete - his signature is that paneled look with the 4 indentations. Pretty interesting stuff - concrete is usually very ugly but he obviously goes to great lengths to make it aesthetically appealing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Did you know Obama asked for military vehicles at his inauguration? And then lied and said he didn't, but emails proved he was lying?"

It's so easy. I can't wait to try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genius </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, who won again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ballots out for Harambe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump, the catchphrase president, has catchphrase minions. No surprise there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is the ultimate illustration of privilege and its hollowness. He gets into office and the stock market goes up and we get a better than average jobs report. He takes the credit for it because he created a "positive business environment" just by being there, despite the work put in over the past 8 years to revive the dead economy left us by the previous Republican in office. So he's done nothing other than get elected and markets get a boost from it - fair enough, markets do what markets do and business "feels" more confident with Trump in office. No need to mention that he's inheriting a functional, growing economy, right? Rather than having to turn an economy in nose-dive right side up, as was his predecessor's task. That's the same privilege at work that Trump has benefited from his entire life. Other people work hard and he gets credit for by mere fact of existing (see: Fred Trump, for starters).

And now we get to see how his actual governing and leadership impact things, if anything actually ever gets done on that front. We'll get to see just how far in the hole we wind up after however many more years of this cluelessness we have to deal with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's clear that tradition and custom have lost any force. Actual laws need to be in place to prevent shit shows like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fucking excellent, thank you so much for sharing. You did indeed dodge a bullet with that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's a vast reach to expect that the American people will be able to stop paying for a billionaire's weekly vacations? This is completely bizarre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well 1992 is only 8 years ago.

 - Me, to this day, despite it being 2017 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea of a page goal rather than a book goal. The one thing I've found difficult to balance is longer vs shorter books. I usually ready about 50 pages a day, so maybe it makes more sense to make that my standard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I like having a schedule. It keeps me motivated and actively thinking about reading. Habits become more and more solidified as you engage in them, so for many people, myself included, having a goal and a schedule is a big help in solidifying those habits. Thankfully we are all allowed to choose how we manage our time, whether it's scheduling books to read or trolling the pages of a subreddit whose purpose we disagree with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try as best I can to balance reading books I've had on my shelf to read forever, and new books that I am excited about. I try to alternate between the books I put on my "2017" list and a new book. That way I'm still steadily working through my backlog but I also get to mix in new and exciting impulse books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's more an infowars story. Breitbart will just imply that they're traitors. Breitbart is terrible but more down to earth (literally) than infowars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't have that reaction, that's what they want. They want to derail the conversation and get off-topic. Just stick with current events and continue to press on what's happening now. Whether or not something similar happened in the past is not relevant to what's happening now. If there's a problem, there's a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  bizarre

done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's one of the few books by him that I haven't read yet, but it's on my list! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's great so far and looks to be a quick read! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week I finished **A Walk in the Woods** by Bill Bryson. I am a hiker and I worked at one of the visitor's centers mentioned in the book, in addition to having hiked some of the New England portions of the trail. I am also a fan of Bryson's from some of his other books, so this was a hit for me. He's a very perceptive person and a good researcher, so I always feel that I gain a good insight into the topic when I read his books. I was a bit surprised to see some negative reviews on goodreads where people bemoaned Bryson's negative attitude and judgmental tendencies - he's an equally harsh critic of himself as he is of anyone else, his "superior feelings" are nearly always ironic (because he's a notorious bumbler), and the awe and appreciation he often expresses balance out his grumblings (which are frequent - but humorous). I guess it just comes down to things working for some people and not for others!

I started **The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-time** and I'm a fan so far. It is in the tradition of Flowers for Algernon and The Sound and the Fury in that it offers a perspective you don't often see from a narrator. I appreciate the way the author works his narrator's tendencies into the book through the use of graphs and images, and it's also very entertaining. Since this is a short book I'm also going to start **Consider the Lobster**. I haven't read any of David Foster Wallace's non-fiction but I'm pretty excited about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could probably skip the rest, but some people like Jessica Jones I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At one point, when I was living with 4 other people and getting $200 of my rent paid by my employer each month, I was paying about $250 for rent and utilities, but I was also only making $12,000 that year because it was a national service program. Nothing close to a typical situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only civilized but merciful. Khabib says that's why he put the submission on Michael Johnson - so that he didn't have to keep pounding his face in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No controversy in that 30-27 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You at the show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, I agree that that's the point of the scene. And yet it shows the general public reacting to him with awe - he's cool all of a sudden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good lord, that name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, I'm getting this creeping feeling just from reading that name. In a good way. This book series is like the real-life Candle Cove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit! I forgot how creepy that substitute teacher is. I have a feeling that this book series, along with "Scary Stories to Tell in the Dark", lies at the root of my interest in Weird Fiction like HP Lovercraft and Laird Barron. They are the adult version of these bizarre tales. I never made that connection before. I need to reread this book. What I remember most distinctly is a character who "doesn't believe in socks", which was always something I couldn't wrap my head around fully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With that username I can't do anything but upvote you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The better questions is - shouldn't something truly good stand on its own rather than relying on knowledge of its creator? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it were a more consistent theme throughout the films, it would fit better. It was also a strangely-framed scene - having no music actually does a much better job of conveying the awkwardness of the scene. Including the music puts you more in Peter's mind rather than the perspective of an observer seeing a weirdo snapping and strutting down the street. Additionally, all of the intended irony in the scene is undercut in the "jazz piano" scene where he actually *is* supposed to be cool happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is probably a big part of the issue. The version of "misguided cool" they chose to portray is no one's idea of cool, not even a "nerd's". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the rest of the movie were halfway decent I could stomach this scene because you're correct about its intent. The rest of the movie is also terrible so after cringing through this scene I had had enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on a plane and they when I saw this movie. There was a crying baby behind me, a fat guy snoring next to me, and my ipod was dead, so I really wanted a movie to distract myself. When this scene happened I popped out my earphones and just ensconced myself in the cacophony surrounding me instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's time to stop laughing at Trump, to be honest. We're past the point where it's funny. I get that laughing at the absurdity and tragedy of it is a great way of coping, but this shit is too serious to laugh at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a person who actually read the article instead of posting photos I got on the_donald that don't disprove anything in the article, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, absolutely - the story is about the specific instance shown in the video, where Trump appears to refuse a handshake after being asked by both Merkel and a reporter. The subheading of the article is: "President greeted German leader with handshake upon her arrival but appeared to ignore requests to do so as the pair sat together in front of TV cameras". I am guessing most people posting photographs of them shaking hands and calling it fake news didn't even open the article. They shook hands earlier in the day, and Trump's body language and decision to ignore requests for a shake after the closed-door meeting indicate that something happened over the course of that meeting to sour relations between them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the claim that Trump didn't Merkel's hand at all? No, it was that he refused to shake her hand. Which he appears to have done in this instance, as he was asked both by her and by a reporter, and he acknowledged neither. He was just fine with shaking it before their meeting - once they sat down behind closed doors, something appears to have happened, as Trump emerged looking like a chastened child. In fact, if you read more than the headline, you'd have seen that the first thing under it is: "President greeted German leader with handshake upon her arrival but appeared to ignore requests to do so as the pair sat together in front of TV cameras" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you guys came up with another funny nickname for people you disagree with, congrats. The_don's lingo, always changing, but always inoffensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's why it's Donald and Hobbes instead of Calvin and Hobbes. Donald has all of the obnoxious qualities of Calvin without any of the redeeming charm and other positive traits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [he's like a smart person](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3OG6itojBiI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one positive thing that comes from provoking British ire is learning new Britishisms like whelk stall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure "people" were - just not many people. Two people is people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The federal government can sign accords with other nations (like the ones we're currently signed up for) and enforce regulations by withholding federal funds to states that don't comply. And the better idea is to prevent the pollution from existing in the first place than suing after it already happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say California has stringent environmental regulations and Utah doesn't. Guess what? California still gets a bunch of shit flowing down into it via the Colorado river. Carry that logic forward to all forms of pollution. It doesn't just stay within state borders.

Environmental regulation only REALLY works when its global, and more directly, the start of that is making sure its nationwide here. We *all* pay the price for a lack of environmental regulation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This still sounds like largely moderate Democrat positions on the issues... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last time I was in the office, I was working late with one of my coworkers. She said that it's the same every day - it's usually 5pm that she finally has the chance to do actual work because at that point everyone's gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great point. Before working from home I always envisioned it being hard to stay motivated and be productive. I've found it to be the exact opposite, with my job anyways. I always have deadlines and things to do, so I am never in a position where I find myself struggling to stay focused, and with no one here to interrupt or distract me, I can just home in (no pun intended) on my work. In fact, I've had to force myself to take breaks (I'm on a ten minute one right now) and stop working at a reasonable time at the end of the day instead of cranking through until 7 or 8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work from home 95% of the time, with ocassional days in our main office, and the difference in the amount of work I get done at home vs in the office is stunning. In the office, every 10 minutes there's a distraction. Someone walks by and wants to chat - or I get pulled into a meeting I don't really need to be in - or I'm halfway through the 5 minute walk to get to the bathroom and someone calls my name from down the hall... it is really amazing when I compare the amount I'm able to get done from home, where I get to sit down and actually focus, vs being in the office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He hasn't provided any. So the claim is evidence-free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who can live without another edgy Tomi Lahren tweet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not that subtle or informed amigo. Not by a long shot. Trump could hardly iterate the difference between Andrew, Stonewall, and Michael Jackson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If /r/AskTrumpSupporters is any guide to go by, even some of THEM are starting to wake up to reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...aaand the second ban was just stayed. Failed again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he derailed TPP. Other than that this has been a parade of failures, ineptitude, and embarrassments. What a crappy administration this is. The saving grace is their incompetence. Otherwise we'd *really* be in trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 00:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/the_don is, yet again, spinning this as a 4D chess move. This time, he's supposedly trotting Paul Ryan out to back this bill so that he can team up with Rand Paul behind the scenes and create the ultimate plan. Reality is that the administration 100% wants this thing to pass, but Trump is trying to get it there without having to actually take blame for how bad it sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too, and frustrated that McCain just huffs and puffs, but at the very least it lends to an environment where other Republicans can (hopefully, eventually) start to take more substantive action and know that there are people in their party who are sympathetic to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The words that a President says have incredible consequence and importance. They basically *are* actions. For an easy example, have you heard of the "Trump Bump"? When he calls out a company on twitter, there's a noticeable effect on that company's business (positive or negative). His words also represent the policy of the United States, which is why it matters when he talks. He is our primary representative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can it really be called brutal honesty when he's making unfounded, evidence-free claims about wiretaps? I'd call his feed a blend of narcissism, pettiness, inaccurately framed ideas, and delusion, with truth sprinkled in occasionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is that some parts of the dossier have been demonstrated to be true. None of what Trump claimed about Trump Tower being wiretapped by Obama has been remotely demonstrated to be true. These aren't equally invalid claims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The intelligence communities themselves have said Russia meddled in the election - the intelligence agencies are saying the exact opposite about Trump's claims of being wiretapped by Obama. Tomorrow Comey is expected to announce details on whether Trump is being actively investigated for ties to Russia, so again, the intelligence communities, not Obama, are leading the charge on this. These are not equivalent situations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, it's 35 pages and much of it can be skimmed through quickly. The "watching hookers pee on a bed the Obamas slept in" is in fact in the dossier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 07:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, if the AHCA that Trump is backing gets passed, many Trump voters' lives will be in shambles. Hopefully it won't get to that point but I wish Trump had America's best interest in mind, not to mention his own voters, instead of just backing the first thing that seemed to line up with a campaign promise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 06:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's absolutely worth the vague notion of "the degradation of the prestige of the office" to get universal health care codified in law. Once the US gets universal health care it's very unlikely we'll ever go back. Getting there is nearly impossible and there's no chance it's going to happen under Trump with a republican congress. But if it did, in this fantasy world, it would absolutely be worth a hit to the prestige of the office. That can be remedied and rectified later. Universal health care would be an unimaginably important step forward. Any chance to get it needs to be taken advantage of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it easier to just have a portion of our taxes go towards health care for all? We need to get that $3,000 for health care from somewhere, right? Presumably through taxation of one form or another. So why not just take the next logical step and have universal healthcare? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This leaves us in the scenario we had before the ACA, where people went bankrupt and/or couldn't find insurance to cover them because they were ill and insurance companies didn't want to cover them since it would cost them to do so. There are some areas of life where it makes sense to have some government protection of the people. Defense is one - health care is another. We're literally talking about the health and wellness of the population - there's no reason we need to leave that up to the whims of for-profit businesses when a better solution has been demonstrated by pretty much every other developed nation in the world.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't insurance only work if people who aren't using it pay into it? That's how most forms of insurance work - you pay for it when you aren't using it so that you can use it, and other people pay into it when they aren't using it so that you have it when you need it. If everyone who is paying into it is also using it at that exact moment, there aren't funds in the account to cover everyone. That's why you need healthy people paying into it - and the healthy people have it in the event of an accident or if they do wind up developing a condition for which they need care. There are definite fixes that need to be made to balance costs for healthy people, but fundamentally speaking you need to have healthy people (such as you and I) paying into the system for it to work at all. Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just like to plug The Atlantic - I get it every month (well, 10 times a year since there are two "combined" issues) and it has never failed to be full of interesting and awesome articles. Very much worth the cheap price of subscription. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that a couple of weeks ago - excellent book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Walk in the Woods by Bill Bryson! It's an older book at this point, but one I've been meaning to read for quite awhile since I'm a hiker and a fan of his other books. I live near the Appalachian Trail and have hiked small portions of it, so his descriptions hit home for me. He's also a hilarious writer and does an excellent job blending his own experience in with a larger discussion of the trail, its many iterations, its history, its interaction with the environment, and many other fascinating elements of background information that contribute to a very entertaining and fulfilling read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 13:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does a real disservice to your point to just be dismissive and /r/iamverysmart - particularly when it seems very clear that the person you're arguing with has looked into this much more deeply than you've demonstrated that you have. I am opposed to white nationalism but this does nothing aside from make it look like you don't have an actual argument to stand on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Call me crazy but isn't the entire point of insurance that there's a pool of money available because a lot of people who *aren't* using up those funds are paying into it in the event that it's there for them too, if they should need it? It doesn't work if the only people who get insurance need to use it for more than they pay into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was only in two of the several tweets that he used quotation marks, anyways. The other times he straight up said it. And he has used quotation marks in weird, nonsensical ways in the past in his tweets. 

Recently he said:

 For eight years Russia "ran over" President Obama, got stronger and stronger, picked-off Crimea and added missiles. Weak! @foxandfriends

Last week:

 ...is all of the illegal leaks of classified and other information. It is a total "witch hunt!"

My 65 year old aunt does the same thing on facebook. She'll comment things like:

 Wow, what a "nice" photo!

or

 You look "great"!

I think she thinks they're italics or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Rewatch the video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2BpgHcanjCQ). Sessions did not respond to Franken saying "about the 2016 election". No one said that in that section of the questioning. The only reference to the election was Franken saying "in the course of this campaign" referring to anyone associated with the Trump campaign - Sessions brought himself into the scenario and denied having "any communications with the Russians". It looks like an awful lot like post hoc rationalization to define "any communications with the Russians" as anything other than what it means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're discussing whether or not she *can and should* be the subject of criticism (and political parody in the case of SNL). She has an active role in the administration and is fair game for both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 89% of people think you need to provide a source for statistics rather than just posting numbers - I guess you fall into the 11% that just sees numbers and accepts them because they align with your narrative? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone is in a meeting, they are participating in the decision-making process and are fair game to be criticized. That is why her situation is different than Barron's or Tiffany's. She's playing an active role. As you said, she's likely an adviser since that's her described role in the administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an seriously awkward piece of writing. It's only a good idea to use a "big word" when it fits better than a more common synonym. That's how you avoid clumsy bullshit like "admittedly more situationally capricious than particularly courageous." Get rid of half of the words and the meaning is far clearer.

And "ubiquitous trait" is a terrible way of describing a part of the human body. A neck/skull is not really a trait, and if he meant to refer to its fragility, "property" would have been better than trait. 

Finally, you would in fact not be surprised to find something "common" if it were ubiquitous, since that's exactly what being ubiquitous means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, and she's totally fair game to be criticized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Melania participated in the birther conspiracy bullshit.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sSTx1ZODEcQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you have a reason to be there then. What was Ivanka's reason? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that was not the question posed to Sessions. The question wasn't even about Sessions' meetings. The question was what Sessions would do as AG if he discovered that anyone associated with the Trump had met with Russia during the *course of the campaign*, not *about* the campaign. And Sessions took it upon himself to deny having met with Russian officials despite not being asked about that. He didn't specify that he had actually met with them, just not about the campaign. He said he hadn't met with them. In other words, he lied, and his excuse is bullshit. It's the cover-up, not the crime, that's the problem - that is, unless the crime is worse than what we've led to believe and they actually *were* colluding with Russia during the campaign - in which case the crime is definitely worse and the reason for the lies starts to make a lot more sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This dude is the adult embodiment of "I have a girlfriend but she goes to another school". He was *almost* in a mercenary conflict - he took down a charging water buffalo - he stabbed a bear to death - come the fuck on bro. He's the dude who brings a motorcycle helmet to class but doesn't actually have a motorcycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vitor lookin' like a sorority girl on a walk of shame with those shorts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you say Trump overcame the odds to win the election? Because overcoming an 85% loss prediction is overcoming the odds. The fact that he won doesn't mean 15% wasn't an accurate reading of his chances at winning. The fact that something most likely won't happen does not mean it won't happen - it means it might, and in some cases, does happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ?I_do_not_support_Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This demonstrates a misunderstanding of how sourcing works in credible news outlets like the AP. They don't just take a call from someone and report it. They vet sources and have long conversations with editors and to the best of their ability, verify that the sources are legit. They also try to corroborate with other sources whenever possible. Typically the "anonymous source" is not anonymous to the journalists. The source asks to remain anonymous to protect their identity, so they are anonymous in the story. Not to the journalist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're giving them more credit than they deserve. They want to pass *something*, *anything* so that they can tell their voters that they repealed Obamacare. That was one of Trump's major promises and one of the major promises of a lot of these House reps. That's why they're trying to crank this thing through and that's why Trump is doing his best to get it passed. The backup plan is to "let it fail", but they definitely want to get this shit-heap through if they can. For Trump this is supposed to be a display of his "negotiating skills". But he picked a terrible showcase because EVERYONE hates this bill and the CBO's analysis next week will seal its fate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck would anyone think Trump would know how to fix healthcare? That's insane! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breitbart already came out against it. T_D is torn on how to conduct themselves, with Trump standing behind this shit bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, you mean the man who said "nobody knew healthcare could be this complicated" doesn't understand healthcare policy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which was the super bloody fight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
