<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4941</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 19:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's an idiot. Everything is dive with him. A champions league game he was commentating not too long ago a player got kneed in the chest and after all the replays all he could say was "ya he's at it again, gone down far too easy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And abandoned it after a couple of games so the players for a 3-5-2 were Mcgyvered into a 4-4-2 or watever non sense he decided to play after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They did not force OEMs to use Android 

They force google apps on them if they want Android to be anyway usable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 02:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, no variance in weather at all from the Arctic circle all the way down to the Mediterranean.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it strange? China has been investing in it for years and years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie is Social Democrat. Social democrats believe in the free market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm seriously starting to wonder if anyone part of Hillary's campaign team even watched him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 16:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best to look through through individual projects under the Rust or Servo umbrella e.g https://github.com/rust-lang/, maybe it's just me but Servo ones seem to have more tasks with the easy tag and seem to be a bit more beginner friendly.

Edit: Lots of help wanted on Bindgen https://github.com/servo/rust-bindgen/issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 14:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a documentary that's trying to get people to vote for Hillary, i really, really should have said that the video is edited and leaves out the end where he says it'll only feel good for a day or month. . .like Brexit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 13:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 12:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This e-mail and any files transmitted with it are intended solely for the use of the individual or entity to whom they are addressed. If the reader of this e-mail is not the intended recipient or the employee or agent responsible for delivering the message to the intended recipient, you are hereby notified that any use dissemination, forwarding, printing or copying of this e-mail is strictly prohibited.

#**LOL** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 12:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does Texas or New York stack up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 09:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooo what was he doing in Africa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . . .the point is you don't so any of that, you take a pill most likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does that mean he's a CNN cameraman? Was the news anchor sent to Africa by CNN with the cameraman or was it like an independent documentary or literally anything apart from official CNN business? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there no end to the madness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 01:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because there's still cancerous material in it? You're literally setting it on fire and smoking it. Treatment for the likes of epilepsy is a specific compound at a specific dose at specific intervals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A comment in there...

Hillary has the charisma of a tropical skin disease...



...and as many skeletons in the closet as the Khmer Rouge.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus those airstrikes were brutal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why pay reparations though instead of investing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there something wrong with what he said? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but also increases the likelihood the Rs nominate someone extreme.

That worked well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is she not one of the biggest barriers to gay marriage in Germany? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just doesn't match with reality though. A weaker currency is good when you import little, the UK is the opposite. [UK trade deficit widens unexpectedly as exports fall despite pound drop](https://www.theguardian.com/business/2016/nov/09/uk-trade-deficit-widens-september-exports-fall-pound-drop)

Alan Clarke, an economist at Scotiabank, said that a weaker currency was not necessarily a key driver of exports. If we are lucky, the weak pound may boost exports, but I would highlight that **export growth tends to be driven more by the strength of overseas demand, rather than the exchange rate.**

And the people may have voted for sovereignty, but that is absolutely not what they'll get. You've probably heard of the court case where British judges in British courts made a ruling on British law and what was the response by the leave campain? A 100,000 man march! 

[The march would be a reminder about what we voted for, so there is no slippage on the single market which we think this case was used to get a negotiating stand on," the spokesman said.(http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2016/11/06/nigel-farage-to-lead-100000-strong-march-on-supreme-court-on-day/)

If you and the leave voters think this will finish with a net increase in Democracy you're sorely mistaken.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to a Republican congress and Senate.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tank is obviously too much, but it will be significantly worse off than before

[Brexit blows $31 billion hole in British budget](http://money.cnn.com/2016/11/08/news/economy/uk-economy-brexit-25-billion/index.html)

[U.K. inflation forecast to quadruple next year](http://money.cnn.com/2016/11/02/news/economy/inflation-uk-brexit/index.html)

[Pound sterling beats Argentine peso to become 2016's worst performing currency](http://www.independent.co.uk/news/business/news/pound-sterling-argentine-peso-worst-performing-currency-eu-referendum-brexit-a7127246.html)

This is before the UK even *triggers* article 50, what'll happen when they do trigger it and then eventually leave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder where you alt-right people will be when the UK's economy tanks. . .further. . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also wants to blow up Iranian boats if sailors put the finger up to a US ship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would the situation be with an EU army? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he really the man to steady the ship and get us playing good football again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Expeditionary Force - EF - Optional Branch countries can chose to opt into responsible for power projection on the world stage. Entire army composed around navy e.g. US Navy

Never going to happen. If this is even a remote possibility then the EU Army is dead on arrival. The vast majority of people and countries will be against it *because* it'll be like the US navy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Libya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's defensive then I'm for it, but if it's for invading Countries like Libya, completely leveling the place and then leaving it to Islamists then no chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking the piss. She has her 7 year old daughter's head filled to brim with non-sense that she's now cowering in her mother's arms because one of the most corrupt politicians in American history didn't get elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why Trump won Michigan and the rest of the rust belt, he actually went there and said the right things, while Hillary didn't bother going to Michigan *once* since the Primary.

Michael Moore talks about exactly this in his new documentary (try and ignore the jarring music). 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wxDRqeuLNag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More people have been deported than even before under Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to Hillary Clinton's relentless propaganda worked, do people honestly think Hillary would do more to help the average woman than Trump would to help the poor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? what could possibly go wrong. . .

Worried Daughter (climbing on to the sofa to cower in my arms): I dont want to go to school today. I feel like I wont smile at all. Why do people hate girls and people with brown skin? What did we do wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Germany don't real either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 15:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ireland itself had 2 female presidents, how stupid is this woman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This ones better I think https://imgur.com/nau216L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you read the story of Detroit and then what Trump went there and said it's hard to imagine how anyone thought Hillary could win in Michigan. 

[Michael Moore even called it](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wxDRqeuLNag) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hadn't been there since the primary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rubbish. Any and all hard data says otherwise. 

https://theintercept.com/2016/02/24/with-trump-looming-should-dems-take-a-huge-electability-gamble-by-nominating-hillary-clinton/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Green Party candidate took a pile of votes from her Florida causing her to lose Florida. 

Did Gary Johnson not take more from Trump than Stein from Hillary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you bother reading the article?

People often talk about racism/sexism/xenophobia vs. economic suffering as if they are totally distinct dichotomies. Of course there are substantial elements of both in Trumps voting base, but the two categories are inextricably linked: The more economic suffering people endure, the angrier and more bitter they get, the easier it is to direct their anger to scapegoats. Economic suffering often fuels ugly bigotry.

And some counties that voted Trump, voted Obama. From the article *again*

Low-income rural white voters in Pa. voted for Obama in 2008 and then Trump in 2016, and your explanation is white supremacy? Interesting.

https://twitter.com/TPCarney/status/796384207631159297

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/economics/12146579/India-overtakes-China-as-worlds-fastest-growing-major-economy.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Majority of white women did. Hillary only got 51% of the educated white women as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, India is the fastest growing (major) economy in the world, the number of people in abject poverty is plummeting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What actually happens if the VP dies, is there another VP election or just hope and pray the actual president survives the term?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Fiscal union

It'll never happen. Where we are now Germany has all the benefits of a fiscal union without any of the drawbacks. In the US the likes of California and New York have to subsidise other states every single year. Good luck selling that to the German people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *fantasy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alcohol Will Be Banned in Public Spaces During the 2022 Qatar World Cup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 15:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 14:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their GDP is absolutely terrible. One of the most resource rich countries in the world with a population twice Germany's but a GDP half Germany's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 13:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To make matters worse they're one of, if not, the most resource rich countries in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing Florida man it was probably Harambe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theoretically you could win with something like 25% of the popular vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And QPR need a manager. . .coincidence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 21:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is literally just a list of tweets, who upvotes this shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary won't be swore in until the end of January and won't order a carrier fleet sent to the Mediterranean on her first day,  4 or 5 months at the earliest before she orders anything and by that time the war could basically be over in all but name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Visual Studio isn't even that bad and that's so massive these days it's nearly it's own operating system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 14:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  why on earth would i when there are IDEs out there that save me a LOT of work?

For God sake don't start. Just don't. /r/Programming has these debates (read: flame wars) every now and again and they're never fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  his policies belong in a children's coloring book.

This is brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ireland has like 7 or 8 different parties and 20 independents at the minute. No party came anywhere near a majority.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [@QalaatAlMudiq Now: Rebel withdrawal from whole 1070 Project as supply line is cut off.](https://twitter.com/QalaatAlMudiq/status/795944105612288000) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 21:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should tell Colm Cooper he's now an international celebrity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kF6xuXu7zIA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 11:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guna guess he's American where full grown adults can't even buy alcohol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the one posting this shite here because you and your internet friends were called far right and you're just looking for people to say you're not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 12:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't? Have you been to /r/europe, /r/worldnews, /r/news, /r/the_donald (and related subs the_farage etc) lately?, the genuine hatred of anyone not white in almost every major sub is obvious for anyone to see and then there's the stormfront brigade and /pol/ brigades and the list of things really does go on.

If you want a list of far right subs just go to 'other discussions'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 10:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its from /r/hardware </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is absolutely nothing to be said for him. If the club had thoughts of sacking him they should've just done ages ago and got in Steve Bruce, now though I'm struggling to think who we could realistically get that might actually be decent. Seen people looking for Warburton but I can't see him leaving Rangers for us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MacBook Pro Wi-Fi isssues when using USB-C </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 16:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did he do (twice) as a matter of interest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 17:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would the Shia militias on Iran's payroll not make a big difference as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 16:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a referendum to repeal the 8th was voted down it would be for no other reason than this arrogance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  One could also call some sections of the rebel umbrella terrorists.

FTFY. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 13:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is the last chance to leave in once piece, basically? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 16:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I hope the straights will forgive me

To the gallows with you, I say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 11:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leading members of the House of Lords have also spoken of plans to delay Brexit by **threating** to withold approval of Article 50.

Threat**en**ing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 22:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually an 'i' for Katib as well? as in Katib h**i**zbollah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. . .just looked up Akula and ya numbers for torpedoes and SAMs but not Kalibr. Strange. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wikipedia page would most likely have it listed under 'Armament' for each of the subs/ships. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The fresh fish itself though, it should not have a strong "fishy" smell at all. 

Should hardly smell at all. Get a fresh fillet of Salmon and you'll have to stick your nose right up to it to get any smell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The weeks are really going by, 82 for Servo and 154 for Rust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Weeks In Servo 82 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 20:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 77,185 said they speak the language every day outside of the education system, a further 110,642 said they speak Irish weekly, **while 613,236 said they speak Irish less often.**

Rubbish. Those ~600,000 can't speak a word of Irish outside of "Will ya have some Binne in your tae" and "Tiocfaidh r l". It's no different to about 80% of the population say they're Catholic even though most only go to mass at Christmas and Easter and couldn't name 3 of Jesus' disciples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 14:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Factual answer == Pedantic Bullshit. . .ok?

I think you need to cut down on the green. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 13:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/VKcAYMb5uk4?t=8s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on DX: GNOME and Rust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 10:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 23:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything in football has to be 'BREAKING' these days, from rubbish, made up transfers rumours to Jos Mourinho farting in a bathroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 13:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clubs will get fined for a single fan flying a single Palestinian flag ffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 11:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot have moved to Syria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . . .great? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 14:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully languages like Rust continue to grow to make multithreading easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 23:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't live around loftus road so this is the first game I've watched in a long time, but that 4-4-2 did not inspire any confidence. The defense was exposed every time and the attack was toothless, it's like we didn't have a midfield. Everything in attack should be going through Chery in the middle imho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot about Leeds, seems like an eternity ago . . . . . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never get excited for QPR on sky sports. Fuck me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tesla doesn't even have the best electric cars either, these people need to stop drinking the Musk brand Koolaid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun store runs ad saying it wont sell to Muslims, Clinton supporters. . ."I dont feel safe arming them." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 19:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://github.com/servo/servo/issues?q=is%3Aopen+is%3Aissue+label%3AE-easy

It's *extremely* easy to get started, the easy tags are usually mentored as well and there's also the #Servo IRC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 17:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  released

It's not a product with a ship date, it's a continuous process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 01:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Samsung has been involved in the Servo project for a long time and web browsers have to use webkit on iOS so there's no Gecko to replace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 23:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe take a look at Ferris' live coding videos? he codes a Nintendo 64 emulator from scratch. There's 12 videos and they're a few hours long each 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fsi9HPcyrU8 index=1 list=PL-sXmdrqqYYcznDg4xwAJWQgNL2gRray2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither. Components in Servo *now* e.g WebRender will migrate *to* Gecko. Both projects continue as normal it's just there'll be more overlap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the drivers are unsupported

Never had a problem with drivers on 2 laptops over 4 or 5 years of Mint from 14 to 18, that's general use not gaming though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 22:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking at the highest end XPS 15 for 2,049.00 so probably about 500 less than the macbook and it has a 15.6" 4K Ultra HD (3840 x 2160), i7-6700, 16GB ram (upgradable to 32), GTX 960M and 512GB SSD. It also has 2 usb 3.0, 1 HDMI, 1 thunderbolt and 1 sd slot. Whatever it's missing (if anything) certainly isn't worth the extra 5 or 600 euro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quantum also covers projects which are incorporating Servo's ideas (but not code) into Firefox, or even things unrelated to Servo.

If you're incorporating Servo ideas but not code does that still mean the code will be written in Rust not C(++)?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The TL;DR is that components *from* Servo are being integrated into Gecko. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a talk by Jack Moffit from a few weeks ago about some of the components involved (Stylo, Webrender etc), it contains some unbelievable benchmarks between different engines.

[Jack Moffitt - Servo: Today   Tomorrow](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UGl9VVIOo3E feature=youtu.be)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intel's IoT sector is already doing brilliantly, it's growing massively every single year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Wiki Page](https://wiki.mozilla.org/Quantum) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also the original post of this link on /r/Rust https://www.reddit.com/r/rust/comments/59oggb/a_quantum_leap_for_the_web_contains_updates_on/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to read more this is the [wiki page](https://wiki.mozilla.org/Quantum). . .and there's also a [post I made a week ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/rust/comments/584340/whats_the_status_of_the_firefox_oxidation_project/) with comments from people actively working on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Servo was always an R D project, it was never going to be a finished product in the same way Firefox is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 12:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2016/09/09/manchester-derby-match-on-course-to-become-the-most-watched-matc1/

with the Premier League confirming what it calls its household reach stands at a record 901 million, a figure that does even not account for multiple viewers in many of those homes or people watching in pubs and clubs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The US could stop right now building any military equipment and still be the worlds leader in military hardware for the next 50 years. Wrap your head around that for a moment." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 01:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It sucks that Servo isn't going to replace Gecko in desktop Firefox anytime soon

There is huge amounts of working ongoing though. You can read more comments about the progress in my post here https://www.reddit.com/r/rust/comments/584340/whats_the_status_of_the_firefox_oxidation_project/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WebVR Coming to Servo: Part 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they do get the brunt of the political bias in his papers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SOHR: 2746 IS fighters, 2814 rebel and Islamist fighters and 3804 civilians have been killed by the RuAF since its campaign began in September 2015

http://www.syriahr.com/en/?p=51553

The SOHR is very biased the rebels as well btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone count how many lines of code is in Rust or Servo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  SHILLARY RAPES TURTLES. 

Thank God I don't live in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia is going building 3 supercarriers FYI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 16:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/user_history_bot @subject4941
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 12:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you I was very confused since teams have won all 6 games in the group plenty of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure enough the first This week in Servo in 2 weeks just happens to have 9 screenshots of Firefox and Stylo side by side, to my untrained eye there doesn't seem to be much difference between them anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 00:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> `your PATH on fire`

`Mind and senses purified`

`your PATH on fire`

`Mind and senses purified`

`your PATH on fire`

`Mind and senses purified`

[Northern Ireland v Ukraine. Will Griggs on fire! Lyon - Euro2016](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Rq7aJ09yp1w). First thing I thought of reading the title  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title in the post (and this I suppose) should be Serv*ice* should it? Like in the github repo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 23:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Already posted an hour ago](https://www.reddit.com/r/syriancivilwar/comments/585q03/us_and_uk_reject_russian_offer_of_syria/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 22:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely massive win, right up there now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Poetry] Girl honks at a ship (Loudish) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 21:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's Gerry Adams alt account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the status of the Firefox Oxidation project? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wiki doesn't seem to have been updated since June 6th. https://wiki.mozilla.org/Oxidation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is though that if these extra threads aren't already utilizing all the current 4 cores what difference will an extra 2 make? As far as I know it's almost never the CPU that's the bottleneck when playing games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game engines rely on single threaded performance way more than anything else. Nearly all the main game logic occurs in the main thread.

Stackexchange has a good thread on this https://gamedev.stackexchange.com/questions/7338/how-many-threads-should-i-have-and-for-what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the status of Iran around Mosul, any Iranian commanders or anything there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 18:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If ISIS doesn't already know where the 10s of thousands of soldiers are attacking from then their chances of surviving just went from nearly to 0 to exactly 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A professional foul is a jersey pull or ankle tap this was a full on kick to his leg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 17:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cynical challenge is more an ankle tap to stop a break this looked more like a full on kick, like a lash out nearly. Red is *maybe* harsh but not really surprising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carl Cox and John Digweed are the oldest of the lot... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 15:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He isn't even that Underground. Like he's the headline of any festival he plays at, was resident of Space Ibiza for over 20 years and has played in nightclubs all over the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
