<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6412</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I knew it reminded me of something, but I couldn't think of exactly what... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 11:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it were made for Americans the same button could just have three Z's on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When C-3PO says, "Thank the maker," he's thanking Darth Vader. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 22:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 08:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In grade school, a small argument ensued when our substitute teacher began telling us that Ben Franklin was such a great president that they put him on the hundred dollar bill. That was a weird one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: There's pork bacon and there's turkey bacon... why no beef bacon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 15:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 19:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be a fairly happy person, content and polite. Nobody has a perfect life, but mine was okay for the most part. About 4 years ago, a plow hit me while trying to make a left at a red light. I know for a fact that this moment was the exact, precise, unequivocal moment that changed everything. My car was a wreck. Drivable, but a wreck. We pulled to the side and the young-ish plow driver asked me not to call the police as he would lose his job. So I didn't. Exchanged info and that was that. DON'T EVER DO THIS. No matter how minor the accident, call the police so a record exists. Needless to say, the guy fell right off the face of the planet. I was forced to get a new car out of pocket. Long story short, this began a strange windfall of events that turned me into the much more pessimistic, untrusting individual I am today.

As for the driver, his name and face will be etched into my memory for as long as I live. I'm not a violent person and I'm certainly not fast. But if I ever run into him out in public someday, he better run as fast as he fucking can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 22:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rickman, definitely. I almost feel like he completely captured exactly what I pictured in my mind's eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 22:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like this one a lot for some reason :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 22:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot another big one that stuck immediately for me was Thomas Jane as Wolgast in Justin Cronin's The Passage. The moment I read the description for the character, it was the first face that came to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 22:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oddly no. I find that my mind just sort of does it automatically. And once it's there, it sticks even if I'm not thrilled about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
