<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4159</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Badeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ass fasho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> feelsbadman. I wanted Diamond this season. I got pretty close but kept demoting to plat 5 and then went up and back down constantly. Dont think im gonna get Diamond this season. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA] Plat 4, 665W 668L </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: IGN:Kindlee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 07:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be cool. Props man. Usually everyone on Reddit has regurgitated ideas that want front page just for their own sexual satisfaction. Cudos man, an OG post! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 08:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Survey is dumb. Just let the creators do their thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 06:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprised most people aren't concerned about how he could potentially lose a shit load of money because he's ignorant. Now why don't you wonder why the wall in your bedrooms' color is that color and then post about it on Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your mom </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what concerns Redditors now a days? The shade of color they use? Come on man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've waited too long :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does mac get a client update so i can actually play it as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 22:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried submitting a poem last month to them to see if they would respond. Nope, they gave me an automated response and i emailed back and they didn't say nothing back. Feelsbadman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 23:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've clocked over 4k ranked games and have never been gifted a skin :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 07:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puny bronzy! Your opinion doesn't matter to me! For I am strong and you are weak!!! *intensely rubs nipples* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 09:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How you make it so that your homescreen wallpaper is super dark like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 09:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Download ifile go to /system/library/coreservices/systemversion.plist, edit doc, where it says string9.3.3/string change it to 9.0.3. Press done, close ifile and cydia from your backgrounded apps and then you can download anchor :D works for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 01:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should get something to change the font on the lock screen to make it look like vice city text </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 01:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How you get your folders to be raised so high up? And big font? Oh and what repo do you have for custom wallpapers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jailbreak for mac? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 21:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 19:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wish i had 8 ms :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone forget? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 18:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 06:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thought the exact same thing lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 01:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linkarino? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 16:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'de play the dick out of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summoner spell timers for the enemy team, if they are in vision and blow a summoner it should show on your tab menu. That's just my opinion though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 23:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Fox Needs to be Talked to </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 04:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, full disclosure i'm not an expert on the LCS i'm just a viewer and a regular league player.

I also know that Rick Fox knows some things about the game exemplified in an interview [How Well Does Rick Fox Know League of Legends?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sN_CSXKr8EY) but he really needs to know A LOT more. If you look at TSM's owner Reginald or OG's owner xPeke they used to play League professionally and can step in when they're losing control of their team. That's why TSM has always been very prominent in the LCS, not because of the players are underperforming but because they aren't being instructed properly.

Rick Fox needs to realize that his team is in danger of relegations and he could potentially lose a lot of money that he put in with high hopes for his new organization. But he can learn the game more in depth at a later time.

Right now he just needs to get a new coach for his team and someone that can understand drafting. The draft in the 2nd TSM game was embarrassing. Only person that had wave clear on their team was lucian, if he bought a static shiv that is.

I'm not putting down the players of Echo Fox either, they just need someone to guide them and Rick needs an adviser. It's a business and he's about to lose it.

Edit: Grammer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 20:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a shame. Would really like that skin. Thats what needed to know thanks :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pax sivir skin on ebay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 20:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought i heard that riit doesn't redeem skin codes anymore. Is it legit or a scam can't find anything about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 00:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1st comment rekt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 21:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay this made me lawl :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 21:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im platinum and enjoy beating on = gold scrubs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 09:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah happens to me too sometimes. It happened ALOT last week for me idk whats up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 02:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it night shift in the brightness settings? Could be on for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 09:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just put it this way. When i play against bronze or silver or even gold on my smurf, I think of them as babies and treat them as such and usually win the game easily like 20+ kills :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 04:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's not fixed what are you talking about lol? you right click at one point and then a + left click at the same point and it moves you to that target before you auto attack again. this is legit a serious problem with ur game and makes adc's life very hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
