<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9746</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little late to the party but Tyrion Lannister and Kaz Brekker could probably get away with anything if they plotted together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At lollapalooza a few years back I think it was Foo Fighters and Explosions in the Sky. I chose Explosions and don't regret it one bit. I do love the Foo Fighters though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because one of my close friends found out she was cheating on me and confronted her and then told me. Unfortunately, it was only one person's word against hers and I told her if she wasn't happy or didn't want this that she could leave now. She said she truly wanted to be with me and, me being the sucker I was at the time, I believed her. She then started going out with a bunch of "guy friends" every night that she never used to do before my friend found out about her extra curricular activities and would rub my nose in it by calling me at 2 or 3 AM when she got home from those guys' houses. I take a lot of that blame because I should have ended it but man I felt like a piece of shit after it all. Cut all communication the month after. We were dating for almost a year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 00:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ctrl+f "Cowboy Bebop" 


Excellent, Excellent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 15:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I still listen to it frequently on Spotify. What a great game overall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 20:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a few that I think were missed: 

Morning View - Incubus

The Earth is Not a Cold Dead Place - Explosions in The Sky

Tourist History - Two Door Cinema Club

Kintsugi - Death Cab for Cutie 

Blue Sky Noise - Circa Survive 


Those are the few that come to mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 18:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *SPOILERS FOR ASOIAF*

I will never forget reading in A Dance with Dragons 

"For the Watch" 

I remembered waking up in the middle of the night after hearing those words in my dreams. What a fantastic chapter that bestowed utter disbelief onto the reader. Well done, George.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
