<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject695</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the time, I will hear these songs but not know the name of them or who they are by.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly wasn't sure which song is Party Rock Anthem and looked it up just now. Yeah, I heard that song many times but I never knew the name of it or the artist. Now I know!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 07:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, me too! I was around 6 or 7 when Peewee' Big Adventure came out and it took me awhile to not look away every time that scene appeared. My cousins relentlessly made fun of me for this:)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 09:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The principal is male, not female.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 07:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignore him. His previous posts show that he's just a troll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 07:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, not anger issues. Just classroom management and inability to connect with the students. I thought about going into administrative, but I unfortunately can't afford to go back to school right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 05:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand completely. I have a b.s. in education degree that appears to be pretty much worthless because I found out the hard way that I'm not fit to be a teacher. After being unemployed for nearly a year, I enlisted in the military (Air National Guard)  to get benefits and some income.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 03:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your sentence structure is very bizarre, similar to Lark Voorhees's writing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 03:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eww, no thanks. That just reminded me of Win Ben Stein's Money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 01:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, that Michael Jordan is so niggardly about tipping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 23:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I worked there in the late 1990s in Ohio as a teenager and they didn't have that back then. I wonder if it depends on which state you live in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 05:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you are mistaken. It was Red Shoe Diaries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 07:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. I'm pretty sure she means all corn sugars. If it is listed as part of the category of "Corn:" , then she doesn't mean every food sugar. What she should do, is make new cards with better formating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 05:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that makes more sense. I apologize for  insulting you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 03:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry you are being downvoted. Apparently these people aren't familiar with Operation Ajax and Operation PBSUCCESS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 13:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 13:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot Gone, Baby Gone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 04:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic Alice in Chains  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 23:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have you tagged as probably a writer from the final season of Dexter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 01:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I wouldn't be able to sell or trade in the older 3ds because the buyer would want the charger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 01:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Bayonetta 2 and that they included the first game makes it such a good deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-23 02:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Fall starring Gillian Anderson and Jamie Dornan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 20:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not familiar with the story, what did they do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 21:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why Resident Evil 2 for the N64 is such an awesome technological feat. It has all of the videos and the prerendered backgrounds and characters actually looked better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 18:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://youtu.be/0_QfilVbAd4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 00:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my fetish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 19:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Local and national news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 17:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aroo, Agnew! 
http://i.stack.imgur.com/2aGJ4.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 07:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I never realized he was the Russian mold removal guy. He was great in that episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 18:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, a poop-opticon!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 07:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a guy, I swear that I have been thinking the exact same thing! Bear with me here, as I have had quite a bit of wine tonight, but the desire and need to have a baby is just one of many things I don't understand about women. To me pregnancy and giving birth is horrific and will drastically change your life forever. It seems to me that having children makes living a normal life next to impossible. When someone tells me, "So and so is having a baby", my thoughts are so fucking what? I applaud you for choosing what's currently best for you and your body and for not caving to peer pressure and societal ideals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 03:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely recommend Arrested Development if you hate stereotypical, clichd sitcoms. I did find what you said to be really funny and refreshing to hear from a female perspective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 02:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sorry, it's a joke from Arrested Development:-P 
http://giphy.com/gifs/wOfmYO0pFGpDa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 01:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marry me! Seriously, I'm friending you now:-)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 22:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, that reminded me of this:

 http://alliosnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/12/a-christmas-story-o.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 08:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You live on the set of the TV show, Dallas? Awesome, what is Patrick Duffy like in person?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 07:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not a bullshit story. Toyota knew it was a problem and covered it up. 

http://abcnews.go.com/Blotter/toyota-pay-12b-hiding-deadly-unintended-acceleration/story?id=22972214

Edit: Good job downvoting someone who provided facts that burst your bubble that Toyota can't do no wrong. Can't disprove the facts? Just downvote them instead. Well fuck you, and your Toyota lovefest. 

Edit 2: Hahaha, keep proving my point, assholes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 06:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Crackle it is, then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 06:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you completely, thank you for saying what I am thinking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 23:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider myself to be very liberal but for some reason I can't stand Lena Dunham.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 22:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you and your big ugly face is an unfunny joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-07 22:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, that ruins it for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 03:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been wondering if any of these flipping shows are staged. Can you tell me how you know for certain?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-05 03:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to be that most guys who flip houses are dicks. For example, Scott Yancey of Flipping Vegas and Jeff of Flipping Out are some of the biggest dickheads I have seen. The job must attract people with megalomaniacal personalities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 11:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should call your county job and family services office to find out what is going on. They are there to help you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 10:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me so goddamn sad:-( even though I don't know you. I hope somehow you are strong enough to fight it. Do you have people to talk to for support to help you out when you have urges?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 08:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he wasn't the same after she died. Her family blamed him and he blamed himself and went into a deep self-destructive depression.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 08:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is a strange song and it unfortunately turned out to be his swan song. It's about how he blamed himself for his girlfriend's death.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
