<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1966</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he felt hurt enough that he needed an out. It's possible she wasn't outright rejecting him so that he still had some hope, and he needed a straight answer so that he could move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gray-mane or Battle born </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude smuggled a skull from the catacombs to America then fucked it, effectively turning it into the world's riskiest flesh light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We ded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 03:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fridge horror implied in this is astounding, though, friend. The implication is that rape and domination and enslavement aren't, by daedric standards at least, evil. Your very own criteria suggests that it is only the minds of men and met that make such actions evil.

The insight here, perhaps, is that daedra thoroughly lack objectiveness. If they all merely take an interest in a handful of activities... is it any different from a young Khajiit dabbling in the arcane? 

Now, I am not defending these activities. But the implications of your observation are troubling, and may explain more of mortal affairs than I'd like to admit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skyrim also hints at dissent in hammerfell with a quest very similar to the synth quest that hinted at fallout 4.

In fallout 3 you hunt a refugee synth. Fo4 takes place in the Commonwealth and centers on synth conflicts.

In skyrim you hunt a refugee redguard who either sold out to the thalmor or betrayed the thalmor. Tes 6 is theorized to center on another conflict with the aldmeri dominion. Maybe Hammerfell with a dlc in the isles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
