<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6129</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   we lose our country once and for good (or for another 50 years maybe), or you guys will lose here in Ukraine.

You already lost your country, mate, the moment your Govt send the troops to shoot at their own. Donbass, as Crimea, is not your country anymore and only a blind person won't get it. You will lose in the rest of Ukraine, from where the blood thirsty scum filling the lines of the ultranationalist Ukro-Nazi Bandera rabble battalions come too.  Why? 'Cause people will realize that Maidan did not change the system, it simply put even more unscrupulous and corrupt ppl in charge. The difference ? They serve their own interests better and exploit the artificial divide they themselves created and fostered. Although it will be too late. I'm not Russian, not former USSR either, my country is in the EU but I've seen all that type of transformations and foreign exploits before, 25 years ago and was also for a change, on the side of where the honest ppl on Maidan stayed and got used by the corrupt who took over shortly. They went thru one and the same CIA script all over Eastern Europe. You are no exception. Good luck in your delusions and  - ,  - ,  - .   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [  -   ](http://censor.net.ua/news/433238/ubiyitsa_voronenkova_byvshiyi_boets_natsgvardii_istochnik_tsenzornet)

[      ](http://112.ua/glavnye-novosti/ubiyca-voronenkova-umer-v-bolnice-379717.html)

[        .](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/C7mfqgiXgAIP1m5.jpg) JK. 

   : https://twitter.com/myrevolutionrus/status/844881964293390337   . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Losing it, I see... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Ukraine, all military secrets are in the open. Could be anything, doubt it has anything to do with Donbass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are talking out of your ass though you were explicitly told that the ppl that were set on fire and killed in the Trade Union building had nothing to do with the clashes in downtown Odessa (if u r talking about that ofc as you seem quite delusional and far from what has happened). Also we are talking Maidan here but it's no wonder liberal fascists will spin and avoid truth. Huey Long and Jim Garrison were both right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of us, as usual. Defending the right cause is not work, bud. If that's your only argument, carry on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it thousand times -Set Kiev on fire, take them out IRA style, bring the war to their doorsteps and the war will be over in a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unarmed my ass. You are oblivious and delusional or haven't seen a single video from the square. At least watch Oliver Stone or the french journo documentaries before you talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US army leaked on bringing troops to Ukraine for joint exercise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moderate drinking linked to lower risk of somebut not allheart conditions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m1jbML6_s9E feature=youtu.be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Entire Ukrainian city being evacuated as munitions depot catches fire, explodes (VIDEOS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN: Title, content, discontent and disconnect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find the whole UN report and DL it and check the graphs there. There are all kind of comparative charts in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmaker says U.S. foreign surveillance 'unmasked' Trump associates | Reuters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Saakashvili ran away they don't have whom to laugh at and ridicule in their songs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the mob on Maidan Sq which attacked and killed security policemen guarding it? Did they ask for it too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you mean as they did with the unconstitutional coup d'etat and deposition of democratically elected Pres after Maidan? It's not something new for them to wipe their asses with their own laws -that's more of a rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Akika Kurata)... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kai Fine Art: (Akika Kurata)... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats Embrace Russia Hysteria Conspiracy Theorist Louise Mensch. The fun starts here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happiness Index in our neck of the woods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a new trend the MSM applies lately called selective bias. It's quite funny and beyond entertaining. After reading such a twisted BS I start  thinking very highly of myself :))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You conflate the title (which is intentionally construed to invoke negative attitude towards Kobzon) with what he really said. No where in his words I see 'happy', explicitly or implicitly. It might be somewhere in the rest of the interview but def not in the quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French Interior Minister Bruno Le Roux Resigns - WSJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  theres nothing good coming out of Russia 

It's still winter. I guess the heat around you comes from Russia. Cutting SWIFT is a good idea, things will get switched to a different system, a monopoly doesn't serve anyone. Closing borders? Fiiiine. Just Do It. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Guardian view on the French campaign: a defining election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank that lent $300m to Trump linked to Russian money laundering scam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank that lent $300m to Trump linked to Russian money laundering scam...or if you didn't know Russia owns Deutsche Bank now you know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyber Firm at Center of Russian Hacking Charges Misread Data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a play of words, associations, alliteration and connotations, some semantic shit, to be frank:

First, it contains allusion to the KKK:

Creation and naming

A cartoon threatening that the KKK will lynch scalawags (left) and carpetbaggers (right) on March 4, 1869, the day President Grant takes office. Tuscaloosa, Alabama, Independent Monitor, September 1, 1868. A full-scale scholarly history analyzes the cartoon Guy W. Hubbs, Searching for Freedom after the Civil War: Klansman, Carpetbagger, Scalawag, and Freedman (2015).[46]
Six Confederate veterans from Pulaski, Tennessee created the original Ku Klux Klan on December 24, 1865, during the Reconstruction of the South after the Civil War.[47][48] The name was formed by combining the Greek kyklos (, circle) with clan.[49] The group was known for a short time as the **"Kuklux Clan"**. The Ku Klux Klan was one of a number of secret, oath-bound organizations using violence, which included the Southern Cross in New Orleans (1865) and the Knights of the White Camelia (1867) in Louisiana.[50]

But also from C. Doyle's Sherlock Holmes:

Have you never said Sherlock Holmes, bending forward and sinking his voicehave you never heard of the Ku Klux Klan?

I never have.

Holmes turned over the leaves of the book upon his knee. Here it is, said he presently: Ku Klux Klan. A name derived from the fanciful **resemblance to the sound produced by cocking a rifle**. This terrible secret society was formed by some ex-Confederate soldiers in the Southern states after the Civil War...."

So, briefly, **BLOODY EVIL RUSSIA**. Doesn't matter that the Klan historically was a pillar of the Democratic party in the US. Just browse Klan, Democratic Party and you will see some nice pics from 1924 :)))  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She lives in the States. And you posted quite a wall of text partly right, partly wrong e.g that last quote you posted above. Europe has never ever been 'a monolith of sorts'. Also Holland/the Netherlands has quite a history of colonialism itself. That's no better as a statement than what she blurted. Just saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   ANNEMARIE TOEBOSCH

Uhhhh... she's Dutch.

[Dr. Toebosch is a Germanic linguist that has published on the morphosyntax of Dutch and Plautdietsch (a language of Netherlandic Mennonite immigrants in the Americas) and on language variation in Brussels. She teaches the Dutch language courses and has additional teaching experience in Linguistics, Composition, and ESL.](https://lsa.umich.edu/german/people/faculty/toebosch.html)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more they lose ground, the more outlandish they become. I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, come on, man. Ofc, the Russians are to blame that Tillerson doesn't want to meet with the NATO asswipes. You are obviously not in the loop./ssssss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit's New Profile Pages Will Let Users Add Pics and Bios (Hello, Faceit.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>    </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, Maxine, you're so funny. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Niall Ferguson: Why the West is now in decline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>       </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And to get back to my friend Steinbeck who used to quote Burns and the immortal Will, too - did we miss the Winter of Our Discontent again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exclusive: Tillerson plans to skip NATO meeting, visit Russia in April - sources | Reuters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 09:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russias North Pole station in the making </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 08:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.unz.com/akarlin/russians-are-happier-now/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IMF delays more aid to Ukraine to assess cost of blockade | Reuters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 07:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Russia Recruited Ernest Hemingway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
