<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3861</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conservatives: advocating for a smaller government that's just large enough to kill you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, isn't that lovely. 

I really hope this killing spree isn't allowed to take place, but I'm not too optimistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who has so much has taken a course in journalism knows that there are cases where anonymous sources are acceptable, and necessary. My guess is that the "journalist" who wrote this knows that, but is just pushing an agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dean Heller Suddenly Reverses Planned Parenthood Stance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case, you'd better kiss investigative journalism goodbye, because that isn't happening without anonymous sources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flag of France if it were colonised by Jesus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump's remarkable hypocrisy on transparency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Devastation and a war that rages on: visiting the valley hit by the Moab attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkeys Vote Could Mean the End of a Courtship to Join the E.U. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Is there really such a thing as a straight communist?"

Nope, they're all gay, apparently. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Influential German MP calls for end of EU talks with Turkey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grecized America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flag of Canada If it were tinier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One woman deciding not to enter politics is a choice. Every woman deciding not to enter politics is reflective of some other problem affecting society as a whole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And rampant suppression of opposition. That too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really hoping Erdogan was defeated in this vote, but after the way opposition was being suppressed, can't say I'm surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 90% of top mayoral roles 'likely to be held by white men' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be so pessimistic, I feel like John Roberts or Anthony Kennedy will probably tip the vote towards sanity. It's still a bit concerning this is a possibility though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is, the percentages are probably even higher in reality, because a lot of people might hold disgustingly racist views, but not feel comfortable revealing them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bad news for the country. Basically, because of Trump's pick, the court might approve government funding of religious institutions. Which will basically mean government funding of just Christian institutions, since that's the real aim of the religious right. Hopefully the more moderate conservatives on the court will stop this, and I think there's a good chance at least one will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Trump pick aboard, top U.S. court tackles religious rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you see, the problem with that is that Bernie isn't a socialist, and neither is the New Deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MP calls for castration of sexual harassers in draft law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With General Assembly adjourned, crowded 2018 race for Maryland governor begins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds feared buried in Sri Lanka rubbish dump landslide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gas attack was faked, and so was the moon landing, also 9/11 was an inside job. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds feared buried in Sri Lanka rubbish dump landslide </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Single payer healthcare would be great. Literally every developed country can afford to give its people universal healthcare, and even some less developed countries. US healthcare costs are some of the worst in the world, and our system prioritises the health of the wealthy over the health of the poor. We need to make the change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man accused of attacking rally protester says Trump inspired him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royal Navy escorts two Russian warships through Channel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rouhani says Iran needs "no one's permission" to build missiles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Turkey should vote No </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sent to Mexico.

Edit- and since this is coming from CPUSA, expect an ice pick to the head afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be like Trump and spend all your time at your resort golfing instead of doing your job! Now that sounds like a good way to improve quality of life. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not Islamophopic to oppose putting gay people in concentration camps. There is nothing acceptable about what's happening in Chechnya, I don't care what religious beliefs they subscribe to. You can't just accept persecution and genocide as "part of their culture". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration says no U.S. trading partners manipulate currency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a little? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe I miss you so much. 

I can't believe the Trump admin still hasn't come around to condemn what is going on in Chechnya. I guess it's a combination of Trump's love of Russia with the GOP's hatred of gay people that is leading to their inaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Professor Who Predicted Trump's Win is Making the Case for Impeachment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what happens when you let the bourgeoisie do whatever they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia special election is next test for GOP's success under Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.N. rights expert praises Cuba social welfare system; hopes for more dialogue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish this could pass. Sadly, the Republicans aren't going to have it, since they're so intent on bringing back coal (the dirtiest power source) for reasons likely related to donations from the fossil fuel industry. The damage they do to the environment can never really be undone. I'll know who to blame when the consequences of climate change become overwhelming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. His free SUNY tuition policy was spot on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of sad that this is considered a top qualification to becoming president. I personally could care less if a politician is boring or awkward as long as they have good policies and experience. If only this was a sentiment shared by the American public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
