<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7498</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a flawless book. I finished it in one sitting as well. Don't even get me started on Boxer....tears.


If you liked the animal aspect of it, look into *Watership Down* by Richard Adams. It's not as symbolic as Animal Farm, but more of an adventure. It has a very real feel to it, beautifully written, and is basically about Badass rabbits fighting and planning for survival from their perspective. It's longer and has more of a buildup, but again you won't get as much of the humor and allegorical stuff you get with Animal Farm. Although you do get to see some humans through the eyes of the rabbits which is fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard The Martian is incredible in audiobook. I own it too but haven't gotten the chance to start it yet. 

As for 11/22/63, I read the hardcover and it got me back into reading. I loved it so much from start to finish. OP will also get their money's worth because it is long. I've only heard snippets of the audiobook but I'm sure it's great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a copy of [A Constellation of Vital Phenomena](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/18428067-a-constellation-of-vital-phenomena) by Anthony Marra based on very positive reccomendations. I think the story takes place late 90s/early 2000's in Russia. 

I have not read it though yet, but heard the prose is great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! You're in for a treat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. Let us know what you decide to go with then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would go with your gut of what interests you the most.

- **Fahrenheit 451** - This would be my choice for you IF you're not a heavy reader. It's short, easy to understand, shows you the importance of reading and having your own freedom of thought, and extremely relevant to school and education. I'm sure there is a ton of credible academic research out there on this novel for you as well to gather from. 

- **The Road** - Post Apocalyptic, also short, easy to read but deceptive (lots of hidden meaning behind few words), engaging, but VERY bleak. It is a very dark book, both in its setting and emotions. There are endless amounts of things you could talk about in your report about the minimal style. Mccarthy uses very few words of dialogue to convey his powerful messages. 

- **One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest** - This one is my favorite book out of all of them. But if I'm being completely honest with you, I doubt I would have liked it when I was in grade school. It's a bit longer of a read than the other two, but not bad. Kesey creates such a vivid picture of a mental hospital using such astonishing visual descriptions. I think it takes a little bit more getting into initially than the other two, but it was the most rewarding payoff for me in the end. The setting is almost all in one place and not that much happens plot-wise, which is why I think you may like the other two more if you're plot driven. 

All three of these are great books, and I recommend trying to read them sometime down the road (no pun intended). Good luck with your report and have fun reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - To Kill A Mockingbird
- Flowers for Algernon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading Mrs. Dalloway right now and although it was difficult to follow at first I got a hold on the style fairly quickly. There's not really a very exciting plot in this either but multiple perspectives and the characters internal thoughts is really interesting to me now. What helped me with Dalloway is to look up a list of characters names as I go along. Now that things flow easier I realize it's nothing like I've ever read before.  

To the Lighthouse sounds sort of similar from your description, although I haven't read it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, thanks. I love hearing about some of his lesser known stuff from someone that's clearly familar with him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your favorite works by Steinbeck? 

I'm still kinda new at being an avid reader, but Steinbeck has been my favorite writer so far that I've read. I have only read East of Eden, Of Mice and Men, and Cannery Row. Loved them all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this time I thought there were no decent bookstores in my area..looks like there's a great one under an hour away. Going to need to make the trip soon. Not that I need more books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11/22/63 - late 50's/early 60's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read IT so i'm not sure how this recommendation compares and its not a scary novel. I'm pretty sure the only thing in common might be the "heavy childhood" part. But..

*To Kill A Mockingbird* is one of my favorites due in part by the naive, innocent perspective it is told from. I supposedly read it in high school but didnt remember any of it until I tried again a few months ago. It has that vibe of childhood nastalgia when they're playing different games outside in the summers and witnessing adults do things they don't understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds good. Thanks for the tips. And I am in no way turned off by a book that's dark. But i think books I like the most contain a fluctuation of emotions rather than completely gloom in both setting and emotion the entire time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 03:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished *The Road* today. Can confirm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 02:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it. I will add The Orchard Keeper now as well. I tend to really like writing that uses gorgeous prose to capture a vivid image of the setting, so I'm really looking forward to it. I will just have to see for myself if his style is for me or not. I feel like I only caught smaller doses of this in The Road compared to what I might see in his other works.  

Any suggestion for a good starting point with McCarthy after reading The Road? Are they all just as dark or are there any that have a bit more brightness in its atmosphere? I might enjoy something even more if it is not so bleak.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished The Road by Cormac McCarthy. What an experience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So dark and bleak, yet beautiful at the same time. The minimalistic writing reminds me of Hemingway's *Farewell to Arms*, but consistently dark throughout where the latter had fluctuation both in colors and emotions. Both have that sentence structure where they use the word **"and"** about 5 times in one sentence.

This is my first experience with McCarthy. I'm wondering if this same spare and minimal type of writing is what he uses in most of his books, or is it an experimental thing solely for this novel?

I plan on reading his other works eventually and just I'm curious what I can expect. I've heard some of his books can be difficult to understand, but I had no trouble understanding The Road. This might be one of the more readable ones, though? Others I plan on getting to:

- Suttree
- Blood Meridian
- No Country for Old Men
- Child of God
- The Orchard Keeper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to get a Macbook to automatically connect  to a prefered WiFi network.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks great. I actually think I read it in middle school, but that was ages ago and I don't remember any of it. I will have to give it a go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I loved that chapter so much. I think I was hooked as soon as I read this:

*When a child first catches adults out -- when it first walks into his grave little head that adults do not always have divine intelligence, that their judgments are not always wise, their thinking true, their sentences just -- his world falls into panic desolation. The gods are fallen and all safety gone. And there is one sure thing about the fall of gods: they do not fall a little; they crash and shatter or sink deeply into green muck. It is a tedious job to build them up again; they never quite shine. And the child's world is never quite whole again. It is an aching kind of growing.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I haven't gotten to this yet but I've liked the King i've read in the past. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks really enticing. Plus, I live not far from Gettysburg so I will definitely check this out. Do you know if it's best to read Gods and Generals first, or does The Killer Angels work as a stand alone book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A somewhat odd request for a book with particular similarities to The Breakfast Club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for books where there are a group of people, teenagers or adults, that are gathered in a particular setting and become very close by the end of the story.


- I'm looking for a book that will include at least a handful of major characters in a similar situation or setting that may be very different but end up forming a bond. 

- They don't all have to be in one place the entire time like in the Breakfast Club, but they should at least spend a lot of time together throughout the story in a particular situation and form a bond.

- Some other shows/movies that have a similar vibe are *Freaks and Geeks* as well as *Undeclared*. I'm not looking only for comedy books though, but more so the aspect of them sharing a similar situation. I do also like the coming of age part of these such as in a high school or college setting where all the characters attend. This is not essential, however. As long as I can connect with all the characters I'll be happy. 

- **Before anyone suggests it...** I already have read *Perks of Being a Wallflower*, which I did really like. I'm also not that big into Sci-fi or Fantasy unless it is centered around human characters.

- I prefer books that are well written, provide character development, and offer interesting insights on life. Don't stress if you can't pinpoint these traits, I'd rather hear what people come up with and decide on my own if they suit what I'm looking for. 

- That being said, I do also like quality literature as well as lighter books that I can kick back and breeze through. Don't be afraid to suggest any heavy hitters. 

- This might be a weird example and the only similarity i'm thinking about is the particular setting bit. But in *And Then There Were None* I enjoyed how I got to know a group of characters really well cause they were stuck in a mansion together. **I don't** really want mystery suggestions, though. 

I know this might sound like an odd request, but I'm sitting here watching *The Breakfast Club* for the first time in a while and thinking....damn I really love how they knew nothing about each other and by the end, they all formed such a comradery.  

Thanks for the suggestions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Me reading East of Eden:*

**Chapter 1** - Description of the land in Salinas. Okay, I love the prose though even if it's just descriptions of mountains and valleys. 

**Chapter 2** - Meeting the Hamiltons. Alright, here's a family. Nothing really has happened, though. 

**Chapter 3** - Oh here's another family, enough with the introductions alread-- *MOTHER OF GOD.* This is my new favorite book. 

Definitely give it another shot if you loved the wisdom and insight on life that was in Cannery Row. There's a lot more of that to be seen in EoE. You were still at that point where nothing really has happened yet.

EDIT: If you liked Cannery Row mostly because of the comedy, judging by your username, there's not as much of that to be had in EoE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cannery Row is not really centered around a central plot like many novels so that aspect won't really draw you in. Except there is one thing you could consider a plot that will be introduced. It drew me in from the writing and then eventually the characters. It gets incredibly funny and Steinbeck also drops some bombs of wisdom on you out of nowhere. Keep up with it, you're probably still meeting the town and characters if I'm remembering correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I see an East of Eden post I have to come and check out the recommendations people give. It's the epitome of what I look for in a book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me know how you like it. I own this and haven't gotten to it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Road, by Cormac McCarthy**

 - My first McCarthy experience. Very particular in style. Minimalistic in dialogue and descriptions but effective.  Reminds me of the style Hemingway used in Farewell to Arms, except in that there was a fluctuation of dark and bright colors, both in mood and setting, whereas in The Road it has been basically darkness throughout so far. 

*After that:*

**Mrs. Dalloway, by Virginia Woolf**

 - This will also be my first experience with Woolf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some of my favorites that are quick, easy, and engaging. 

- And Then There Were None, Agatha Christie
- Perks of Being a Wallflower, Stephen Chbosky
- The Giver, Lois Lowry
- Flowers For Algernon, Daniel Keyes
- Animal Farm, George Orwell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're into U.S. history *Five Presidents by Clint Hill* was fascinating to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved Cannery Row and Vons is always fun. Going to check these out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's epic. Here are some quick tips.

**1.** Get the Robin Buss translation from Penguin Classics. Unabridged.  

**2.** Read a little bit about France in the 1800's - Bonapartists vs. Royalists. You don't need to be an expert by any means, but a general understanding will make the book that much more interesting. 

**3.** Get familiar with titles of peoples names in the french language and their abbreviations. This will help differentiate the characters when you first start to meet them. Don't worry, you get to know them well while you read. 

- M. -- Monseur = Mister
- Mme. -- Madame = Missus
- Mlle. -- Mademoiselle = Miss

**4.** The scenes in Cristo are notoriously long. So if you ever feel like "what does this have to do with the story, please get back to the main plot"...theres a reason for it. These scenes make the end that much better. 

Besides this, enjoy the ride! There's no denying there are a lot of pages, but once you get into the story the book will fly by and you will wonder where all those pages went. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 17:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said. That's definitely the best approach. Sometimes certain books and authors connect with you better at different stages in your life, so if something bores you now you can always put it down and try again in a few years. Most of the books I read in high school I had to struggle through back then and now I love them after giving them another shot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 16:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome. Also, i'm not sure if this is what your looking for but in regards to *East of Eden*. If you want an intro into Steinbeck's style you could always give *Of Mice and Men* or *Cannery Row* a shot as well. Both are short and have a ton of great outlooks on life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Flowers for Algernon* is basically emotional empathy building 101. It is also a powerful work of self acceptance that holds your attention throughout. Starts out written differently than your typical book, but only initially. It's an emotional ride, just to forwarn you.  

*To Kill A Mockingbird* also taught me a lot about life and the positive and negative qualities that exist in every person. Understanding other peoples perspectives is important. 

Both are easy to read and enjoyable in my opinion. 

I also suggest giving *East of Eden* another shot one day when you're in the mood. I don't know how far you got, but it definitely picks up and has so much great stuff in it:

"And now that you don't have to be perfect, you can be good." - John Steinbeck, East of Eden


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flowers for Algernon is one of my favorites. 

So many great books in there. Nice haul!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only read the first one but it's definitely a fun book. Enjoy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More accurately it was $32 and change. Most of them $3 and a few for $2. I was as suprised as you are when I saw so many books for so cheap. The place sells overstock books so the majority of the books looked terrible to be honest. I had to do A LOT of digging, but i'm glad I did. I feel like these might be cheaper prints, but they look just fine to me as none are abridged. Titles like The Orphan Master's Son, The English Patient, A Visit from the Goon Squad, and many others I recognized by the titles. Others by Russo, McCann, Haruf, and Fallada I recognized by their names and figured they looked decent enough to be enjoyable. They are all in pretty good shape too, the bindings are tight and pages look new on the inside despite some sun damage on the outside of a few. They no longer have that coveted new book smell, but i'm just happy to get a hold of them at all. I will definitely check out Empire Falls now. Thanks for sharing all your experience with these!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's a memoir. I've heard good things about it. Looking forward to reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great to hear. I've had Ragtime on my list for awhile. Historical fiction is an interest of mine so i'm excited to read it. I recognized Christine and decided to go for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not finished yet, but it's really hitting its stride. I was told it could surprise me, so i assumed they simply meant the plot, but the writing itself has definitely exceeded my expectations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Several of them I picked up because I knew the Authors, but am unfamiliar with the books. Anyone read these? I would love to hear some thoughts on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Couldn't hold myself back at a local discount shop. $30 total, fairly new. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watership Down - Richard Adams </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was evening of the following day. The north-facing escarpment of Watership Down, in shadow since early morning, now caught the western sun for an hour before twilight. Three hundred feet the down rose vertically in a stretch of no more than six hundred  a precipitous wall, from the thin belt of trees at the foot to the ridge where the steep flattened out. The light, full and smooth, lay like a gold rind over the turf, the furze and yew bushes, the few wind-stunted thorn trees. From the ridge, the light seemed to cover all the slope below, drowsy and still. But down in the grass itself, between the bushes, in that thick forest trodden by the beetle, the spider and the hunting shrew, the moving light was like a wind that danced among them to set them scurrying and weaving. The red rays flickered in and out of the grass stems, flashing minutely on membranous wings, casting long shadows behind the thinnest of filamentary legs, breaking each patch of bare soil into a myriad individual grains. The insects buzzed, whined, hummed, stridulated and droned as the air grew warmer in the sunset. Louder yet calmer than they, among the trees, sounded the yellow-hammer, the linnet and greenfinch. The larks went up, twittering in the scented air above the down. From the summit, the apparent immobility of the vast, blue distance was broken, here and there, by wisps of smoke and tiny, momentary flashes of glass. Far below lay the fields green with wheat, the flat pastures grazed by horses, the darker greens of the woods. They too, like the hillside jungle, were tumultuous with evening, but from the remote height turned to stillness, their fierceness tempered by the air that lay between. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
