<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject721</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cobb Stage 3 package, then spend the other $7K on Installation, brakes, and paying someone to rip everything out -- assuming I'm looking for "maximum performance".

Not much point in a bigger turbo or anything like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derp. Woops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the Heal from leech not stack? Just refreshes the duration? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video compilation? Just brake check him at 10 mph then ask if he wants to see what 20/30/40mph is like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the use of "still" in his post.

As if anyone's going to swap out the entire drivetrain in their Focus.

Like who was expecting it to be anything but FWD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeaaa. I test drove a Focus and stock the torque steer bothered me.

It's not half as bad in the Fiesta, but it's still noticable and it bothers me every time. 

Can't imagine how it is with this thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That **really** surprises me about Boston. The entire fucking city is a giant melting pot.

Like, going to Faneuil Hall  is one of my favorite things whenever I'd visit. They have food from practically everywhere!

Maine always struck me as "The South of New England" in that I know a lot of ultra conservative, Bible-Belt-esque people from there so it doesn't surprise me a ton... But yea... That's shitty, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (And to reiterate, *even if it is only illegals, it's fear mongering policy designed to control people with their emotions and fight against a boogeyman of the government's creation.) 

I agree; I'm certainly not defending Trump -- I think it's an absurd policy which would provide nothing for the country and is a waste of money. 

I just wanted to make sure I understood it correctly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the most part, welfare and gun control aren't the first things that come to mind when most people think of Hitler.

So, no, again it's not a reasonable comparison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abortion: A conscious decision made by the person who will have the procedure done, which effects exactly zero people beyond the mother and possibly the father.

List of crime committed by specific subgroup of a tiny population: ???

---

What I don't understand is this: Your problem is people are here illegally, correct? So what do crime statistics matter? Whether their only crime is that they snuck into the US or not, you want them out, correct? I'm not saying that's unreasonable, no one likes the concept of their tax money supporting people who aren't paying into the system. **However** I do not see how this list will accomplish/improve anything.

For someone who rambled on about cutting taxes and trimming the budget, you know what I see? Pointless regulation that will only cost money.

Guess what? Legal citizens commit crime, and on a much larger scale than illegals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (b)  To better inform the public regarding the public safety threats associated with sanctuary jurisdictions, the Secretary shall utilize the Declined Detainer Outcome Report or its equivalent and, on a weekly basis, **make public a comprehensive list of criminal actions committed by aliens** and any jurisdiction that ignored or otherwise failed to honor any detainers with respect to such aliens.

That is the exact text of the Executive Order.

Honest Question: Does "Aliens" mean "any non-citizen, regardless of the legality of their being here"?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what state?

I live in the North East, have worked for multiple companies which employ Americans, Canadians, and Indians. Never heard anyone openly take issue with this. Also know a guy from Wales, never heard him say anything like that.

One was a global finance company, the other is a medium/small nonprofit. So, pretty opposite ends of the surgeon l spectrum too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have **you** read it? It very clearly states what people obviously have an issue with:

 (b)  **To better inform the public regarding the public safety threats** associated with sanctuary jurisdictions, the Secretary shall utilize the Declined Detainer Outcome Report or its equivalent and, **on a weekly basis, make public a comprehensive list of criminal actions committed by aliens** and any jurisdiction that ignored or otherwise failed to honor any detainers with respect to such aliens.

So, yes, he literally said to go and publish a weekly list of crimes committed by illegals.


As the other guy said, you can already publicly find information about crimes committed; why do we need a special list for aliens? What is the purpose? What do **gain** for the new overhead created by this special list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Volume of blood on hands and that's about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know Duerte had such influence over ~~Taiwan~~ Thailand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my first thought upon reading the title.

It's easy to make the knee-jerk reaction and say, "Of course mentally ill people shouldn't be able to own guns" but... 'mentally ill' is a big fucking umbrella.

I have ADHD, but I'm not a threat to anyone. If I was told I couldn't purchase a small pistol for personal protection or a hunting rifle because of my attention span issues, I'd be pretty pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, it's pretty interesting to see design ideas from decades ago when car companies were a little more... Open...

He has one or two other series on Japanese imports which are equally interesting, but I think the S-Cargo is the clowniest of them all.

He did do one with a RHD imported Skyline which was interesting. It might be less interesting if you're not as "into" cars in general but rather just enjoy the truly weird stuff, but I thought it was cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would a claw-based Viper Strike build be viable now, with the 1H / claw buffs?

I'm a filthy casual who plays infrequently; last I knew claws are trash and VS is too but I always liked both :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always under the impression that flat LoH is superior early on because you don't have enough base damage for LL% to give you a significant amount, but later on once your damage is better than percent is superior?

Does LoH leech instantly?


Disclaimer: Filthy Casual so bear that in mind if this is a dumb statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I feel every time I decide to reinstall PoE :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blocked at my company (but so is reddit). Womp womp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are claws good now?

I play very on and off, check out a league or two per year so I'm pretty casual.

I was planning on not returning until 3.0, but with all the 1H damage buffs   Claw-specific changes, I'm interested in trying PoE again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 07:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Smoking Tire](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCgeGealT0QYcrnoYRMltDZg) - Primarily does "One Take" videos; drives around random people's cars through some remote-ish back roads in California, usually pretty knowledgeable about many cars.

[Engineering Explained](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UClqhvGmHcvWL9w3R48t9QXQ) - I believe he's an engineer for Nissan. He explains a lot of the science / math behind various car-related technologies

[Chris Harris On Cars](https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC8AMAhCRmep7VJKe1sxvHFg) - Doesn't really get updated much now that he works for the new Top Gear, but all of his old videos are great. Just a charismatic, genuine British guy.

[Mighty Car Mods](https://www.youtube.com/user/mightycarmods/videos) - I don't watch these often, 2 Aussies who film project cars being built and discuss car-related technology and stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't seen this one before.

When he gets genuinely unusual cars like this or the [Nissan S-Cargo](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ee8-6DfMEGE) he's much better. His format doesn't work great with 'legitimately cool' cars, but you can't just easily get easy access to all manner of truly weird cars so you gotta do other stuff too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's quite popular on /r/cars; if you've been subscribed for more than a week you probably know who he he is and what you're getting into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly he has a pretty weird niche, and it doesn't work great on "legitimately cool" cars.

But if you look at some of his other videos like the [Nissan S-Cargo](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ee8-6DfMEGE) he's a bit more genuine because it is a weird car.

I'll admit he's fairly scripted, but overall he provides a particularly different perspective from "traditional" car journalists like Chris Harris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, it's *almost* preferable to The Title is the Punchline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Santoku Does Not have any specific uses (Any site or video claiming otherwise are wrong.) The Santoku is basically The Japanese Chef Knife great with anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, anyone? Guy or girl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A less than well off city in the North East. So most people who could afford a $70K car aren't driving those around here.

I dunno, maybe I have seen one. They look the exact same as a regular Challenger. At least, they do to someone who isn't exceptionally keen on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a '14 FiST.

I'm far from a financial position to switch cars, so that helps keep me planted... But when I'm in a better position the temptation will be strong.

My current plan is to try and hold onto it until it's paid off. I've got 5 years remaining on my student loans and 5 years remaining on the Fiesta. When both are paid off, that will be about $1200 I'm not mailing to a bank every month.

I can save up and buy something fucking *awesome* with an extra $1200/mo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tesla: ... I feel it's overrated.

Compared to what? There is nothing like it on the market.

Yes of course there are more luxurious cars. They have barely been around a decade and a half. It takes time to perfect things.

Of course there are better performing cars, as they don't have to deal with the weight of the battery pack and have different heating concerns.

But what is there that is pretty nice, pretty fast, and **all** electric?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make it sound like the **only** thing the car has its straight line speed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't really call any of them exceptionally popular, though.

I guess I see a good number of Chargers, but far fewer Challengers than I do Mustangs / Camaros.

Chrysler? Who the hell likes Chrysler.

The Hellcat sure does generate a lot of clicks online, but I've never seen one. One of the big-wigs at my company was thinking of buying one, but that's all I've heard about it on real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What?

If you're expecting an automotive journalist's perspective on cars, then yea CR isn't for you. But in just the "general" sense their information is plenty relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things don't cease to exist just because you can't see it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't supposed to?

Who's stopping you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. Test drove both a Fiesta and Focus ST on two separate occasions.

Both times I was handed the keys, salesman was like "Go take it for a spin while I finish up with some other customers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related: disallow the use of the phrase, "love to have fun"

Everyone likes having fun you dolt :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a interesting idea.

I don't know the specific term, but I know people are working on types of software to "understand" language, so it can detect tone/emotions behind words.

It'd be really cool to apply that to automatically disallow the sending of messages by abusive users.

(Just looked it up) Apparently IBM actually offers free limited usage of the software used by Watson? https://www.ibm.com/watson/developercloud/tone-analyzer.html  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
For Dresden Files it's that Harry is sexist AF, even if it's mostly benign sexism.

I read the first book, was advised to skip #2, and started #3 but yea I genuinely disliked just how sexually charged the books were. I mean, there was no downright banging, but so many comments and things just felt wholly unnecessary.

Couldn't finish it. Just didn't care about the mystery, or Harry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What the fuck is this website](http://i.imgur.com/YEAm53L.png)

If I keep scrolling it's just more ads. Christ I hate the internet on my phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'd be a little uncomfortable being in the same room while someone else is digging around my SO's innards. But he/she/they are doctors, and if it'd make her more comfortable, I'd do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. One of the few games to really 'wow' me with its story / atmosphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Punching a train head-on

Choking yourself to death. Being able to maintain the grip after you go unconscious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fencing

* Expensive lessons
* Didn't get on with anyone in my class
* While the Beginner class begins at a set date, the Intermediate class just "exists" until the instructor thinks you're good enough for the next level. So I finished my Beginner class and just get thrown to the wolves

I realize the only way to get better at *anything* is by learning from those who know more than you, but I just didn't like the environment. I'm in my mid/late 20's and most of the class was highschool or early college students. So between not getting along with anyone, also didn't think I was progressing so I said it wasn't worth the $75/mo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "you get it dirty, you clean it up." 

I can understand that mentality when a roommate leaves a dirty dish on the stove... But if one person is cooking for two, the other absolutely should clean it up, yea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really into AC, but wasn't the setting leaked a while ago? I just googled it and I see articles from November. Doesn't look like the mention of Egypt was edited in as an update.

I'm on mobile / at work though so I can't search too thoroughly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have this one beanie hat I really liked, would wear it almost daily in the winter. It was just plain black, with a splotch of green and text overlaying it.

 I was working from home 5 days per week at the time, too. I'd usually walk to the convenience store and grab a drink/snack before work.

One day I didn't have the hat on and swung by the store, the cashier was like, "Hey you're not wearing your Monster hat!"

It has nothing to do with the energy drink at all but I guess I could vaguely see a resemblance from the perspective of someone indifferent to what it actually was. Have scarcely worn it since then :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buffalo NY actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They both just have such cold, beady little eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [?](http://i.imgur.com/vZpHvmc.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think it's even weirder if you [don't resize it](http://i.imgur.com/ep7h8HQ.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see what you mean.

Single male in the foreground, both sitting upright. Hand position is *vaguely* similar. Person takes up the main part of the foreground with a dominant background color (green on the left photo/ red on right painting), with a smaller rectangle of different color to the upper right. Like, even the red from the sunset in the painting is roughly nose height. And the blue container things in the photo are also right about level with his nose (from a 2D perspective)

Very different *colors*, but the raw "framing" is definitely there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/AccidentalRenaissance/comments/5w6skb/the_bride_and_groom/deasfce/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This over-developed piece of trash website](http://tooyoungtowed.org/#/mental-health-violence) seems to be the source.

(Not saying their cause is a piece of trash. Just that from a usability standpoint, it's awful.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's going on here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw them live last week... One of the best shows I've ever been to.

Third time I've seen them; last time the venue sucked ass and the time before that was just after RS1 came out -- which I enjoyed, but it just wasn't a great setlist. Also had to drive 3 hours, each way, on a work night.

Also you didn't link the timestamp for the actual title track :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one HPDE I've done did not require full face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five long years, he wore this watch. Up his ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 22:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't think it's necessary at all.

My two internships I had in college were through my school's Employment Office. One turned into a full time job.

My second job I found through a staffing agency, as well as my current job.

LinkedIn has done two things for me:

* [Leaked my data](http://www.csoonline.com/article/3086942/security/linkedin-data-breach-blamed-for-multiple-secondary-compromises.html).
* Cluttered my inbox with notifications from jerkoff recruiters who didn't read my profile but think I might be an excellent match for this great opportunity they have. 

I would never use 'regular' social media sites like FB, Twitter, Instagram etc. for professional purposes, unless I owned my own business and was using the company page for some reason. 

In that case I can see the argument, but then it's really just marketing   PR, not "social networking". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternatively: city street parking.

That's my problem, anyways :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think I will have massive regrets here? 

Probably. But sometimes you need to do the "smart" thing and not the thing your heart wants.

I sold my 350Z due changes in my commute and I miss it. The Fiesta is great, but I absolutely miss the Z. But it's just much more practical / gas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, did they? I didn't hear about that.

That is pretty douchey, but IMO far from Ferrari and their whole, "If a journalist wants to review our cars, we're sending a tech to tune it for the track they'll be testing on" bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And way more torque.

And cylinder deactivation.

Love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's special about Montana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same boat. I could inherit Bill Gates' fortune and *maybe* I'd buy an F40 but that's it.

Every time one of those "Porsche/Lambo/Ferrari rental autocross" threads pops up I'm just like, I don't care if Ferrari makes legendary cars, they're run by shitlords so for me it's Porsche or Lamborghini.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say Obama inherited a much worse administration going into his first term than Trump, but honest question: What did Obama achieve in his first month?

That just seems like too little time for anyone to do anything, really.

Not defending Trump, I'm just curious what "par for the course" is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No more ugly Thag the current amorphous blob of red than the current gen, IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to look it up out of curiosity. [It's actually the northern states](http://cdn1b.static.pornhub.phncdn.com/insights-static//wp-content/uploads/2016/02/pornhub-insights-us-top-search-terms-map.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pizza Sticks? (I haven't played since before Breach) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As others said, I'd post it for a little more than you bought it for.

Either they meet your price or haggle down and you break even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long do you see yourself keeping the car? Would this be your DD, or just a toy car? If DD, do you need a vehicle?

Unless you really want a roadster, I wouldn't do it personally.

Yes 10K miles is effectively a brand new car, but the Z has proven itself to be a very reliable sports car even at 100-150K and beyond.

Unless you aim to keep the car for a very long time (in which case, the extremely low mileage **is** a huge boon) I'd rather buy something with higher miles but get '06 or newer. I just found an '07 Touring with 78K miles on it for $12K on ebay. Even though I said it is a very reliable car, I'd look for something with closer to 50K than 80K but you get my point.

I'd say sit, save up more money, and find a newer model for a similar price. Z's are only getting cheaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, for the older people today, it's what you write on then stick to your phone to remind you of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard of this game before but yea I went from home,

"Hmm what's this? This looks pretty. Er... hmm.. OK never mind" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As others said, it's likely just the battery. I'd google your year + model and see if you can find the manual which might explain how to change the battery.

I've got a '14 Fiesta and the car warns me that my battery is low but I am dumb and can't figure out how the hell to get it open :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the new headlights+taillights, and the interior. 

I don't like the "we glued a tablet to the dashboard" look but it's less awful than the giant thing in the current gen.

I agree that the body changes to the front aren't spectacular though.

Does anyone know if they Liquid Blue paint will be an option? I read one article which said it is, but I haven't seen any other confirmation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is exactly why those, "hurr durr are the new cars like Group B?" articles that were floating around in regards to this year's faster cars annoys me.

Motorsports are so strictly controlled nowadays. You'll never see a class again so open to do whatever the manufacturer might want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea if you need to season it you're not cooking the pigeon right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 08:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scrolling through /r/all I didn't see the sub, definitely expected r/AnimalsBeingJerks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 08:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's doing job research by playing as a terrorist in order to better spot them in real life, duh. Give that man a promotion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but how many idiots did you hear spewing "Barack HUSSEIN Obama" acting like that's enough to condemn someone over.

Discrimination is against the rules, but you can't easily prove it if/when your opponents [and their supporters] internally discredit you based on it -- and it definitely happens in this country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The moose can only take one one sheep at a time, and the wolf must cross each time a sheep crosses, what are the fewest number of trips to ..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit I had no idea. That's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given this is a racing engine, not a production car, but Nissan makes a 3-cylinder 1.5L which puts out 400HP.

http://www.motorauthority.com/news/1086869_nissan-reveals-zeod-rcs-400-hp-3-cylinder-engine-confirms-2015-lmp1-entry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than Nissan, they had the 370Z race a chicken.

Given it wasn't just *any* chicken, it was Pepe Carrera, but still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect it's probably super rural areas that still only have DSL and no other option </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sincerely wouldn't be surprised... But who the fuck is going to sign up for an ISP that doesn't have to tell you what speed you're paying for!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ive said before, that the president understands the pain and suffering that many people go through, who are facing especially terminal diseases, **and the comfort that some of these drugs, including medical marijuana, can bring to them.**

Is anyone else bothered by the tone here? 

To me, to sounds like he's saying, "I don't really think marijuana has medical benefits, but if the terminally ill want to get high, then fine" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  logic industry.  

He's a programmer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Internet providers with fewer than 250,000 subscribers will not be required to disclose information on network performance, fees, and data caps, thanks to this rule change.

Will not have to disclose the information to *who*? The gov/FCC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Backwards](http://i.imgur.com/KnXkIR0.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Used to work for an international bank. Our production deployments were **only** done on Fridays, and we didn't start until 8PM, so that the banks on the west coast were closed.

Ughhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, but that's a V series. No one's complaining that an M series is "too stiff for a luxury car", are they?

If you want pure comfort, don't buy the performance line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't the first one produce more batteries than any other factory in the world? I thought the first one was sufficient to meet their production needs for a while?

I'm sure it'll be years before 3 more are operational, but it seems questionable to invest in so many so quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the [Required / Prohibited Conduct sections](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fair_Debt_Collection_Practices_Act) of the Fair Debt Collection Practices Act! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 04:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right Click - View Controls, you can pause it and use the arrows to seek through every frame.

You can see it quite clearly [here](http://i.imgur.com/PIubIb4.png). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a carpenter. You ever been on a wooden rollercoaster?

I don't want a wooden train... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU SHOULD GET YOUR INPUT CHECKED, THAT'S TWO BANANAS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I DON'T HAVE MUCH DATA ON IT BECAUSE MY DRIVE HAS BEEN CUT IN HALF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~BARK~~ SHOUT AT THE DEVIL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be confused with /r/totallynotrobots  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea about it until just now, honestly. I've always only seen the ["modern"](http://i2.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/original/000/427/566/b67.jpeg) version.

I was driving to find that one and stumbled across the wikipedia article and was like, "What!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We're both good boys and deserve treats though, I think.

[I agree](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/f/f8/Internet_dog.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 01:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/CoolDinosaurPictures  Wuld like this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those that come up every single time anyone discusses gambling?

https://www.google.com/search?q=gambling+ethics ie=utf-8 oe=utf-8

It is a widely debated topic.

Why do you think most states don't allow it except for state-run lotteries, or casinos in Native American reservations? Or why most professional sports don't advertise official Betting platforms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did hear the i-series do use CF, but I wasn't sure how much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just did a quick Google search... Forum post saying a 350Z hood weighs ~20 pounds, CF is ~17... Very small return for your investment.

Definitely better off saving up $1K for new, lighter wheels. You could drop 3lbs per wheel, **and** that's unsprung weight too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't looked in a long time, so maybe I'm wrong, but to my understanding is that CF hoods are barely lighter than stock so it doesn't make a ton of sense to replace *just* that.

Like for your average autocross driver, would you rather spend $500 and save a couple of pounds, or spend $500 on tires/suspension mods?

Its weight savings becomes significant the more you spend... But for one single thing like that, it's kind of pointless. Only reason not to just get an imitation one is simply to say, "Yes, it's real carbon fiber."

For professional racing teams, it's worthwhile because that's not going to be only weight-saving change, so when you add up all those reductions it becomes significant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not trying to be a dick, but I realize it's expensive today.

The entire pretense of my question is under the guise of it becoming an affordable material, which is why I linked / mentioned the article.

The question is simply:  Does CF behave in a similar enough manner to current materials that we **could** see a world where cars are primarily made out of CF (once the price is worked out), or is its "conditional strength" such that it's not optimal to largely (if not entirely) replace steel/aluminum in current vehicles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Race cars see much more abuse than daily driven cars.

I would argue that each individual collision / "instance of abuse" is most likely far worse for a race car than your daily driver, yes. But these race cars have the budgets of major corporations behind them to fully repair it, no questions asked, after each race.

If you get rear ended in a hypothetical carbon fiber Corolla, have it repaired (based on insurance pay out) and then you get t-boned in the same region but from a different angle... Then how does it hold up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but what I meant is of you're looking at something with a fully CF monocoque, if you're spending that much money on a car, crash test ratings *probably* aren't your top priority.

Like, yes Koenigsegg need to meet minimum safety requirements, but is it going to be "as safe" as something built with traditional materials currently? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The advantage of carbon fibre is that it is extremely strong and light. Meaning that if you could produce it cheaper and put it into more cars, you can achieve great gains.

That's what I'm talking about though. Hypothetically, say CF can be produced at a cost that would make it viable to replace current materials. Is it safe enough for "daily driven, road-going use" that's going to see hundreds of thousands of miles of driving and be subjected to the abuse every Joe Schmoe's DD is subjected to.


Your input on dent/scratch/shatter is interesting though; I hadn't factored repair costs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How safe is carbon fiber for mainstream, daily-driven vehicle use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was reading [this article](http://techau.com.au/mass-production-of-carbon-fibre-solved-by-csiro-and-deakin-costs-set-to-crash/) (which is now no longer loading for me...). Basically a group of scientists/engineers in Australia claim to have invented a "scalable" way to produce carbon fiber, dramatically reducing the cost to produce it.

Now, to my limited understanding, carbon fiber is extremely strong *in one direction*, based on how it's weaved. So for its current usage in things like motorsports or very high-end performance cars,  this isn't as big of deal because:

1) Motorsports have other existing safety regulations (roll cages, Hans device etc)

2) Performance vehicles which currently make extensive use *generally* don't rack up too many miles / aren't bought for their safety ratings

Given its "conditional strength" from weave, is CF actually safe to replace steal / aluminum with for autobody construction for every-day cars that will be the sole means of transportation for millions of drivers? Are they actually safe when considering the wide array of crash test requirements a vehicle must conform to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I wish US plates were as slim and clean looking as EU style.

Looks great with the white ST badge, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously? The Titanium comes with a backup cam and the non-ST gets a glasses holder? I'mma fight someone :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Ya never know...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iZfayydpIKc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? I know our software at work throws up a modal JS window and you can supply functions to be called when any button, including the X.

So if we showed ads we could just do something along the lines of:

    var clickedOnce = false;
    function CloseAd(popupName)
    {
        if (!clickedOnce)
        {
            clickedOnce = true;
            ShowAd();
        }
        else
            ClosePopup(popupName);
    } </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The are plenty of 4 cylinders that will let you "feel what you're driving"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I simply want to participate in each event for my region.

I only got to do 1 last year, and the year before that I did a 'real' track day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything Japanese that meets your financial constraints will be fine, really.

If mileage is your top concern, why V6? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what specifically you're referring to, but the Le Mans Sunset Metallic on the [350Z](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/d/d8/Nissan350Z-01.jpg) is nothing like this Orange Spice color </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like my Molten Orange... But Orange Spice is wayyy nicer :O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the title should probably mention he was drunk, as per the description:

 Horrific footage shows the moment a 45-year-old drunk man driving a four-wheel-drive deliberately speeds into oncoming traffic and kills a woman

This title makes it seem like it was just some guy who had enough and whimsically decided to smash into oncoming traffic or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing OP meant being produced today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, the honking as he goes by.

Also for some reason this was in the recommended videos afterwards: [green i8](https://youtu.be/svQ3F-q09Ss?t=14) is gorgeous :O

Yellow one around ~1:15 too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not the first time this comparison has been made. I don't get it though

Clickbait. That's all. Throw "Group B" in the title and people will listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my thought, too, but I'm no lawyer.


If the lawyer is decent I think they could make a very strong argument for unauthorized access (her phone) + impersonation (her account). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly couldn't even get through the first half of that article.

Just the attitudes of every single person they quote pissed me off. "Obama wanted to destroy America", "Obama takes too much off, but Trump is working hard deserves time off", "Consistency is so 2012", "protect the churches" (I'm all for religious freedoms but somehow I'm getting the impression they really only care about one church).

*Ugh*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Usha Ram says her manager gave her permission to take home the food.

 Her boss, Janif Mohammed, fired her to warn other staff against theft.

 Mr Mohammed, who defended himself, says Ms Ram was an exemplary employee, a "wonderful lady" and a "good worker". The two had worked together since 1989.

What a fuckin' dick.


 At the time of her dismissal, in January 2014, she was earning $21,000 a year and working full-time. Her husband is physically disabled and she also supports an adult daughter with a mental disability. She is the sole earner in her household.

 The judge ordered the franchise co-owners, Mr Mohammed and Michael Lacombe, to pay her $21,000 in general damages, or the equivalent of one-year severance. The judge also awarded her $25,000 in aggravated damages for emotional distress.

Often times, I find these "emotional damage" payments to be excessive and terribly prone to manipulation... But this woman's situation, I really feel bad for her. I do believe she thought she believed she has permission for what she did. Then to be fired for it, while supporting her husband and disabled daughter... That's gotta be stressful. I was a mess when I got laid off and only had to worry about student loans / myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  deploy pig.

[Uh oh](https://youtu.be/BVook-vxzDY?t=8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you guys store your sunglasses? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably one of my biggest complaints with this car. Which I guess is a good thing, but damn. I miss the little flippy-cup thing near the cabin lights in my old vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, I'll see if I can find it, if no one else knows of anything closer. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between the salt and snow and potholes it's not ideal. But oh well. You live where you can find a job, eh?

Walking distance will be nice. Working remotely 5 days per week was amazing -- saved so much on fuel, oil changes etc.

And 5-6 years until I'm free of student loans, and I have about the same left on my Fiesta ST's loan... So in 5 years I'm hoping to look into getting a house with a garage so I can do the two car setup. Keep the FiST for winters, get a cheap Z for the summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I'm not from Buffalo. Is [this](https://www.google.com/maps/place/AppleTree+Business+Park/@42.8878816,-78.7654769,13.75z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x89d30c7e1f709e2d:0x5b4d14bee4c0e147!8m2!3d42.8905943!4d-78.7520487) where you're talking about? Or at least near where you're referring to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea; example: https://youtu.be/YmFb776XgRs?t=153

Not my video but we had a few like this where I lived back in Massachusetts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh really? Well, either way, looks stunning.

Got a new job where I couldn't work remotely whenever I wanted (read: every day, lol), and moved to a new apartment further away from the office. Live in western New York which *usually* gets **hammered**. So I didn't want to deal with the ground clearance / snow / MPG, and was kind of wanting something a *little* more practical. But the main reasons was having to commute 5 days + ground clearance.

Go figure, the winter I sold it we barely even saw a snowflake. And this winter has been tame as hell so far too. A little bitter haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a Touchless car wash? Ideally downtown/EV area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highs of 47 on Saturday! Hoping to get my car washed. There's a Delta Sonic on Delaware not too far away, but any time I go there and ask for Touchless they still drape stuff over the vehicle. Looking for something that is *actually* touchless, but my Google Fu is failing me.

I know that one on Main Street   West Ferry, next to Autozone, but I don't even know if it's actually in business? I drive by it once or twice a week and never see anyone there.

Anyone know of somewhere? I don't mind a 10-20 minute road trip to whatever suburb, but in the city would be cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one to the right, in the back, looks overwhelmed :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * 3rd / 5th gear grind
* High oil consumption
* Uneven tire wear
* Window motor(s) might die

These are the most common issues with the early years. I had an '03 with ~50K on it when I bought it, sold it around 80K. I didn't have oil or tire problems, but I did replace the passenger side window motor (covered under the extended warranty I purchased), driver side door handle (snapped during a brutally cold winter - $60 parts   labor I think?), and 5th would grind a little bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll never get tired of that green wrap, man.

I miss my Z :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty confident they're not stock. Usually vehicles which offer any kind of fancy racing seats will be ripe with branding, and I don't recognize that logo that's embossed.

The carbon fiber lid on the cubby hole between the two seats is just a wrap too, I'm sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The knobs need googley eyes, pronto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, would be fun for like a media PC in the living room or something along those lines. Not a full blown gaming rig or anything like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, rad.

How are  the temperatures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 23:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I made a case for a custom server out of lego and spend like $20 total on legos this way.

You can't say things like this and then not post the pictures </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to say this, but there's really nothing you can do.

My 31 year old brother unexpectedly passed away in November. It'll be 4 months exactly, tomorrow. I can still remember every single detail about receiving the phone call. Flying home. Going to the funeral. Every little detail like it just happened a minute ago.

It sucks, but it does get easier to bear.

I'd strongly recommend talking to a professional. Grief counselors are a thing. It's helped my parents a bit. I've already been seeing a psychologist for other issues, but she's been very helpful with this too. Her husband also unexpectedly died a few months before my brother, actually...

Everyone dies. It's a natural part of life. It sucks, but sooner or later it happens. All you can do is try to make peace with that fact. Make peace with the fact that you can't understand it, won't understand it. You might have a lot of questions that you'll never get the answers to. It's those things you need to learn to control, so they don't get the best of you.

Sorry for your loss. A sibling isn't the same as a SO, but I can understand what you're going through. I imagine it's  awful in different ways, but yea...     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine, Dungeon Peons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D D with wargame buildings and minis: everything flies off the game and is severely damaged, requiring tons of effort to strip dried glue so it can re-glue it, repaint it etc

D D with Legos: sweet, I get to play with my Legos again


I'm OK with strictly "theater of mind" D D with no props at all, but honestly, if we're introducing minis I think Lego would be great (aside from the price) because the stuff might separate but it's not going to *break*. Not like a mini you have to assemble, anyways.


Also what age group are you playing with where people are just knocking tons of stuff off the table? I could probably count on one hand the number of times a drink has been spilled on the game table in the 7 years I've been playing D D and Wargaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom sold my childhood Lego collection, so I have two options:

* Spend $200 buying four of [these](http://www.target.com/p/lego-classic-large-creative-brick-box-10698/-/A-16747749) suckers
* Spend $100 - $200 on a kit with rad D D Lego figs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
You don't need to look that far back, though. You could go back 5-7 years and find high mileage Hyundai that will be reliable.

And besides, they still do their 10 year / 100K warranty. Even if the car isn't **the most reliable**, you're covered. Sure as shit beats the 3 year / 36K on my 2014 Ford.
 

I'm on mobile so I can't figure out how to link search results but if you simply go to /r/Hyundai and search for "reliability" you get plenty of threads. I see posts of people taking about '05 SUV's with 200K miles where they've had to do nothing but standard maintenance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then don't be pedantic and focus on the specifics. Can pretend it's different opioid abuser? There are plenty of them out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See: Netbooks. 

And "wearable" tech.

Everyone jumped on the smart watch band wagon just because Apple was doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Leaf is a better option than the i3 too, but the other guy did say "Buy Tesla or German" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cars Hyundai produces today are very different than the Hyundai of early 2000's.

They make great looking, decent cars with an unbeatable warranty. They've come a long way in the last 10-15 years, they just haven't been able to shake that consumer image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they look like shit too, but that's purely subjective and is quite irrelevant when discussing build quality / reliability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, ya, you can get performance outside of Germany, but let's not pretend a Mustang GT is comparable to a 911 just because it makes more HP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... it would be much better to buy a European electric car or a Tesla rather than this substandard GM vehicle.

Don't get me wrong, I'm as much of a Musk fanboy as many redditors are, but what are you even saying?

Have you looked at the [Model X problems](https://www.google.com/search?q=model+x+quality+issues oq=model+x+quality+issues gs_l=mobile-heirloom-serp.12...0.0.1.7222.0.0.0.0.0.0.0.0..0.0....0...1c..34.mobile-heirloom-serp..7.6.1062.lYYUkZEXQLo)? Car starts at $86K (USD) and goes up to $116K and the trim on the body doesn't even line up. That is substandard for a $20K car, never mind something that costs more than most people's annual pre-tax income.

Like let's not pretend Tesla is perfect. They have their problems. As do the Germans.

So, not only is the Model 3 not even out yet, but if you can afford the $42K for an i3 you're getting a car with a 100+change mile range, or 180 of you buy the hybrid. That is substandard.

VW doesn't have anything fully Electric on the market last I knew, but even if they did I personally don't like them -- especially not after "Dieselgate". And I'm pretty sure Audi and Merc don't have anything all electric, either.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said, I think he's a pretty slimy piece of shit. 

But I don't think "junkie" is an appropriate word and it dehumanizes people who need help. It doesn't help anybody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just me or does Hexblade seem like what the Eldritch Knight is supposed to be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing an Eldritch Knight this season in Adventures League. I'm having *fun*, but the class seems objectively terrible. I'm really **not** a "min maxer", so I could just be playing it poorly but my issues are primarily:

* Needing STR, INT and wanting CON, you're spread thin on stats.
* Restricted to Evocation and Abjuration spells
* Gaining higher level spell slots so slowly

It's a fun, flavorful class, but I get the feeling that if I tried hard enough, I could probably just multi class between a caster and a melee class and be equally effective, or probably even more effective.

I read through the Hexblade PDF earlier this morning and... Wow.

* Use CHA instead of STR or DEX, minimizing "desirable" stats.
* Improved Crit
* Bonus Damage
* Healing

I realize those last 3 are only against your Cursed target, but only requiring a Short rest between uses isn't a steep requirement for how good it is.

Level 10 there's just a 50% chance to evade **any** Attack Roll by the cursed target!? Not just melee -- spells and ranged attacks too.

Then at 14 you can daisy chain your curse freely.

And this is all on top of what you get just for being a Warlock.

---

It just all sounds so fun and I want to be playing that right now. EK is just like... Neat I'm 7th level and now I can cast 2 second level spells from an extremely limited spell list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [The Dragon Reborn] Just finished #3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 85% of the way through this book I was thinking, "Pretty good but I think I enjoyed #2 more."

Just finished that last 15% and **damn** that was a great ending.

Mat is the best. I really love this "Dark One's Luck" thing and I can't wait to see how Jordan utilizes it in books to come.  Not sure what to make of Mat's comment to Thom when he left him with Mother Guenna. I *think* I accidentally [spoiled](/s "Mat dying and coming back, so I assume his comment was foreshadowing his own death"). But with my shitty memory maybe whatever I glimpsed was talking about a different character... Or so I'm trying to convince myself  But I laughed so hard when he killed the first High Lord in the Stone and then raised his staff triumphantly, accidentally felling another High Lord behind him. I can picture the scene perfectly.

Egwene's developments as a Dreamer is going to be awesome. I know this whole time Moraine / the Amrylin was saying how Egwene and Nynaeve have the potential to be some of the strongest Aes Sedai but damn. "Tying" up and shielding one of the Black in Tel'aran'rhiod in her dream was cool.

Nynaeve's a fucking badass too but I can't even remember what she did earlier in the book that made me think so. Did she weave up some Balefire? I can't remember, and Book 2   3 are blurring together for me. Her interaction with Mother Guenna in Tear was thoroughly amusing. That said, her persistent "Fuck the Aes Sedai and Moraine for everything they've done to me/us Two Rivers folk" still annoys me. I don't care if she is/could be Aes Sedai Numero Uno -- maybe she could've helped Egwene, but I don't believe she could've done fuck all for Rand. And besides, The Wheel weaves as The Wheel wills. It's not Moraine's fault, you woolheaded sack of vegetables.

I'm not sure what I think of Perrin. I don't dislike him, he's understandably apprehensive of this whole Wolf thing. It's just that with Hopper warning him, his "uncomfortableness" with his eyes changing, his enjoyment of the Blacksmithing work he did in Tear -- everything -- I have no idea what to expect out of him. Him saving Faile was rad, though.

Rand is a badass. Callandor is awesome. His fight with Baalzamon, or whoever it was, was badass. The sword itself almost reminds me of a Shardblade from The Stormlight Archive, except way more fucking powerful because it's a sa'angreal and not just a badass magic sword. I think I should've seen that coming, but eh I suck at predicting things in books. It was a cool surprise, to me. One thing I didn't quite get is why the seal was unbroken this time. RAFO, I suppose!  My only concern, this book we barely saw Rand. What glimpses we did get he was often going on about being afraid of hurting those around him. I'm afraid he's going to become a "distant" character because oh the whole "I could kill everybody" thing... But surely he's too important to be left on the edges of the focus.

Also, I just love Loial. He's just so... happy-go-lucky. Like he knows shit's dangerous, but he just has this certain confidence to him that things are going to work out, that he's not going to throw in the towel and return to his Stedding. Not without sufficient material for his book!  I can't help but picture the Ogier like some sort of cross between Aslan, the lion from Chronicles of Narnia, and the Khajit from The Elder Scrolls. Like I've seen fan art of the Ogier and I know that description is way off, but just the way Jordan describes his "mane" and "tufts of hair", a very deep voice and a splitting smile and huge tea-cup sized eyes... I just picture a walking, talking humanoid Lion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opeth - The Seventh Sojourn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What legal rights does a tourist have when visiting the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just reading an article on /r/technology about a new proposal by the Department of Homeland Security. What they're suggesting is that international tourists would have to surrender the passwords to their social media accounts in order to gain entrance to the US.

I'm -- obviously -- not a lawyer, but my understanding of the 5th Amendment and self-incrimination is that a US citizen cannot be made to give up the PIN to a combination lock, or a password to an account. You **can** be made to surrender a key to a physical lock, but not made to give up knowledge basically.

So **if** this DOHS proposal were to hypothetically be applied to US citizens traveling from state to state, this would be a huge violation of our 5th Amendment rights, right?

This made me wonder about the legal rights of tourists visiting the US. Are they granted to same freedoms and protections a citizen are granted? If so, when does the visitor come under the protection of the Constitution? I assume not until DOHS / Border Protection / Whoever says, "OK welcome to the US"?

Note; /r/legaladvice told me to post here instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sorts of legal rights does a tourist from another country have in the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 14:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seattle Aquarium cancels octopus sex act due to cannibalism concerns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Politeness on a programmer forum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any tips for a newer Disgaea 2 player? (PC) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 15:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played the shit out of Disgaea 1, but I didn't get half as into the sequels when I was a kid. Playing 2 on PC now, I'm really enjoying it.

I just hit 100 last night, rest of my party is 40-70 or so. I'm slowly accumulating Felonies. I've got maybe 30 on Adell. Try to throw a stack of dudes into the gate when I can, but it feels sort of pointless because I know eventually I'm just going to recreate almost my entire party once I unlock the higher tiers of characters. Should I only focus on Adell / Rozalin until they're able to carry everyone?

I've mostly been working on unlocking the classes, as soon as I do I delete my current and create a new one then just level them via bonus gauge EXP.

I've also been using a Fist weapon on Adell. I like the displacement effect from Triple Strike as I can punch a guy off the Dimensional Gate in Item World if needed, but I don't like the mixed stats and overall I think that Swords just have better skills. But at this point I don't want to switch.

What about Healers? I was "taught" to give them Bows in Disgaea 1, but this time I've been experimenting with Staves and I like it way more. I can level up via Healing, Bonus Gauge EXP, or just participating in Team Attacks. I see no reason to use a Bow when the Staff will let me cast from further away. Plus I can have the Healer create a Mage and teach the Healer to cast offensive spells this way instead of plinking dudes with arrows.

Are any of the Named characters worthwhile? Adell and Rozalin are my two best, backed by an array of Skulls (though in hindsight I wish I went with Mages instead). I was thinking about leveling Pram and Plenair and a few others who have "S" or "A" tier Weapon Proficiency. I figure it's probably better to have character skills in addition to the weapon skills, no?

Any tips regarding Felonies? I've mostly been throwing the Baliffs onto items I want to level; Imperial Seals and their higher tiers, weapons etc. Should I just get a Legendary low-level item and blitz through it instead, Gency'ing out to slap a new Baliff onto it once I've cleared the current one?

Lastly, I see I can petition the Assembly for Cave of Ordeals. Is this identical to the COO from Disgaea 1? I remember there was a single stage with a 33 group of enemies. I can't tell you how many times I Winged Slayer'd that map, grinding Laharl for hours as a kid. I hurt unlocked The Big Bang, I think it is, which also has a 33 attack pattern. But only a 27% chance to pass the COO bill, at best. Don't want to waste my time trying to bribe the bill through if it's not as ludicrous as it was in Disgaea 1.

**Edit** Oh! Also, what effects a Miss chance? It seems like my Skulls miss their spells way more than I remember in D1. It's so frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that 46 years ago today, a NYPD Officer was shot in the face during a drug raid and the officers officers with him refused to make the call to the dispatcher indicating an officer was shot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm trying to integrate a PHP application into my ASP.NET one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My company's flagship product is an ASP.NET web application which uses MVC 4 and is hooked up to a MS SQL database.

We currently use some tremendously old PHP web forum software as a means off providing customer support, and it's my job to replace.

The current software has two major issues:

* Requires a very old version of PHP, so it's running on a Windows 2003 server which we want to scrap.
* Currently, anyone can find it and create an account and spam the forums.

I've been looking into using phpBB. But I'm having a lot of issues wrapping my head around something that I know *is* possible, I just have no clue how/where to begin.

We'd like it so that once the user logs in to our main application then clicks the Forum link, they'll automatically be logged in there. Fortunately, phpBB does support MS SQL but the password hashing it uses is different than what we use so I'm a little unclear on how this might work. Ignoring that, I'm not sure what is the best/safest way to achieve this sort of "shared authentication":

Session variable? Assuming the new forum will be running on the same server as the main application (currently not the case).

Use a "common" cookie on the client machine for the two applications? Is that safe?

Simply pass their credentials as part of the POST data to be parsed by the forum software?


I've never had to do anything like this, haven't worked with PHP in over 5 years (and even then it was in college), and would still consider myself *relatively* new to web development. The majority of my experience is with desktop applications.

Just hoping anyone here might have any advice or worked on something similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [The Dragon Reborn] A question about this series of Egwene chapters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished chapter 23, where Egwene completes her trial and is raised to Accepted. But I'm a little confused about this chapter

Something was wrong and the ter'angreal, the arch, started to behave weirdly. Once she got out, once she finished the trials, Alanna (Green) apologized profusely for not speaking up about what she felt and for endangering Egwene and wanted to share in Egwene's chores/punishment, which the Amrylin said no to. Then this paragraph comes up:

 The desire to confess had died in Egwene. ... She [Alanna] couldn't have deliberately caused the ter'angreal to go wild; I did that. Can she be Black Ajah?

What did she want to confess? That she was responsible for the ter'angreal misbehaving? How did Egwene come to that conclusion?

I remember in The Great Hunt during Nynaeve's trial she channeled while within one of the arches and when she came out she was warned that is terribly dangerous and not to do so again. But Egwene doesn't know that, right? So why/how does she blame herself?

---

I'm reading at work and get interrupted relatively often so my concentration gets broken. A lot happened the past few chapters, I just want to recap to make sure I've got it right:

* Verin gave Egwene the ring which supposedly helped the last Dreamer cross into the 'Dreamworld'
* Verin also gave Egwene the dossier with information on the 13 Aes Sedai who disappeared with Liandrin
* Sheriam mentioned... Something about 13 Aes Sedai and 13 Mydraal (or was it Dreadlords?) being needed for something but I can't remember for what. To make someone who can Channel succumb to the will of the Dark One? To still/gentle someone? Or something else entirely?


---

Overall I'm enjoying the book a lot, but it really feels like the last 2-4  chapters dumped a ton of information on the reader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driver side door won't close / Recall notice for faulty doors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Below freezing and I went to go brush off the snow from my car / let it warm up prior to leaving for work this morning. Had to use a little effort to get the door open, and now it doesn't close. It doesn't full on swing open, but it's very clearly not secure. If I even bump it with my elbow, it'll swing open.

I found this recall online:

https://media.ford.com/content/fordmedia/fna/us/en/news/2015/04/24/ford-motor-company-issues-safety-recall-in-north-america-for-doo.html

So I'm going to call the dealership when they open in 30 minutes. I bought my 2014 in June of 2015, and this was issued April 2015... so it's very possible this was never performed on my car.

But 20 minutes after this happened, I ran out to my car again as I needed to park it elsewhere... and the door is fine now.

Could've just been the cold, I guess, but I've never heard of a car being stuck frozen open. Mostly just wanted to share that recall notice. I know it's a year old, but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
