<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8653</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 17:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Know ye not that ye are the temple of God, and that the Spirit of God dwelleth in you?" -VOSL

"Be careful of your thoughts, for your thoughts become your words. Be careful of your words, for your words become your actions. Be careful of your actions, for your actions become your habits. Be careful of your habits, for your habits become your character. Be careful of your character, for your character becomes your destiny." -Attributed to different sages

So what kind of God do we want ourselves to be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't want to strawman you.

Thanks Brother. Just an observation. Masons regardless of their religion should read or at least get a basic understanding of the essence VOSL of all ages to get a better glimpse of human nature (not limited to the Bible of course.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The unerring standard of truth and justice yet most Freemasons of my generation won't read it. The typical excuse, "I'm not religious, bro." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 17:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Freemasons like their secrets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 03:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sculpture "Self Made Man" by a female artist- Bobbie Carlyle. I used it as well on one of my [digital posters](http://i.imgur.com/0UCycm1.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 22:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I watch him spend his first two years on antibiotics due to illness. He used to be very sickly but now he's a lot stronger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 22:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And so I have to ask you- what is wrong with that? He's my kid and he's doing Muay Thai. Is it not appropriate in this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 07:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. All the best! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 01:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to downvote you. I'm living with depression, severe anxiety, and PTSD and I can guarantee you that Muay Thai is indeed way cheaper than therapy. 

A little background: I was diagnosed about 3 years ago only but suffered from it practically my whole life. I was prescribed zoloft and other related meds. Worked well at first until I started getting suicidal thoughts. I lost my job, was taken to jail due to my condition, almost lost my marriage too. 

I never played sports my entire life and I don't have much confidence in my physical capabilities. A lot of my anxiety comes from the thought that I may not be able to defend my loved ones in case I have to. [Last September I joined a local gym here in Toronto and my life turned around](http://imgur.com/V54MXoN). What I pay for Muay Thai per month is nothing compared to what I went through living with depression. I still have the anxiety in me but it is not as severe. I am no longer depressed and absolutely more confident physically and mentally. 

Source: I don't use a throwaway account. You can go back in my history and you will see that I talk about this things. I even wrote a blog about my mental ordeal on November 2014 and posted on my [business website](http://www.fraternalties.com/blogs/news/15850180-demons-depression-and-mustache). There is no shame in mental illness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 07:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a push from Canada's Ajahn Suchart (met him at Krudar Christmas party in Toronto). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 01:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. Click the title on the video and it will load in youtube and you can view it fulls creek there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 17:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search in YouTube Saenchai or Somluck Khamsing for fancy footwork. If you want slow and deliberate stalking footwork, look up Yodsanklai.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 06:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope all involved will find peace and harmony within themselves when the dust settles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 02:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The talent here is your capacity to do the same thing over and over and over in pursuit of perfection without losing focus. That's only possible if you truly love what you do. Obsession is the key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Remember, you get what you put in it! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nonsense. [Here he is at the Sick Kids emergency room.](https://youtu.be/gtHWLjeWfTw)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A wonderful and perfect Matrix won't be able to sustain itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My religion is Love and Respect and whoever goes against my religion is an infidel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 05:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I saw your comment on my kid's channel. It was the very first comment that we ever received! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 05:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great boost in confidence when you see your before and afters.

[Photos of my weight loss](http://i.imgur.com/eX9eeb6.jpg), and here's my actual [before and after](http://i.imgur.com/V54MXoN.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 05:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 34 years old with no previous sports experience. Began training just a few months ago (September 24, 2015 to be precise). It's been only 3 months and I [can see and feel the difference already.](http://imgur.com/V54MXoN) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think my 6yr old kid is becoming a little too enthusiastic with Muay Thai. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 05:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 03:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true. I skipped with a PVC jumping rope wearing a suit and tie and it's even harder! [Proof](https://youtu.be/KqGzMqaOPtM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 02:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put it this way, I am a 34 year old father of four. I work from home as an [artist/designer of sorts](http://www.fraternalties.com/) (can be a very sedentary job). I have never played any kind of sports my whole life save for a few Taekwondo classes I took back in gradeschool (never went past white belt). The only physical activity for me was cleaning the house, cooking, and running after the kids. Before Muay Thai, I was overweight, clinically depressed (anxiety + non-combat PTSD), smoked a lot, ate a lot, suffered from severe sleep apnea, and was just trapped in a bad physical shape overall. 

I have been interested in Muay Thai forever but was hesitant in joining because I have constant fears in my head that I wasn't good enough and will just probably end up either hurt or humiliated. 

Last September I decided to sign up after much encouragement from my wife and kids who were at the time beginner students at a local gym in our neighborhood here in Toronto. I found out that all my fears were unfounded. The people are respectful, nobody's acting tough or aggressive, and everyone is just nice. I've been training regularly with my entire family for 3 months now and I love every bit of it. [Check out my before and after.](http://i.imgur.com/V54MXoN.jpg). Mind you that I joined the gym on September 24, 2015 only. That before and after only have 3 months in between.

Go for it my friend, you will not regret it! Sawasdee kap!

[edit: added date for reference] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My babies love spicy noodles! (xpost from trees) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 04:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 02:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your eyes don't lie my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 01:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all time? Nai Khanom Tom, the father of Muay Thai.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ish happens: Toddler tries Muay Thai camp. Fails miserably. Forgets his name. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 00:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching my boys eat noodles gives me the munchies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 22:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holidays, 4 kids, small apartment, punching bag in the living room. Nothing can go wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 22:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The names of months recited by a toddler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 18:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 23:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do more intense workout wearing the same suit that I wear when we form lodge. [I did it once. It's possible.](https://youtu.be/KqGzMqaOPtM)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 22:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post title in Hollywood terms http://i.imgur.com/b8hnpke.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 22:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a long time subscriber. Reputable and knowledgeable writers and editor. Content is simply top notch. Every article I have read is a Masonic gem. Very worth a subscription specially if (1) you don't attend lodge too much; (2) your lodge don't host education nights; (3) you want to expand your knowledge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 19:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 2014 was a very dark year for me- I lost my job, almost lost my marriage, I was overweight and very (clinically) depressed. I didn't want those problems to spill over to 2015 so I made a resolution to quit smoking, be physically active (I never played sports in my life), lose weight, and try to beat depression the natural way (I was previously on zoloft). [I think I did well](http://imgur.com/Aj3PBbC). I tend to do even better for 2016.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 18:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father and father-in-law both died when my wife was pregnant with our now [6yr old boy](https://youtu.be/x2ajGfT3YxE)- he has born with kidney reflux and had to be on antibiotics for the first 2 years of his life. 

My mother-in-law died of breast cancer a day before the birth of our now 2yr old twins- both of them were born with [Peters Anomaly](https://www.facebook.com/FraternalTies/photos/a.448480046997.246876.346888431997/10153534189746998/?l=82b4124c98). There were atleast 3 more deaths in between. We are immigrants with no close relatives where we live, we haven't been able to fly home to pay our last respects to our dearly departed. 

Our relationship became so toxic that sometimes the cops get involved when we fight. Glad we're over that now. Psychiatric help, philosophy, and [lots of exercise](https://youtu.be/p2X5X-r2D1I) helped.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We found out that our 2yr old twin boys with vision problems can read! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 05:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 08:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there! Though I never bought anything from your website, I was one of the many who admire the novelty of it all. I really liked it at first and would visit every once in a while but after some time the novelty, I guess, simply wore off. There's nothing there that gave me a sense of brand loyalty that could have helped me keep on coming back so I guess I just slowly forgot that the website existed. Until today.

I'm not sure if I can be of much help but here are my thoughts:

1. Connect and Engage your followers - you're on all social networks as you mentioned but you really do not have a strong presence. Take your [Facebook page](https://www.facebook.com/Thisiswhyimbroke) for example, the posts are very sporadic and most of them are shallow posts like "please like this page" "heyyy all". You cannot expect your followers to become fanatics if you don't know how to communicate like you believe in yourself and your merch. 

2. People want to see fresh and curated content- some of the stuff on display there are the same stuff that I remember seeing years ago.

3. Use your own products and posts photos of yourself actually using it. Why would I buy from someone who don't even believe on the same stuff they're selling? Use your own stuff and be proud of it. Post photos and true stories and slowly develop a cult of personality. Became the product and it would be easy to sell anything. 

These ideas I give you are from my own personal experience. Please visit my [Facebook page](https://www.facebook.com/FraternalTies) and see some of my posts and the comments from my audience so you would get a clearer view of what I'm talking about. I hope this helps. 

//edit: link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 18:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True words. Thanks Brother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 04:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Distributorship will solve the expensive shipping and custom fees. We will make an announcement about this very soon. 

To be notified, please sign up here: http://www.fraternalties.com/pages/vip-signup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 01:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been toying with the idea for a while now. Still figuring out the execution but it will happen. Thanks for the push! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 01:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Brother! It's on its way. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 01:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fraternal embrace from Toronto! Thanks for the support Bro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 07:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I like it. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 20:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me the address you signed up with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 20:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 20:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Proof.](https://youtu.be/EGPhWuBLyqI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day I will try the[Quintuple Windsor](http://www.fraternalties.com/blogs/news/6416888-various-tie-knots-for-the-gentle-manly-man) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 04:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A variation of. Mine is a bit simpler to make.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 01:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [How about a full windsor?](http://i.imgur.com/2ZK7mqS.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My necktie looks like a trowel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 01:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 02:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the William Mercer Wilson award.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 02:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was the Senior Warden when due to a combination of health, marital, and financial issues I was left with no other choice but to submit my resignation. Our W.M. at the time was gracious enough to extend his service as the master of the lodge for another year just to wait for me, but right in the middle of my 2nd term as the S.W., I had to step out of the progression line to the east because things in my personal life are definitely going south. 

Lucky for me, I never felt that I was left outside of the 'inner circle' because I'm still their go-to guy when they need someone to deliver the final charges (any degree) to a candidate- meaning I still go out and help if I can sans the administrative responsibilities that comes with being an officer. The other thing is I also have a Masonic facebook page with a good amount of activity and following. 

I was right next in line to be the Master of my lodge but I gave it up for my family's sake and I don't regret it. It did not make me less of a Mason. Titles mean nothing to me- character is all that counts. My hiatus turned me into a better observer. It's been a good experience overall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 22:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "hooks" are 2 wedges with a spacer in between. Without the spacer, you don't have to drive it through the rock- the wedges will simply fit right into the hole without much effort. Once the wedges are in place, simply insert the spacer in between and align the holes and secure it. Here's a good diagram http://cdn2.bigcommerce.com/server5800/v9jar2/product_images/uploaded_images/lewis.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 18:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my boys listening to a Lewis tool demonstration in an open lodge http://i.imgur.com/5wTu5oR.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The post from u/-R-o-y- reminded me of the shirts that I printed for my twin boys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 18:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SMIB.

For this one time, I think I will be forgiven for using that term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 06:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that it's a stanley folding ruler and not a square. Also, the square is not a measuring tool. Or so I was told.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 15:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. It was the earlier version of the paisley necktie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 05:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once designed a necktie using silk fabric colored with Pantone 2955C- that's the BBC approved Tardis Blue. It didn't do well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 18:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not agree with a word you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it. -Voltaire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Parisian Freemason once made an observation that is relevant to what's happening in his hometown Paris right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 07:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 14:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Brought to you by Socrates.](http://i.imgur.com/FL8qpnv.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The liar and the ignoramus may somehow get into Masonry, but no Masonry can get into them." -H.L. Haywood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 06:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was scanning my old postings for #tbt and I came across [this one that I made in 2013](https://www.facebook.com/FraternalTies/photos/a.448480046997.246876.346888431997/10151539554871998/?l=da7ccb2a5e).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 14:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have something to say, Brother. Say it. We're all learned men here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 14:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see an enterprising fool, I see accountability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 14:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I do respect and appreciate that ours is a speculative art, I think you simply just speculate a bit too much, my Brother. Did I change our tools and symbols here, ask yourself that. Did I change the S C? What's with this talk about the "Symbol for all of Freemasonry" being looked at as a gay pride symbol? Aren't You the "Symbol for All of Freemasonry"?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wisdom to contrive, Strength to support, and Beauty to adorn. For my GA Brothers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 05:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just in case you might want a 'good men better' hoodie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 07:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean to spam. I was asked before by a few members here who don't FB to post when I come up with a new print design. Check it out http://i.imgur.com/J0Vb3eJ.jpg

It's Teespring but this is not a fundraising campaign or anything. I just need a hoodie and I really want this for myself. If I make 75 bucks from it, I'd use that for grocery and I'd be more than happy. Not looking to sell a lot of it either- I set the goal really low so we can get it printed right away. If you like the design and would like to have one for yourself or a brother, here's the link: https://teespring.com/freemasonhoodies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] Sometimes I can't believe that this kid was born with kidney reflux, had e coli infection when he was a few weeks old, spent the first 2yrs of his life on antibiotics, and is dealing with reactive airway disease. He stays strong because he doesn't sit around all day on his butt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 06:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 05:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea there's a few around. But I also have 4 kids. The youngest are twins who turned two just a few days ago. The only time that I can workout is between 11am-1pm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 05:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great exercises indeed! Yoga is in my list but I can't tai chi around when my son does this https://youtu.be/x2ajGfT3YxE 

He'd rip me to shred.

Unless https://youtu.be/KM1pcfFNsnE?t=1m15s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it! Simplicity and Strength! http://imgur.com/SUuW4Hc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing how much better one feels when you're physically in good shape.

This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truth! I am really pre-occupied with the skipping rope right now. It's truly a great feeling when you find your rhythm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. My family doctor's been telling me this forever. But my anxieties prevent me from participating in the only exercise activity that she prescribed for me- swimming. I can't be around too many people sometimes. She don't want me to do high impact sports because it might not be good for my plantar fasciitis, weak knees, and back pain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, if it works, it works! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. Upvotes for OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] I'm an overweight guy with anxiety, PTSD, plantar fasciitis, and sleep apnea. Here's how I spent my Movember day 3. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 08:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can skipping rope save you from killing yourself? Movember Day 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 07:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movember Day 3. My cable tow is a skipping rope. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 07:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the old adage goes, "you cannot help others without helping yourself first."

Here's me cable towing this afternoon at the gym- https://youtu.be/ChsDFKMSHvo

Some background: This is my second year doing Movember. I've been struggling with anxiety and depression for several years now. I was taking Zoloft until it made me feel suicidal. I'm no health professional and I will not recommend anything to you but intense exercise is a big help to me. I joined a local Muay Thai gym just last month and I am already feeling the positive physical and mental benefits.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 05:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am Filipino and there's no problem like this in the Philippines (as far as I know) or any of the North American Filipino lodges that I've been to. I spent my entire DeMolay years in the Philippines but I was Initiated, Passed, and Raised in a 'white' Canadian Lodge- I was one of the only two Filipinos in my lodge. We're the combo-breakers. I love my mother lodge will all my heart, I enjoy the deep philosophical exchange with my lodge brothers, and I do not have any inclination of joining another lodge; but after the labor is done, the refreshments consumed, and the parting words said, we all go back into our cars and go our separate ways- of course until we meet again at the temple. 

This is simply not how it is done back home. Over there, Brothers there know each other's birthday, there are regular family events (fundraising, talent shows, etc.), they visit each other's house, and there's a certain degree of fun frat attitude that just cements the lodge together- and they carpool a lot. They don't just go to lodge to usher candidates and to recite words- they also go to have fun. Philosophy and deep thoughts are all nice and cool but the fun factor is a good motivator so if that is missing you will have troubles getting members back in Lodge. Now, gimme me my trillions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 04:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Masonic usage, I was told that the actual name for this sign is the 'Masonic Honor Dots'. Some say that it was perhaps derived from the 3 supernals. Holy Trinity; Holy Family; the myth of Isis, Horus, Osiris... Nobody really knows the actual connection but since a lot of Masons insist that everything good comes in threes- instead of using a plain and boring single dot, we use three to make the punctuation thrice blessed and perhaps lucky. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 04:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Therefore_sign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 16:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a second there I thought I was in trouble with yous people because I like Facebook. Facebook rulz bruh!!!1 Twitter on the other hand... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 22:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for one probably wouldn't know even if it's right under my nose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 20:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh noes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 20:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you asked for it. http://i.imgur.com/rBkZqHc.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Past... Present..... Future....... Time Immemorial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 16:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 04:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got my support, Brother. Been following you for a couple of weeks or so now.

jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 00:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something something refreshment http://imgur.com/VPEzXU5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 22:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry brother but due to my ignorance on this matter, I can no longer continue this conversation with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 18:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're just renting bro. Anyway, before yesterday, I didn't know much about the OO. A GL officer from us (G.R.C. AF AM) who was also there yesterday told me good things about the OO. And then also yesterday, after I posted the same photo on my FB page, a Brother and OO member informed me about the "infamous side" of the OO. If you would like to see the rest of the conversation, follow this link https://www.facebook.com/FraternalTies/photos/a.10152433872996998.1073741854.346888431997/10153484811686998/?l=7cb62b9a29 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 17:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We tolerate even those who don't to tolerate. I think that's another way of looking at it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 06:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I visited a PHA lodge who rents from the OO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 06:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And everyone wears white gloves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
