<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4083</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man I want one of these more and more every day.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You seem to be really mad about me trying to make a point

I'm not mad.  You just keep ranting and raving about Hillary and your fuzzy math affirmative action legitimacy when I already told you that both are laughable.  I know how the EC works, and it's just a hilarious thing people use to try and tip the scales in their favor.  

Obviously there's a feeling of inadequacy otherwise you and Trump wouldn't have to harp on it so much.  But to your credit, you're not straight up lying about how many EC votes you got.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pleasant -

Panamera.

"It drives almost like a 911."

I'll be the judge of that.

Holy shit it does feel like a Panamera.


2015 C300 refresh.  Transmission is a bit lazy but everything else about that car blows the BMW equivalent out of the water.

Also the C43  The 335/340.  C63 doesn't have shit on the M3 though, and performs even worse up against the M2.   :(



Unpleasant -

Audi A3 -  It's a Volkswagen and not even the good one.

Audi Q5 - Helped a friend pick out an SUV for herself.  The Q5 was decent and she almost went for it but the interior was garbage and the VW Outback was ultimately the better driving car. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a My comment had nothing to do with Hillary

b lol at your fuzzy math affirmative action bullshit you have to use to reaffirm the legitimacy of a dude who lost the popular vote with less than 20% of a population's support.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is obviously some misunderstanding of my use of the word terrorist/ism and I apologize for taking it out of its colloquial use.

Dude is a terrorist.  Don't apologize.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But sure, go ahead and judge literally 65-70%

Trump got 62 million votes out of a population of 325 million.  [So less than 20%]
(https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d7lxwFEB6FI).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No one would enjoy dailying an Elise.

I know a guy who said that bout the 4C and now it sits under a tarp for 25 days out of the month.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To their credit the Outback stopped looking like a Wagon over the past few years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in 4 to 5 years Lotus will hopefully pull a Porsche and I can finally get into one without the dreadful paranoia of being stranded on the road some where... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He tries to be polite in someone elses ride

Bit of drama a few weeks back when he went from, I think, a GT4 Cayman to a vanilla Cayman and was NOT very polite to the owner.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Huh this car from 20 years ago isn't as fast as cars today.  Weird." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That silver striping reminds me of the 996/997 Targa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  This is why I am curious as to what they were talking about.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyday Driver was discussing a Porsche X4/X6 prototype. Anyone know what they were talking about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a four week old EP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be a problem between the computer and the keyboard.  I'm looking at similar year 3 series and C class, similar mileage, etc.  All within a similar price range.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have always driven terribly but now there are significantly more people on the road without the infrastructure to support it.  So now commutes are significantly longer and slower and people are looking for more and more ways to distract themselves from something they hate doing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Im sorry, I know what I said offended people and why and I made a ignorant mistake."

Okay.  Good enough for me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dallas Toll, Austin 45, 130.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Texas here.  Certain roads the speed limit is pretty much unenforced at "reasonable" levels if you have TX plates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every type of car used to be sub 100hp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do.

Yet another underpowered hatch for the US Market.  Yawn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and the reports on how the WH took it

Link?

I can't believe I missed this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 00:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally I'd say these kind of responses are a bit hyperbolic.... but considering I've had this problem for almost a year.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time I saw em I didn't know anything about it.  They were playing on a big line up, other band ended their set and before the other band could even unplug and unpack the stage these two dudes run out with their gear and start jamming immediately.  Was really cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't blame me.  Nothing at the top that usually shows you other instances of where this is posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Regardless that's an odd fit. Big lightning bolt fan here.

Austin TX.  Lots of hippies.

The track was Captain Caveman took.  It was an awesome site.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't work for me. :( :(  Gotta reboot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  Nothing side loaded, nothing weird like that installed.  Latest iOS version.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you might run into the same issue.  Nothing tried and true and all, but I was in your position once, so just keep it in mind and good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Many of the people in the company have been here for a while which is why I feel comfortable financially.

Are you in IT?  You'll start needing to look into looking around at other companies eventually.  IT wages can stagnate otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this a bug or something I'm enabling by accident? How do I get rid of it, regardless? Happens all the time. iMessage overlays on top of the Phone application. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've bailed of Miata's for now because they aren't practical enough

That's why you have more than one car.  One practical, one fun.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  3 awesome cars

You're gonna need to make more than 50k a year depending on your definition of awesome.

50k a year?  Get your Golf GTI and then get a good last gen Miata.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally don't care.  I live in Austin where people generally listen to good music.  Last couple of times I heard loud music and noticed who was listening to it it was:

a Some long hair in a VW convertible blasting Lightning Bolt.

b Some asian chick blasting Black Sabbath's Wicked World in an A4

c Some dude in a busted Ford listening to Roy Buchanan 

I approve of both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 03:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're as good as CPO but you have a deductible on top of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen them mention on more than one occasion that a two seater only 911 would "no longer be a 911".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude on the right is sitting on the white tile.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  EddieX

Thought it would be, then I googled, and got nothing.  Thanks!  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to Eddie's channel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But if you leftists start attacking anyone to the right of you

I like how in your polemic against people labeling and then attacking others simply for not sharing the same ideal, you just go ahead and assume I'm some kind of Leftist or something.

So you're an internet tough guy with a bunch of guns sick and tired of having your feels hurt and are passively hinting that you might shoot some people because of it.

Thumbs up.  You've really made yourself out as the correct party here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH.  So you're gonna shoot a bunch of anonymous people on the internet that called you bad names.  Makes perfect sense and you totally don't come off as an unscrewed right wing weirdo.

lol at that grandstanding.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what does this mean for Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's surprised that Ferrari sold an incredibly visible and insanely famous person one of their cars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many hectares of land do I need to grow to reap 40 pounds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You do understand than 1950 is already called modern right?

You realize we're talking about an isolated feudalistic society, right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The place with the avocado margarita has a good ceviche.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot about this place.  I'll hit em up first thing Monday morning!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 04:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  When my Hemi was totaled out it had some problems (died over 200k miles deep).  I got about 3k more than I valued it at and they didn't severely undervalue it due to the mileage.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biscuits and Tomato Gravy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been a while since I've been in town.  Loved this stuff.  Other than tracking down a Ward's some where, any good cafe's in Jackson serve this for breakfast?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Insurance companies suck.

Geico has actually done pretty well *by me*.  I got a check for $200 bucks a year and a half after a claim.  Then they called me.

"We finally tracked down the uninsured drunk who totaled out your Hemi and got him to pay back your deposit."

EDIT

And NO!  Not related to that article.  That's very serendipitous!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Was it malicious?

Mao had seen what the concentration of industry in major cities did to China pre Revolution.  He saw what it did to the Soviet Union.  It left the cities comparatively comfortable while the countryside remained poor as dirt and incredibly ignorant.  The peasants had 0 chance of ever becoming anything other than a peasant and lived their lives hoping for some good old "trickle down" economics to drip out of the cities.

The industrialization drive during the GLF was an attempt at "democratizing" access to industry, to prevent the solidification of the peasant class, and to make all of China equal in production.

They just kinda went about it the wrong way.

Or, maybe if they had the internet where information was known instantaneously instead... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/Doug-DeMuro

Since you're the "third party in case shit" guy on this sub now, what do you think of Turo's insurance?  I've read that it does its best to come off as protecting the renter but it pretty much leaves you on the hook for any and everything.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have time in my life to play every game I want to play.  So if the choice is between Game A with a style I like and Game B with a style I don't, then Game A it is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  if you don't like it the game isn't going to click with you.

Yup!  That new Obsidian game is probably pretty good.  Too bad it looks like a bad Samurai Jack rip off.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe he just got fired for incompetence and this is their coverup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure this person is also a gigantic pussy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should try debating them.  I hear debating people solves problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if there's anything we know about the USSR, it's that they were rolling in cash and had their shit together.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest losers in a war between the US and China will be Hong Kong and Taiwan.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Are they a superpower? India?

They lack the expansionist ideals that would be a precursor to being a super power.  Because if India expands, Pakistan will nuke, and vice versa.


 France? The U.K.?

They lack the expansionist ideals that would put them back as a world super power because if they expand, they have to take on the USA, and they both know what happens if you cross the USA.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are only temporary issues.  The Soviets went from Russia only to the USSR with satellites in South America, the Middle East, and Eastern Europe in the span of about 30 years.

The USSR collapsed about 30 years ago, but with a Russia friendly Trump there's nothing stopping them from building back up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America never experiences it.  We export it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Leaped right into poverty and famine.

China was already poor as dirt and lost 15 million or so to famine the 10 years prior to the GLF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Making uninformed decisions that directly resulted in millions of deaths is just a little different from participating in an activity that was completely normal then, but seen as barbaric nowadays.

This was a decision made before the understanding of modern biology.  Turns out people back in the day didn't know things we know today and acted accordingly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Officer Slurz McKenzie reporting for duty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The popularity of carrot cake was revived in Great Britain because of rationing during the Second World War.[5] Carrot cakes first became commonly available in restaurants and cafeterias in the United States in the early 1960s. They were at first a novelty item, but people liked them so much that carrot cake became standard dessert fare.[citation needed] In 2005, the American-based television channel Food Network listed carrot cake, with its cream-cheese icing, as number five of the top five fad foods of the 1970s. Carrot cake was voted as the favourite cake in the United Kingdom, according to a survey in the Radio Times in 2011.



I find this suspect.  The article requires a citation itself and I remember my grandmother talking about how they would eat carrot cake during the depression, well before the 1960s.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But my point is that marketing based on Feels isn't new nor is it a trend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I need to get on a list or whatever cause I would have driven one around Houston over this past weekend myself.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of which ever it is, it's still a metal as fuck logo for a car.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've always thought this trend in marketing reflects the idea that we live in a "post truth" society.

People identify themselves with their commodity.  Video game kids identify with Playstation and shit on Xbox.  Found on Road Dead lolamirite?  Lesbians loved Subaru for a long time.  Etc.

This is not a trend, nor is it new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay Grandpa.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  than a mid engine layout

And they're apparently about to fix this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, it's not men's fault that they routinely shove women out of the work force to be the primary caretaker of a child, don't consider that to be "work", and then penalize women for that when women try to reenter the work force...

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Competes with and priced similar to the C63.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I don't find the lack of a manual troubling tbh

If it an absolutely 100% track car only I can see the issue with auto only.

But I don't know a single M2 or M3 owner who doesn't double it as a daily and in the commute in my town a manual is just downright dumb.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [In that price range it absolutely is.](https://i.ytimg.com/vi/u7-GY3CCP2s/maxresdefault.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm waiting a year or two.  If no one on this sub complains about theirs randomly catching fire or falling to pieces, I'll seriously consider it.

How has the 4C been, maintenance wise?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the Giulia Quadrawhatever is an M series competitor.  But with better handling and more power apparently.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Austin.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new 718 is similarly priced, similarly practical, and outperforms the 4C.  No real reason to get a 4C over a Corvette or a 718. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nothing could be finer than Alfa Romeo returning to the States..even if you don't want or get one, just knowing they are out there is a beacon of hope to all who cherish driving

I'm just glad to see a legitimate Italian car marquee coming back and not half assing it like they were with Maserati.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In an indirect way, the US government

US Government, Chase Bank, IBM, Exxon, Chevron, Coca Cola, Ford, Random House, basically every mega rich American was funding the Nazis.

Directly.  Not Indirectly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young man wants to celebrate the first car they've ever owned or bought. It's the more "economical Mercedes" called the CLA250. Celebration ruined when someone shows up to point out that very thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Because, everyone's first car means something special to them

And you felt it necessary to shit on this particular OP's choice.  Bravo.  

 immature person

You're trolling on Reddit.  Pull your head out of your ass.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not sure why all the backlash.

Because the know the answer already.  The "cheap" Mercedes will continue to have the cheaper interior and cheaper feeling ride quality.  It's not going to magically drive as well as a C300 between now and the last time someone asked.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LPT for America only.  9/10 you see this in the third world it is a setup for a scam only.

Source: Spent lots of time in China/SE Asia/Central and South America and see Westerners getting scammed (at best) or mugged (at worst) when they try to do the right thing.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems legit.  Hope you like it!  Keep us posted! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind if I ask price?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a Prius as a baby driver.  My wife was "not a car person".  She bought a Fiat, which was garbage, and then a Prius for the space and gas mileage and was happy with that until she drove my C300 and then she kinda realized why one would want a German car (responsiveness, handling, comfort, etc).  So she would increasingly leave the house for work earlier than I and would take the C300, stranding me with the bathtub.  

I drive significantly less miles than she, work from home often, so I figured I'd get something as a weekender/occasional daily for myself and ended up with the C43.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a baby?  No?  Don't need the E class.


Do you give a shit at all about how your car sounds?  Do you drive your car hard at all?  You want something that is torquey as fuck?  C43.

Just want something stylish and comfortable to drive?  C300 and take the run flats off of it.  Actually, if it is in your budget, take the run flats off of whatever you choose.

Considering getting a completely fucking loaded C43?  Suck it up and spring for the C63.  

The engine on all of these cars is fantastic, and the new 9 speed is pretty good, but the 2016 and below with the 7 speed?  7 speed is super fucking lazy.  So if you are an enthusiast then I'd get 2017 and stick with it.  If you don't care and it's never gonna leave Comfort mode it doesn't matter.

MY2015 C300 has the best interior.  E Class didn't update until this year, the 2016 have the really old interior.  Thing still has a phone number pad on it.  Looks like an Atari controller.

I have a C43 Cab and a C300.  Really considering getting rid of the C300 and getting a Panamera.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought the same thing!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No pics.  Bummer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At 3:30, is he driving a C4?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1995 Porsche 911 993 Commercial Narrated by Patrick Stewart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1990s Battle: Ferrari 512TR vs. Porsche 911 Turbo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1990s Battle: Ferrari 512TR vs. Porsche 911 Turbo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FCA owned Ferrari directly up until the beginning of last year.  Now the same investment company that runs FCA runs both.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Theres no rest for the wicked, and theres no resting on laurels when it comes to the almighty Porsche 911. Its been through a gradual evolution ever since it first debuted, leading to what is universally considered one of the best sports cars in the world.

You'd never know this listening to Porsche fans.


MY2019 seems pretty damn soon what with MY2017 being the release for 991.2.  

I guess 991.2 was just their test bed for turbo'd base.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice when this happens.  Most Porsche owners I know say it happens frequently.  I never get any road-friendship from other Benz drivers though.  :(   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 17:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engine noise and outer styling are pretty much the only selling point for people from what I understand.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I had a '14 loaner and while the driving dynamics were pretty good when pushed hard, the rest of the car was underwhelming.

I recall the sound dampening being very sub par.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Were you looking at a '14 Ghibli?

Maybe.  I was looking at them around the time I bought my MY15 C300.  Just seemed.... hilariously over priced in comparison.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Afla's uniqueness and apparent quality travel upstream and benefit Maserati? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious.

Was looking at Mas' a while back and the "Italian Engine wrapped in a Chrysler 200" reputation was *well* deserved.  It was a complete **joke** that they were asking for as much money as they were given all the corners they cut, parts and style wise.

Too bad what with the exterior styling being on point, performance being decent, and the engine sounding fantastic.

I had completely written off Alfa as well.  I test drove a 4C when our local dealership got the first one in.  Cramped, unnecessarily underpowered, and a bit expensive.  Wife bought a Fiat and we ended up selling it 10 months later due to problems with the computer and the car magically getting stuck in auto-manual shifting mode, which lead to some closer redlines more than once.  And the general Fiat offerings being kinda garbage.

So basically I expected 0 out of Alfa.  But the Giulia and the Giulia Quadriwhatsit have gotten some astonishingly great feedback.  Their SUV seems to be reviewing very well.  The interiors are actually pretty damn amazing as well.  Other than the fact that the front of the cars looks like a fucking emoji ( :- ) I'd be on board.

So what would this mean for the bigger sister marque?  Surely Maserati can do better than to spruce up a garbage econobox and then ask 80k for it.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 01:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think Afla's uniqueness and apparent quality will travel upstream and benefit Maserati?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this answer is also taking the piss!  Ferraris!  Common!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 23:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the Cabrio section.  Essentially...

"There's no reason to track a Cabrio.  We know it performs well.  It performs almost as well as the Coupe.  But dear God if I wreck this thing my life is way more at risk than otherwise and I'm a complete douche bag for tracking a Cabrio." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was completely glossing over the steering wheel push to start a joke?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BMW Sticking with Diesels in the United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 21:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
