<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9926</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 08:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a feature on the Note 7 (R.I.P.). It really did make a impactful difference in battery to turn it down to 1080, or even 720 in a pinch.

Despite all the myriad modes, nothing touches apples power saving mode. 20% can last me 5 more hours of sporatically messing with my phone. It is magic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that include wifi calling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I amassed a 200gb iTunes library. I still go there for a bunch of the unreleased stuff, and old mixed tapes, but for anything mainstream or contemporary spotify is the dream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arent you still in return Window since it just came out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just (in 2017) purchased a 2012 computer because it is superior to the new (2014 era) computer. 

This is unacceptable. 

All I need is a new GPU capable of 4k, and I will buy another one, and dedicate this one to media center duties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like Mac mini is on the way out 



All I want is one that can run 4k 60hz is that too much to ask. I need to run a vesa arm in my setup, so iMac is a no go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's get this wave going!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone with a g5 plus care to share your feelings on it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for a budget phone for one of my lines, and this really seems to fit the bill. Amazon is selling 64 GB 4GB ram version for only $229 brand new (with adds). 

I have seen a bunch of reviews that gush about the hardware, but I am just curious if it is fully compatible with all VZ services, and if the coverage works well in the real world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.samsclub.com/sams/html/desktop/samsung/preorder.html?xid=plp3800103-elec:pov:1:1 pid=_Aff_LS siteID=lw9MynSeamY-SR5tASYOQxDiHFw8bkNxzw pubNAME=Slickdeals+LLC mobiledetect=false

This is a way better deal IMO. I would rather skip all the nonsense and have the $150 GC in hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a grown-up power wheels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From this angle it looks like equal parts Jeep wrangler, and giant bloody turd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You are lucky I responded to you.

This fucking guy.  

Get over yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah JOD was great. The S8+ now requires a $130 deposit, and I'm sure the $1,000+ iPhone 8 will be more. This makes JOD no longer viable.

And yes I am switching for the network. Normally it is no issue, but my GF will be doing a project in a rural area for the next 6 months, and T-Mobile is no where re to be found out there. I have never had a issue, but rarely leave metro Honolulu. I will certainly miss the free international. 

I honestly will just go back to paying cash for my phones. No big deal, I just needed help navigating this step. Even in the links provided to me by the other guy it is still very ambiguous, about how you receive your money back. 

Thanks for taking the te out to reply I suppose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be getting the UDP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back into the VZ way of customer always last lol. I really have no choice though, so here we go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I am having a hard time with it is because that is how every other provoder handles this. Tmobile, and att will cut you a check for your balance. I didn't realize that Verizon had a underhanded version of the promotion. 

I will most likely just sell my phone on CL if that is the case. 

Thank you for your help, but you can keep the condesention.  I am very knowledgeable in certain fields, and I wouldn't talk down to someone who came to me for help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is uncanny how smart they are too. We saw a group of them distract another car of tourists, while his mate slipped all the way in their caravan, and slipped off with a giant loaf of bread.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so it seems like this is my best bet. Just wipe the slate with T-Mobile, and shop for the best deal retail on a S8+? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does VZ no longer offer the option to just pay off the balance of your phone? Ultimately I would probably rather have them just clean the slate with T-Mobile, and start fresh. 

The last thing I want is to have a promotion that is metered out over a long period of time since I compulsively change phones constantly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they not offer the $650 switcher promo anymore? I thought it was industry standard at this point to pay off balances as a enticement to switch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the trade in $480 is distributed over 24 months? 

Fuck all that shit. I generally change phones twice a year, and this year will be no exception.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry the maths are coming at me fast here. 

I would be getting their S8+ so $450+$200 visa right?

So no matter how you cut it all roads lead to $650 from vz. If I do as others suggest, and sell on swappa for hopefully $600 net, and walk up to best buy with no phone, does that put me at a advantage? 

I could get the phone for $750 from BB, or $700 from Walmart. I'm just having a hard time rationalizing what is my best move.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S8+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would have been much cooler yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think you have to worry about anything fucking with keas. I almost got carjacked by a group of them in Milford Sound.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how is this different from a hand roll? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just take the light bulb out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh to be a fly on the wall as you laid, belly down in the bushes, trying to find a glamorous angle to take a picture of this POS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is absolutely no way you drive that car, and don't have at least one Looney Toons character, tattooed on your meth addled body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I get some advice on switching to Verizon (trade in questions) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a variety of reasons, I will be bringing 4 tmobile lines over to VZ shortly. I am pretty happy with my 7+, but am also interested in the s8+. 

My question is mostly regarding what to do about my 7+ trade in. I owe $650 on it currently. I understand that VZ will pay my phone off, **or** give me a elevated trade in credit on the s8, but I'm wondering if stacking the best buy or walmart deals would be more beneficial then getting the $650 credit.

I went to a authorized retailer, and left even more confused. The rep said that since they are running the s8 promotion, I had no choice but to take the $480, and then the $170 difference would be made up in bill credits, over the span of 24 months.

There is no way in hell I will keep the phone for 2 years, and will most likely, be headed to the iphone 8 in fall regardless. How does this effect, the math?

TL DR am I better off getting $650 up front (jump through a bunch of hoops for bill credits), or buying phone from walmart/bestbuy and getting refunded over time?

Unrelated question



What is the best $400 phone for my GF, with the camera being her top priority?

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a tmobile 7+. Will I have issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why im switching in 2 weeks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miss my 69 c10. Certainly do not miss the death defying handling, or the .5 Btu Hvac. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see cute commuter, I see vibrating clitoral stimulus device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least the picture gallery landed on a happy ending </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 07:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you really made it  when you pull up in a $399 lease special "luxury car", that is so stripped out, and devoid of features you are jealous of the guy in the kia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just cancelled my s8 pre order. After a few days I realized how insane the position of the fingerprint reader would drive me. I will just stick with 7+ for now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you dropped $100,000 on that car it would still be a piece of shit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> auto della ragazza (chick car in Italian) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sell used golfs in your price range you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still this sentence is much higher then most would get for actually killing someone. I know of someone who mudered someone in cold blood, and plead to less then this.

 This was a split second asshole move, that was probably meant to scare them.

No question this guy is a POS. Still super long sentences should concern us all. It could be us up there some day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 11:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is what closed magoos back in the day. I always feel like they were super strict about ID even though there is no way I look anything but over 21 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The greatest honor to be bestowed on a roaster, by a roastee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 10:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may be unpopular but 15 years seems pretty harsh considering no one died. I think he certainly deserved time, but the dude is 70, and this is a death sentence. 

I think 5 years seems like a pretty reasonable amount of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could destroy N Korea in a span of a week. The fallout of millions of brainwashed citizens flooding S Korea, and China would be a catastrophe. Then there is the small issue that no one knows where **ALL** the nukes are. So we not only would have to destroy them we would also be racing against time to secure everything before it disappeared. The power vacuum that this would create would also cause a situation as bad as the Arab spring, and Trump would be cursed for generations, for not exhausting every diplomatic avenue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In their heyday these were coveted enough to be mentioned in rap songs in the same breath with Mercedes. 

 Rolling in MPVs every week I made 20 Gees

-Biggie smalls

Then again they also had a penchant for reflectively shiny suits, and wearing ski goggles as casual wear about town.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shocked headlights and grill look like a catfish who just had a popsicle slipped up its bum with no warning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen one of these on the road in years. They were as reliable as lending your junky brother $500.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a b6 from new. 3 years in the interior rotted away like they made it entirely out of jolly ranchers. 

Also have fun with your litany of intermittent, undiagnosable electrical issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like this guys disposition. He can really articulate a complex issue into a very understandable brief statement. I would like to see more of him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should make friends with the local drifters, and street racers. Plug it into their cars on a friday night, and maybe you can give your mother a heart attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is really a step too far though. IMO you are a adult, and you will need to assert your independence eventually. This is the perfect opportunity to tell them to BTFO. 


If you continue to allow them to act like this, then you only have yourself to blame when it continues. My parents were so apathetic, that they may as well have been roommates, but I have a few Asian friends whos parents were controlling all the way into adulthood. Each of them eventually ripped the band aid, and confronted their parents eventually. I would say those who did it earlier were better off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just keep it. At this point any other flagship will actually cost your more over the long term. At this point your best bet to save money is just keep it for a year or 2 more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a roll of toilet paper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can hear the banjo scene in Deliverance playing through my iPhone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how they managed to make these ugly while the Holdens are so sexy. Its something about the front bumper. It's kind like Scarlett Johansson had a identical twin sister who was the same in every way but her face looked like Danny devito.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cant really blame people who read the car magazines, and were convinced that the Mazda 6 was something special. 

There are people who read Dianetics as gospel, and belive every word on info wars. 

People look for validation. If you can find a outlet that will reinforce your shitty beliefs, then you will tend to believe them. 

For some it is the blog saying 9/11 was a inside job, or the church giving you a deeper meaning by promising a afterlife. For you it was Motor Trend convincing people that the less reliable, slower, second hand ice cream cone depreciating, marginally better handling Mazda 6 was the smart choice over a Camry/Accord. 

God bless the people who bought into the nonsense. Your sacrifices in resale value, kept us in miatas all these years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did your 400 pound, diabetic, lark scooter driving, Muumuu wearing, Virgina slim smoking, Obama hating, Obama care using, grand mother hand this down to you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the generation that 
 they bolted a giant Gillette Mach 3 razor blade on the front in place of a grill right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the polar opposite of a sleeper? A awaker?

The rx8 looks scream at the top of its lungs, that life with it will nothing but long milky power slides, and swinging from chandeliers. 

One little detail that they left out. They benchmarked a 50cc Chinese moped for the power output.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gina's BBQ healthy serving of whatever meat, 3 scoops rice, 4 scoops of whatever side you want. 

$10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine somebody dropping in on you with one of those things. It would put a axe wound in your back. 

That being said I am really curious to try one. Has anyone who is a bit of a novice to SUP ever rode one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You like it with extra leptospirosis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it really matter what side of the car they stuck that little lawnmower motor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere out there there is a Japanese redneck doing the saddest little coal roll in one of these.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naming a FWD lumina coupe Monte Carlo is like renaming Justin Bieber, Johnny Cash.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the kind of car a deposed kleptocrat dictator, of a banana republic would be buried in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is a GT it was never a rental car. 


Instead it was passed around like the town whore, by a bunch of enlisted guys. By this point it has so much differed maintenance, that it is just a mustang shaped pile of duct tape, and zip ties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cute you even got your Jeep painted pumpkin spice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without darkness there would be no light. 

Without sadness you would never know happiness. 

Without POS broke down S10s you would never know how much more reliable a tacoma is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually as compared to 10 years ago it is better. They are putting in bike lanes in a lot of places. The problem is that drivers are totally not conditioned to look out for cyclists. I suppose this is a issue everywhere, but for a variety of reasons our streets are engineered in such a way that any trip will leave you forced to ride in some very dangerous areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like musk has a robotic hairline if he was that bald 20 years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't help that Honolulu is not a bike friendly city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 01:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. 


My dear friend just had his arm broken when he got hit yesterday, and my co worker was hit 2 weeks ago and needed to be hospitalized for a few days from injuries. 


I'm a pretty die hard cyclist but I am beginning to reconsider. I like being alive and mobile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On this one issue I am really against the anti business regulations that localities put up. For far too long NIMBY interests have been against cell towers. The sheer number of new towers required for the coming wireless future may necessitate forcing the issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will try this. It is always frustrating only being able to eat half the tub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know but we consumers we I'll benefit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah pretty dangerous to get in bed with trump. Couple weeks in and a bunch of carriers ruined already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 11:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should make a bunch of little N5 badges to sprinkle around the exterior.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is on the level of (R) fake news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Big Bird has fallen on hard times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did a shit job weed whacking the lawn Pedro. Next time I'm calling ICE on your ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hmmm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are a lot of knowledgable people on here. Do you think tmobile will be able to deliver on there promises of better coverage in short order? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love T-Mobile, and have even encouged many people to switch over. However I have been running into a lot of issues recently. To make matters worse my GF is working on a project in a rural area off, and on for the foreseeable future. T-Mobile has 0 coverage within 15 minutes of her site, meanwhile Verizon is fully usable. 



I really want to stick with T-Mobile, but I have been encountering more, and more dead spots, and also more congested towers. 


I want to believe Neville that he has this together, and help us on the way, but I am on the fence if I should stay. 


I was just wondering of someone with a deeper understanding of the spectrum auction, possible sprint merger, and work in progress is actually going to make their coverage rival Verizon, or if it is just smoke. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize Pai was capable of doing anything but fucking consumers over. I'm sure he had to kick a puppy just to get the evil feeling back after this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You poor thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less practical fwd based mini van for those to vain to buy a Odessey.  No time for vanity when you are covered in baby puke, and goldfish crumbs. Just do the right thing and give in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't call a 5.4 300 HP v8 a "powerhouse".  

Ford is getting 300hp out of the V6 in the new mustangs, and that thing is a slug. 

Noise doesn't equal speed. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice stock image, anybody want to roast my car. 

http://auto.ferrari.com/en_US/wp-content/uploads/sites/7/2016/09/ferrari-laferrari-aperta-2016-gallery-prew-1-tr.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that is my one apprehension. I am lucky enough to travel a fair amount and $10 a day adds up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are only a few mods away from being hot cars.  Those mods being a can of gas and a Zippo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new unlimited plan is only about $20 more then I am currently paying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you use this on verizon? Thinking of moving over in a month or so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why pay Maaco $150 to respray my faded roof, when I can pay $150 to a Chinese fellow on ebay, for a roll of sticker bomb vinyl?

If log of shit was the look you were going for, then mission accomplished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure to take a nice clear well composed photo of you standing next to it posing.  Make sure to have on a big smile. Put on your leathers, and have your helmet in hand. Remember the best light for photography is a hour before sunset. 


Then post it to FB, or at least email it to your parents.


They will need a photo for your memorial services, so you might as well have a good shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't fuck it up. Once you pass probation you are on easy street for life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is good. cayenne powder on pickled mango is $$$ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practice this simple phrase in the mirror

"Eh you fucka, get away from my tree" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make your own, it is so easy. 

Tamashiro's has great deals on all grades of shrimp. Last time I was over there I got some tiger prawns the size of tennis balls, and did them n shore style. Ended up saving money, and eating good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat the tofu poke from times, and tamuras all the time. $7 per pound vs $12-16 is great value. However if you are thinking it is healthy you are dead wrong. Do yourself a favor, and go look at the nutrition on pre fried tofu, It is like eating a Big Mac per serving, vs pure protein Ahi. 

Also ahi is winners ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon service/speeds Oahu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 10:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tmobile has become trash in town. It is so congested I can hardly use it anymore, in certain areas. Today I had 3 bars of LTE in Kokohead, and could hardly load a webpage. Now that VZ is offering unlimited, I am contemplating switching.  

I was just wondering what others experience is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am totally doing this next time I catsit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking forward to being able to tell it to do things on the phone like turn off wifi, or set brightness. I can see it coming in handy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any rumors about the s8 active? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder when/if there will be one this year, and if it will still be curved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am moving from T-Mobile iPhone 7+ to Verizon s8+. Pretty stoked all around. T-Mobile is getting so congested around me, and I can't wait to be able to use my phone again. 

iPhone is pretty boring. I will probably end up buyimg the iPhone 8 though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note 3 is still a surprisingly great phone in 2017. I pulled mine out of the drawer for a minute after the note 7, and damned if that thing didnt hold its own. The only thing that showed it's age was the camera, and even that was passible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn that runs like butter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you like the s3? I am debating whether the fit 2 will cut it for me. Mostly just need steps, and notifications.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it shows up in a timely manner this year. It was early June by the time I got mine last year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too was like you until I cracked my note 7. Thankfully they recalled it. 

These designs are not rugged. I intend to at a minimum put on a grippy skin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Att has a BOGO deal but there are a lot of hoops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I hate how cases look on the curve. Alas I must have this. I opted for the insurance for sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not being a math nazi or anything but FYI 6.2 - 5.5 = 0.7 not 1.2

I played with it today.  I wish they stayed with 16 by 9 aspect ratio. They could have gotten to 6.7, and still been manageable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will never suspect that you were the arsonist all along.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you are a cunt, when even a large crowd of annoying Aussies can't stand you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toyata are absolute geniuses. 

They know the demographic for this car is all distracted teenage girls, and barren middle aged office women.  Knowing their propensity to back into inanimate objects, they sell them a car that looks like it got rear ended straight from the factory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Painting a Volvo arrest me red is about as incongruous as the queen of England in racy lingerie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 08:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong sub. This isn't R/roastmyrefridgerator  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 800+ credit. I was being facetious. The question was more rhetorical. Why should I be forced to pay a non refundable deposit on a phone that I dont intend to keep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
