<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7982</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 20:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. There was some small hope in me that when I posted this both would see it and meet in the comments section. But no luck... Yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit. 

I mean, I totally knew that. That's why the hypothetical guy is so excited that it's Maple. ^^^I ^^^totally ^^^didn't ^^^know ^^^that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh definitely not me. I already found the girl of my dreams that I wow with my Family Guy knowledge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 17:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that he says baseball bat knowledge, but not baseball knowledge.

Girl: "So if the ball bounces, then goes over the wall, what happens?"

Boy: "I have no idea, but did you see the bat that guy is using? That Maple Grain is marvelous. The wood was harvested from a small grove in the middle of Vermont." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's our first clue. We need to know what the extra 'C' means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An "I Saw You" in today's Inlander </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 16:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My suggestion for Training </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Small Training improvement suggestion: Correct shot video clips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm trying some of these All-Star training, and some of them are tough. I would like the ability to see how shots should be done, so I could practice the techniques, vs just guess and check.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the relevant municipal code:

https://my.spokanecity.org/smc/?Section=12.02.010 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So with the shoveling rule it's honestly barely enforced. The only time I really seen them go after it was back in 08 I think when we had tons of snow and kid's were walking in the streets to get to bus-stops instead of using sidewalks. That being said, maybe just shovel every 6" or so, to save your back some work and avoid a build-up of ice underneath. Then shovel what's leftover at the end.

This snow event looks to be a prolonged one, so maybe just shovel every morning is your other option.

For the parking issue, I would still follow it if you live on a semi straight street. If we hit stage 2 they are almost guaranteed to plow it at some point. I've seen them do every cul-de-sac in my neighborhood. This big reason you want to follow it is because the plows will probably just block in your car if you don't, and plowed snow is a bitch to remove.

FYI, a big one is make sure you keep the fire hydrant clear of snow! I feel like they would write a ticket for that much quicker than they would the sidewalk rule.

Let me know if you have any other questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really dumb question, so I guess this is the right place to ask.

I got an email today form my Student Loan financier, going over the interest and how it applies to my taxes. One thing that confused me is this:

**What's included in your number?** The interest on payments received between January 1, 2016 and 5:00 p.m. Central time on December 30, 2016. 

So my question is: Why is December 31st not included? Is the interest I pay on that date just not applied to my taxes at all? I know it's small, it just seems interesting to me that they don't include it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah no worries then. Hell of a coincidence I guess. There's actually a lot of bots out there that will copy top comments from one sub to another, so they can farm karma and sell accounts, which is why it's good to call it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 06:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Did you copy the top comment from the Cow Chop subreddit with minor edits?](https://www.reddit.com/r/CowChop/comments/5ggnxz/spicy_fan_mail_disaster_behind_the_cow_chop/das2fus/) 

lazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earl Thomas om Twitter - This game has been so good to me no regrets.. A lot is running through my mind including retirement thanks for all the prayers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 04:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 23:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bring steak and wine with me to Chuck E Cheeses </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad told me a story about his first day at police academy. They were in the classroom, and the teacher was lecturing on a topic. All of a sudden a man ran into the room and "stabbed" the teacher, then immediately ran out. The teacher got back up, then had each student write down a description of the suspect. Once done, the teacher read off the results, and each one had multiple mistakes. Witnesses are incredibly unreliable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest they are all pretty good. If you're looking for fancy-ish you can go to Masselow's or the noodle place. The buffet is a great choice as well. I like their deli, and Fatburger can give you a great burger. Hell it's even good to just go in, play some Keno, and get a $3.50 German Sausage delivered to you. There are quite a few different options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 16:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's too late now, but if you're ever in the same situation Northern Quest is probably your best bet. Multiple restaurants to choose from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an Amazon locker by my house now. Locked inside until I enter the code to get it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an opinion about sports that they know is dumb and controversial, but say anyways. It's the ESPN equivalent of Clickbait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 03:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael may have taken the point lead this week in RLFF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice choice. I personally hope the Hawks can beat the Cowboys, especially if we are at full health. But man Dak and Zeke are good, so it will be tough. Anyway it goes I think the NFC wins this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Superbowl: Who do you got? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great choice! The best part about being the Browns announcer is that if you mess up a name the fans just assume it's their new quarterback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In between matches can you please channel your inner John Madden and draw plays on the screen?

But seriously, this is awesome. Can you do an informal AMA? If you could be the announcer for any team, which would it be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the Grand Coulee Dam was built, it's main purpose was touted as being for irrigation. The electricity generated was going to be used for the purpose of paying back the loans used to build the dam. However WW2 quickly changed the focus from irrigation to power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever taken discrete math? There may be a test question that would interest you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally!

Nice job with the name idea /u/CGA001 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. Oregon seems to do it right.

http://www.oregonlive.com/education/index.ssf/2016/06/5_things_to_know_about_oregons.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the cities themselves should decide. A living wage in Seattle is not a living wage in rural Washington state, but both have the same minimum wage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the best solution, but try to right click on taskbar, and check auto-hide the taskbar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't work when our state likes to keep voting to increase ours above everybody else. I kind of wish people would see the issue when one state will be $13 an hour and the other still below $8.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Turns out smaller businesses do better when the markplace has consumers with increased purchasing power.

I live in Washington. I go to a small general/grocery store that primarily caters to farmers and ranchers, staffed almost entirely by high school students making minimum wage. Now the states has voted in a large minimum wage increase, and the store will have to pay these workers more.

But here is the issue, the farmers and ranchers won't have increased purchasing power, as they still have to compete with ranchers and farmers from Montana, Idaho, and other Western states. So where will the money come from? 

The store itself will be forced to do something to account for these extra wages. Whether it's laying off some of these high school workers, cutting hours, or raising prices on products. As far as I can see any solution is a bad one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> French said the Clean Air Agency has been wrestling with this issue for months, but the ordinance was never added to the commissioners agenda. Instead, it was raised as a miscellaneous item during Tuesdays meeting, a move that doesnt appear to violate Washingtons Open Public Meetings Act.

There comes a time when its the right time to bring something forward, French said, adding that he didnt want to cause an uproar before testing out the ordinance. You dont want to advertise these things before they even take effect.

This really annoys me. They knew this would cause issues and debate, so they purposely didn't cover it as an issue until they already allowed it. I don't think these "miscellaneous items" should be allowed, or at least should be curtailed. 

The policy came as a surprise to Crystal Oliver, who advocates for laws that are friendly to pot farmers and recently served on the Clean Air Agency Marijuana Advisory Committee.

I did not see it on the agenda or I would have been there, she said, referring to the commissioners meeting, which had no audience other than a Spokesman-Review reporter.

This seems very shady by Al French. It sounds like they literally waited until nobody was at the meeting to bring up issues with the proposal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spokane County bans new outdoor pot farms as odor complaints roll in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let me tell you this-- /r/_____ is one of the most malevolent, cruel, coldhearted online communities you'll ever find... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me tell you this-- /r/Drama is one of the most malevolent, cruel, coldhearted online communities you'll ever find, and even as a supporter of free speech it appalls me that Reddit would allow such a vile, festering hub of bigotry and sadism to exist. You think [slur]town was bad? That subreddit, if you pick up on the dog-whistles (and many don't even bother with that-- say want you want about Stormfront, at least it bans "n[slur]"), will reveal itself to you as Reddit's number one hub for the web's most hardened Nazis, Klansmen, Fascists, and Gamergaters. You'll notice on the sidebar that it encourages members to be as dramatic as possible. That's intentional. They encourage arguments in the comments section. That's intentional. You know the Three Minute Hate (it's from this underrated book 1985, give it a read, it's scary how much it parallels our society)? It's like that, they want to stoke the flames of reactionary rage so they continue to dogpile every progressive and minority who enters the subreddit, normalizing these evil feelings. They brigade from subreddit to subreddit, having an entire cabal of mods spanning hundreds of communities, gaslighting lived experiences of the oppressed and unashamedly bolstering Reddit's homegrown white supremacy movement. They've kink-shamed hundreds of people too, some even... to death. I fear that /r/drama may be producing an entire army of Dylann Roofs and Elliot Rogers, and I highly suggest that nobody dares visit that horrible subreddit, lest you potentially fall victim to its corruptive aura.


https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/5fnq57/whats_the_dumbest_thread_that_made_it_to_the/dalvrxh/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a joke...

But then again on this site who the hell can tell anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want to see Chris try to cook with Gordon Ramsay. And I hope it's the Americanized version of Ramsay, not the lovable, only a slight ass British version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it's Office Space 2 - The Bobs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Best city in the world!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ilqfw72sc54) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm totally in on RT Funny Fantasy League.

ALL ABOARD THE BLANCHARD HYPE TRAIN... CHOO CHOO MOTHER FUCKER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 19:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I think Jon meant Jaggir Koppen, who famously beat the USA team in the Schpupel Championship of 2012. He was a bit of a cunt about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of options for you.

There is a weekly FAQ thread, but that's hard to find sometimes. The other options is /r/tipofmyrooster, which is the perfect place to ask your questions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I think this is how Gavin sets it up for Dan.](https://i.imgur.com/uNsVW.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anybody mentioned Clover yet? It adds tabs to Windows explorer, so you don't have to open a ton of separate Windows. Incredibly useful for work applications.

http://ejie.me/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing it wrong. A better question is why random comments get Reddit Gold. At that point you're hedging your bets, because it's about 50/50 on whether you get downvoted, or actually receive Gold.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/AHMichaelJones I think your mom has some explaining to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 22:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice one! Savage! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand where you're coming from. This comment string is the first time I've heard they renamed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we see Kanye make a return? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 18:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like perfect timing for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gavin's is the British spelling, Michael's is the freedom spelling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kanye West hospitalized after abruptly canceling national tour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one in the crawl space with all of the candles made me cringe. But then they tried lighting the Ouija Board on fire and it was even worse. These guys are crazy, and yet I can't stop watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 19:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! I'll give them a call and see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect, thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 18:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh good call. I'll just put up a sign that says "Duck Season" and wait for them to come change it to "Rabbit Season" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where in Spokane can I find duck breast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 17:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to make duck breast prosciutto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 16:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, smoking weed in public isn't allowed in Washington. However, they do have these new disposable vapor pens. They are about the size of a cigarette, and will offer a quick hit of "special" vapor. When you get here, I would give a few places a call (you have so many stores to choose from) and see if they have it. It may be the best discrete way of getting high, beside edibles of course.

Also if you're new to smoking, let the people at the dispensary know that. Every dispensary I have gone to is full of super nice people, and they honestly love to help and teach newbies.

Now after you do it, make sure you don't use too much, and enjoy the hell out of our city. Downtown Spokane can be beautiful in the Winter, and visiting a dispensary beforehand will make it even more special. 

Also check out the Spokane Comedy Club, and see who is on tap when you come. You might get lucky and get a great comedian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kind of funny, I'm working on something just like that. However it isn't even close to done, so so for now you can check out this link and look at the comments there:

https://www.reddit.com/r/roosterteeth/comments/5d2v4d/i_want_to_build_a_primer_for_new_fans_with_the/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's funny, 1927 would be the perfect time to predict financial collapse too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go, they have some suckers that are Mango flavored with a chile powder on top, and they are incredible. Give them a try! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://sports.mynorthwest.com/12835/a-closer-look-at-the-seahawks-intentional-safety/

Seahawks have done this as well. Up by 6 with little time left, and they were afraid of the punt being blocked or ran back. The interesting thing is that they wouldn't necessarily do this anymore as extra points aren't as guaranteed. But it could still happen if you're facing a great kicker, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm buying one. Not at full price, but at this discounted price I will.

On days when I wear ties to work nobody really cares what the design on it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> colorizebot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My grandpa in a Model A </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 02:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're all Druish.

I know what you're thinking... "That's funny, they don't look Druish!", but they are, I promise you. They just cover it up with their Hollywood makeup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earl Thomas is great. he even gives out free safety advice to Seattle!

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-EJ59-axIFI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 19:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call on all of these, especially the old shorts. Have to make sure they know who Pongo is too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call! They're probably the best intro videos out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call, just a link to the playlist should work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it, I may make this the intro to Chris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an awesome list to start with, thanks! I'll let you know if I need some more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect! Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The part where the fucking Jumping Spider Zombie flies in the air for the first time made me laugh harder than I have in a long time. It was just so fucking unexpected.

Also, Jumping Spider Zombies, band name, called it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pete Prisco actually. He hates the Hawks and Wilson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Pete Prisco, he hates Russell Wilson for some reason. Here is what he said about the game:

Seahawks Russell Wilson was sensational against the Patriots. If he continues to play like that, I just might admit that he is great

In case your curious, here is what he said back in 2015:

The Seahawks fans hate me now, but thats okay, Prisco told Felger   Mazz. Its because I kill Russell Wilson. I dont think hes that good. I think hes just OK.

He does it just to be controversial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to build a primer for new fans, with the best older videos to watch to get "up to speed", and need your help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 15:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everybody. One question that seems to pop up a lot in the sub, and I believe on the website, is from new fans wanting to know where to start. Rooster Teeth has been around for a good chunk of time, and there is so much content to wade through that it can be a bit daunting for the new fans. I would like to make it a bit simpler, and have an easy reference to give to new fans. Eventually I would like to see it go under the Wiki on the sub if possible.

So although I know a lot of videos, I also know that the best way to compile a large list like this is to crowd-source. I think the best way to do this is to come up with categories, and go form there. Here is what I'm thinking of so far:

First and Foremost, the funniest moments in RT history. Headlight fluid, facility tours, WWE intros, Cheesemaster, etc.

Next would be the "inside jokes." First ever Tower of Pimps, People Like Grapes, Mark Nutt, and probably some others that don't just involve Gavin.

After that would be "intro" videos, basically videos where you get to see what all of RT are like. Would include 

So with all of these I need help finding videos to add to all of these categories, and also any categories you think would be useful to add. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 00:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, it was a good answer. You just said it a bit... Dickish. Don't mind me though, I'm just on a personal crusade to make this Subreddit a nicer place overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 23:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand it was a simple question, but do people really have to answer it in a shitty way like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If dogs used the internet, what websites would they visit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 22:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 17:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you're saying, but in my (un-verified) experience, I think I see way more "fake" service animals than real ones. Obviously I don't know if they are real service animals or not, but when it's a middle-aged overweight housewife with her little tiny dog I get suspicious. I don't care too much, but I'm pretty allergic (bad asthma) to a lot of animals, so I try to pay attention and avoid these service animals more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to the others listed, here is [Chase Honey Company](http://chasehoneycompany.com/honey.aspx), based in Otis Orchards. They sell it by the gallon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, stories by Tyson. "Green eggth and ham" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 07:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice analysis, but I was really hoping this was a increasingly desperate Browns fan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry no, it's very random. Fluctuates with other countries doing stuff with their military. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 04:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god that stillborn joke!

But congrats guys!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Thanks! I will be sure to donate nonetheless, but just thought it would be cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 00:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends. Once a day maybe when nothing is going on, a few times an hour if Russia or N. Korea is doing dumb shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the awful title, I had no idea how to explain this succinctly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Sherman states that hhis fine for hitting the kicker is un-appealable, due to the NFL saying he hit him after the whistle was blown, but unable to hear it on the video. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, if you hear it only said once that probably is a test or something like that, not anything going on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anybody that's wants to try listening for it:

[Go here](http://websdr.ewi.utwente.nl:8901/). Select USB, type in a frequency of 8992, and Max in for zoom. You'll hear static until somebody talks, unless you choose squelch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he means Rooster Teeth grew a bad batch of weed?

https://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=outdo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry that's what I meant, like headset mics, not microphones to the stream itself. That would just be asking for a raid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to [this](http://spokaneriver.net/wastedirectory/waste_type/styrofoam/) Spokane River website, [Sunshine Disposal](http://www.sunshinedisposal.com/) takes it at their transfer stations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a side idea. I would love that if you donate a certain amount you could play a match or two with the people gaming on the side. For example if I donate $50 I could play a match of Rocket League (my personal fav game) with whoever is on the couch at the time. Then again they would probably get overloaded, but it might be fun!

Maybe they could just bring in animators, etc and have them play with mics on, so fans could talk to at least some people from the company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 19:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit those raffles are gonna generate so much money for charity. Great idea guys! I'm happy to see how much they raise this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is the issue I see with it. While it's probably great for Seattle, it sucks for small towns, especially in Eastern Washington. I go to a small town North of Spokane and shop at a small general/grocery store there. Every worker in that place is high school age, making minimum wage. However the shoppers there are generally the farmers from the surrounding areas.

The farmers won't be making more money after this law, beef and crop prices are probably going to remain stable as to compete with other states. So where in the world will this general store get the money to increase pay to all these workers? It's almost certain they will have to let some go, as I know the owners don't make a huge amount of money. It's tight margins, and if they try to raise prices their main customers literally won't have the money to purchase anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.google.com/maps/place/Hayden+Creek+Shooting+Range/@47.8207922,-116.6587341,16.25z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x0:0xb74bb08c3c094cbe!8m2!3d47.8215683!4d-116.6633677

https://www.google.com/maps/place/Boggs+Pit/@48.056362,-117.4411018,15.96z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x0:0x9f540f68eda4df02!8m2!3d48.0554639!4d-117.4478441

These two are both decent.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can almost guarantee a majority of those that voted against had no idea what the proposition was, and just selected no because of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would it be possible to breed a seedless apple? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 05:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just trying to add a bit of context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 01:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the biggest thing to remember is that for a majority of the RT employees this is the first time that "their" candidate lost, so that may be part of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My prediction is just a bunch of scenes with everybody shocked. Thats it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trouble is an understatement. We ran for more than 100 yards in 15/16 games last year. We've done it in only 2 games so far this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word objective is not a good word to use when describing future-economics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they're nice for Seahawks fans, but I want him to sale a shirt specifically that caters to fans that hate the Seahawks. "Smear the Sherm" or something more creative than that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Sherman should pull a Bosworth and sell shirts complaining about him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Embrace the hate

[For Context](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brian_Bosworth#Seahawks) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Joel could offend China very easily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to where all the playlists show up and you select which one you want to play (2v2, 3v3), then go back to main menu at do party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a union rep, he supposed to talk about stuff like this. You haven't heard other players complaining about what he said have you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 21:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you start the game, go and load all the playlists before trying to join the party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 17:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/madlads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 21:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not completely. What this means is that when you vote for president you are trying to get your state to swing a certain way. If 51% of Hawaiian residents vote red, and 49% vote blue, the state's delegates will then vote for the red candidate. 

Now what actually happens is that states get entrenched in who they vote for. There could be a state that votes blue in every election, and the result is 75% blue and 25% red. In that case if you are a red voter in that state, your vote is kind of obsolete.

Theoretically, the number of delegates should line up cleanly with the number of voters in that state, but that isn't always the case. So you have situations where a candidate can win the popular vote, but lose because they didn't get enough delegates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really any local place that is willing to set it up. I've voted in a retirement home before, since it was the closest place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If you can't handle me at my worst, then you don't deserve me at my best."

-Adolf Hitler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a cheap harmonica on Amazon. It's a lot of fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The final scene is Homer and Marge tucking the kids into bed. Bart asks a philosophical question, Lisa is afraid of bed bugs, Maggie is afraid of Rock-A-Bye Baby, and they all end up in Homer and Marge's bed to sleep. Marge says something like "I guess we're doing this all over again" and Homer says "Doh!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://wikileaks.org/podesta-emails/emailid/40207#efmBH4BMF

Steve has also suggested that he might be able to help to defray some of these costs himself if we are allowed to pay someone who is on the campaign from the outside.

HRC - advise on legality of paying consultants outside the campaign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for bazickoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 01:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goodell heard he was shooting pictures and couldn't handle somebody being shot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 21:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew I feel bad for the FBI agent that has to look at all of his sexting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal judge denies Monsantos request to dismiss Spokane River PCB lawsuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That post was made after this post. Doubt it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 01:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect, Ill do that. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 01:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so buy prepaid, pay $30, then insert SIM? No waiting period? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> overview for allplacemap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 18:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aah good point. Corrected! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 03:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Physics
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 1945, Harry Daghlian dropped a Tungsten Carbide brick onto a plutonium bomb core, prompting it to go critical and irradiate/kill him. What would this have looked like in the room? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 03:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 22:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck NFL?

The fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I don't keep up with the podcasts, has there been any talk of other DnD campaigns? There's so many people I would want to hear do a campaign, especially the live-action writers. It would be amazing.

Also, just curious, how is H H funded? No ads, free to everybody, is it just an "extra" show? Maybe I've just been missing product-placement or something.

"You enter the Bazaar, looking for a good clothing market. To the right is a large store. An illuminated sign reads 'Macy's'."

Or...

"Roll a D20 to see if you escape the spider's grip"

"I roll a natural 20."

"You pull a Red Bull out of your knapsack and drink it. It give you wings and you fly away." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 17:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to get into the game now, happy I'm not alone!

Fyi, your best friend will be /r/worldbuilding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 16:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems as though he's planning something, maybe cooking something up. Can you smell it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you don't care about the Presidential Election, you should really vote for local reps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atleast cite your source if you're going to copy word-for-word. 

https://reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3d4u5k/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] After the sulfur mines start to dry up, Satan is struggling to pay the bills and keep the heat on. Unfortunately, he is forced to take an office job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 22:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try travelling across the state. Not only the tickets, but gas, food, etc. Adds up quick. Spokane already has a 30000 seat stadium used only for high school football games, so a developmental league would be awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 21:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All their GTA Heists. And if you haven't watched H H yet definitely download those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
