<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4516</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 14:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true, bellydance comes from dances performed by men and women in and around the Middle East and Mediterranean at social gatherings. The women's dances are thought to derive from ancient birthing practices, pre and post natal exercises to strengthen the body and the men's from combative practice. It's true that the dance does condition your abdominal muscles and pelvic floor, which is good for sex, but also good for avoiding prolapse after giving birth, helps correct your posture, helps with breathing and all the isolated movements are good for your brain. 

It was westerners who sexualised the dance by depicting it as risqu in art, cinema and popular culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 13:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had something similar at my wedding, but phwoar!! It didn't have a pork pie in it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 23:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also a bellydancer, it can be very beneficial when I am on top. Most movements and undulations feel amazing for both partners and just practicing the dance strengthens your pelvic floor so you can massage your partner from the inside. The pelvic strength can help in missionary as well making it easier for you to meet his thrusts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 00:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put away all the shoes. ALL of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 07:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if you did have a union they wouldn't be able to help you with this if you weren't already a member. 

Apart from that, this hasn't actually happened yet right? Wait and see what happens at the meeting, document everything, if the boss does attempt to humiliate you in front of the team you may have a very good case for workplace gender discrimination. But it may not even happen despite the tip off. At any rate, I think it's bullshit that you shouldn't have to deal with in 2016. If you need to chat about it feel free to PM me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 01:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he attempts to address this non issue in front of your co-workers it would definitely be classed as bullying and harassment. In my country gender based discrimination is seriously frowned upon and can get employers into a lot of hot water. 

Personally if an employer brought this up with me in an open forum such as a team meeting, I would tell them that I would be more than happy to discuss the non issue with them further, but not in a public forum such as a staff meeting. And I would request that the union delegate be present for support. Then I would report my concerns to my supervisor's manager, and further up the chain, seek advice from HR until I got satisfaction. Are you in the union OP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 01:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was never spanked as a child, I guess I was just a very good child, but I find spanking now with my partner very erotic to the point where I would never think of spanking a child as I now consider spanking to be a sex act.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 00:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. There's a fair amount of gore and fighting and war wounds and such as well. It's not for the squeamish. They were dangerous times to be alive. I still think it's worth it, it's a great show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 17:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the television series Outlander, it's about four eps into the second season and the first season is out on DVD. It is awesome, romantic and quite explicit. Great sex scenes that really cater to the female gaze. It's also generally pretty great, you'll both enjoy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 12:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes a long time to get an insurance payout. Right now they need food and shelter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 06:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a red herring but yes, I'd probably be offended if you referred to me as a "female" even knowing its your standard vernacular. I get offended when shop assistants address me with "Are you right there" instead of "Hello how can I help you" even though I know that the former is a standard greeting for young Australian people these days. I find it impolite, impersonal and offensive. As I do being referred to as a female. I'm a woman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 06:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time I saw one I was like "you what mate?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 34F and my boobs are incredibly sensitive, I usually orgasm when my SO plays with my breasts. It's a weird sensation, different to an orgasm from clit or G spot play, almost a feeling of comfort or peacefulness at the same time as being turned on, like a whole body warm hug.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally hate it. I can't think of anything I dislike more during sexy times. It's just not a nice feeling for me. It actually kind of hurts for me, which is why I hate it so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a trick to using them? Or are European hotel bidets just poor quality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those ads you have over there for pharmaceuticals are heaps weird hey! This is a great parody. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate being referred to as a "female"? As if I'm some kind of specimen. I'm a woman. I never refer to men as "males"  it just shits me so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 00:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be this long to ride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 11:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. It makes me sad that we let ourselves get so scared by our politicians and the media that we will forego public decency. You can actually see that he's embarrassed that he made a mistake, but what made him think that was an ok thing to do in the first place? Fear. The only way to fight this is to rip your TVs electrical cord out at the socket.  So sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 11:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need dis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 00:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that as "I'm going to be a birdie soon" and was like "Ok then, fly away mum so I can eat all dis food" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 00:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super private? Sounds more like super controlling. This is seriously not how real relationships work OP, it's super abusive and I'm disgusted that he would violate you by sending your naked pics to his mates. I would personally be so mortified, then I would probably seek sweet justice, but that's me, I hope you make the right decision for you, look after yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The modern electric or battery powered vibrator probably came out of those experiments but it is thought vibrators were in use in antiquity with phallic gourds being filled with bees so they would vibrate. I've read a few fragments from Ancient Greece that described older women secretly buying dildos from a false fronted shop lol, like "Ooh just going out to buy some vases *wink wink*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly I think about my SO, but occasionally I will think about an admirer I once had who nothing ever happened with, I like to think about what might have happened had I let myself go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 00:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be worried that this behaviour might be Jane acting out something that has been done to her.

Edit: I see I'm being downvoted, that's cool, but I just wanted to clarify that this is not armchair psychology, I'm a behaviour analyst and work with children who have experienced trauma. Sexual exploration in childhood is normal and healthy, but when the child is aggressive, persistent or repetitive it can very often indicate that child is acting out something. If I didn't consider it in the realm of possibility and keep it in the back of my mind I wouldn't be a responsible clinician.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 01:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this was "How to eat pussy like a champ" with Nina Hartley. It's a pretty great video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 09:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it's not Erika, check her stuff out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 09:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love her stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 00:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first two days of my period I usually feel like I have a moderate hangover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 13:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. The scene in The Two Towers where they bury Eomer. 
2. The end of Hero (movie with Jet Li) OMG
3. All of The Hunger Games, because I know how it ends. Haven't been able to watch the last one just yet.

Special mention: Dancer in The Dark. I will never watch that film again. Not even once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 11:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $12 an hour? Is that fucking for real?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 10:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this one day I was on a day off and vacuuming in an old shirt of my husband's and g-string (thong for those in the northern hemisphere) I was bending over to get under the lounge when there was a knock at the door....at this point my anxiety rose exponentially, because you see we had, at that time, sliding glass doors, and whoever it was had a rare view of my most southern parts.

I rose and turned demurely, pulling the shirt down frantically and answered, "Yes"
The lady payed no attention to my discomfort and proceeded to attempt to be invited in so that she could give me a copy of The Watchtower and tell me how I should change religions, because whatever I was wasn't the right one. I very badly handled the situation due to aforementioned near nudity and anxiety, and she left muttering about how rude I was.

Flash forward around 9 years. I knock on a door on my business to meet a client I would be supporting (Desperately needed for support) Guess who answered the door? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 23:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coregasms are annoying, push ups are the worst for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 23:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had these before after thrush from a strong course of antibiotics, it will usually go away of its own accord after a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 20:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but not nearly as often as I have been told this by random men in the street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 20:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The simple answer is that not all vulvas are built exactly like the diagrams in sex ed books, and not all clitoris owners are as vocal as others when it comes to giving directions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I'm Australian and have always used condoms with my long term BF, I never liked hormonal forms of birth control and they keep me from getting pregnant when I don't want to be just yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you're ovulating and still have a couple more clear weeks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 23:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was young and first discovering sex, Brazilians weren't a thing, so because of pubes covering everything up I never knew that my long labia were different to anyone else's. I sexed and forplayed with my BF with abandon, face sitting, 69 everything. I had loads of fun. It wasn't until I tried shaving and I started looking at porn (long labias are censored in porn in my country) that I started to get crippling insecurity over my long labia. Only in my 30s have I started to let go of those silly insecurities and love my lovely lips again. I feel like the culture of plastic surgery has a hell of a lot to answer for, women have been born with different size and shaped lips for centuries, it's totally nothing to worry about. Just have sex and have fun!

One position that I love is a sideways 69 that works up to face sitting, we will be eating for two and suddenly he will pull me up on top. So sexy, maybe you could try that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 23:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was also my husband. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 08:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 23:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, if the man is serious about his cycling his shirts would have a chamois inside to soak up the scrotal sweat. You'd probably get more sweat marks on seats from ladies lunching in their active wear.

Edit: I went hiking in the weekend and then went for a coffee, left embarrassing bum sweat mark on seat, announced this to my sister. The people at the next table were amused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 23:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Budgie smugglers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 14:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tampons in Aus are far more comfortable and absorbent. Whenever I have travelled in the USA I always took a big supply of tampons from home after the first time. I hate the applicator tampons you have over there, they are thin and uncomfortable and the applicators are intrusive and too long and they hurt and are hard and cold. And you need to change them more often.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 01:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word does get misused a fair bit these days but when we talk about individuals who use behaviours of concern we talk about triggers and function. As in what was the antecedent that triggered the individual to use the behaviour and what function does the behaviour serve for the individual, as in, what are they trying to communicate by using the behaviour. 

At any rate, I feel like laying OP off is an ineffective behaviour intervention, it doesn't help the individual to learn alternative behaviour and just sets them up for further failure, a worse reputation. But it's a fine line when your safety is at stake OP. Organisations have to look after their staff. It's just a really sucky situation OP and I hope you find another opportunity soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 11:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the short shorts question, you are obviously not Australian. Stubbies and singlets were practically the uniform for men when I was growing up. I saw many an accidental nut in my youth.

Edit: just had to also say that the last music festival I attended I saw two labias poking out of two separate ladies' short shorts. I think the circle is complete and the argument is over. At least it is down under. Most of the time it's too hot to care how little clothes we are wearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 12:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen this film approximately 300 times and this is still my reaction to the prospect of watching it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 00:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved offices to avoid a seriously long commute and left my work BFF behind. No more Pho Fridays, no more meetings just to gossip, no more. I was so lonely for about two months I would cry every night when I got home.

I'm better now, I compensated by becoming a workaholic and no longer taking breaks. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 23:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's soy protein in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am deeply uncomfortable with the name of this product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 12:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to two of my friends in a bar in NYC where the waitresses convince you to dance on the bar and then encourage you to take off your bra and throw it into the pile of bras that decorate the roof of the bar. Then when you want it back you can't get it back. I refused to take off my bra. But there were tears from my friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 06:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having read both of our comments, I don't think you do disagree. We simply have different ways of saying the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 23:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The longer you let co-sleeping go on the harder it is to break the habit. Had you both worked together earlier to get him sleeping in his own room, the whole traumatic experience could have been avoided. I know there are many reasons for parents co-sleeping with their child, including cultural ones, so no judgement from me. But in my job I often come across parents who have allowed their children who have autism or intellectual disability co-sleep with them well into their late teens, and only start to see it as a problem when they are all outgrowing the bed. Those situations are almost impossible to deal with.

You are right to be annoyed, your husbands way of dealing with it leaves a lot to be desired, but it sounds like you weren't working together to fix the issue either. Now that he is sleeping on his own, can you see the benefit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 03:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George is pretty incredible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 11:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love my hitachi, but I have a sensitive yet fairly resilient clit. A lot of women get over sensitive and probably wouldn't like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 05:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may be because most people masturbate in secret, meaning they have to keep quiet. For me, I moan, that and rhythmic breathing helps me get there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a lot of people moaning while aroused is involuntary. We don't just moan because it's what is expected of us or to turn our partners on. Moaning, in my case at least, helps with arousal and achieving orgasm as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 21:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my country laws are being proposed so that if you hit somebody and it causes their death, you are sentenced with murder, regardless of your actual intent to kill or just injure. 

Nobody has the right to take away another's life through pure stupidity and anger. This idiot should rot for taking away this beautiful young woman's life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 21:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 13:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have only ever been able to orgasm using a vibe, or with a partner but recently after reading many posts in r/sex I decided I needed to work on making myself cum with just my hands, I felt like I had missed that step along the way and wanted to experience it. I also felt like as I get older it's becoming harder for me to achieve orgasm with a vibe and with my partner, so I thought I might need to work at it a bit and re-train my brain and body and find out what I had missed.

I heard about https://www.omgyes.com on r/chickflixxx and decided to check it out. It's a pay site, but fairly cheap, there are instructional videos and descriptions, an interactive component to the app and I got some great ideas to try. In the past few months I've been able to bring myself to orgasm, really intense orgasm, three times. I feel like I can transfer the techniques to sex with my partner and teach him the new ways that work for me as I am maturing. I don't know if it will work for everyone but it worked for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 10:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for translating. I tend to reddit early in the morning or late at night so my brain doesn't auto translate to universal speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 10:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha reading it back I tend to agree. Seriously though, trakkies are as bad as stubbies or budgie smugglers on a fat bloke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Aus we call them trakkie daks and I've seen way too many bogans sporting them with thongs, a singlet, flanno and a Winnie Red hanging out of their mouth to ever associate them with the sexy times. Yes you can see the package, but most of the blokes that wear them in public, we you don't want to be imagining their package in any way. 

But I'm open to coming back to the U.S. to research these magical sexy pants you speak of.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 03:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think she was. She was saying that the "girl's talk" was real. That what they spoke about in their girly chat was revolution and critical theory, rather than gossiping about men and clothes. She wasn't saying that women who talk about men and clothes aren't real girls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 14:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if you insist... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 03:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only forever, that's not long at all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 01:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is heartbreaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the reasons that I put in my reply to your other comment, I was flippant and defensive and should have handled it better. I would be happy to talk about my beliefs in person, but the public nature of the Internet has opened me up to ridicule before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it is tomorrow here now, the sun is shining, the birds are singing and I am only mildly hungover. Things are looking up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has been my experience that people who ask about my beliefs are usually only looking for an opportunity to ridicule and discredit them. It has happened a fair few times that I have attempted to explain the beliefs I have that are so closely tied to my cultural identity only to be told I am wrong and crazy so now the question gets me on the defensive straight away. I was flippant and should have handled it better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have had the shittest day of my life yesterday and then had some beers and said something flippant. I can see how it would offend 

I get where you are coming from too, and yes it is always best to hear the personal story than the textbook account, however in my experience, Internet people who ask about my beliefs are usually not actually curious but only looking for a chance to ridicule and discredit me, to prove that I am wrong. It's happened to me many times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 23:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, tone doesn't translate well through text. I can see how my comment might seem offensive. This wasn't my intention but may have to do with the utterly shit day I had yesterday, the beers I had to try and feel better and the fact that I've been attacked by Internet strangers for my beliefs before under the guise of curiosity. 

Suffice it to say, my beliefs have more to do with my cultural background and identity than with the crazy Neo-pagan stereotype but because I've been attacked before by people on the Internet who have called me crazy, pointed out the holes in the beliefs that are part of my cultural identity and tried to convince me that Jesus is the only way, I'm just not comfortable sharing anything else. Once bitten, twice shy. 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 22:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have a look out for it, but yeah she wasn't advertising that particular book. It was very confronting to walk out of an intensive care unit and see that. Highly disrespectful as well. But it's a free country, people can believe what they want to believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 15:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't think I owe an explanation to anybody about my cultural and spiritual beliefs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 15:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that it is rude to encourage others to form their own opinions. My personal beliefs are my own and I do not need to justify them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 14:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious. Think a little deeper and outside your square mate. Good try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 14:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I don't owe you anything and there is this thing called Google, and another thing called a brain. Go explore and form your own opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 12:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big time. Life is not about who is right or wrong it's about connecting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 11:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! Let's not be insane together! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 11:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. Yes there are a fair few people who are sanctimonious about their paganism, there are those like me who love and respect the earth and the connectedness of humans and nature. 

There are a fair few people who get all mystical and sanctimonious about Jesus as well. I left the hospital this arvo and went down to the train station and saw a lady handing out flyers with a picture of a young man on life support wit the caption "Why do bad things happen to good people?" I get confused over which is more harmful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 11:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was brought up pagan, I am highly doubtful that I am insane, but maybe I am and nobody is game to tell me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 21:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I almost forget, it gets brought up again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you slapped him in the testicles, cause they're so nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 12:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And follow the links to her xconfessions.com they are my favourites! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 11:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite would probably have to be "Reign of the Phallus" by Eva Keuls, followed by Elizabeth Grosz's "Volatile Bodies" and Ann Summers' "Damned whores and God's police"
Edit: I'm also a bit partial to Judith Butler and her big long words, and Camille Paglia has some classic moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 10:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I hadn't seen that subreddit, I'll check it out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 22:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I walked into my GPs office specifically for a referral to a nutritionist, and got denied, I wish we could swap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 21:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm dying to know as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 21:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch. I haven't been to the states in years but I remember each time I've been to Boston, parking and accommodation were so expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 21:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes so has mine. He seems to have bounced back again this time as well, but he just doesn't seem as happy to be alive as he was before. Although we went on a slow walk yesterday and he ate a little bit of steak and afterwards he cuddled into me for ages, so I think we just spend however long we have now taking him to all his favourite spots and treating him to all his favourite food until he lets us know it's time :( I'm so sorry you've lost your puppy dog :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 12:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And parking is so so fucking expensive in Boston </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Sunday in my country right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
