<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4858</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather it were nazis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Syphilis?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 months? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joking aside. Please delete your post. What if someone from Sony saw it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 11:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scotland's diversity comes from Pakistani/Indian, Chinese and later Eastern Europe, there was never the influx from Caribbean and later Africa that made London as diverse as USA (13% black). There have always been a few black people but no black communities. SE England is now so full that more and more people are coming to Scotland for work or because they can afford a nice house or being sent if refugees/poor migrants statistically some are black. If it had been the early 90s then that would have been the black population of Glasgow in the video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 11:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well London is extremely diverse. USA is only 13% black about the same as London. Londoners tend to think they are England. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 12:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't seen it Good Night and Good Luck  http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0433383/ is a movie based on CBS Ed Morrow and his broadcast that began to publicly question the anti communist witch hunt/purge in USA. It shows that despite "free speech" censorship is real and how it can work. Edit : didn't mean just now but there was still the first amendment in the 50s and rightly or wrongly there was censorship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 12:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finland has a population under 5.5 million that is very homogeneous. It is like some management consultants took the existing process charged a few million reinvented the wheel and it will be back to business in a few months. I can absolutely see some Finnish 27 year old who has come back from google/fb standing in front of a room of Finnish civil servants preaching the "new ways" etc and all of them thinking "this again, every 10 years, my father talked about the 60/70s evidenced based policy science of public housing?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 11:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  sidled

saddled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 11:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you milking horses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 11:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kind that wants him to fuck up, get sacked and pose no leadership threat ever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 11:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah politics online can escalate quickly. One of the problems I see is it is so tribal and each "tribe" has its message and narrative and everything is bent to accommodate/reinforce the values. You see it with the dog whistle issues that people rally round. 

I suppose the problem is that the FBI probably has too many people who are suspicious to pay close attention to. But then that is in itself a measure of success that there are no networks operating, no growing Islamist insurrection threatening the state which was the intent of AQ back in the 90s. To have growing cells in USA carrying out plots and attacks radicalizing the organic muslim population. Nowadays as bad as the handful of deaths are it really is the mentally ill, inspired by ISIS doing a shooting or one act they get killed doing. AQ in Iraq at one point were doing car bombs everyday in Baghdad that is what they wanted in USA/Europe but they failed. 

As to mass surveillance various spy types have mentioned that they now have too much data and are being overwhelmed making targeted surveillance difficult. That should be their clue to row back on the mass collection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 09:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ban foreign funding for religious cultural expansion above a certain level ie no more Saudi mega mosques, deport/deny access to foreign preachers that proclaim hate for the west. Enforce existing laws that ban segregation of the sexes and hate speech against gays, jews etc. Many reporters went into mosques and found preachers praising the Taliban and AQ/ISIS so fine them get their assets and close the mosque. Give money to the moderate forms of Islam. Register Muslim preachers just as you register the Christian established religions preachers. But a good starting place would be for the left to embrace its old school principles and stop pandering to Islamism because they are generically anti-USA/Israel. There are so many examples of the left working with islamists to fight "oppression" then once they win the left is decimated Iran, Turkey etc Political Islam is incompatible with socialist progress in every way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 09:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catholics and Protestants were tamed by various European states and neutered by deliberate actions from the English Reformation to French Revolution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 10:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Pharrell Williams stroll past at the end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  #Allcuntsmatter #Austrailianversionsofamericanthings #whysomanywordsinreddit??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theresa May for PM has been talked about for quite a while but you are right about the ease and speed of transition being surprisingly fast. I remember the chat months ago (well before brexit and before Boris got all the publicity) that after Cameron it would be between Osbourne, Gove and May.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 18:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All cunts matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 09:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would see the drug lords as the tyrants and his democratically elected government refreshing the tree of liberty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://projectcensored.org/24-cheneys-halliburton-stock-rose-over-3000-percent-last-year/
http://readersupportednews.org/news-section2/308-12/16561-focus-cheneys-halliburton-made-395-billion-on-iraq-war
https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/cifamerica/2011/jun/08/dick-cheney-halliburton-supreme-court

Dick Cheney but there are others. It would be easier to believe his claims that wars were needed and the best option for the country if they hadn't enriched his bank balance so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 12:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am all up for justice and avoiding exploitation but when people are ignoring facts just to jump on the hate train and continue the narrative it becomes just mob rule/witchhunts. People are getting really excited about things because they fit the narrative without doing any basic research or thought for themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 12:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just out of interest what kind of bike is it, group set etc. Is it an old school MTB frame? I tour on a 1991 mtb frame and think they are brilliant for loaded touring also carradice canvas FTW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 11:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Namibia, Malawi and Botswana were good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 10:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So 2006. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 10:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top politicians give no bid contracts worth billions to themselves after deciding to have a war. Shall we have war Mr Halliburton? Hmmm let me think, no war no money but war we get $39 Billion hmmm gosh darned it think of those boys on the frontline but erm better have war please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 10:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To give it some USA context the only challenger to Theresa May was Andrea Leadsom. Andrea was popular within the party and by all accounts an effective MP for her constituents but the general public hadn't heard of her. Within 3 days of her going into the public eye by running for leader it came out that she was a devout christian and that founded the basis of her decisions, then she said being a mother she thought of the future implying Theresa May, no children, was a worse candidate. That was poison even in her own party people told her she had crossed the line. Imagine in USA if being a devout Christian and going on about the children and family values made you unelectable. And this is the centre right party in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 17:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't ignore the campaigns and growth of environmentalism in the 70s 80s and 90s. Have a look at all the legislation and regulations set up. That didn't happen in the soviet bloc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 17:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.gerdludwig.com/stories/soviet-pollution-a-lethal-legacy/#num=content-308 id=album-37

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Environmental_issues_in_Russia    

http://www.multinationalmonitor.org/hyper/issues/1990/09/ridgeway.html

https://fee.org/articles/why-socialism-causes-pollution/    

http://thefederalist.com/2014/01/13/if-you-think-communism-is-bad-for-people-check-out-what-it-did-to-the-environment/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 16:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 60s-90s Communism was far worse because the environment was not the priority.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked document says 2,000 men allegedly assaulted 1,200 German women on New Years Eve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 12:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 00:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IN the 70s Palestinians/pan arabist terror groups used to fight amongst themselves https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abu_Nidal_Organization vs PLO

Also during the spanish civil war the republican forces spent as much time fighting each other think bolsheviks vs anarchists etc From wikipedia  - Pro-Soviet Communists committed numerous atrocities against fellow Republicans, including other Marxists: Andr Marty, known as the Butcher of Albacete, was responsible for the deaths of some 500 members of the International Brigades.[268] Andreu Nin, leader of the POUM (Workers' Party of Marxist Unification), and many other prominent POUM members, were murdered by the Communists, with the help of the USSR's NKVD.[269] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 20:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To address the actual article Hannah Bryce never says how the addition of a woman would make infantry more operationally effective she just trots out PR statements and platitudes. There is no evidence the addition of women will make a group of infantry soldiers more aggressive or dangerous which is the real job description. In fact the evidence says the addition of women makes groups less effective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 20:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are talking out your arse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 15:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating as a leisure pursuit itself and its encouragement by corporations making money giving people what they want all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 00:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I am way past the point where I believe any of the celeb stuff is real, I think it is all scripted and plotted by industry producers, PR and agents out in advance including relationships, marriages etc in effect it is a living soap opera product. There are really cool things happening all over the place that are real and have real effects on peoples lives rather than which sport guy has been told to sleep with which Kardashian girl this month. Taylor and Tom fake. It is a shame that all news is so tragic imagine if FOX news did a happy cats of Iran or good news stories from around the world that people could talk about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No others have passed and I doubt anymore will pass. Perhaps the army will do the same pass a couple then enforce the standard and say to the rest see you aren't good enough. But then  someone will build their career (lawyer,activist or staff officer) on saying there are so few women because of sexism and then there will be gender fair test as in the rest of the military and quotas like the rest of the military.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 23:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ever served? Ever been in a frontline unit? Tell me the nations that had mixed frontline combat units. Most of the examples I can find the units are not infantry that would be used in a deliberate assault on an enemy position. Guarding a camp or escorting things, even basic patrolling is very different to actually attacking a defended enemy position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have any experience of the large scale military you would suspect that this is the thin end of the wedge and next some desk jockey will further their career by enforcing gender compliance quotas then getting good PR and introducing gender fair test to help women naturally avoid injury while serving. 

They have done it with equipment from rifles to radios they know are shit but tests are designed to be passed then test exercises are 100% perfect, everyone is happy, they get promoted then leave to join the bidder that won. Except a few years later the frontline troops are getting killed because of the greed and ambition of the desk officer who now has a massive pension and is working in civvy street as a consultant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet they will have different fitness standards to the ones that the men currently have. They have easier fitness standards in the rest of the Army for all the other jobs so the frontline will end up no different, just as they did for the fire service and police.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but the Spanish Army is pretty shit and not worth drawing any conclusions from.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily Edinburgh burnt all its future money (almost a billion  for 10 miles) by building 1 tram line instead of getting electric buses into its great bus network. Literally invested all the cash in 1980s tram tech. Long live the monorail!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should have been sacked and jailed for incompetence for the post invasion mess. There is no part of the post invasion situation that suggests it had been thought of or planned for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it would be nice for them to lose all the Arab and banker bribes they got paid after he was PM all for the job he did in power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 22:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is like the banks claiming not to have seen the financial collapse back in 2008, yeah you just sacked anyone who warned about the growing house of cards and marginalized any public figure who warned about it and recommended reform.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 21:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time for a new Dixie Chicks album? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 21:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't he did. The americans were going anyway and Blair's decision was to be with them no matter what. Everything after that was to shape the discussion to let parliament vote to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 20:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK:I'm putting together a little concern, which would enable those of us in our, uh, rarified profession to avoid embarrassing overlaps.
 
Rest of World:What, like a union?
 
UK:More like a club. You know, work less, make more. 

RoW:Wow, sounds like a great idea, but... thank you, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 16:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.washingtontimes.com/news/2015/may/25/womens-combat-roles-in-israel-defense-forces-exagg/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 16:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is so sad that the original in the 1980s was more progressive than this cash cow milking movie. Think of the characters like the secretary she was the every woman doing a shitty job surrounded by idiots, she was sassy and good at her job. Think of Winston a normal everyday guy who needs a job, the everyman who heightens the weirdness of the fact they are hunting ghosts but isn't ultra black he is just "average joe". Sigourny Weaver is a top class classical musician who rejects the advances of one of the main characters making him look like a jerk. There are movies that deserve some retrospective payback from women but Ghostbusters was the wrong target go remake Porkies or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 15:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH LAWD JESUS GET THE WATA!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 11:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know the brand but here is a blog you can use to justify spending thousands on a round the world bike or see you can tour on any bike. Might take the pressure of the decision. But lots of useful stuff about touring bike choices.
http://tomsbiketrip.com/how-to-build-the-ultimate-round-the-world-expedition-touring-bike/
http://tomsbiketrip.com/which-touring-bike-should-i-buy/
http://tomsbiketrip.com/how-to-go-cycle-touring-for-the-price-of-a-round-of-drinks-part-1/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 10:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-j64cjkVjc0 not from the assholes page cos fuck them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 22:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think his point is that if you killed all fat people the world would be a better place because you would have freed N Korea.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 22:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet no phone footage from anyone and a lot of fb likes and general love for the guy on his feed. Anchorman gif required. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 22:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true it is like children's TV now with so much repetition it is unwatchable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 18:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see the comments if this was posted in redpill and TwoxChromosones, I suspect there would be a different slant heh heh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 11:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on your definition of race because India has different ethnic groups that self identify as different, different religious groups that have carried out massacres against each other from time to time and there is wealth inequality and the caste system woven through everything. Many of these could consider themselves a different race. India is so big it can have an mini civil war and no one hears about it. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Naxalite%E2%80%93Maoist_insurgency 
USA is a bubble or an echo chamber as far as race stuff goes for a variety of reasons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 11:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to reset your dial if you think the Sun is far right. Far right is neo nazi stormfront shit. Right wing sure but nowhere near far right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 10:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1032 up votes. Was it worth it? Hope they heal as new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 16:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And look how that turned out for the locals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 12:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one shoots handguns or SMGs for fun in the UK. You are an idiot if you think bolt action rifles or shotguns are the same as .44 magnum revolvers or an uzi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It blew my mind that me and some friends could go into a shop in vegas and shoot guns out the back, uzi, 44, 45 (indoor range) etc merely having a single round would get you jail time in UK. The shop had guns on the wall behind the counter and you could just choose then shoot them in the indoor rage. Americans can't even begin to understand how different UK is. No judgement USA bros.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will the mods let this stay up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dozens of teens 'sexually assaulted by foreign youths' at popular music festival </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 09:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 11:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that given that Tony Blair was Scottish as was a lot of his top level team that the Scots didn't really clean much up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 16:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-scotland-politics-36667356 those fuckers have been around for a while now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 16:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edinburgh is more like a big town than a real city even compared to Glasgow it is small and fairly quiet outside of the late opening during festival. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 14:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USA science would collapse without importing foreign brainpower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 13:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I truly hate this country now" so I gues you haven't really been anywhere else! Oh wait you are sooo caught up in the moment!!!!! people like you are the people that Charlie Hebdo told to fuck off with the sudden FB "Je sius Charlie" support/fashion trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 13:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watching Hell on Wheels and read up on some US history and killing Mormons seems understandable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 12:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "Islamic World" lol. Edit there is as much of an Islamic World as there was a Christendom during the third crusade.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 12:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dance fat monkey dance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 09:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 90s will never die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 17:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironic bitter tears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the cheese and other toppings are serious long term energy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finding the pub beside the campsite stopped doing food at 8:30 pm 5 mins before you got to the bar, thinking 4 pints and 4 packets of crisps (different flavours) had filled you up and so who needs real food? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 20:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are not on a mission like a coast to coast or LEJOG where completing is half the purpose of the tour and you are going to mainland europe skip Wales and don't waste the days in misery inducing weather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 20:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is totally safe and very feasible. Just have the spare cash to stay at campsites if you can't find a safe/remote place to stealth camp. Be flexible with time frame so you can stop and have short days till you are familiar with how far you can cycle and build a touring routine. Also you are 21 so just tell your folks some little lies to make them feel better then go and do what you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 20:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terra Nova Laser Comp 2. Far more storm proof than you would think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably has more parallels with the fight against Militant/SWP in the 80s by Kinnock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He shits on the media so what does he expect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Brexit was a pretty clear policy and he was terrible at opposing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes finally you catch up with Europe and the idea that the state should be secular...Oh wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fit privilege. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well after the lifeguard video and the swimming pool poster I think I know which Americans you are talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you ski on in the blue mountains whilst dodging the sharks, spiders and snakes. Crocs don't ski. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So nothing to do with Brexit and more to do with ISIS killing and raping and making people think Islam isn't so cool as it was in the 80s.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain how it does when it cannot refuse entry to EU citizens unless they are on the risk (criminals) register or have a fake passport/ID card?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 15:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes no sense. If UK does regain control of its own borders from EU policy then it will be free to stop EU citizens from entering ie very poor EU citizens who end up living on the streets. If you disagree with borders politically or even agree with the EU border policy then fine but don't pretend that currently the UK could prevent non criminal EU citizens from coming to the UK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 15:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK Muslim halal shops sometimes sell fake halal because it is cheaper and they make more profit http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-29084371. Which would annoy me if I was an observant muslim.

Sometimes different sects murder each other http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-glasgow-west-35976958. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 12:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gallery/33uob Dylan's falcon is green. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
