<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2122</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 10:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too, wouldn't mind a link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to see Pine doing well outside Star Trek. And hopefully the underrated Ben Foster gets some deserved awards attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'll play Batman, I'll play Bane. Hell, I'll even play Michael Caine!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 08:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least Mad Max: Fury Road did ok enough and cleaned up at the Oscars. It's also done great in the home market.The Intern made some cash. Creed as well, but MGM was also involved so I'm guessing they took some profits. San Andreas was profitable, but I'm positive The Rock had a huge backend deal. The Conjuring series is a huge cash cow, but James Wan is starting to get PAID.

Eh, they could be Paramount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 08:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If directing World War Z means Fincher will have a passion project of his made after this ("One for them, One for you"), then I'm all for it. 

I still want him too, but I'm just a little shocked, especially due to the recent trend of hiring lesser-known directors for blockbusters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 02:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix U.S. straight up sucks! :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cut to Daniel attacking Eli with bowling pins after Eli asking for a signing bonus was gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 08:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Nice Guys is an underrated movie and is really good. Why didn't people see this in theaters?"

- A r/movies recommendation post a year and a half from now

I myself only just liked it, but I do wish it had done better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 08:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "His retirement should be the *least* of his worries right now..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alex Pettyfer. I remember him being hyped up around the time I Am Number Four came out. Since then, I haven't heard of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing Blanchett is playing the Rusty to Bullock's Ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 09:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I late for the new cast members party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 06:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Taran had another two seasons in him, and Pharaoh one more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 21:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget a good writer in Jon Spaihts! But I saw somewhere that the CGI drama won't affect the movie. Hopefully, we'll see a trailer before the end of the month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Winding Refn is a good director, but I don't know about his writing. 

I myself thought The Nice Guys was just OK, but I wish it had done better though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 08:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he should bring in another writer if there is a sequel, preferably one with more experience in comic book movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 07:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Children of Men ayy lmao /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 02:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many Cy Young votes could he get? That ERA is hard to ignore.

*Meant to put votes after Young </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked Costner in A Perfect World and Bull Durham. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 22:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised at how little Dicaprios performance did for me in Gangs of New York. Seemed dull IMO. And he's as reliable as they come.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 21:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think one of the reasons that the Fast and Furious films have been so successful lately is because they put a lot of emphasis on family. And what is one of the important things in life to Latinos? 

"I ain't got friends; I got family!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 11:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inherent Vice. Joaquin Phoenix was tied up somewhere at the end I believe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 10:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked Ethan Hawkes character in Boyhood. He gave the best performance in the movie IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 10:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's the 'A' chain "Cinepolis" which is the most popular one in Mexico. The 'B' chain is "Cinemex", so this won't affect the box office in Mexico too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 10:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Devil Inside deserves the F. Killing Them Softly might be more of a D IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 18:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $700 million. The UK will adore this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 11:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH GOD! MAKE IT STOP!! :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew that song was from Moneyball when the kid-escapes-from-the-truck scene came up! Great song and even greater scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 23:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did get his Robert Redford on in The Big Short. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 02:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cloud Atlas. I just finished watching it. Movies like Cloud Atlas are the reason I love cinema. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mystic River   Prisoners

Annie Hall   500 Days of Summer

Apocalypse Now   The Thin Red Line  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 11:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey, is Jonah Hill busy? He is? Alright. Get Josh Gad's agents on the phone." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 11:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was great in Her, but I kind of wish Woody Allen had found someone else for his 21st century muse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 11:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keanu Reeves picks good movies, but his acting isnt. Nic Cage is a good actor, but his revent movies aren't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 11:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he'll show people a new side to him in the upcoming Passengers. Trailer apparently comes out this Thursday btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 23:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 23:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know why you're getting downvoted. It was only okay, and didn't really add anything new to the buddy cop genre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 21:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mel Gibson's "FREEEDDDOOMMMMMM!!!" in Braveheart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 11:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope Clooney does justice to a Coen brothers script with Suburbicon being his next project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Greengrass would be way more regarded if he stop using shaky cam. Captain Phillips is very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 10:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of parents wouldn't want to take their kids to a movie with "Suicide" in the title. SS is aiming more for the teen demographic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 22:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting the Bond contract would be huge for them. I was about to mention Pacific Rim 2 but Universal is distributing it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still liked the second act, though. The third act ran out of steam, however, but it was still ok enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 11:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess no one in the article or the comments section of the article has no idea that Leo is a bankable star. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 10:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to see this movie don't I? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 10:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deakins also lensed No Country for Old Men that year, so maybe he cancelled himself out, allowing There Will Be Blood to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 10:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, Fargo would be the perfect show for Steve Zahn to star in. Hopefully Noah Hawley lurks around Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I have no idea how he won the Oscar for Jerry Maguire. William H. Macy deserved it WAY more for Fargo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zahn was terrific in Rescue Dawn. Even better than Bale, I'd say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will always like his cameo in Ocean's Eleven when he's getting hounded while leaving a bar, while two of the biggest stars in the world, Pitt and The Cloon, walk away unnoticed. They're both in character but I've always found the scene funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eva Mendes is still around somewhat. She was good in The Place Beyond The Pines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 07:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darn, you beat me to it. Anyway, the site is pretty informative whenever you start to wonder "Hey what happened to the guy from ___"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, a lot of people may have thought The Nice Guys was just like every other buddy cop movie of its nature and decided to skip it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I just saw The Nice Guys and it was pretty good. Why didn't people see this in theaters?"

- A /r/movies self post a year from now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 08:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh also, a lot of his movies are cast in exotic places. Or at least locations that are kind of far from civilization. Shooting in those areas can drive up the budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 05:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing Matt Damon, since Ari represents him on the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 20:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like rugs and the Dude's house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 09:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They mean more along the lines of original IP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 09:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to see Paramount doing well outside the Transformers franchise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Random dude starts walking towards her*

"Hey, get back here!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 10:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he has a lot of talent but he's had nothing but clunkers on his IMDB since Whiplash. Hopefully, War Dogs and Bleed for This add some hits to his resume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 10:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really hope Besson keeps the story simple and isn't another Jupiter Ascending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 10:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man has a love affair with visual effects and the prequels at least do great in that aspect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 09:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walsh crushed it on the indie scene with Daze and Queens Boulevard. Too bad he couldn't make it with a bigger film, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 02:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit. If only Villenueve and Nolan weren't busy as hell. Wait, is Fincher up to anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 19:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McBride said he won't be the comic relief in a recent article, so who knows? Maybe it'll be a turning point in his career regardless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 18:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The chickens have come home to roost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 10:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like we might have to wait a while longer. He did lose a lot of money on Horace   Pete unfortunately, so he might be more inclined to take a guaranteed salary to make another season.

http://www.independent.co.uk/arts-entertainment/tv/news/louie-season-6-might-never-happen-i-don-t-think-i-have-stories-for-that-guy-anymore-says-louis-ck-a7020441.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 10:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tune in every night folks! It's the Crying Cleaning Lady Show! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 08:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget Mystic River! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 08:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically, the script with the "What's in the box" ending was never supposed to make it to David Fincher's office. There was a mixup with UPS. The revised script had a different ending, but Fincher loved the original so much, he wanted to make that one instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 08:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious to see him In Alien: Covenant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 06:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep :(  I especially loved David Lynch's character during The Late Night trilogy as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main reason I watched was for the flawless Charlize Theron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He passed away last year actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked him in Louie as the guy who entices Louis CK with interest for Late Night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 04:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hhmmm I Iike this character. I wonder if there was a way for me to do the same on the pitching mound..."

- Jeurys Familia while watching Jeremy Renner in The Hurt Locker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 04:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But did we lose?"

-Jeurys Familia on his save situations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked this one, check out Before The Devil Knows You're Dead, also directed by Sydney Lumet and shows the aftermath of a heist gone wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 08:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'll bring you something all right. I've decided to make you a special project of mine. You ain't going to have come look for me at all.

- Brolin as Bond to the villains </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 10:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go a little higher and say Sully will open between 25 and 30 million dollars OW. I see it as this year's Captain Phillips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 10:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did like the scene where someone is challenging PSHs character on his upcoming book and its beliefs. The movie needed more scenes like that and Freddie questioning PSH as well. But alas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 00:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget le Children of Men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 23:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moon is also a le underrated gem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 20:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did a Brooklyn detective named Jake Peralta create this site by any chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 10:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Master. And I really do like PTAs work. But The Master seemed really dull to me. The cinematography was splendid though and the late PSH and Joaquin did great. At least witg There Will Be Blood, you could feel it building. The Master was headed nowhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 10:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silence is getting a release at the end of this year just in time for awards season, as is Live by Night. It's possible that most people won't see them until January 2017, though, as was the case with The Revenant and American Sniper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 18:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually felt the same way about Jennifer Lawrence. I first saw her as the teenage daughter on The Bill Engvall Show and I thought "Man, she's pretty talented and attractive. " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say it really started with Inside Llewyn Davis, since that really put him on the map, but agree to disagree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With The Counselor, Exodus: Gods and Kings, and Robin Hood amongst his recent output, you may have a valid point. I actually liked Prometheus, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 08:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Usual Suspects is complex enough as it is. You need to be on your toes for all of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 08:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand the dislike for AH; the plot was a mess. And while I liked The Revenant, I concede the middle part was boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 04:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "One of the greatest shows of all-time!"

- Your sister in college </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! That's Mr. Bozo to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 08:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I weirdly like that episode, even if it is mean-spirited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 08:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know your studio is having a bad year when Sony's slate actually looks kind of financially viable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 08:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How's the writers room doing on the Transformers universe?"

- Paramount execs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Coens would do more justice to a Strangelove remake. The characters in there are straight up their alley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was cured all right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never go full retard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 05:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hello?"

"Yes?"

"Is, uh, Frankenstein there?"

"...Not in the sense that you mean." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 02:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clooney said they just laugh a lot behind the monitors. And he's worked with them four times already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 20:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at this game! It went by fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 18:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Coens. Their movies may be bleak, but they themselves are a hoot apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 07:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matthew Vaughn and Jane Goldman also contributed to DoFP script, while Kinberg alone wrote Apocalypse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 15:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm predicting "A good time...if you're drunk" from Jeremy Jahns when he reviews it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 15:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pixels would've been much better if Edgar Wright made it instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 15:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I did. I've always wanted to see what a Darren Aronofsky blockbuster would look like and I had a good time watching it. I appreciated what The Fountain, but ultimately it wasn't for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 09:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 09:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three of them are teaming up for The Irishman actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 08:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially lately. Transformers 3, then Pain and Gain. Transformers 4, then 13 Hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 08:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clooney also subscribes to the "One for them, one for them" method. Ocean's Eleven, then Solaris. Ocean's Twelve and Intolerable Cruelty, then Syriana and Good Night, and Good Luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 08:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think it's his worst. Which is saying something, since it still has some things going for it.

But his best work for me is Black Swan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 01:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the review embargo was lifted the day OF the premiere or the day before, this would flop. However, I think it'll just barely break even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 08:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His OPS has gone up to .769 from .620 last Saturday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 08:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I do. People are less inclined to go to the movies now and they'll want to see movies that are more worth their time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 08:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've missed this meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 02:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. Ruffalo stuck out like a sore thumb and was pretty mannered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 02:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good scene but I feel that it sticks out like a sore thumb, since the rest of the movie is lowkey in the way it presents itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 02:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Big Short was too comedic.

Mad Max: Fury Road was a technical marvel and not much else in the eyes of the voters. 

Room was too small to win. 

The Martian was well-done but it's sci-fi which they look down at.
 
The Revenant was thematically hollow according to the voters.

Bridge of Spies was good but the nomination was more of a sign of respect to Spielberg and Hanks.

Brooklyn didn't really have a chance in the other categories besides Best Picture, so a win there had no chance.

Spotlight may not have been very cinematic, but it dealt with an important social issue and had many respected actors in the cast (actors make up the biggest part of the Academy).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
