<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6782</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SELLING] 2 x Corsair XMS3 DDR3 1600MHZ CL9 4GB (2x2GB) RAM/Memory Kits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **SOLD**

I've got **2 x Corsair XMS3 DDR3 1600MHZ CL9 4GB RAM (so total of 4 sticks, 8GB) kits** that are now unused since I just upgraded to 16GB RAM. None of the 4 sticks have ever given me trouble and have been running at 1333MHZ since I purchased them from Centrecom. They are both part number: **CMX4GX3M2A1600C9** 

http://imgur.com/a/WunM8

I'm willing to sell **everything here for $70 (4 sticks) or $40 cash for one set (2 sticks). I am open to offers.** Please note that I do not have the original boxes. 

Pick up in 3165 or willing to bring to you within reasonable distances. Not willing to post. Please PM me here if interested!

You can find the exact same model for sale at: 

Centrecom here: http://www.centrecom.com.au/corsair-ddr3-4gb-pc-128001600-2x-xms3-2gb-cmx4gx3m2a1600c9-ram

And a StaticIce link: http://www.staticice.com.au/cgi-bin/search.cgi?q=CMX4GX3M2A1600C9 spos=1 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 02:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Not Meant To Be (to win!)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 03:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alter Ego </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 02:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alter Ego </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 00:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alter Ego </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 12:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea if this is correct but it sounded similar enough back when I made it. http://onlinesequencer.net/41218 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 01:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alter Ego </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 03:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desire Be, Desire Go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 02:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desire Be, Desire Go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 06:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The **Bold** Arrow of Time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 04:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it means a lot! Pretty sure I replied on there too haha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeremy's Storm (again for me).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 05:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jeremy's Storm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/GrandTheftAutoV_PC/comments/39kgbg/my_game_settings_have_completely_broken_after_the/

Same problem, on top of this settings also won't save for me any more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] Pacific Standard Setups   Heist - Hard - 40/20 Split (Right Now!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 13:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for 2 players on PC right now for the Pac Standard (all setups + final heist). Will pay 20% of the final cut to those who join. Please add us on RSC and send a message there if you would like to join. We would like to finish this as soon as possible and we have plenty of experience. Our R*SC names: ThickishTunic15   timoloney

It is expected that you have all relevant heist gear (Heavy Vest + Helmet).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 12:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply, basically looks like there isn't a set solution to this problem. Guess I'll have to deal with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 14:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sent you an fr on Social Club. R* name: ThickishTunic15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My game settings have completely broken after the update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 12:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the update, none of my game settings will be updated from what they were previously. They'll be changed for the duration of time that the game will be open but as soon as the game is re-launched, everything returns to the original values. It seems to be happening to any option I change and means I have to manually reset the options each time I play and it's getting damn annoying. On top of this, every time I start online I have to agree the EULA. I haven't really heard of anyone else having this issue and it's super annoying considering the game crashes all the time too. Any possible solutions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 05:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chocolate Brown base and Cream pearlescent works a treat on some cars. 

As seen here (not my picture): 

http://prod.cloud.rockstargames.com/ugc/gta5photo/1799/Gdc_s5Uo7EmVcYcXunSGuA/0_0.jpg

http://gtaforums.com/topic/708108-massacro-appreciation-thread/?p=1067361159 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it isn't that fast compared to other cars, but off road it holds its own just like the Kuruma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Benefactor Sterling is quick off road just like the Kuruma! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the Sterling off road, it feels just like the Kuruma. Not really all too unexpected with all the rally mods but I don't think many people would bother to actually try this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 11:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely fantastic! Only nit pick I have is that the drums kind of overpower a little bit. That said, can barely tell the difference between this and the original at so many moments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 12:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey just sent a message along with my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] Pacific Standard Setups   Heist - Hard - 40/20 Split </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 11:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for 2 players on PC right now for the Pac Standard (all setups + final heist). Will pay 20% of the final cut to those who join. Side note: we will not be taking the shortcut jumping over the alleys and will instead shoot through the police. PM me your R* SC name, post here, or add me or my friend directly in game. Would like to start soon as possible. Our R*SC names: ThickishTunic15   timoloney </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xposting from your other thread:

Are you using a controller by any chance? Is your RAM running at full speed? I figured out that my game was crashing predominantly because of my controller drivers, and secondly because my RAM is actually 2 different kits which meant running at full speed wasn't stable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 16:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you using a controller by any chance? Is your RAM running at full speed? I figured out that my game was crashing predominantly because of my controller drivers, and secondly because my RAM is actually 2 different kits which meant running at full speed wasn't stable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] Pacific Standard Setups   Heist - Hard - 40/20 Split (Right now!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for 2 players on PC right now for the Pac Standard (all setups + final heist) to play. Will pay 20% of the final cut to those who join. Side note: we will not be taking the shortcut jumping over the alleys and will instead shoot through the police.
PM me your R* SC name, post here, or add me directly in game. Would like to start soon as possible. My R*SC name: ThickishTunic15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 14:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you still need 2 people? My friend and I are looking for 2 as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 14:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! The final part there was probably my favourite part to make as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 14:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Check this out now: https://soundcloud.com/turbolag/apocdreams10cut 

Probably isn't perfect but this song has so many damn instruments to replicate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I recreated The Hours on Guitar Pro, what does everyone think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try and work on them some more, but yeah as you said GP isn't the easiest to work with! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 03:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you point me towards where exactly it's wrong? I'd try to fix it if possible since I want this as accurate as possible. :) Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry did mean setup**s**. We'll be starting from the beginning and hopefully completing all of this in one sitting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] Pacific Standard Setup   Heist - Hard - 40/20 Split (Right now!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 14:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for 2 players on PC right now for the Pac Standard (all setups + final heist) to play. Will pay 20% of the final cut to those who join. Side note: we will not be taking the shortcut jumping over the alleys and will instead shoot through the police. 

PM me your R* SC name, post here, or add me directly in game. Would like to start soon as possible.
My R*SC name: ThickishTunic15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finally finished my recreation of Apocalypse Dreams on Guitar Pro! Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 11:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 09:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ['04 Subaru Liberty](http://i.imgur.com/26oGjgu.jpg)

[And the dash sweep](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1T17bmLILc0
) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 17:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 year and 7 days apart, I had a similar idea... haha http://onlinesequencer.net/12469 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I reboot a lot too, thankfully my SSD means I can boot into game very quickly if not I'd be sitting here wasting more time launching than playing. But yeah it seems to be a similar problem, although after I reboot, about half the time I'd get stuck on the pause menu spinning symbol or the phone won't work. I doubt this has anything to do with hardware.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried both OVERclocking and UNDERclocking the GPU but it seems to make 0 difference to crashes OR performance towards the game... That said, the game runs quite well other than the times it doesn't want to work at all lol. That said, I've only tried underclocking it minimally so maybe I'll give that another shot but at a more extreme underclock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Constantly crashing during heists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 17:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My game is constantly crashing during heists and setups. It sometimes happens in exactly the same spots but other time just seems to fail randomly. I have only crashed once during free roam (started today) and never crashed during a normal mission (non heist). What usually happens is the game will simply freeze for a moment, then the screen will go completely white and the normal Windows "Program has stopped working" screen is showen. Alternatively, the pause menu will be endlessly showing the spinning symbol and phone will not pop up. Sometimes I can play for hours on end without a single crash and other times I can't be in a game for more than a minute. Albeit rarely, sometimes the game will cause a BSOD as well. 

I'm running the retail DVD edition of the game (on the latest patch) and on the latest 2.4.1.21 Nvidia drivers too. The crashes have been happening since day 1 and no driver or patch has stopped the crashes. 

My PC specs are as follows: 





Part | Model
---|---
CPU | i7 870
Mobo | Gigabyte P55A-UD3-DS3L
RAM | Corsair XMS3 (4x2GB) CMX4GX3M2A1600C9
GPU | Gainward Nvidia GTX 960 
SSD | Transcend SSD370 256GB 
OS | W7 Home Premium 64bit
PSU | Antec EarthWatts 750W



If it makes a difference, I play with my PS3 controller too. 

Is there anyone else experiencing such crashes? It's really damn frustrating and makes me look like an ass when I keep leaving games after a minute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 16:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R*SC: ThickishTunic15 

Just sent an FR.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 16:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm down, R*SC: ThickishTunic15

No mic though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No prob, you can add me anyway and invite whenever something opens up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm down for the next 2 hours or so. Send an add my way if interested. 

R*SC: ThickishTunic15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is 100% accurate since I got this down by ear only and I think the piano part ends at around 4:07, but hope it helps. 

https://youtu.be/Sw0Ipi8wLKg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
