<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trouble with that argument is that the Mexican immigrants are doing jobs Americans are too damned spoiled to do. The Farm Workers of America tried to give jobs to Americans. Out of 10s of thousands who applied, most never showed up or quit after a few days because the work was too hard. I believe only about 100 out of almost 50,000 actually stayed. Americans don't want to do the hard work of working in the fields in the hot sun or doing the grunt work on construction sites. Like my dad used to say, "They don't want a job, they want a position." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, they care more about keeping their jobs than they do the good of the country. I was shocked by the fact that my dem senator votes across the red line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about this. Why would companies be so adamant about bringing in workers from other countries if it was costing them the same as American workers? They say there are not enough qualified workers here, but that's just not true. When this whole thing started, thousands of Americans were getting laid off from tech jobs and being replaced by Indian workers at lower wages. All the tech companies are complicit in this scheme. Bill Gates once threatened to relocate MS to Canada if he didn't get more than the limited number of H1B visas, and we all know how crooked he is. 

So it would cost  him less to move an entire HUGE fucking company to Canada than it would be to hire Americans? Are you fucking serious? 

And it's not even the visas themselves that are causing people to lose jobs. Once they are here, they bring over their families on special family visas, and those people take jobs for lower wages too. It's a racket that is costing everyone jobs. 

Most tech grads now end up in startups, because the big companies won't hire them. Very few recent tech grads are hired by the big tech companies. I know people who work at MS and Google, and they say that many of the H1B hires are low-level techies who make 75% of what American workers would be paid. Plus, they are often hired as temps, saving the companies even more money.

Add to that that only the higher echelons of Indian society have access to that kind of education, so we are promoting their caste system (which they say no longer exists, but it does). 



I'm personally glad he is doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when they launch a nuke at someone, and we shoot it down, exploding it all over a large area where the radioactivity is spread by the winds and water, who is then responsible for the destruction left in its wake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but there are a lot of those. Once the old farts who control this country die off, we will be able to elect a woman president, but not until then. Hell, they have only had the right to vote for less than a century. Married women couldn't even own property in their name until 1839. Laws may change, but attitudes don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In short, we are doomed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, "I've had my lawyers working overtime on how to avoid the Emoluments Clause applying to me." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is why she isn't paid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's pretty darned disrespectful of his mother, from some of what I've seen and read. But what can you expect of a child who has his own complete home on a floor of Trump tower? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many conflicts of interest is this now? Dozens, I'm guessing. I hate the GOP congress for ignoring this shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty well known that many super-intelligent people have very little common sense. That's the difference between "book smart" and "street smart." I'm not highly educated, and I do have a lot of street smarts, but I pride myself on having a modicum of common sense that I see lacking in many of my more intellectual friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FL will never get their shit together. It's really two separate states: the North and Central parts which is more like the deep South, and the South, which is the southernmost northern state. I lived in SW FL for many years and absolutely left because it was too white, conservative and TBH, yankee. Sorry, but I'm a born and raised southerner, and northern attitudes don't sit well with me. Has nothing to do with the Civil War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mysogynists and anti-intellectuals are extremists, IMHO. Anyone who hates women just because they are women (and especially hates strong women) and hates educated people just because they are educated is an extremist. Or a fool. You pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, I'm 100% against everything Trump stands for, and I'm not going to go out and bust heads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they are not. This kind of talk is what is dividing us. If you want to see violence, just go look at the extreme left wing. Remember GreenPeace driving stakes into trees to harm loggers? Remember them firing on whaling ships? Extremists are always the violent ones on both sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As with the right and the left, these violent leftists are from the extreme left, just like violent Trump supporters are from the extreme right. Unfortunately, they don't have tattoos on their foreheads, so there is no way to identify them as troublemakers until they start punching people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but what I want to know is where did the Alt-Righters come from? Are there that many of them in Berkeley? No, they came from outside with the stated intention of revenge. That is what bothers me, that we are going to have roving bands of violent alt-righters attacking peaceful protesters all over the country.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I abhor any violence toward women, I do sort of see the point that the antifas should have known what to expect. You don't jump into a dog fight without expecting to get bit. I used to protest in the 60s, and I always expected someone to get hurt or arrested. Luckily, it wasn't ever me, because I learned really quickly not to touch a cop, and to sit down with my hands behind my head when people were getting tossed into the paddy wagons.  Then Kent State happened. I'm not sure this administration will not cause another Kent State, maybe even at Berkeley if they keep up the protests there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to unite when both sides are so entrenched in ideaology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they go to check in, and suddenly, they aren't registered. That kind of scam, like the ones they pulled during the primaries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know how the Jews took over the banking industry? In ancient times, money was considered dirty (i.e., "filthy lucre") and Jews were the only ones who would handle it for people. They recognized that "he who controls the money, controls the world." They did the same thing with media. Control the money, control the message, control the world.  ETA: Smart people, the Jews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever moved into another county that was  mostly red? 

These were my problems when I did that:

I moved counties temporarily, and my old county did not send me my requested absentee ballot. Voter registration peeps in new county said I could not register there unless my DL had my new county address on it. This was done to me TWICE, and I found out that the state voter ID law does not say this. Had to get the Obama campaign to call Super of elections to straighten this out, and was able to change registration over the phone.

Got back to my old county and was told by a worker at SOE office that I had to have a birth certificate, SS card and proof of residence to change the address on my DL before I could re-register to vote in this county, even though they could see I had been registered here before. That was all lies. Same old "Your DL address has to match your local address." At the time, I was not permanently settled, so didn't want to have to go down to the DMV and pay the $25 to change my address. Found out THIS was all lies too by calling the Dem Party headquarters here, and having them call the Super of Elections who called me personally and changed my registration to this county over the phone.

I have been registered to vote in FL since 1987. I could not believe the BS I had to go through to vote.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they could be hacked to remove a lot of dem   independent names so we'd have the same nightmare they had all over the U.S. during the primaries, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He couldn't stick to a position if you put gorilla glue on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm over it. It was a long time ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I'm worried about early voters. If their votes were on those machines, they don't exist, right? I'm assuming there were no backup copies of the data made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the early votes were put through those machines, there is no record of them, I'm assuming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typical. You wouldn't believe the BS they tried to pull on me in FL in 2012 and 2016 to keep me from voting. I'm tenacious, though, so they didn't get away with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you joking? Look at who our Attorney General is. No way he's going to see that there is a fair election there when Trump has already bashed Ossoff. There can be no justice here. We are screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd want to steal them so you could replace them with machines programmed not to register that dems voted, that's what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eveler said Cobb County will replace the devices at its Piedmont Road precinct before voters cast their ballots.

Of course they will -- with machines that don't register that dems voted. All I can say is that someone needs to be outside taking names and info on everyone who votes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there goes Roe v. Wade. Of course, they would have to have a case where someone was FORCED to have an abortion, which is the only reason it's still standing. Until that happens, they can't challenge the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Queen Elizabeth. She is afraid to step down because she is afraid Charles will ruin the monarchy, and she hates Camilla. She'd outlive Charles if she could, just so Wills would take over. It could happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is another good reason to get Congress back. There are so many reasons why we need to do this, it's unreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, whites still pretty much are an economic force. It's changing, but very, very slowly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only because they won't vote for anyone that does represent their interests.

Of course they won't. Do you vote for people who don't represent your interests? We all vote for whoever best represents our interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I pretty much hated that phrase. I thought "If you go low, we'll show you what low really is" would have been better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they take pleasure in your suffering so much as all they know is that homosexuality is a sin and that non-believers go to hell, so whatever suffering is brought upon you, it's God's will. They don't rejoice in it, and they would probably do anything they could to get your back "into the fold," but they just don't know anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most intolerant people have been indoctrinated from birth to be afraid of everything different from them. They aren't bad people (with the exception of skinheads and the like). They just don't know anything else. When I left Christianity, most of my friends said "You'll come back to Jesus." They simply didn't understand how anyone could be happy otherwise. When I didn't come back, they slowly dropped me, one by one. They're still cordial, but they think I'm evil and that Satan has taken over my life. It's the only way they know to explain it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People hate things they don't understand. This is the entire basis of racism and sexism. Honestly, I don't especially care for the arts, but I understand why they are important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to look out for people who were employed in industries that are no longer needed (coal mining) or downsized by automation and outsourcing (textiles, auto making). It's hard to get industry to move into an area that has no skilled workers, or to get service jobs in an area where no one is working. You wouldn't build a restaurant in a town that had a high unemployment rate, would you? 

What these people needed was re-education and relocation money. One problem was that many of them were too old or didn't want to move. There's no helping people like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was young and only knew how to do one thing, my father said "One-trick ponies get put out to pasture." That is exactly what has happened to a lot of these people. They only knew how to do one thing; i.e., work in a factory or a coal mine or something like that. When those jobs were gone, they did not know how to start over with something new. For some, it was lack of education, for some it was age discrimination in hiring (I've experienced that myself), and for some it was lacking the economic means to move to an area that had jobs or to obtain training for a new occupation. 

I was raised in a state that had a lot of textile mills, and you don't know how many times I heard from people who had been laid off when automation took their jobs "I don't know how to do nothing else. What am I gonna do?" I've sat down with a lot of people and pointed out to them that they DID know how to do othet things, and tried to get them to turn that into an occupation, but they just weren't capable of running their own business. Some did. I have a friend in my home state who now sells organic herbs, seeds, and plants from her little 2-acre plot and does better than she did in the mills, and one who sells quilted and hand-sewn items at craft fairs and on etsy. Most of them, though, just went on welfare and watched their lives slide downhill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily, they aren't, but they will never stop adoring him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary may not be the most honest person alive, but she has worked her tail off for this country, and especially for women and children, for most of her life. So she capitalized on it. So what? She didn't cheat anybody out of their money. They gave it to her willingly. She didn't pretend to be anything other than what she was. Men hate her because she is actually smarter than most of them, and has much more gumption. Women hate her because she is everything they didn't get to be. Yes, she is arrogant and haughty and not a real fluffy-cuddly person, but we don't need a fluff-cuddly person for President. We need someone tough as nails who can't be manipulated and pushed around by people around them, and that sure ain't Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Case in point: Ben Carson. Brilliant (by all acounts) neuro surgeon. Otherwise, sort of light on the brain power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even intelligent people can make mistakes. This is the country who elected Nixon, remember. It was a single-issue election -- get us out of Viet Nam. They didn't care about anything else. I'm a lifelong dem and I voted for him. It was my first Presidential election, and I voted for Nixon. Talk about not being able to live something down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Trump is doing a fine job on his own of showing why voting for him was a mistake.

Only for the level headed people. For the war-mongers and hate-mongers, he's still a God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing I can say is that if she had been elected, the political revolutionaries (aka Berners) would still be protesting and picketing and raising hell because she cheated Bernie out of the Presidency. She would have to move way far to the left to please them, so they would have actually gotten more accomplished by having her in the WH. Sometimes people can't see that even when something looks bad, it's still what is in your best interest. 

These are the same people saying that they won't vote "blue no matter who" in 2018 to help us get congress back. The far left is just as bad as the far right, you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then there were the Bernie-or-Bust people, many of whom totally ignored their God Bernie and voted third party, or even for Trump, just out of childish spite. Those are the ones who made me angriest. Here was Bernie, begging them to vote for Hillary so Trump wouldn't be elected and destroy our country, but suddenly, what he said was not important.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The alt-right and the right-wing media have been brainwashing these people for many years now. When all someone watches is Faux News and they listen to Alex Jones and read Breitbart, what do you expect?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrogance again. Everyone thought Hillary was a done deal, and they honestly thought Trump had done himself in. Plus, congress just wanted a GOP president. They didn't care who it was. This whole election was a botched job from the start. If they entire thing had been run honestly, we would have President Sanders in the White House and we wouldn't be watching 50 years of accomplishments and freedoms, along with our environment be destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never post. I find it all rather amusing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably the only way congress couldn't ignore it. I don't think Comey cares much for that bunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, if they keep on pissing on the IC's boots, that tape might just "disappear" and be leaked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they have the tape, why have they not released it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, as much as I hated Bush's policies and think he was a crappy President, I don't think he's a bad man. I think he was manipulated by bad men. Trump -- he's just a bad, bad man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even think most of them believe in the GOP. They have been brainwashed by right-wing media to hate "liberals" for years now. They aren't intelligent enough to see through the lies. Anyone who thinks Alex Jones is real is beyond help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can fix this, IF we get off our collective lazy butts and vote in 2018 -- straight ticket! We can't let our ideals get in the way. I actually had someone tell me that it wasn't his responsibility to fix the establishment's mistakes, and he wasn't ever voting for an establishment dem. This is the thinking that got us here. We have to put country before ideals for awhile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see the bottom falling out once he declares war on -- somebody, anybody -- and reinstates the draft.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cult is a tiny part of the people who voted for him, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wandered over today. Nothing has changed. Someone had just brought in a new batch of kool-aid a they were lapping it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like the weather in FL. Give him a few days, things will change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "But her emails!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think so. Pretty obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kids are both grown men, so we're surviving it together. Nothing like a White House on Fire to bring a family together. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which makes it all the more sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, the joy of walking through life with blinders and a 3rd grade education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True dat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooooh!!! Taco pizza!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You jest, but I truly think the man is in early dementia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to learn to lean over the plate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is concerned with how much money he can make off of the government before they kick his ass out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that. Here, have an upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. The left wing is coming out their stupor, getting organized and starting to coalesce into something powerful and strong that can take back our country and put it back on the right track. That's something that has needed to happen for a long, long time. 

2. Just about everything else. Our freedoms are being eroded, our poor, our elderly and women are being attacked at every level and we still don't know how much Russia has influenced the government. Oh -- and we have a malignant narcissist 3-year-old and an alt-right drunken Leninist running the fucking country. PLUS, the GOP in congress can't seem to pull its diapers up on its own anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot feel sorry for them. I try, I honestly do, but I can't. When someone shows you who they are OVER AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN, you should believe them! They thought it was all an act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we need to show out in force to take back congress in 2018, and even in these special elections. We have to some control back so we can stop this shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And lying. Don't forget lying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of them actually believed him, or didn't believe he would take "their" SS or "their" health care of "their" food stamps or close down "their" Planned Parenthood. The mental machinations of some of these people are un-fucking-believable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's already killed a shitton of civilians. He's just letting the military run wild, like kids in the toy dept. of WalMart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are quite a few of your own who are horrified too, and will be more horrified when missiles from N. Korea come raining down on their heads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald? Is that you? Or maybe Steve? It's one of you, I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, I love Futurama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoever is keeping count, on day 100, they should publish a tweet that says "100 Days, XXXX Lies"  I'm sure it's into 4 figures by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why hasn't there been more support of the president's move to the center on these issues?

Because he changes his stance from one day to the next. Just when you think he's going to be o.k., he's threatening to bomb N. Korea or some such shit. He's off the rails! You can't believe anything he says, because his next tweet might just change everything. 

And he WON'T stop talking about Hillary and the election and Obama. JHC! He's right - the election is OVER! GET OVER IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 Days of Horror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This administration is just out of its league. Do they not know that Kim would love to nuke us and that he is not sane? What is wrong with them? 

This is so serious. One thing you never do is play chicken with a crazy person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This feels more like middle school every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's what they were HIRED (by us) to care about. It's just not what is going to get them reelected in their districts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My town has probably the worst postal service in the state of FL. They will do things to spite you if you complain to management. Once I lived where they had cluster mailboxes, and the mailperson put a package into the wrong box. The person whose box they put it in just happened to be there when they delivered the mail that day, and said "You put this into the wrong box. This is her box right here (pointed to it)" Did the mail person put it into my box? No, she threw it into the back of the truck. No shit. All to the loud complaints of my neighbor asking why the fuck she did that. So neighbor tells me, I call the PO, can't get an answer, so I make a complaint to the main complaint service online. Tracking showed that the package was delivered, then it suddenly changed. By the time I got the package 2 weeks later, it had been to CA, back through MI, and then back to FL. I've heard this is a common tactic they use when someone complains about them. They just send your package around the fucking country to teach you a lesson. Unfortunately for them, my package was medication (which I put into my complaint), so they ended up having to answer for that, plus pay for me having to go out of pocket to get more meds. 

I've had them cram a package so tightly into my box (because they were to fucking lazy to walk to the door and deliver it properly) that I could not get it out, and had to sit and wait for them the next day to get them to remove it from their side.  I've also sat and watched out the window as they tossed a package marked "fragile" across my 6-ft high gate into my courtyard, when the gate was unlocked and the front door was 10 feet away. One of them left a pink registered mail notice stuck into my gate, and then it rained, and luckily, I found it on the ground in the morning, but the ink was all smeared, so I had to take it to the PO to find out WTF it was.

Glad you like the PO. Obviously, you live in some place where they are decent. I don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I wish I was duckponder. LOL I can't afford to live downtown, unfortunately. Maybe someday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry. I never had to take a test for them, because I joined so long ago when they were first starting. All I can say is that they probably aren't taking any more people on right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I know why they always ask "Is it plugged in?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a book I forget the name of that describes your life in terms of levels of a house. She is what they call "basement people," those who settle for less because they seriously don't want to try to improve themselves. They are the ones who say "It's just how I am. Accept it."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CC is weird. They will reject you for not having your sample in the right font. You have to read all the rules very, very carefully and follow them all to a "t". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I call tech support, I always say "I've turned it on and back off, I've done this and this, etc., etc." so they can just skip that shit. I get really aggravated with Mozilla support because all they can ever say is "Does it work in safe mode?" when I've already said that I checked that. then they still say "Start it in safe mode and check your add-ons." To them, it's always a fucking add-on, no matter what. Half the time they're wrong, and the program is just fucked up.

I've learned so much about FF just because their support forum personnel have no clue and I have to go in and find it myself. Every time I used to post, there would be at least half a dozen people who would say "I have that same problem!," but to Mozilla, it was always our fault. 

Then there is Microsoft, who always tells you to refresh Windows. WTF? I want to say "Have you ever personally refreshed Windows? Do you realize that it's an all-day process and that things may be worse after you do it?" 

Bad tech support is way worse than bad users, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. They've already tried to build a huge development in Hawthorne, and are still trying, but they can't get the plans for the bypass road through. SE is the next area they will try to gentrify. They are already doing it, and then they will just push the black community out further and further. 

ETA: Waldo would be more of a business community, because of the access to the airport and also railways, I think. Businesses would build up all around the airport and then they would turn 301 into an I-10 spur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GrandMA voice, please. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We actually have "chicken rescue" organizations to take the chickens when they no longer lay. WTF? Kill that sucker and eat it! That's what I mean by "think they are farmers." Farmers don't send animals to rescues. They eat those suckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
