<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9801</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perfect example of missionaries lying for the Lord. I asked if any church leaders get paid. They said no. I then asked specifically if Henry B. Eyring gets paid. They again said no. Either these missionaries have been lied to, or they're lying themselves. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NY attorney general fights to keep birth control free if 'Obamacare' revoked. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  supreme court after Trump appoints a conservative justice.

you nailed it. I doubt one appointment would change anything regarding abortion, but if Trump gets to name two justices, we could see Roe overturned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ginsburg and Kennedy aren't exactly young. If either of them kicks the bucket in the next 4 years and Trump gets more than one appointment to the high court, a law like this could seriously impact abortion case law in this country. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you live in Indiana, you can use this [LINK](https://iga.in.gov/legislative/find-legislators/) to find your state senators and state reps to voice your outrage over this bill. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They want to get sued for this law because they want a challenge to Roe v. Wade to get to the supreme court.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you live in Indiana, you can use this [LINK](https://iga.in.gov/legislative/find-legislators/) to find your state senators and state reps to voice your outrage over this bill. 


**I mean it. Fight like hell.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire purpose of this bill is to trigger a lawsuit. They think this might be the one that guts Roe. They may be right, they may be wrong. 

From an article about the bill: "Nislys bill is meant as a test case to see if a new U.S. Supreme Court will overturn Roe v. Wade  the 1973 decision legalizing abortion.

'Its time to bring the Roe v. Wade era to its logical conclusion,'  Nisly said. 'My goal is to deregulate abortion right out of existence in Indiana.'" [Link.](http://www.journalgazette.net/news/local/indiana/Coalition-fighting-abortion-bills-17233889)

That said, either abortion is wrong, or it isn't. Whether the abortion happens at 12 weeks or 8 months makes no difference in regard to whether abortion is wrong or not. The government should not be able to dictate what medical procedures a woman can and cannot undergo, and the government certainly shouldn't be telling a woman what she can do with her vagina. But considering our next President thinks he can grab pussies whenever he pleases because he's a "star," I suppose we shouldn't be shocked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know many are irked by political posts, but this legislation is largely driven by religious conservatives who want to use the law to impose their religious views regarding life on society at large. This is an issue important to secular folks. 

If you live in Indiana, you can use this [LINK](https://iga.in.gov/legislative/find-legislators/) to find your state senators and state reps to voice your outrage over this bill. **FIGHT LIKE HELL INDIANA.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever heard a religious friend say "life begins at conception?" If HB 1134 passes in IN, that will be reality. It defines life as beginning when the ovum is fertilized by sperm   restructures IN's criminal code to reflect that, making abortion the same as murder. The GOP has the votes to pass it. :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Indiana HB 1134. It defines life as beginning when the human ovum is fertilized by human sperm   restructures IN's criminal code to reflect that definition. If passed, having an abortion will be considered the same as murder. The GOP has a super-majority in the IN legislature. Fight like hell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Indiana HB 1134. It defines life as beginning when the human ovum is fertilized by human sperm   restructures IN's criminal code to reflect that definition. If passed, having an abortion will be considered the same as murder. The GOP has a super-majority in the IN legislature. Fight like hell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close but nah  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea. Simply arguing trump hiring hookers to piss on him is more believable than Obama being a Kenyan Muslim.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea if Trump fucked hookers or not. I'm arguing it's more believable than Obama being a secret Muslim from Kenya or sandy hook being a hoax, all things these people believe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how all the gullible folks I know who ranted for years about Obama being a secret Kenyan Muslim, pizzagate, sandy hook truther shit, etc. are now scratching their heads and being like, "You don't REALLY believe that Trump hired hookers to piss on him in Moscow, DO YOU?"


And my only response is this: "Well that's a hell of a lot more believable than Obama being a secret Muslim Kenyan and it's more believable than sandy hook being a hoax and it's more believable than pizzagate!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All of my friends on the right keep asking, "Do you REALLY believe Trump hired hookers to piss on him?" And I can't help but say, "Well, that's more believable than 'Obama is a secret Kenyan Muslim, Pizzagate, sandy hook being a hoax' and all the other conspiracies YOU'VE spewed before!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same friend who is still convinced that Obama's birth certificate is a fraud asked me today if I truly believed the leaks about Trump hiring hookers for golden showers. The way he asked it was full of indignation and shock. 

I'm like, "Bro. You believed pizzagate, that the Clinton's ran a global pedophilia ring.....but you think it's incredulous that Trump hired hookers for some piss play?"

This same guy posts every conspiracy theory known to man regarding sandy hook. 

Yet I'm gullible for considering the possibility that a man we already know is pervy might let some hookers pee on him. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how all the gullible folks I know who ranted for years about Obama being a secret Kenyan Muslim, pizzagate, sandy hook truther shit, etc. are now scratching their heads and being like, "You don't REALLY believe that Trump hired hookers to piss on him in Moscow, DO YOU?"

And my only response is this: "Well that's a hell of a lot more believable than Obama being a secret Muslim Kenyan and it's more believable than sandy hook being a hoax and it's more believable than pizzagate!"

**EDIT:** I have no idea if Trump truly banged Russian hookers and partook in piss play. I'm arguing that it's more believable than Obama being a secret Muslim from Kenya or that sandy hook was a hoax, all things these same people believe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump shouted down CNNs Jim Acosta as fake news then took a question from Breitbart. Only one of those outlets champions a white nationalist movement. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump shouted down CNNs Jim Acosta as fake news then took a question from Breitbart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New TV commercial calls for leaks about potential Mormon tax fraud. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New TV commercial calls for leaks about potential Mormon tax fraud. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV campaign targeting Mormon churchs tax status kicks off in Utah. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  in a move expected to be opposed by the dominant Roman Catholic church.

If the Roman Catholic Church really gives a fuck about reducing the abortion rate, they need to quickly remove their heads from their asses and realize that free birth control will prevent more abortions than any prayer, protest, legislation, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  in a move expected to be opposed by the dominant Roman Catholic church.

If the Roman Catholic Church really gives a fuck about reducing the abortion rate, they need to quickly remove their heads from their asses and realize that free birth control will prevent more abortions than any prayer, protest, legislation, etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippines will offer free birth control to 6 million women. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte has ordered government agencies to ensure free access to contraceptives for 6 million women who cannot obtain them, officials said Wednesday, in a move expected to be opposed by the dominant Roman Catholic church. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says: "give daddy your Russian whore piss." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changed it to "truth." It's late. My bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truth is relative. People who believe in objective truth are terrifying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman, denied abortion while in jail, sues Tennessee sheriff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman, denied abortion while in jail, sues Tennessee sheriff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "While Mr. Trump and his cabinet nominees deny the reality of climate change, people throughout the world are suffering and dying." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is with religions cutting dicks? If you're a Jew, they cut your dick at 8 days old. If you convert as an adult, you must be circumcised. If you're already circumcised, a rabbi will prick your dick to draw blood. Some Muslims wait until puberty to circumcise their boys. WTF? Possibly NSFW. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muslim circumcision is arguably worse than Jewish circumcision, as in some cultures they wait until 7-12 or puberty to circumcise the boys. 

Jews wait until the 8th day of life to circumcise a baby. [Link.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brit_milah#Ceremony) 

What a way to welcome a new man into the world....by cutting off part of his penis without any input from him. 

Oh, and if you want to become a Jew as an adult, you still have to get circumcised! For converts who were circumcised prior to wanting to become Jewish, there is a ritual called [hatafat dam brit](http://www.mayyimhayyim.org/using-the-mikveh/the-process-of-conversion) where a rabbi or other authorized Jew will draw a drop of blood from where your foreskin once was to symbolize your covenant with the people of Israel. 

In some branches of orthodox Judaism, the Rabbi will perform a ritual known as metzitzah b'peh, during which the rabbi will literally suck on the penis to "clean" the circumcision wound. This has actually led to babies in NYC dying after contracting herpes after this ritual. [Link.](http://abcnews.go.com/Health/baby-dies-herpes-virus-ritual-circumcision-nyc-orthodox/story?id=15888618)

I have to say it: what the fuck? 

However, not all religions are keen on cutting dicks. Hindu and Buddhist holy books make no mention of circumcision. [Link.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Religious_male_circumcision#Asian_cultures)

In African cultures, circumcision is really terrible. No painkillers. Really awful ritual. Not safe for work video. If you have a weak stomach, do not watch. It shows an African circumcision. [Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lvW2b9ujdWo)

What the fuck is it with religion and cutting our dicks? What the fuck?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much do top Mormon leaders make? It may be more -- or less -- than you think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 02:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't attack Christians. I made a very specific point to use the phrase "religious conservatives" in my post, not "Christians."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it before, I'll say it again.

No amount of protesting, lobbying, campaigning, praying, etc. will prevent abortions more than increased access to affordable birth control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planned Parenthood partnership provides free birth control. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it before, I'll say it again.

No amount of protesting, lobbying, campaigning, praying, etc. will prevent abortions more than increased access to affordable birth control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planned Parenthood partnership provides free birth control. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Provide a direct quote if you want. Watch the entire video, you'll hear Trump say he thinks women must face some form of punishment for having an abortion. Took some work for Chris Matthews to get it out of him, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it before, I'll say it again. 

No amount of protesting, lobbying, campaigning, praying, etc. will prevent abortions more than increased access to affordable birth control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've said it before, I'll say it again. 

No amount of protesting, lobbying, campaigning, praying, etc. will prevent abortions more than increased access to affordable birth control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planned Parenthood partnership provides free birth control. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at the University of Utah have teamed up with Planned Parenthood to create HER Salt Lake, an initiative that provides women with access to various methods of birth control free of charge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll edit it in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the whole post. ;) Typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because our voter turnout is so low :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not taking issue with people who voted for Trump thinking, rightly or wrongly, that he would be good for the economy. 

I'm taking issue with the religious right, the people who constantly lecture us about morality and family values, who voted for a man who has demonstrated time and time again that he has no morals or family values. 

If you voted for Trump because you liked his economic message, more power to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump sensationalized his entire campaign. "Mexico will pay for the wall." "Mexicans are rapists and murderers." He's just getting a dose of his own medicine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mentioned it was a typo in my post before you even made this comment. Did you read the whole thing? ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just implemented something similar in Maine. We'll see how it goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Women who have abortions must face some kind of punishment.  -Trump](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i2mHh9TtEks)

That statement helped more with evangelical voters than if he had said, "I repent of my sins and embrace Jesus." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree, but in a multi party system, a candidate could win the presidency with only 25% of the vote. Is that a better alternative?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be the first to admit that the pussy grabbing comment has been sensationalized, but that doesn't take away from any of the other vile things Trump said that most Christians would lambaste me for....but when Trump does/says them, they vote for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The funny thing to me is that the conversation begins with Trump relating how he tried to put the moves on someone and got shut down

relating how he tried to put the moves on a MARRIED woman, while Trump was also married. Again, family values on full display. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you fucking hillary supporting libshit

I voted for Bernie, but anyone you disagree with is just another CTR shill I'm sure ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "Trump has a choice: He can admit he lied or tell Republicans to stop trying to take health care away from millions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas narcotics agent Corky Schalchlin: no solid evidence that marijuana is medicine. We need to educate Mr. Corky Schalchlin about the medicinal benefits of cannabis. With a name like that, he certainly needs a little medicine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland reconsiders its constitutional ban on abortion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "Trump has a choice: He can admit he lied or tell Republicans to stop trying to take health care away from millions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that all Christians voted for Trump.... but post election stats show that the vast majority of evangelicals certainly did. And since they are typically the ones fighting the morality wars, my point stands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck WWJD. It's WJVFAPB (would Jesus vote for a pussy grabber). The bright side of a Trump Presidency is that religious conservative hypocrisy is exposed. They were willing to throw family values   morality to the wind to elect a thrice married self proclaimed pussy grabber. We all saw it happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember a time when religious conservatives stood on their pedestal and looked down from their moral high horse and would lecture the world about family values, respecting life, the sanctity of marriage, etc.

I believed they were spewing bullshit that they likely didn't follow in their own private lives, remember [Ted Haggard???,](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ted_Haggard) but now we KNOW it.

If family values means voting for a thrice married man who brags about grabbing married women's pussies, that's news to me.

If family values means suggesting that you [would date your own daughter,](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=diMp241gAcw) I didn't know.

If respecting life means you were [in favor of abortion](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tsOlXidHXRE) until you started thinking about running for president, LOL

Religious conservatives have no leg to stand on. The next time they try to look down from that high horse of theirs, remind them that they knowingly voted for a pussy grabber.

EDIT: Typo in the title. I'm aware it would be WJVFAPG, not WJVFAPB

EDIT 2: Not that all Christians voted for Trump (that is why I said "religious conservatives" instead of "Christians" .... but post election stats show that the vast majority of evangelicals certainly did. And since they are typically the ones fighting the morality wars, my point stands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The next time religious conservatives try to lecture you about family values or morality, remind them that they voted for a thrice married self proclaimed pussy grabber. Their holier than thou days are over. Would Jesus vote for a pussy grabber? #WJVFAPG </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember a time when religious conservatives stood on their pedestal and looked down from their moral high horse and would lecture the world about family values, respecting life, the sanctity of marriage, etc.

I knew they were spewing bullshit that they likely didn't follow in their own private lives, but now we KNOW it.
If family values means voting for a thrice married man who brags about grabbing married women's pussies, that's news to me.

If family values means suggesting that you would date your own daughter, I didn't know.

If respecting life means you were in favor of abortion until you started thinking about running for president, LOL

Religious conservatives have no leg to stand on. The next time they try to look down from that high horse of theirs, remind them that they knowingly voted for a pussy grabber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A common argument from theists against transgender rights is that transgender folks are mentally ill. That's pretty rich coming from people who exhibit excessive fear (hell), delusions (God is real), and seeing or hearing things (God is communicating with me.) All classic signs of mental illness. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 20:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A common argument that I have been hearing a lot more recently from theists is that transgender people are just mentally ill and we shouldn't cater to their delusions and illness. 

Religious lawmakers have [said it.](http://wgme.com/news/local/state-representative-criticized-for-referring-to-transgender-people-as-mentally-ill)

Pastors [have claimed](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6PsdevibR5I) that transgender people are mentally ill. 

Greg Locke, pastor of Global Vision Bible Church, describes transgender people as [troubled and confused.](http://mediamatters.org/video/2016/04/28/foxs-cavuto-asks-anti-lgbt-pastor-about-confused-troubled-transgender-people/210134)


Pope Francis [even said](http://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2016/04/23/franklin-graham-men-pretending-women-not-use-womens-restrooms/) that sex education should teach respect and appreciation for sexual differences, including self-acceptance and learning to embrace the body with which one is born, rather than playing with **fictional identities that deny reality.**


**We want to talk about fiction, mental illness and denying reality?** WOW.

* Dead men don't come back to life. 

* Men can't walk on water. 

* Virgins don't get pregnant. 

* Talking snakes aren't real. 

* You can't fit two of every fucking animal on one boat. 


Believing those things is denying reality. 

Talking to your imaginary sky fairy every goddamn morning and evening and before each meal and fearing eternal damnation in hell every day are signs of metal illness. 

To audacity of these folks never fails to blow me away.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let me get this straight: Alabama balked for years about forcing businesses to insure their employees and complained about fines for businesses that didn't comply. Now, Alabama wants to force businesses to have an "attendant" to monitor appropriate bathroom use. No attendant? $3,500 fine. WTF? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can read about the bill [here.](http://www.al.com/news/index.ssf/2017/01/alabama_bathroom_bill_targets.html) 

That's right, folks. The Alabama legislature is so busy regulating bathrooms that they haven't **expanded medicaid, sought relief for the environmental impacts of the multiple pipeline leaks in Alabama recently, or any of the important shit facing the state.**

They want to complain when businesses are mandated to insure their employees, but then think it's 100% acceptable to fine businesses over how they operate their pisser. 

I feel like my IQ dropped a little just by reading that article... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-spirit Sioux Falls woman second reported transgender murder of 2017. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-spirit Sioux Falls woman second reported transgender murder of 2017. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-spirit Sioux Falls woman second reported transgender murder of 2017. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy sunday from an atheist! I've been studying various Christian beliefs on salvation and I am VERY confused. How is salvation a free gift if you have to stop sinning (actively change your behavior) to earn it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 18:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full disclosure: I am a raging atheist, but I admit that I know absolutely nothing and it's 100 possible that I'm wrong. I just don't believe I am wrong, yet. It's entirely possible that one day I might discover that I am wrong. 

I've studied southern baptist theology (whew, what a trip), Lutheran theology, Calvinism, Mormon theology and I've very, very briefly studied a little bit about Adventism. 

Common themes are obviously faith, grace, works, etc. But each and every denomination seems to have a different take on it. 

Every single denomination seems to think that salvation works just a little bit differently. 

The main issue I'm having, and admittedly this is mostly in nondenominational evangelical churches, is that their explanations of salvation are either blatantly contradictory or they don't make sense at all. 

For example: One non denominational church I recently visited teaches that salvation is an unearned gift from God that we receive by repenting of all of our sins. 

Ok, so in order to get this "unearned" gift, you have to earn it by actively changing your behavior. The fact that they can explain this with a straight face, as if they aren't completely ignoring the meaning of the word "unearned," is almost laughable to me. 

If salvation is truly unearned, changing your behavior wouldn't be required. 

Not to mention that this specific church also acts as if they don't understand the meaning of the word repent, which means a change of mind (opinion/belief) regarding God. Am I wrong to say they are using the word repent wrong in this situation?

If you believe that you have to follow rules, change your behavior and do all these things in order to receive salvation, why pretend like you believe in grace and just say that you have to do the proper works? 


Another fun one I've encountered was this: 

Another church I visited teaches that irresistible grace can be resisted or received by human free will. Not to sound overly controversial, but how the heck can **IR**resistible grace be resisted? Again, it's as if they don't even realize they are being blatantly contradictory. 

Why not just admit that you don't believe in irresistible grace instead of trying to (illogically) say that irresistible grace can be resisted? 

Honestly, and I think many will be shocked to hear me say this, the Mormons are the most honest and consistent with their beliefs. 

They will tell you up front that they believe that works and ordinances are required for salvation. No sugar coating it or trying to alter definitions of words to fit a narrative specific to their theology. They will tell you that they believe that God's grace is sufficient to cover where we fall short, but that there are things (works) required of us as well. 

Help me understand. Where do you guys each fall when it comes to how salvation works? 

If Christianity is true, why are Christians so divided about how one even gets "saved?" 

Thanks for letting me ask all these crazy questions. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "People should not be dying in the United States of America because they couldn't afford a check-up or a prescription." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Colorado state university offers veterans free tuition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 'immaculate conception' problem: Maryland medical marijuana growers must break law to grow plants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "While the five largest drug companies made $50 billion in profits last year, 1 out of 5 Americans were unable to fill their prescriptions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 15:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and the Clintons have quite possibly the greatest control in history over the donor class of an entire party.

Then why did Bernie [raise more than her](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Democratic_Party_presidential_primaries,_2016#Campaign_finance) during the primary? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iran actually does this. The religious leaders in Iran do not tolerate homosexuality, but if you want gender reassignment surgery, the government mandates that insurance companies pay for most of the procedures. [Link.](https://www.buzzfeed.com/lesterfeder/why-irans-mullahs-bless-sex-reassignment) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arkansas passed MMJ last year, but the MMJ commission has set the application   licensing fees so high that small businesses are essentially excluded. To apply, you must pay $15k. If your app is approved, you must pay a $100k licensing fee. You must also prove $1 million in assets and $500k cash. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot the pussy grabbing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A trans bathroom bill has been filed in TX. How many bills have been filed to ban sex offenders from bathrooms? ZERO. This has nothing to do with protecting women and kids. They want to use trans-folks as a scapegoat while ignoring the average of 70 reports/week of child sex abuse in US churches. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bill has been filed in Texas that would, if passed, limit where transgender people can pee. [Link.](http://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/05/us/texas-transgender-bathroom-access.html?_r=0)

Their main argument is that women and children need to be protected from those pesky men in dresses. 

First, that shows a clear lack of understanding regarding transgender people in the first place. **Do you really want someone who for all intents and purposes is female, has real boobs that grew thanks to hormone therapy, to go into the restroom with your sons instead of daughters?**

Also, where the fuck are the bills banning sex offenders from bathrooms? If we're truly concerned about the safety of women and children in restrooms, might we consider banning people **who have actually been fucking convicted of sex crimes** as opposed to poor transgender people who have never been convicted of any crime? 

I suppose that's just too much logic for those poor bastards in the Texas legislature. 


Honestly, and this is just my theory, but I think transgender folks are being used as a scapegoat here. No doubt we have an epidemic of child sexual abuse in this country. **But it ain't happening in bathrooms.... in fact, it's pretty damn common in church.**

On average, there are around 70 reports per week of children being abused sexually in American churches. [Link.](http://churchandstate.org.uk/2016/05/kids-more-likely-to-be-molested-at-church-than-in-transgender-bathrooms/)

Where are the laws banning clergy from public restrooms? Where are the laws banning sex offenders, you know people with an actual history of sex abuse, from bathrooms? FUCKING NO WHERE. 

These asshats don't care about protecting the children. They want to distract you from the real problem. 


If you live in TX and want to contact your senators regarding this legislation, you can find their contact information [here.](http://www.senate.state.tx.us/75r/Senate/Members.htm) Let them know you'd prefer they ban actual sex offenders from restrooms as opposed to innocent citizens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A trans bathroom bill has been filed in TX. How many bills have been filed to ban sex offenders from bathrooms? ZERO. This has nothing to do with protecting women and kids. They want to use trans-folks as a scapegoat while ignoring the average of 70 reports/week of child sex abuse in US churches. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bill has been filed in Texas that would, if passed, limit where transgender people can pee. [Link.](http://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/05/us/texas-transgender-bathroom-access.html?_r=0)

Their main argument is that women and children need to be protected from those pesky men in dresses. 

First, that shows a clear lack of understanding regarding transgender people in the first place. **Do you really want someone who for all intents and purposes is female, has real boobs that grew thanks to hormone therapy, to go into the restroom with your sons instead of daughters?**

Also, where the fuck are the bills banning sex offenders from bathrooms? If we're truly concerned about the safety of women and children in restrooms, might we consider banning people **who have actually been fucking convicted of sex crimes** as opposed to poor transgender people who have never been convicted of any crime? 

I suppose that's just too much logic for those poor bastards in the Texas legislature. 


Honestly, and this is just my theory, but I think transgender folks are being used as a scapegoat here. No doubt we have an epidemic of child sexual abuse in this country. **But it ain't happening in bathrooms.... in fact, it's pretty damn common in church.**

On average, there are around 70 reports per week of children being abused sexually in American churches. [Link.](http://churchandstate.org.uk/2016/05/kids-more-likely-to-be-molested-at-church-than-in-transgender-bathrooms/)

Where are the laws banning clergy from public restrooms? Where are the laws banning sex offenders, you know people with an actual history of sex abuse, from bathrooms? FUCKING NO WHERE. 

These asshats don't care about protecting the children. They want to distract you from the real problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A trans bathroom bill has been filed in TX. How many bills have been filed to ban sex offenders from bathrooms? ZERO. This has nothing to do with protecting women and kids. They want to use trans-folks as a scapegoat while ignoring the average of 70 reports/week of child sex abuse in US churches. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bill has been filed in Texas that would, if passed, limit where transgender people can pee. [Link.](http://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/05/us/texas-transgender-bathroom-access.html?_r=0)

Their main argument is that women and children need to be protected from those pesky men in dresses. 

First, that shows a clear lack of understanding regarding transgender people in the first place. **Do you really want someone who for all intents and purposes is female, has real boobs that grew thanks to hormone therapy, to go into the restroom with your sons instead of daughters?**

Also, where the fuck are the bills banning sex offenders from bathrooms? If we're truly concerned about the safety of women and children in restrooms, might we consider banning people **who have actually been fucking convicted of sex crimes** as opposed to poor transgender people who have never been convicted of any crime? 

I suppose that's just too much logic for those poor bastards in the Texas legislature. 


Honestly, and this is just my theory, but I think transgender folks are being used as a scapegoat here. No doubt we have an epidemic of child sexual abuse in this country. **But it ain't happening in bathrooms.... in fact, it's pretty damn common in church.**

On average, there are around 70 reports per week of children being abused sexually in American churches. [Link.](http://churchandstate.org.uk/2016/05/kids-more-likely-to-be-molested-at-church-than-in-transgender-bathrooms/)

Where are the laws banning clergy from public restrooms? Where are the laws banning sex offenders, you know people with an actual history of sex abuse, from bathrooms? FUCKING NO WHERE. 

These asshats don't care about protecting the children. They want to distract you from the real problem. 

If you live in TX and want to contact your senators regarding this legislation, you can find their contact information [here.](http://www.senate.state.tx.us/75r/Senate/Members.htm) Let them know you'd prefer they ban actual sex offenders from restrooms as opposed to innocent citizens. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 18:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton lost and DWS is no longer in charge of the DNC. To continue focusing on them is a waste of time when there are much bigger battles to fight and when they've both been mostly stripped of power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nations first transgender killing of 2017 is in Mississippi. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A year ago, Trump called Bernie a liar for merely repeating to voters what Trump himself had said, that he believes wages are "too high." Trump then promised never to cut SS or medicare. Now, the new GOP budget cuts both. We must remind everyone that Trump is the big fat liar. #PinocchioNoseTrump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump tweeted last spring that he was the only GOP candidate that would NOT cut ss and medicare. [Link.](http://time.com/4622703/bernie-sanders-donald-trump-senate-tweet/)

Now that he and his goons have won control of the congress and the presidency, they released their new budget plans and guess what? **They're planning on cutting ss and medicare.** [Link.](http://www.sanders.senate.gov/newsroom/press-releases/sanders-blasts-republican-budget-slashing-health-care-for-millions-of-americans)


We have witnessed this from Trump before when he called Bernie a liar for telling people that Trump had said....exactly what Trump had said. 

[Link](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VRmi28fjNOs) to a video where Trump says wages are too high.

[Link](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/681155057136578563) to the Tweet where Trump called Bernie a liar for telling people that he had said exactly what you can watch him say in the video linked above. 

Trump lies so much I'm surprised it's his small hands and not his huge nose that he's self conscious about!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A year ago, Trump called Bernie a liar for merely repeating to voters what Trump himself had said, that he believes wages are "too high." Trump then promised never to cut SS or medicare. Now, the new GOP budget cuts both. We must remind everyone that Trump is the big fat liar. #PinocchioNoseTrump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump tweeted last spring that he was the only GOP candidate that would NOT cut ss and medicare. [Link.](http://time.com/4622703/bernie-sanders-donald-trump-senate-tweet/)

Now that he and his goons have won control of the congress and the presidency, they released their new budget plans and guess what? **They're planning on cutting ss and medicare.** [Link.](http://www.sanders.senate.gov/newsroom/press-releases/sanders-blasts-republican-budget-slashing-health-care-for-millions-of-americans)


We have witnessed this from Trump before when he called Bernie a liar for telling people that Trump had said....exactly what Trump had said. 

[Link](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VRmi28fjNOs) to a video where Trump says wages are too high.

[Link](https://twitter.com/realDonaldTrump/status/681155057136578563) to the Tweet where Trump called Bernie a liar for telling people that he had said exactly what you can watch him say in the video linked above. 

Trump lies so much I'm surprised it's his small hands and not his huge nose that he's self conscious about! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainline Christianity can blow me....explicitly for pleasure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virginia Gov. Terry McAuliffe's budget proposal includes a $6 million pilot program that would provide women with long-term contraception such as intrauterine devices at no cost. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I fuck, I am not choosing whether or not to conceive. Bearing children is not the sole purpose of sex, and this fuckwad in the KY senate needs to realize it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kentucky Republicans propose abortion ban after 20 weeks: One had a choice early on to make a decision to conceive or not. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, this bill does include exceptions for rape and incest.. but this guy is still a complete fuckwad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This week, Arcview Market Research announced that in 2016, the legal weed market in North America generated $6.7 billion, up 30% from 2015. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should ask Mr. Stivers exactly how one "chooses" to conceive. Last time I checked, we have very little control over whether or not we get pregnant when we fuck. There are so many factors in play. Ovulation, sperm count, etc. 

Or is he suggesting that anyone who has sex is "choosing" to conceive? Because that's just not true. If the only purpose of sex was to make a baby, porn wouldn't exist.

I can personally say with 100% honestly that I have never once chosen to conceive any of the times I've had sex in my 28 years of life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Speaking of the bill on Tuesday, Kentucky Senate president Robert Stiverswho said he'd like to ban abortion even earlier than 20 weeksclaimed women have a "choice" of whether to conceive a child and "the legislature has its ability to determine" the course of a pregnancy after that. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KY Senate Prez: 'To conceive or not' is a woman's only choice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol fair criticism. Edited it to teens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for relevant username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because access to contraception has always been political and faced religious opposition. Ever heard of [Griswold v. Connecticut?](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Griswold_v._Connecticut) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God forbid teenagers have a sex drive. Do religious folks magically forget that they were horny, too, when they were 16? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that teens in Dallas aren't fucking at the same rates as teens in inner city Chicago takes nothing away from the fact that nationwide, 47% of students in high school report being sexually active. And i'd bet good money that if you surveyed only 16-18 year old high school students, that % would be over 65%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2013, 47% of high school aged students reported being sexually active. That's nearly half. [Link.](http://recapp.etr.org/recapp/index.cfm?fuseaction=pages.StatisticsDetail PageID=555) Kids aren't abstaining. Not a large majority, at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can get on board with requiring the pharmacist to offer assistance to all women buying birth control. 

Hell, my pharmacist asks me if I have any questions or concerns every single month when I refill my blood pressure meds anyways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the f word. 

Are we 12? This is reddit. You can find way worse on here than me saying fuck a few times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also, you get that there is a difference between access to BC and education, right?

You realize that a 15 year old girl who has never been taught to monitor her cycle, when she's ovulation or how birth control works makes it highly unlikely that she would use birth control, right? 

Bitching about how I frame my opinion is pointless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm not sure you coulf have been much more toxic. 

It's hard not to respond with a bit of vitriol when I've legitimately watched friends have their lives ruined or largely set back due to mistakes that could have been avoided by proper education.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What a woman, or anyone for that matter, chooses to do with their body is not of my concern.

I agree with you 1000000%. However, you cannot deny that the two issues (abortion and contraception) are linked. If women had access to birth control in the same way they do advil, the abortion rate would drop drastically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess what prevents abortion more than any amount of prayer, protest, legislation, etc.?

Fucking birth control. 

Guess what dramatically lowers the teen pregnancy rate? Teaching teens about how to fuck with PROTECTION, including birth control, instead of teaching abstinence and waiting for marriage. (My 6th grade health class included nothing about condoms, birth control, ovulation, etc. In lieu of all that, we signed cards promising that we wouldn't fuck until we were married. This was in a public school.) What hormone ridden 16 year old is going to fucking abstain? Very few. 

Don't come at me bitching about your pro-life dogma if you don't think birth control should be readily available to ANY woman who needs it because THAT is how you prevent abortions effectively. 

**EDIT:** shit, thanks for the gold. Now, go teach your teens about condoms and ovulation so the next generation doesn't make the same mistakes many of those in my generation made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. Andrew Cuomo calls for free tuition at New York public colleges. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov.Andrew Cuomo calls for free tuition at New York public colleges. The Democrat unveiled his plan Tuesday morning at LaGuardia Community College in Queens alongside U.S. Sen. Bernie Sanders of Vermont. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over the counter birth control might soon become a reality. It has the support of medical organizations and politicians from both parties. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "Either Donald Trump lied to the American people or he's got to say that he will veto any cuts to Medicare, Medicaid or Social Security." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "Either Donald Trump lied to the American people or he's got to say that he will veto any cuts to Medicare, Medicaid or Social Security." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannabis legalization group to give out, smoke marijuana joints in DC during Trump's inauguration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannabis legalization group to give out, smoke marijuana joints in DC during Trump's inauguration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Center for Reproductive Rights and Whole Womans Health, an abortion rights group, has filed a lawsuit challenging Texas' requirement that aborted fetuses be buried or cremated. The center and other groups say the regulations serve no medical purpose. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outgoing Vermont Governor likely to pardon hundreds of marijuana offenders. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With governor's signature, recreational marijuana to become law Jan. 30. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With governor's signature, recreational marijuana to become law Jan. 30 in Maine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic Senators call on Trump education Secretary nominee DeVos to pay $5.3 million in unpaid fines for election violations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's a great idea! Want to REALLY create some jobs before you take office? Stop making the shit YOU sell in Mexico and various other foreign companies, Mr. President-elect. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders statement on Trump's Secretary of State nominee. "Not only is Mr. Tillerson a pal of Russia's authoritarian leader, Vladimir Putin, but he is the head of one of the largest oil companies in the world ... Very sad. Very dangerous. Mr. Tillerson must be opposed." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders statement on Trump's Secretary of State nominee. "Not only is Mr. Tillerson a pal of Russia's authoritarian leader, Vladimir Putin, but he is the head of one of the largest oil companies in the world ... Very sad. Very dangerous. Mr. Tillerson must be opposed." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "It is not utopian thinking to say that every American should have health insurance as a right. It's a reality in many countries already." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Most people don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know that the Catholic Church spent millions of dollars lobbying state governments to defeat proposed laws that would have extended the statue of limitations for child sex abuse cases, which would have given past victims more time to come forward? The church cares more about saving face than protecting the kids. [Link.](https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2016/may/12/catholic-church-fights-clergy-child-sex-abuse-measures) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis 'told about alleged child rapist' two years before his arrest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis 'told about alleged child rapist' two years before his arrest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A 2002 survery by Christian Ministry Resources found that, on average, there are 70 reports per week of child sex abuse in American churches. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kids more likely to be molested at church than in a transgender bathroom. Child abuse accusations against US protestant churches average 70 per week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kids more likely to be molested at church than in a transgender bathroom. Child abuse accusations against US protestant churches average 70 per week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kids more likely to be molested at church than in a transgender bathroom. Child abuse accusations against US protestant churches average 70 per week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A user details on r/exmormon how he had to block his Mormon Bishop's number from his teen's phone because he kept texting his kids about their porn habits. LDS bishops regularly interview minors alone, including questions about porn and sexuality. Let's call this what it is: grooming, not religion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women with diabetes can use hormone birth control, study says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Elizabeth Warren seeks to pull pot shops out of banking limbo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-abortion advocates in northern Idaho say they are collecting signatures for a ballot initiative that would outlaw abortion in Idaho. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's pick for Labor Secretary doesn't think workers should get breaks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmaker seeks big boost to Hawaii's minimum wage. By 2022, the minimum wage would hit $22 an hour. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 22:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 21:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I deleted the xpost. The way you worded it originally made it sound like you knew this same guy ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State lawmakers voted Wednesday morning to delay the opening date for recreational marijuana stores in Massachusetts by half a year  from January to summer 2018. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State Rep. Chris Corley accused of punching wife in face, pointing gun at her. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats to all the hard working Americans who will get raises next year! But remember, your pussy grabbing President elect has repeatedly said that he believes [wages are too high in America.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y7E90tAfW4w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minimum wage to increase in 21 states next year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2016, men go to jail for conducting themselves like the good prophet Joseph did. Yet TMB's still revere him... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youth pastor arrested for having sexual relationship with a 14 year old girl from his congregation. Sound familiar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 19 states and nearly two dozen cities and counties will see a minimum wage increase at the beginning of the new year! Congratulations to all the hard workers who will be getting a raise! Never forget, however, that Trump said during his campaign that he believes wages in America are "too high." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Climate change" deleted from Wisconsin DNR website. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No surgery before puberty I'm sure. However, if a transwoman waits until after puberty to begin hormone therapy, the transition can be more difficult and less successful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so where are the laws banning people from teaching religion to kids? Where are the groups shunning parents who indoctrinate? oh, wait, that's right....There aren't any.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ha, a trans 8 year old? i call absolute bullshit. this is just the parents pushing their own views and beliefs on the child. 

That's exactly what I say when I see an 8 year old catholic, Mormon, Baptist, etc. Absolute bullshit. That's just the parents pushing their own views and beliefs on the child.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not speaking against religion or anything - just don't understand how appropriate it is for the age.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How sad that parents think their 8 year old is able to know what religion they are. People need to stop forcing their religious beliefs on their kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If an 8 year old is old enough to decide to get baptized and love sweet baby Jesus and that not be considered indoctrination, I see no fucking problem with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8-year-old transgender boy barred from Cub Scouts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd hardly call 6% Christian a "large minority." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy Carter to Obama: Before you leave office, recognize Palestinian state. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "Oligarchy is not just an American issue, it is a global issue. The top 1% of the world's population owns more wealth than the bottom 99%." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Same-sex marriage passes first hurdle in Taiwanese Legislature. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A transgendered black man was slashed multiple times on a subway train Christmas Day after he offered his seat to a woman who refused to sit next to him because he was black, police said. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we had just elected our first LGBT President, I would bet good money that the Mormon Tabernacle Choir would NOT have accepted an invite to perform at the inauguration. They will, however, perform for the pussy grabber. #FamilyValues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mormon Church likes to pretend to be politically neutral, but make no mistake, they are political. 

If we had just elected our first LGBT President and the Mormon Tabernacle Choir had been invited to perform at the inauguration, I would bet good money that they would refuse. 

But when we elect a man who has been married three times, cheated on the majority of his wives and who brags about grabbing woman by the pussy, the Mormon Tabernacle Choir jumps at the opportunity to perform. 

Fucking selective values. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If we had just elected our first LGBT President, I would bet good money that the Mormon Tabernacle Choir would NOT have accepted an invite to perform at the inauguration. They will, however, perform for the pussy grabber. #FamilyValues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 18:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mormon Church likes to pretend to be politically neutral, but make no mistake, they are political. 

If we had just elected our first LGBT President and the Mormon Tabernacle Choir had been invited to perform at the inauguration, I would bet good money that they would refuse. 

But when we elect a man who has been married three times, cheated on the majority of his wives and who brags about grabbing woman by the pussy, the Mormon Tabernacle Choir jumps at the opportunity to perform. 

Fucking selective values.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 17:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scientifically possible? Yes. By god? Probably not. Lol perhaps I should have said immaculate conception instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corey Lewandowski actually says Trump presidency means you can say merry Christmas again. Everyone should tweet "happy holidays" @CLewandowski_ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "Lack of mental health treatment is a major crisis. Less than 50% of adults with mental illness received the treatment they needed last year." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mormon Choir's inauguration performance is the height of hypocrisy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With statewide legalization, UMass bans marijuana. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With statewide legalization, UMass bans marijuana. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With statewide legalization, UMass bans marijuana. The same day Massachusetts new marijuana legalization took effect, UMass Vice Chancellor for Student Affairs and Campus Life Enku Gelaye sent a letter to students saying weed is not allowed on campus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police find 55 pounds of fentanyl in traffic stop in Connecticut. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can view a list of Joseph smith's wives [here.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Joseph_Smith's_wives)

In [D C 132](https://www.lds.org/scriptures/dc-testament/dc/132) (part of Mormon scripture), Joseph laid out for church members what he claimed God had given him as the rules regarding polygamy. If a man wanted to take another wife, she must be a virgin and must be vowed to no other man. Joseph smith broke BOTH of those rules, the very rules he claimed God had specifically given him outlined in D C 132. 

If that doesn't help one see that smith was just a horny guy with a very active imagination, I don't know what will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are people so surprised that the Mormon Tabernacle Choir will perform at the pussy grabber's inauguration? Joseph Smith and Trump have a ton in common! They both have had multiple wives, they both have a thing for other men's wives, they're both con men and they both pretend to be Christian! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mormon Tabernacle Choir has accepted an invitation to perform at Donald Trump's inauguration. [Link.](http://www.deseretnews.com/article/865669773/Mormon-Tabernacle-Choir-to-perform-at-Trump-inauguration.html)

For some reason, this seems to have shocked a few people. 

But once you really think about it, Trump and the Mormon Prophet Joseph Smith have a great deal in common!

They have both been married multiple times. 

They both have a thing for other men's wives. Trump bragged about trying to bang a married woman in the Access Hollywood leaked video, and Joseph Smith married women who were already married. Who woulda thunk it?! 

They're both con men who convince poor people to give them money. Trump University, anybody?! 

And they both pretend to be Christian, even though Trump apparently didn't know that Christians refer to it as "2nd Corinthians," not "two Corinthians." [Link.](http://www.npr.org/2016/01/18/463528847/citing-two-corinthians-trump-struggles-to-make-the-sale-to-evangelicals)


The Mormons and Trump are...well...a match made in [Kolob.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kolob) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are people so surprised that the Mormon Tabernacle Choir will perform at the pussy grabber's inauguration? Joseph Smith and Trump have a ton in common! They both have had multiple wives, they both have a thing for other men's wives, they're both con men and they both pretend to be Christian! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Mormon Tabernacle Choir has accepted an invitation to perform at Donald Trump's inauguration. [Link.](http://www.deseretnews.com/article/865669773/Mormon-Tabernacle-Choir-to-perform-at-Trump-inauguration.html)

For some reason, this seems to have shocked a few people. 

But once you really think about it, Trump and the Mormon Prophet Joseph Smith have a great deal in common!

They have both been married multiple times. 

They both have a thing for other men's wives. Trump bragged about trying to bang a married woman in the Access Hollywood leaked video, and Joseph Smith married women who were already married. Who woulda thunk it?! 

They're both con men who convince poor people to give them money. Trump University, anybody?! 

And they both pretend to be Christian, even though Trump apparently didn't know that Christians refer to it as "2nd Corinthians," not "two Corinthians." [Link.](http://www.npr.org/2016/01/18/463528847/citing-two-corinthians-trump-struggles-to-make-the-sale-to-evangelicals)


The Mormons and Trump are...well...a match made in [Kolob.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kolob) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans won't require Rex Tillerson to turn over tax returns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drug overdoses now kill more Americans than guns. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heroin deaths exceeded gun homicides in 2015. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "We have to summon up the courage to acknowledge that we are in a crisis situation and that bold action is needed to save our planet." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Threats, bullying hit family of KC transgender girl on cover of National Geographic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Church facing $12,000 fine for letting homeless people sleep on property. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump voters dont want Trump to get rid of Elizabeth Warrens consumer agency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 15:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> @SenSanders on Twitter: "We face a major opiate addiction crisis. Drug wholesalers like the McKesson Corporation make huge profits pushing addictive painkillers." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 15:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOPs next battle against gay rights : Proposed First Amendment Defense Act will use religious freedom to legalize discrimination. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 15:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since 1985, American states that passed laws permitting medical marijuana use have seen significant reductions in the number of traffic fatalities. On average, these states had lower rates of automobile-related deaths than states without medical marijuana laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 15:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can disagree here, but hear me out. Also, in this post, I didn't mention their non-profit status. You brought that up.

Ask any Mormon, and you'll hear them tell you that the church uses the profits from it's "for profit" arm to spend on humanitarian causes. 

Let's get this straight...the church owns ranches, insurance companies, apartment buildings, tv and radio stations, etc (some of those businesses are worth billions).... and they can only afford to spend $40 million a year on humanitarian aid? 

Those numbers don't make sense to me. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all the hard work you both put into this! It was my honor to get y'all to the front page yesterday!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I've bitched about the Catholics before, too. I don't blast specific religions. Most of them piss me off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And keep on defending your Profit, even if he would be in prison by today's standards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's nothing defensible about saying you would potentially marry a 14 year old "if times were different." The way you worded it doesn't alter what you said. Wow, dude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but 14 year olds are a lot less mature now than they were in 1830. 


Riiiiiiight. Teenagers physically develop slower in 2016 than 1830's. Got it. 

You just admitted that you would marry a 14 year old, bro. Let that sink in for a moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me get this straight: You have no problem with the church asking teenagers to pay 9 grand to **volunteer** for two years, and you're 100% cool with the church spending 1.5 billion on a mall instead of paying for the kids missions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mormons like to go on and on about how "morality isn't relative." 

If it's wrong to fuck a 14 year old in 2016, it was wrong to fuck a 14 year old in 1830-whatever. 

You can't have your cake and eat it, too. If you believe morality is not relative, then whether or not it is legal or what time period it happened in does not influence the morality of what Joseph did. Am I right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  invests wisely to support its humanitarian and missionary efforts.

Really now? Then why do Mormon missionaries pay $7,000-$9,000 to even go on their missions? If the church is spending all that money on the missionaries, why do they pay so much to go? [Link.](http://www.mormonmissionprep.com/preparing-for-a-mission/lds-mission-cost/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't excommunicate Joseph for marrying a 14 year old, so I don't know why you think they'd do it to a current apostle. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'm sure something naughty will come out about one of the apostles eventually. Remember [Ted Haggard?](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ted_Haggard) Maybe it'll be something like that. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fixed! thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The law of man says you have to follow campaign finance laws. The church didn't do that. To their credit, they paid the fine and didn't balk. Good on them for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you don't like facts. I suppose you think the very essays the church released admitting that Joseph liked 14 year old girls are "anti mormon literature" even though they came from the church itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I truly wanted to "grind an Axe" regarding the Mormon Church, I would detail how Joseph smith conned a 14 year old girl into marrying him when he was in his mid thirties by telling her that it would ensure her family a spot in the celestial kingdom, super VIP Mormon Heaven. [1.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Helen_Mar_Kimball#Marriage_to_Joseph_Smith)

Or, I would discuss how Prophet Joseph violated the very rules regarding polygamy that he told the church that God had given to him in D C 132. D C 132 states that if one wants to take a plural wife, she must be a virgin and she must not be vowed to any other man. Joseph smith married women who weren't virgins and who had already been married. [1.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Joseph_Smith's_wives) [2.](https://www.lds.org/scriptures/dc-testament/dc/132)
Joseph smith didn't even follow his own rules! 

How's that for axe grinding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the first to admit that, due to how the church is structured, everything is taught a little different. I've been to wards where it is taught that plural marriage exists in the afterlife, and then I've been to wards where that isn't mentioned at all. 

In the same way, dating and marriage and how to go about the two are taught differently by different local leaders. I've certainly heard that the primary goal in marriage is to find a partner who is temple worthy, but I wouldn't be surprised if other leaders focus more on finding a spouse you actually love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryan has his own account. I'm sure you could find him if you visited r/exmormon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny you mention that. I was told by a set of missionaries that members must be full tithe payers to even use the bishop's storehouses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most missionaries self fund.   [Link.](http://www.mormonmissionprep.com/preparing-for-a-mission/lds-mission-cost/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
