<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6945</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 16:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I was thinking of the nausea and the body load combined with MDA, I think if I do combine them it'll have to be a small dose of LSA. I'll try and do a CWE to try and get rid of as much nausea as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 16:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao why is that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 16:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man :( I really really wanted Clippers v Warriors with both teams at full strength. Even though we don't match up perfectly against them I think it still would have been an awesome series. Now with Paul and Griffin injured the Blazers are favored to win the series and Pauls window to win a chip is closing. 

Hopefully the rest of this series will stay competitive. I've enjoyed it so far, but I really don't want any more superstars to get hurt, and that goes for every team in the playoffs. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone here ever combined LSA with MDA? Is it worth it or should I do them separately? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 08:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title is self explanatory. But I did LSA last Monday and combined it with cannabis as suggested by another redditor and had an amazing time. Yesterday I picked up some MDA that my friends and I are planning on doing for the NFL draft this week. I have enough HBWR seeds for all of us and was thinking of combining the two. 

Would one overpower the other? Or would it be too intense of a high that it wouldn't be worth it? 

Any advice on ratio would be appreciated as well! Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BUG] Split screen players aren't unlocking any collectibles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 03:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddy and I have been playing Hoops for the past couple of hours and he has been unlocking new toppers/decals/car bodies almost every game and I have yet to get anything. We played last night and usually each of us would unlock something once every 3 games or so, but since the new update it's been just him. Anyone else experiencing this?

Xbox One btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's hard to label a band as a sellout because there are some bands that change their sound as they mature. 

If you asked my Uncle he would say Pink Floyd sold out in the after the Wall. The Final Cut, Divison Bell and Momentary Lapse of Reason have songs that are a lot more "radio friendly" than their older stuff. I disagree, but Floyd is also my favorite band and I appreciate everything they've put out. 

There are obvious sell outs like Nickelback, Fall Out Boy and Metallica but my vote goes to Taylor Swift. 

Her first two albums are lyrically great. I don't like country at all but I never minded when Taylor came on the radio. Nowadays it seems that she's straight up Pop music and lost all of her lyrical integrity in favor of cash. 

All power to them though. There are some bands that treat music as art, two that come to mind are Porcupine Tree and Dream Theater. And there are some musicians that are in it for a buck. 

Sometimes I like to ask myself,"If I was in their shoes, would I stay loyal to my fans or would I chase the next check?" I'm honestly worried that I would end up picking the latter. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never listened to U2 but when their album randomly showed up on my phone one day I decided to never listen to them. That was asinine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me start by saying I don't know a lot about the Black Keys. I listen to them a lot but don't know anything about them personally. 

The biggest thing I've noticed with the evolution of The Black Keys is they sounded a lot more raw and soulful in the beginning and their stuff from Brothers on sounds more refined but the songs are less unique. I still love all of their albums, but it got me thinking...does it sound different because they have the resources to explore different sounds within their music? Or is it more if they got commercial success and fame and changed their sound to keep said success and fame?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 22:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WITH NO REGARD FOR HUMAN LIFE  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 02:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think most cars come with the cigarette lighter "button" anymore but if you have one of the "buttons" it'll still work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 22:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's a toss up between:

Deion Sanders- Arguably the GOAT CB for a position we need. 

Barry Sanders- Behind our line he would destroy. It would be fun as hell to watch. It'd also keep a lot of pressure and hits away from Romo. 

Jerry Rice- We need a solid #2 receiver. With Rice we would have Dez fill that hole. Along with Williams and Beasley our WR core would be set. 

Ed Reed- my personal favorite DB of all time. Church is consistent and Jones is shaping up to be good IMO but Wilcox has been shaky as of late. I think Reed and Church with Jones at Nickel would make our secondary a lot better. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 21:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't. I'm just not sure WHEN he was considered a franchise player. Was it right when he was drafted or a few years later?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 08:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess after Emmitt left for Arizona we didn't have a standout franchise guy. However we did have Greg Ellis and Roy Williams and they were both pro bowl players. I'm not sure when Witten would have been considered a franchise player but I would consider him as well. Bledsoe wasn't that bad for us and we've had Romo since then. Along with having TO and now Dez I think we'll be set for a while. 

I'd have to agree with /u/Chibears85 and say that the Bears went the longest without a franchise guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 04:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nail on the head right there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 04:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was rough. Senior year I stopped hanging out with the high school friends all the time and opted to hang out with my older brother and his friends and just had way more fun and we're all still best friends to this day. And I care a lot about how people see me. Even on Reddit. I try to avoid conflict like the plague and I guess that's why I let my old friends walk all over me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 00:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is the state of Indiana eight hours away from Gary Indiana? /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 17:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some backround. In high school I never had a girlfriend, I was one of the "popular" kids but mostly just because I never had a problem getting drugs or alcohol for parties and people just like being around me, I'm a funny guy but I'm very distant emotionally. 

There was a girl that was one of my best friends growing up. We always had multiple classes all throughout middle and high school. We'll call this girl Mary. 

My junior prom I ended up taking a girl that I was completely enamored with. We'll call this girl Emily. 

Basically, prom with Emily was great. We went out to dinner at a nice restaurant and took a limo to prom. We were inseparable all night, took goofy pictures and slow dances and when we finally kissed she didn't leave my side the rest of the night. Instead of going to a post prom party we ended up going back to my house. We loaded up Netflix I made some nachos, packed a bowl and made a couple drinks and we just spent the whole night together. She ended up staying until about 3am and I took her home. I kissed her when we got to her doorstep and told her to text me when she gets up. 

She never did. 

She started acting very strange the rest of the weekend. I didn't think anything of it. I texted her Sunday night asking if something was wrong and she said,"I'm fine, I just don't think we should talk anymore." She basically dropped this bomb on me and telling me she only went to prom with me because she felt bad that nobody else would. One of the greatest nights of my life happened out of pity. 

I went to school the following Monday and met up with my friends to talk about our weekends. My friend Matt gives me a high five and asks me how it went when I took Emily home. I told him what happened and he laughed. "No seriously how was it?" And I broke down and told him everything, showed him the text messages and all. I ended up sitting in the hallway against the lockers with Matt and a few of our other friends. Emily walked by, saw me crying, looked at the friend she was walking with and just started laughing. 

It was the longest day of my life. On the bus home I was talking to Mary and I asked her,"How come everyone else is getting into relationships and I'm not? Is there something wrong with me? Nobody has a problem being friends with me but whenever I want anything more it blows up in my face."

And I'll never forget what she said. One of my best friends of my entire life. 

"subject6945, you're you. Why would anybody want to be with you? Sometimes I even wonder why I'm friends with you." 

Turns out a lot of my high school "friends" felt that way when none of them showed up to my grad party. I found out who my real friends were after graduating. And now, two years later, it still stings. 

But it's okay. I'm okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 07:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vancouver

St Louis

Vegas

Oklahoma City

Portland

Toronto

Ottawa 

Montreal

San Antonio

For my tenth I wanna say Birmingham or Tuscaloosa but I feel like Alabama is strictly CFB. But I'll pick Birmingham regardless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][REDDIT] Whats the subreddit that has stories about the two guys that discuss a topic, one of them is smart and the other one is dumb. It's called like Tim and John or Tim and Phil or something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 02:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan and Iowa State. My uncle went ISU and two of my cousins went to Michigan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See I do that but when I tell people,"I'll let you know" or "Maybe I'll come out" it depends entirely on how drained I am socially and whether or not I get to relax at all beforehand. If it's 5pm and you ask to hang out at 8 or 9pm then the chances are good. If it's 730pm and you want to pick me up at 8pm, I'm either not going out or I'll meet up with you later. I have to mentally prepare myself before going out otherwise im going to have a bad time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 03:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the NCAA Tournament.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 17:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can kick myself in the back of the head when I'm drunk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 05:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me personally:

1) Kareem

2) Jordan

3) Lebron

4) Wilt

5) Oscar Robertson

6) Magic

7) Duncan

8) Bird

9) Olajuwon

10) Russell

11) Shaq

12) Kobe

So 12th. I based my list on who I would personally want to build a team around if they were all hypothetically draft prospects. I like Kobe and he's an all time great but I feel like the 11 I put ahead of him are more valuable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 22:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AFC West. I feel like all of those teams are fun to watch. 

But if it has to be a specific division rivalry game it's gonna be Ravens v Steelers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paging /r/SquaredCircle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 01:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AHHHHH! I LOVE YOU I LOVE YOU I LOVE YOU! Thanks so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][MUSIC VIDEO] It's a white guy rapping in a storage unit or something, throughout the video he destroys things in the storage unit. Details inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 01:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC it's a white rapper in either a storage unit or a shed or the trailer of a semi and he has pictures on the wall and other objects around the scene. At one point he shaves his head or rips his hair out and toward the end of the video he sets the whole set on fire. I watched it one night drinking with my buddies and I've been thinking about it all day. If I can remember any more details I'll post them according. 

Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 05:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone that doesn't follow soccer (sorry I'm American) what is the significance of this? From what I've read, Leicester is a huge Cinderella story right now as they are leading the Premier League but why is it such a shock and also what is the champions league? 

Forgive my ignorance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 03:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't mind Stephen A or Skip that much. The only time I get annoyed is when they get proven wrong by an athlete or another member of the media and take it as a personal attack and get all flustered. 

I can't stand Jamele Hill though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 09:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is kind of surprising. I'm not trying to criticize or poke fun at /r/sports but I feel like there isn't much discussion on this subreddit. I mostly see highlights and breaking news stories with small amounts of comments. I just scrolled through the first 50 posts sorted by Hot and there are only a handful of posts that even crack 100 comments. For a subreddit with 6 million subs that seems extremely low. 

That being said I love this subreddit. I usually check it first thing in the morning and come here for the crazy highlights.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 21:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm one of the guys on the podcast (along with Crimson) and although we aren't one of the more popular podcasts out there we'd like to at least have one or two of ya'll to check it out. We're open to criticism too, maybe some advice from the more popular podcasters on /r/SquaredCircle or ideas for other discussions. 

Thanks in advance for checking it out!

~ Jake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throw it to Terrance Williams and hope he tip toes it in at the sideline.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a product was guaranteed to be as enjoyable as its commercials what products would be the best? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a product was guaranteed to be as enjoyable as its commercials are, what product would be the best and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 00:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 02:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars, exclusively the prequels. And titanic, but only disc one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 08:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a lot of comparisons between Monster Hunter and Dark Souls. As a huge fan of the Souls series do you think I'd enjoy those too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 08:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone that doesn't have a WiiU and is looking to get one soon what games do you recommend? I want to get Mario Maker, Smash and Mario Kart. What are some other ones that I should look into?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 20:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch college football for the rivalries. Every week it seems there's at least one game where the two teams have a history and that makes it all the more fun to watch. Having Harbaugh back at Michigan makes it easier to watch for me too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 09:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a lot of college ball fans don't like him, but I love him. He's been one of the few constants in my life since I was a kid. Yeah he's made some mistakes, and isn't the most successful coach ever and I can see why some would consider him to be overrated...but he'll always be the coach of SU basketball to me. I love Jim Boeheim. He's loved immensely by most everyone in central New York and if you've never had the chance to meet him you are missing out. He loves Syracuse and is incredibly down to earth and I don't know how I'm going to react when he retires. It might result in a lot of tears. 

:(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 01:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did Katt Williams do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 14:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah no. An interesting dialogue system has been a staple of the Fallout games since the beginning. The system in Fallout 4 is like if someone took the system from Mass Effect and poured water on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 05:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arizona: Fitzgerald
Seattle: Sherman
Los Angeles: Donald
San Francisco: Bowman

Chicago: Jeffery
Green Bay: Nelson
Minnesota: Harrison Smith
Detroit: Stafford

Dallas: Church
Philidelphia: Cox
New York: Manning
Washington: Cousins

Atlanta: Julio Jones
New Orleans: Brees
Carolina: Newton
Tampa Bay: Winston

Baltimore: Flacco
Pittsburgh: James Harrison
Cincinatti: Burfict
Cleveland: RG3

New England: Brady
Buffalo: Dareus
New York: Revis
Miami: Suh

Oakland: Mack
San Diego: Gates
Denver: Miller
Kansas City: Houston

Houston: Watt
Indianapolis: Luck
Jacksonville: Bortles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 05:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Northern Iowa out of 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 20:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JJ Watt. Because he's going to go down as one of the greatest defensive players of all time, and I have a hard on for defense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 03:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'M CITRUS-KIN AND YOU'RE TRIGGERING ME RIGHT NOW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 20:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're seriously not going to buy it now because other people get to play it before you do? Holy shit do  you get mad when people in restaurants get their food before you too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 15:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOBODY LOOK! NOBODY LOOK! NOBODY LOOK! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 23:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. Must have missed that when writing this up. Thanks for pointing that out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 22:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem I have with people saying Aikman shouldn't be in the Hall is the fact that they compare him to quarterbacks now. If you actually look at the 90s he was in the top ten for practically every passing statistic, on top of being the QB for a 3 time SB champion Cowboys team and playing in 16 playoff games. His statline for those 16 games:

11-5 320/502 CMP% 63.75 3,849 YDS 23-17 TD-INT

Along with a career playoff passer rating of 88.3, his career playoff numbers are enough to be a good looking 16 game season in today's pass friendly league.

The other thing is the obvious one, the way offenses were run was a lot different. Sure you had guys like Marino, Young, Elway, Favre and Montana putting up crazy stats, part of it is because they are all time greats, but the other part it because teams didn't know how to play against it due to the fact that not a lot of teams were constantly passing the ball. Instead of a handful or so teams in 2016 that primarily run the ball while the rest primarily pass the ball, it was a handful of so teams in the 90's that primarily passed as opposed to running. Aikman had pretty good stats for a team whose offense went through Emmitt Smith around 65% of the time.

My belief is that the Hall of Fame is reserved for players that cannot be ignored when talking about the history of the NFL. Anybody can use the stats argument for almost half of the players in the Hall of Fame, for example:

Art Monk: Sure he played 16 years, but he was only All Pro twice AND isn't even in the top 10 in any WR statistic despite playing for such a long time. You can say he only got in because of his three Super Bowls.

Lynn Swann: He retired with only 336 catches, 5,462 yards and 51 touchdowns. He's not even in the top 100 for any of his statistics let alone top 10. Oh wait, but he won a bunch of rings.

Joe Namath: Didn't even retire with a winning record. Some would say he's only in the Hall because he was "Broadway Joe."

For the record I don't actually believe any of the above players should not be in the hall. The point is, you can't tell the story of the NFL without Broadway Joe and the Jets winning the super bowl. You can't ignore Lynn "Literally Catches Everything" Swann and the Steelers dynasty. You can't ignore Art Monk, who was part of three Redskins super bowl winning teams that won with three different quarterbacks and it didn't matter who was throwing to him, he was going to put up numbers. You can't ignore the QB of the "Triplets," one of if not the most consistently dominant offense of the 90's.

TL;DR If you're going to use Aikmans stats against him as a Hall of Famer, do it to everyone else that played in a different era.

EDIT: Disregard the Art Monk statistic argument. /u/Khalil-Mack has told me that he retired with top five all time stats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More stuff in Freeside and the Strip, mostly Freeside. I understand the limitations on the engine but I wish there were more buildings in Freeside whether they be stores or shops or anything especially when you look at all of the destroyed buildings that are scattered about. Freeside is such a cool place but there isn't anything to keep me from spending any time there. 

The Strip is cool, I enjoy doing the quests for the casinos but there isn't anything keeping me there either. It just seems, idk, bland. Like there's something missing. 

Id rather have Freeside upgraded than the strip, jut because I feel like you can't really sense the tension with the NCR squatters feuding with the Kings or the Settlers because you only see like 10 people walking around, I inderstand that there's mods for it but afaik there aren't any mods to add shops or anything. 

NV is still my favorite game of all time, but there's always sometime to add. That's why I love Nexus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Romo is a top 5 quarterback
- Aikman has every right to be in the Hall of Fame
- Witten is the greatest all around tight end of all time 
- Passing the ball at the end of Super Bowl 49 was the right call
- Winning the Super Bowl this year did nothing to hurt or help Mannings legacy
- Skip Bayless and Stephen A Smith aren't that bad, I feel like they over exaggerate for views but their discussions are some of the best on ESPN (they'll never be as bad as Jamele Hill)
- If people are going to discredit Emmitt Smith for having an amazing offensive line they should discredit Jerry Rice for having Montana and Young
- The early retirements of great players like Megatron and Beast Mode aren't going to have the impact on other retirement decisions that analysts and pundits would have you believe 

Non NFL just because 

- Even if they break the season wins record the 2015-2016 warriors are not the greatest team of all time, not even top 3
- MTSU over MSU is one of if not the greatest upsets in sports history
- People irrationally hate Syracuse University and Jim Boeheim. All I see on sports forums, 4chan and Reddit is that SU and JB are scumbags, pieces of shit, jokes etc etc with no arguments to back them up. They claim Boeheim is a scumbag due to the Fab Melo controversy and the Bernie Fine incident yet those same people will ride the cocks of Rick Petino and Joe Paterno and completely defend Petino and Paterno to the end. They claim Boeheim hasn't accomplished enough in his career and doesn't deserve to be considered one of the greatest coaches of all time but they still hold Tom Izzo to a ridiculously high standard. 
- Pete Rose has no right to ever be in the Hall of Fame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 04:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Warriors and Curry are phenomanal but wouldn't be able to handle not only Jordan's offensive skills but also his and pippens defensive skills. Add in Rodmans rebounding (which he had down to a science) and I don't see the Warriors winning a series. I also think that the more games they play against each other the better Jordan and the Bulls would be able to gameplan. 

10/10 series Bulls. 

As far as a single game goes I think it would be 7/10 Bulls. If Curry and Klay both go off and get hot quickly they could win, but they would also need to play an amazing game while the Bulls don't. 

It'd be a good game either way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 01:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed 13. It's not the best by any margin, but it's still enjoyable. I liked all of the characters and enjoyed using the paradigm system. I'd say it's worth a try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 00:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ravens would hate that rule.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 22:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Week 1 against the Giants. Probably the most heart palpitations I've had in a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 21:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. My friend told me that the zone is different in the NBA because there's a five second rule or something like that? Where the defensive players aren't allowed to stay in one spot for too long. I've had it happen to me in 2k but I've never understood what that's for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 21:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that why the Spurs are usually a contender? They remind of the Patriots in a way due to how there are never any arguments or disagreements in house. And if a star player gets benched (like Duncan last night) they don't throw a fit because it's for the good of the team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 21:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I noticed that last night during the Spurs game. They never had the same guys matched up on the same guys every play (play? Are they called plays? Possessions maybe?) and it seemed to work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 19:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fallout 3: The first time I left the Vault and realized how big the game was. Close second is tranquility lane. 

New Vegas: Honestly? The first time I beat New Vegas  + all the companion quests + had all of the factions either idolized or vilified and watching the ending slideshows. It was so cool being able to see how you affected the Mojave. 

Fallout 4: Probably going through the memory den. Kellogg is my favorite non companion so it was cool seeing his back story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a casual basketball fan, what exactly is a good defense? And what are the differences between the college and professional game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 12:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgive my ignorance but as a a casual fan that pays more attention to college than professional what exactly is good defense? And I mean in basketball in general. I'm an SU fan so the only defense I can recognize is the zone. What makes the Spurs D so great and what are the differences between pro and college defense? Or even between the two games in general? I see a lot of people praising the Spurs D this year and I don't know what I'm supposed to be looking for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 09:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 09:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy

http://www.xnxx.com/video17492031/katie_morgan_blonder_real_estate_slut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 14:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any reason why it stopped?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 14:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That should be interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 14:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally just laughed out loud. Lmao  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any storylines or rivalries to watch for the second round? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 12:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of how Dayton vs Syracuse was an interesting matchup due to Dayton knocking Syracuse out last time SU was in the tourney. Are there any teams that are playing each other with history of playing in the tournament? I know Kentucky and Indiana is one of them. Two powerhouses that are playing against each other. What other ones should we watch for/pay attention to for the second round?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 15:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the day after the 6OT game against Uconn we ended up watching it again in class. Ended up doing nothing but watching SU all day. Good times. :') </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 08:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randy Moss. I liked Greg Ellis but I would have much rather had one of the best receivers of all time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 20:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 76

Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 18:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly makes them so different? I don't know much about modding. I know how to mod my games but I don't know how they work or how they're made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 18:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true as well. I don't see any graphic enhancements coming to console.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 17:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, and this is just my guess, I don't see the modding community being that large for the console versions. However, I do think that the mods that are released for consoles are going to be polished. I think it'll be more quality rather than quantity. 

That's not saying that the PC mods are quality, because they are. I just don't see the consoles having as much as a selection. 

EDIT: I could be wrong though, and I will eat my words if I am. But I haven't heard anything as far as modding for the console versions, how it's going to be installed and how they're going to be supported.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 22:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use the Rebel Armor from nexusmods. Sometimes I switch to the NCR Veteran Ranger armor. I really don't like using power armor in Fallout. I think it looks kinda stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 16:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My choice was Gray Fox. I personally wouldn't play as Liquid, I never found him to be too interesting. And you play as Big Boss. In 3 different games :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 13:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't played the PO games in awhile so that name took me back. Interesting choice!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 13:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be AWESOME!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ALL GAME SPOILERS] If you could play as any villain instead of Snake in any Metal Gear game of your choosing, who would it be, which game would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 12:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if the title is a bit hard to understand, it took me a few minutes to think of how to phrase it. 

I have two choices. 

I'd like to go through MGS1 as Vamp (the version from MGS4). He's one of my favorite characters in the series and I think it would be fun to go through Shadow Moses as a nigh immortal fast striking knife wizard. 

The other one I would like is to play as Gray Fox through MGS4. I would like to see him and Cyborg Raiden go all out against the Gekko and Vamp. Plus you would start out with Stealth call and I feel he would have a lot of interesting philosophical monologues. 

What do you guys think? What villains would you like to play as?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 19:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This worked, thank you! Just as you said it was reading my 3D Mark folder as my steam apps folder. I moved my Fallout 4 folder back to my HDD, I didn't even realize it was on my SSD. Computer is running way better now. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 14:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgive me for my ignorance but where exactly does Hayward rank among CBs in the league? I honestly haven't seen him play much and the only CB from Green Bay that j recognize is Shields.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 14:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Thanks for the quick response. I'll try this and see what happens. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, 3DMark is taking up 74 GB on my computer, is that normal? Can I delete it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 14:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently got a notification that my SSD is full. I went to check what the largest file is and it says it is 3DMark 11. From my understanding it is a benchmark software, should it be taking up that much space? Can I uninstall it without any issues? I don't think I've ever used this software before so I don't have any problem with deleting it if I have to. 

This is my first time posting on here so if I need to add any other information I will. Thanks for the help!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 19:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat? I was just playing it today and it was working completely fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 19:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Romo v Manning shootout a few years ago. I still watch that one every now and then even though we lost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 18:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only bugs that I've encountered in my most recent playthrough are :

the Covenant bug where you can't do the quest, which sucks because that was one of my favorites. 

Sturges won't talk to me at all. I finished the minutemen quest line and I have no idea why he won't talk to me. My character says "Sturges" and he just replies "Oh yeah?" 

Dogmeat disappeared from my game and I had to spawn him back in. He was in Sanctuary and I sent him to the Castle. After a few IRL hours I decided to swap Piper for him and I couldn't find him. So I slept for 24 hours in game and he stil wasn't there. So I did the player.moveto command and it crashed my game. Luckily he didn't have anything on him so it wasn't a big deal to spawn another one but it was annoying. 

I think it might be because of the mods I have but even then only having 3 bugs isn't too bad. Especially compared to Skyrim or NV or 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 12:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the Pats lose both games to the Bills but still go 14-2. 

Stupid sexy Brady. Stupid sexy Gisele...who kinda looks like a dude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 11:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel so inferior :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 10:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What!? You can have your own empire? I've pumped almost 12 hours into my character and I'm still just a cavalry dude taking orders from the king of Rhodoks. How far in do you get your own empire?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 14:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dee Reynolds isn't THAT bad looking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a question about Logitech Bluetooth mice dongles and connectivity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 06:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was googling for an answer to this question for about a half hour earlier and I couldn't find a definitive answer. I've been using an Xbox one controller with the dongle as a Gamepad for the past few months but today I sold my xbox one and controller for spare cash. I use a Gamepad 90% of the time when I play, it's just comfier for me. Anyway my question is, is it possible to use a Logitech mouse Bluetooth dongle to connect to other Bluetooth devices? I have a PS4 controller and a micro USB cord that is long enough to suffice but I would much rather use it wirelessly. Is that possible or do I need to get a PS4 specific dongle? 

The dongle in question is this one 
https://imgur.com/a/2kAIu

It's for the Logitech M510.

If this won't work what do you guys recommend for Bluetooth dongles?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 02:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh I think some of them are funny. Specifically Tom Cruise and Die Hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 05:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On top of what the other poster said, this video can also help explain what video gamers believe is wrong with Molyneux. 

https://youtu.be/lGo63oAEN20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 00:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can totally understand that. I'm sure I'm not going to convince you to change your mind on the matter, all I want to do is have you look at it differently and apply the expectations you hold for Troy being in the hall to everybody else. 

Another way I guess you could look at it is, Troy is in the Hall because of his rings and being the face and voice of the most popular football franchise for ten years. He's not one of the best QBs all time, but he didn't have to be. 

I have to ask though, using your statistic based argument, who else do you believe shouldn't be in the hall? There's no way Aikman is the only one. 

EDIT: Some wording and punctuation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 15:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would Insurgency be considered a successful indie MP game?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 14:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Easily Vault 108. 

http://youtu.be/hHfZjS4P4Ws </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 14:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem I have with people saying Aikman shouldn't be in the Hall is the fact that they compare him to quarterbacks now. If you actually look at the 90s he was in the top ten for practically every passing statistic, on top of being the QB for a 3 time SB champion Cowboys team and playing in 16 playoff games. His statline for those 16 games:

11-5 320/502 CMP% 63.75 3,849 YDS 23-17 TD-INT 

Along with a career playoff passer rating of 88.3, his career playoff numbers are enough to be a good looking 16 game season in today's pass friendly league. 

The other thing is the obvious one, the way offenses were run was a lot different. Sure you had guys like Marino, Young, Elway, Favre and Montana putting up crazy stats, part of it is because they are all time greats, but the other part it because teams didn't know how to play against it due to the fact that not a lot of teams were constantly passing the ball. Instead of a handful or so teams in 2016 that primarily run the ball while the rest primarily pass the ball, it was a handful of so teams in the 90's that primarily passed as opposed to running. Aikman had pretty good stats for a team whose offense went through Emmitt Smith around 65% of the time. 

My belief is that the Hall of Fame is reserved for players that cannot be ignored when talking about the history of the NFL. Anybody can use the stats argument for almost half of the players in the Hall of Fame, for example:

Art Monk: Sure he played 16 years, but he was only All Pro twice AND isn't even in the top 10 in any WR statistic despite playing for such a long time. You can say he only got in because of his three Super Bowls. 

Lynn Swann: He retired with only 336 catches, 5,462 yards and 51 touchdowns. He's not even in the top 100 for any of his statistics let alone top 10. Oh wait, but he won a bunch of rings. 

Joe Namath: Didn't even retire with a winning record. Some would say he's only in the Hall because he was "Broadway Joe." 

For the record I don't actually believe any of the above players should not be in the hall. The point is, you can't tell the story of the NFL without Broadway Joe and the Jets winning the super bowl. You can't ignore Lynn "Literally Catches Everything" Swann and the Steelers dynasty. You can't ignore Art Monk, who was part of three Redskins super bowl winning teams that won with three different quarterbacks and it didn't matter who was throwing to him, he was going to put up numbers. You can't ignore the QB of the "Triplets," one of if not the most consistently dominant offense of the 90's. 

TL;DR  If you're going to use Aikmans stats against him as a Hall of Famer, do it to everyone else that played in a different era.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 23:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Jimmy Carr.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 12:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOD DAMMIT IS NOWHERE SAFE FROM MANNINGFACE!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Batman has to defend Gotham against these powerful foes, what can he do to win? (Plus some other stuff) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 09:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could possibly be considered a spite post, but I recently got into an argument with my friend over how powerful Batman really is. Let's have five separate types of challenges:

The first challenge will consist of Batman having to defend Gotham City from the characters I post below, individually mind you, not all at once. And by defend I mean that he'll have all of his assets in Gotham to support him in the fight such as Nightwing for backup, the Batmobile and Alfred. He'll also have a week to prepare for the character to get to Gotham. 

The second is the same as above but Batman does not have time to prepare. 

The third challenge will consist of just one on one fights, the arena will be Central Park.

The fourth challenge is the same as above but Batman is bloodlusted. 

The fifth challenge is the same as above but both Batman and his opponent are bloodlusted. 

I don't know too much about Batman. The only version I really followed was Batman Beyond. But I've also played the Arkham games and have seen Batman Begins, Dark Knight and Dark Knight Rises, so I guess for the gauntlet you can use either of those. 

Also if a fight is too unfair feel free to explain what he would have to do to make it 5/10. Again, I honestly don't know much about Batman so this will help me out a bit while also hopefully being a good discussion. 

Mind you, the friend in question thinks that Batman has the capabilities to defeat all of these characters. 

R1 Dr Doom

R2 Sentry

R3 Death Seed Sentry

R4 Void Sentry

R5 Thanos

R6 Thanos with Infinity Gauntlet

R7 Dr Manhatten

R8 Silver Surfer

R9 Starving Galactus

R10 Well Fed Galactus
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 06:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be possible If the radiation in Metro mixed with the fungus from last of us produced the mutants seen in Metro. But in the Last of Us the fungus is only seen to affect humans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 20:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but it's a Final Fantasy game. Those games are usually linear anyway. There's only one main quest throughout the whole game and only one ending. The only difference is the side quests/activities in each game. Either way I quite liked 13. People that complain about 13 being linear should go back and play X.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 23:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in central New York so I'm just gonna be getting Ice types.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 07:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a huge NBA fan so I'm not sure if my opinion really matters but Steph reminds me of Russell Wilson of the Seahawks. Polite, religious and became a household name after being originally as an alright player. I like Steph. I like watching him play. My two favorite players to watch when I was a kid  were Nash and AI and watching Steph makes me feel like a kid again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 14:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romo and the Cowboys vs Brett Favre and the Vikings. He was manhandled all game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 14:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, Murray in an Eagles jersey. He was one of my favorites on the team. I remember when he first started getting a lot of touches and knew he was gonna be really good for us. Then he had that amazing OPOY award winning season and then he was gone. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 07:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's the last two movies I've watched it be Happy Gilmore and Happy Gilmore. If it has to be two different movies it would be Happy Gilmore and Little Nicky. So it would basically be Little Nicky playing golf to get Cassius and Adrian back to Hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 01:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did this when I saw them in Buffalo this year. They also had the Trailer Park Boys, Peter Dinklage and a bunch of other celebs during Roll the Bones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is your favorite game related YouTuber to watch and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 01:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
