<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9743</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions about studying abroad in South Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 15:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend and I are planning to study abroad in South Korea next Spring semester, so in about a year. Last night she messaged me in a panic, saying that she had been reading up on a couple of things. 

First of all, she is concerned about the laws there. She has said to me that many of the laws there are similar to in the U.S (where we both live) but there are bound to be some differences. One thing she is worried about is the legality of her birth control. Is birth control legal there, and what other laws should we know about that are different from in the U.S?

Second, she was telling me that you need to prove that you have a large sum of money in order to get a visa. I'm not quite sure what type of visa she's talking about, be it student or work, but is that true?

Next, she is worried about Japanese Encephalitis. How prominent is that there, should we be worried? She said that it is advised to carry bug spray, but is there anything else we can do about it?

Finally, she read somewhere that the bird flu is still a major problem there. She advised that we keep away from open air markets (which I was planning to do anyway because I'm a very picky eater.) Is bird flu really that big of a problem there? Should we stay away from anything else other than open air markets?

Those are the things she voiced to me, if there is any other advice you may have about studying abroud please let me know :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 15:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked the movie you should read the book or the manga. Each death is depicted in a way that a single movie could never do, and each character has a story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 15:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had more than one this season. This past episode, as well as an Evil Dead episode. I think there might be one more but I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 16:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boss was there, too. He said that Glenn is a dick in real life as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 04:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Numa numa, cockmongler, Don Hertzfeldt's Rejected Cartoons, Badger badger badger, meatspin...

Edit: [Ultimate Showdown](http://youtu.be/WiRH47J_zuI) and the Llama song as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 04:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it depends on the environment the high school is in. I went to a middle-class suburban high school and it was a nightmare. All the cliche tanned white girls in Ugg boots and yoga pants were spitting images of Regina George. As a quiet, short, pale girl I stood out, even though I tried my hardest to fade into the background.

My freshman year I was in AP Bio (which was usually reserved for sophomores and juniors) and one of the sophomores didn't like me all that much. I don't know why, I've been told many reasons. (My eyes are "mean," I'm too quiet, I'm too different, so on...) She and her friends sort of rallied together to hate me. I would get hate messages on Myspace and harassed in school. I remember dissecting frogs in the Bio class and the leader of their group throwing frog parts at me. 

One day I was unable to sit at my regular table at lunch because somebody else was there, so I sat at an empty one. As fate would have it, it was "her" table. She threw a fit and sat at the table directly next to me. I was sitting with my older sister and one other friend, eating a pretzel and trying to ignore her. But of course, she was making rude comments quite loudly, even over the noise of the cafe. I was used to her comments about me, but when she started to attack my sister I flipped. I had a mouth full of pretzel and spit it at her face. We were both escorted out of the cafeteria, the whole place was clapping. I'm still not sure if they were clapping because I spit at her or because I was in trouble...

Of course, me standing up to her with my mouth didn't really help the situation. They took the entire thing to the internet, telling me day and night to kill myself. I would respond with typical "high school" things, like telling them to get fucked by a big dildo. (That comment actually got me suspended, when their encouraging me to kill myself did nothing to them.) Once I learned that the school would rather punish me to maintain the status quo than actually stand up for me I fell into a depression. I did eventually attempt suicide and ended up in the hospital for the last month of my sophomore year. After that, I dropped out of school. (No worries though, I went to tutoring and then an alternative school so I graduated on time.)

I still see some of these girls around, although one died soon after. I can't say I mourned her death, I just wish she had lived a bit longer to understand the effect her actions had on others.

**tl;dr:** my high school experience was pretty bad for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 01:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoshi no Yakata is a good one with multiple (but related) stories, all heavily include BSDM.

Undergrand Hotel is another one of my favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Original Image](http://www.wallpapersdb.org/wallpapers/nature/tree_on_the_meadow_1920x1080.jpg)

[Context](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/19n00s/if_you_were_task_to_redesign_the_human_body_what/c8pinlw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Telekinesis [1920x1080] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 04:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 05:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Return the slab. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 04:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. It took me a couple of times to understand why it made me get the feels. I always cry at the last line, without fail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 20:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In HTML you use a "/" to close or end something.

If you want bold you do  bold  text  /bold .

Saying /thread essentially means end thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 04:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 20, but I've been very doubtful towards theism for as long as I can remember. My mother sent me to Sunday school when I was a child but I got kicked out of multiple classes. (The rebellious atheist stage is great when you get it out of the way at a young age.) My mother said she would accept me being any religion (or lack thereof) if I completed my Confirmation in the Catholic church. To get her off my back I sat through the classes with my mouth shut and went through with the ceremony. After that I renounced any connection to the Catholic church. I was still nervous about calling myself an atheist due to the "what ifs," but then I just said "fuck it." 

My father was a lot more accepting, he renounced his religion in 2001 after the towers fell. He said that no world with a god would allow that. I'm glad that he came out as an atheist, because he convinced my mother to stop subjecting my siblings and I to church every weekend. I haven't been to a Sunday mass (other than my grandfathers funeral, out of respect) since 2001. He says that my only duty as an atheist is to continue my lineage. That's lot less pressure than preserving my soul or saving another.

Whether you find atheism earlier in life or later, it's still a journey. Yes, in the beginning it's scary, especially if you've lived your life with the safety net of religion, but the beauty of a life free of that burden is truly amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father lost his little brother to Neuroblastoma. Tore his whole family apart, it's still haunting to see the picture of the boy I never met in my grandparents house. RIP to Uncle Charlie and little Jackson, and get well soon to the children dealing with it now. Have fun at Disney.

edit: thank you random stranger for the gold :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 04:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds about right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 03:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I look at a digital clock and try to guess exactly when the time will change.

I also like to count things (tiles, steps, books, etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 03:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A puppet that can no longer be used is mere garbage. This puppet's role has just ended..."

-Majora's Mask

**EDIT:** wording

[Sauce](http://youtu.be/1IsIB5L1emg?t=6m29s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 02:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's this girl I knew in high school who told me that she had a twin sister. Nothing wrong with that. She then said her twin sister lived in 10 states away. Still plausible. She then claimed that her twin sister had the same name as her, only spelled slightly differently. Getting a little odd at this point. She *then* told me that her twin sister was cryogenically frozen at birth and then "defrosted" 5 years later, so her twin sister is technically 5 years younger than her.

She also claimed that Jack Skellington was her father and Robert Pattinson was her cousin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 07:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange Circus is a good revenge movie, as well as Death Bell, Sick Nurses, and Reunion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 05:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why?](http://collider.com/wp-content/image-base/Movies/M/MacGruber/Slices/slice_macgruber_01.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 04:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firetruck was firefuck. Eyebrows were eyebrowns. L, M, N, O, P was all one letter: ELEMENOPEE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 04:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I got a less NSFW cat face...](http://imgur.com/SongO) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 04:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cosplay community is extremely judgmental and bigoted. 

If you are cosplaying a character that has light skin, you better not have dark skin! If you are cosplaying a thin girl, you better not be overweight! It is a sin to use your real hair! If your costumes are not hand-made then you are a fake! Your props must be as accurate as possible! 

People in the cosplay community seem to forget they we all started to have fun with it. There's nothing wrong if a black person wants to cosplay a fair skinned person, and there's nothing wrong with a heavier person cosplaying a skinny person. If you don't like their cosplay, don't look at it. Telling them to kill themselves over a fucking costume is pathetic. You are not any better than them for having a better costume. I'd much rather be friends with a cosplayer who does it for the love of that character rather than an elitist douche.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 21:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The right to bear arms for manatees with bear arms.](http://i.imgur.com/IswVqsK.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 04:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea what's going on with the judges. The moth was probably one of the worst things I've seen on this show so far. Not only that, but Megan was the other half of the failing duo last week. I can't see why she is still on the show. Plus, they said that the winner wasn't really the winner because he didn't incorporate the photo elements? I've seen the judges on FaceOff give the win to people who haven't met the needs of the challenge but made a kick ass makeup plenty of times. What was different this time? I'm really not too pleased with this season.

As for the question between solo and partner, it's really hard. In solo we're able to see their creative abilities as well as execution come to light. They also have nobody to blame for their shortcomings. In a partner challenge, they can always throw the other person under the bus. Partner challenges are usually a hit or miss for me. In order to work well together they have to make it flow. You shouldn't be able to tell who did what part of the makeup. When collaborations are good, they are *good*, but when they are bad, they are **bad**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 07:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found the video interesting. Japan is the least racially diverse of all first world countries, so it's probably expected that Japanese students don't notice racism. If you're not the target, you don't usually pay attention to it. Other countries that are far more diverse notice a lot more racism due to clashing issues and mixing of cultures. As for the discrimination portion due to economic background/geographical location, that happens in every country. I know people in the U.S who hate southerners because they are seen as "stupid" and "inbred."
 
It's always difficult for a culture to accept that they have problems like this, especially very proud cultures. Even if you say something that is so blatantly obvious, there will still be people there to oppose you. It took the U.S longer than we'd like to admit to acknowledge our rampant racism, and we're still working on it. It's clear that not all citizens of Japan are blind to the discrimination, but it takes time to change. Keep trying to educate those who will listen, most of the time those who won't aren't worth your time anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 15:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bummer alert: [everybody in this picture is dead.](/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 15:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skinny guys are the best, though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 05:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember he was in one of the original commercials when they switched from "put a smile on" to "I'm lovin' it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 00:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of technique and execution I love Zelo from B.A.P. He goes so quickly and it literally blows my mind. As for writing, I'm quite partial to the raps the T.O.P writes. He also has that deep voice that's perfect for rapping, flows like chocolate. Zico of Block B is another male favorite, just due to is general confidence and wow factor. If these three somehow fused together, I would probably explode of happiness. (That and the sex appeal would the through the roof.)

As for female rappers, Amber of f(x) is a really good one. Lim of the Wonder Girls did an amazing rap in Act Cool which really gained my respect. Of course CL has to be another one of my female favorites. 

I can't really pick a ultimate favorite of any gender, but these are my general top picks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 05:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to play devil's advocate for a moment. Anybody who gets into a car with a drunk driver is an enabler. He didn't have to get into that car.

Edit: that being said, it's no excuse for driving drunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 17:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I thought still having 1 baby tooth at 20 was bad. Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 17:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Number 18.](http://www.ericharshbarger.org/lego/faq.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 16:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once we're all dead and gone, aliens are going to have a blast figuring these out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 01:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What is this, a wallpaper for ants?](http://cdn2.sbnation.com/imported_assets/275870/zoolander-school1.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 19:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shopping for clothes - if you aren't a Korean size, good luck


Finally, being short and tiny will pay off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 17:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Say I'm not the only one.](http://www.superduperinc.com/images/widerLayout/product/zoom/ot2443.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 23:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dog from the instance that I am referring to died from Waggin' Train dog treats. [Here](http://dogaware.com/recall.html) are some other treats/foods that have been recalled due to them causing illness/death in animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 05:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading on reddit a couple months back that some pet foods and snacks from China have been a major cause in the drastic increase of liver failure / other complications in dogs.

Shortly after that story, my 7 year old Aussie began to get sick with similar symptoms. Luckily he went to the vet in time. He is now on a special diet to help, but the vet said his life expectancy has likely been shortened by a couple years. Since then I have been very careful about what I feed him and my other dogs. I urge other pet owners to do the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've had the same piercing setup for years, should I add some, switch some out, or lose them as a whole? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 05:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 04:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pierced asians are always a plus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 00:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summer looks like the road in the beginning of Spirited Away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 23:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I swore never to read again after 'To Kill a Mockingbird' gave me no useful advice on killing mockingbirds. It did teach me not to judge a man based on the color of his skin, but what good does that do me?](http://www.parade.com/images/-v4/health-and-food/2010/0523/spotlight-homer.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
