<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3078</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the spiders here are small and not that noticeable most of the time, we do see more house spiders in Autumn as they look for somewhere warm and they can get pretty big, but only really on a par with what exists in New Zealand from what I understand.

We don't really do big, scary looking animals or insects generally.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't buy one.. I have a swift and at 5" is about as big as I'd like, a lot of the decent handsets out there are huge at the moment, if I want a larger screen I'll either grab my tablet or my laptop.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually that's the common misconception. Modern developed western states are geared around welfare and services, that's where most of internal economic activity happens. You will always have a very high service sector in those countries, because that is what makes them what they are.

What you mean is that people spend more money on services, because people use a lot of services, whether that is getting your hair cut, your car fixed or eating in a restaurant..  Right.. But that proportion is similar between developed countries the UK doesn't have significantly lower manufacturing output when compared to comparable states as a result..

But when you talk about economy sectors in country comparisons you talk about producing stuff that is also at least potentially of interest to people abroad - wiping a grandmas ass in a retirement home isn't. It is economic activity ON TOP of what happens to make life in those countries work.

So for the UK, it happens to be very, very good at exporting financial and business services, as well as exporting goods. I mean the UK, as well as being in the top 7 globally for manufacturing output in terms of value, is also a top 10 exporting country.. 

Now if you said that the number of people employed in manufacturing had fallen you'd be absolutely right, it's fallen massively even whilst exports and production has risen, the same goes for agriculture by the way... 

In this context a difference of 9% of the total GDP is actually HUGE.

You mean between Germany and the UK right? What about Italy, with services at 75% of GDP, or the Netherlands at 80%...  Germany is a massive manufacturer and exporting country, it is the exception not the norm and the UK has a services sector only 9% larger, but of course the UK also exports far more in the way of services than Germany.

In any case, the idea that the UK *'has very little in terms of a producing goods economy left'* is bizarre under both assumptions, the UK went through a period of massively reducing it's heavy industry, which was frankly very damaging in my view, but it didn't get rid of manufacturing, it changed what it manufactured.  

For example,  why produce steel when Germany subsidised it's industry and produces it much more cheaply, same with China.. At that point you can buy steel to produce finished goods (cheaper inputs, no need to subsidise heavy industry and compete with China or Germany on steel exports..) or focus on specialist metallurgy instead (do something that China and Germany can't do - see the UKs unique position in the supply of materials to things like the US nuclear submarine programme..).   

The UK absolutely still produces goods and exports them, it produces a lot of goods for both export and domestic consumption, the idea that the UK doesn't produce anything anymore is a misconception based on a couple of strands (the reduction in heavy industry and the loss of mass employers through both automation and modernisation as well as competition) that don't actually lead to that as a conclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to the extent of the UK.

Services make up 70% of the German economy, 79% of the US economy and 78% of the UK economy.. So yeah, to about the same extent. 

It has very little in terms of a producing goods economy left.

The UK has the 7th largest industrial sector globally by Nominal GDP. It produces quite a lot of goods, more high value and high tech than low tech and cheap, but that's not the same has not producing goods many goods.

That's should be common knowledge since it has been reported so many times.

It's a common misconception..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering the UK economy is largely based on services that's hardly surprising.

Most large developed countries have economies largely based on services, including Germany and the US...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.. I've had some weird substitutions from Tesco in the past I was offered a vanilla airwick air freshener thingy instead of vanilla essence (you know, for baking with) once and the most insulting one was a substitution of Hendersons relish for some sort of American style burger relish... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I agree with you, I still think that outside of France and some EE countries, a lot of EU members see a common EU Army as an opportunity to reduce defence expenditure, rather than increasing capabilities (and will often claim to be able to do both..).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I'd assume you'd have no problems if you 'nicked' the bottles to deal with an acid attack...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That did stand out a little.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Eta to Stockholm: Is terror more of a threat to Europe than before? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egypt Coptic church blast 'kills at least 21' in Nile Delta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London acid attack: Toxic substance thrown over two-year-old boy and parents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London acid attack: Toxic substance thrown over two-year-old boy and parents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salmond says May's indyref2 position will 'crumble' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 11:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question. You could argue that he wants to see EU citizenship become something independent of national citizenship, it might bolster the notion of an European identity grounded in the EU rather than as an add on to national identities. You could also argue that he is trying to use it as a lever in the context of the negotiations with the UK, there are a lot of people in the UK who would likely consider taking it up (probably depending on cost..). If you were being really cynical you might argue that he is looking to set a precedent in disconnecting national citizenship from the EU one, giving the EU a tool to allow people outside the EU to associate with it, even if their country more generally isn't looking to EU membership (so say Switzerland or Norway).

Or it might simply be the stated intention, he's looking for a way for UK citizens who want to retain EU citizenship a route to do so, or get close, presumably with some more restrictive rights and some sort of associated cost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's essentially a set of rights that up until now have only existed because the country you are a national of is a member of a club and pays it's fees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, this isn't so much fake news as it is a case of a misleading headline and a somewhat slanted (albeit mostly accurate) article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well no, because the EU isn't a country and as a result EU citizenship isn't citizenship in the same way that national citizenship is, it doesn't exist in isolation (if you give up your German nationality you don't get to keep your EU citizenship either), it's essentially a set of rights that only apply outside of your own country, guaranteed by treaty.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two problems it raises are firstly, what does EU membership actually mean (at the moment it's tied to state membership and means that you have access to things like free movement) and what does it mean if you can have it outside of your country participating in the EU, and secondly, if it is in any way useful, why on earth would citizens who can get most of what they see as benefits of the EU not want to get that rather than state membership (which comes with costs and responsibilities..).

The answer is probably that this is a bit of a pipe dream, or that it'll mean very little in the end, but it's interesting nonetheless that it is being pushed as it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As warplanes return to scene of sarin attack, Trump defends missile launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As warplanes return to scene of sarin attack, Trump defends missile launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European Parliaments chief Brexit negotiator demands Theresa May back Britons who want to keep EU citizenship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm off bike shopping (and looking at ebay etc.. at the moment) for (and with..) my eldest over the next week so I'll keep an eye out and let you know if I see anything.  A photo or any distinguishing marks/features would be helpful though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, the article even makes that clear (never mind they never arrived..), 
In the case of sodium fluoride it's incredibly common and added to drinking water and used in the production of a huge number of dental products, amongst other things.  As to potassium fluoride, it's used as a catalyst in the manufacture of plastics as well as pesticides and insecticides. That said, they are dual use, so I suppose if you suspect the customer, or someone else in the importing country will divert the chemicals for use in weapons, you do have a responsibility to prevent them being exported. Which seems to be what the UK did..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It all depends on whether or not a core group of countries can be found. If not, then not. There's little use in forcing people, it never works out in the long term.

You can't do it full stop frankly, force to push federalisation would do more to essentially destroy the political project than anything else.

Either they can be convinced in time, or we'll return to nation states without common rules.

Indeed, and to do that you have to have a clear aim and actually make the argument. At the moment (well, we saw it with the remain argument in the referendum in the UK) very few people will make an argument for eventual federalisation, even if it can be shown to provide benefits, because there isn't that EU identity, or common drive for it.

I still fully believe that even France and Germany cannot hope to seriously compete alone in the future. Neither economically, nor military-wise. Regional powers, maybe, but that's about it. In the end it all boils down to answering to greater powers and maybe being the regional hegemon serving their interests.

To be fair, the EU isn't going to be much more than a regional power either, even a federal state, especially one in which Germany has any stay in establishing, is going to shy away from seeking superpower status.  Germany and France can both be significant players on the global stage for the next century without much change, beyond that who knows (I mean if you look at the last few decades you had the Soviet Union collapse, the rise of China etc..).

Being a nuclear power is useless if greater powers decide the rules of the economy, the financial market, the stability of your neighbourhood, etc. What use was France's military in stopping the financial crisis which was due to US-led deregulation? What use was Germany's pacifism in stopping the Iraq invasion and the migrant crisis?

The point on making the rules is that it isn't something that can simply be imposed (Again, look at China..), it is something that works at the global level, very tentatively, through intergovernmental work.  Arguably Germany and France would have more individual say outside of the EU than having the EU speak for it.

As another example, look at military R D. The recent push for more EU-financed military R D also comes from the realisation that powers like the US simply have more resources they can focus to gain a technological edge.

The realisation that the US has been spending a huge amount of money for a long time and so has both breadth and depth when it comes to military capabilities and technology should also be a thing.. I mean look at Russia, it is essentially still relying on the spending and infrastructure provision it put in place as a superpower, if it didn't have that it'd be fairly insignificant militarily.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe in federalism. I view it as an added layer of complexity to governance compared to the nation-state model that has no reason to be there except to allow the leaders to have more influence on the world stage.

The problem is that for the EU to actually succeed as a political project, something akin to federalisation, certainly closer integration, is probably required.  That essentially provides something of a stark choice if you are asked whether you want to be part of the EU or not, do you want to be part of something that doesn't quite work and has to essentially fudge an extra layer on top of (or really at the same level of) national governments, or are you happy to go down the federalisation route which closes quite a lot of options and would create a formal 'top' layer.  Lots of people here seem happy with the latter, personally I think it's a great argument for those who don't want to be part of a federal EU to look at other options outside of it..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, of course. In fact I'd argue that Reddit is actually a pretty excellent echo chamber in part because it doesn't totally exclude opposing views and in part because you can find (and then point at..) corners of it that are 'different', giving more of a feeling of diversity of opinion and more credibility to the affirmations you do get. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I agree, which is why I am a EU federalist.  However, as a more pragmatic approach I do view integration of a core group as essential. I don't see it as too problematic, for one simple reason: the EU as it is now cannot endure. We either retreat back into EEC territory or push forward. If

One of those silly things really, I absolutely can see the benefits of federalism for the EU, in the very least of closer integration, but absolutely don't think the UK should be a part of that and I certainly don't want it for the UK, so it becomes an argument for leaving (ever closer union and integration is how you solve some of the EU's problems, if you don't want ever closer union, membership itself is problematic..). I do wonder what other countries would look at that in the same way, and what that leaves in terms of the core EU.  On balance it may still be more positive than not though..

 the EU as it is breaks down, it might even herald a core group to establish a more integrated, second attempt.

That's a more interesting question, I sort of wonder whether the big drivers that led to what is now the EU are still present enough to make that viable.  The argument that 'no single EU country can make it alone on the world stage', doesn't really apply to France especially or Germany either, there are undoubtedly benefits of union, but if you were starting from scratch, I wonder how many of them would actually be included..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is and will likely remain one of the fundamentally different perceptions between (and I'm generalising a lot here but..) the likes of the US, UK, Canada etc.. and some of the core EU countries.  We both see the impact of the EU and NATO vary differently in terms of ensuring peace and slowly, that is morphing into the view that the EU would be better off without NATO.

You could argue that this then starts to mirror the notion that the EU fracturing is a threat to peace and stability (That is to say that NATO fracturing is absolutely a potential threat to peace and stability) but with people pushing for it anyway, largely because they see the argument as invalid and have their own theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, it's about who chooses to participate, which in turn is driven by how people perceive that their input will be taken and responded to.  As you point out, the mods trying to force a particular agenda one way or the other through censorship or similar simply won't achieve much (and is somewhat unhealthy anyway), and I'm not sure its desirable anyway.

It'll be interesting to see how the sub develops over time though, especially as opinions change and the user-base either turns over or simply ages, you might find it does start to more accurately reflect some of the views that are somewhat omitted (and to be fair, there tends to be more visibility for some fringe positions than you would find in any random sample of people of the same size across Europe..).

At the end of the day, it is somewhere where at present, there is significant pro-EU sentiment, but it isn't without people who take a different line, and that's not going away any time soon either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is absolutely true, but you have to realise that there are some obvious consequences if you think it through.  If you change the power balance within the EU from the states to the people, or simply strengthen the EU, the EU becomes something different, that quite a few people (and potentially states) will see as problematic. You essentially have to either accept the possibility of the EU getting smaller but more integrated, remaining as it is, but still facing significant barriers to integration, or finding some third option (the multi-speed approach I suppose) that only half deals with the issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the issue is at least in part that criticism, and different views are sometimes seen as hate and responded to as though they were, on the other side of that, some people see the problems that the EU has as a reason to actively hate the project, often somewhat irrationally. 

The whole Brexit thing crystallised that really, you have a very small number of people in the UK (who are quite vocal..) who actively hate the EU, would like to see it crumble and collapse almost regardless and that taints the perceptions others have of the much larger group of people who do don't hate the EU, but would rather not be a part of it. Yes the assumption is that those who voted leave, hate the EU and those who voted remain are very positive about the EU. Of course the reality is that most people fall somewhere much closer to the middle...

It's a simplification, and people thrive on simplification, it allows you to mark the 'others' the people you are 'against' rather than consider what you actually have in common, and discuss and weigh up the issues at hand..  In short it's much easier to split people into those who hate the EU (who can criticise it etc..) and those who love the EU (who can't even allow criticism), than it is to deal with the complexities of reality. Which is a huge shame as it creates real barriers to both understanding, and for those who want to remain in the EU, the opportunity to find positive change that brings more people into their camp..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably because you still want to deal with electronic emissions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two dead after care home fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ride Sheffield Opens New 'Cooking On Gas' Trail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd actually argue he boxed himself in with the attacks on Obama over the 'red line'. At the moment the US president is doing a great number on being massively unpredictable and seemingly quite irrational in terms of the areas where he has actual executive power. Whilst I'm pretty sure the Russians wanted him elected, I'm still far from convinced that it has actually handed them any kind of control, but rather that as a President, Trump is essentially harming US foreign relations to the benefit of Russia by being somewhat incompetent and antagonistic towards his allies..

As to the unilateral action, again, I'd say that points to ego rather than anything Machiavellian.. On the one hand there is a President who is running into brick walls pretty head on, apparently deliberately, often for no good reason whatsoever, and on the other people are suggesting it's all well crafted toward a certain goal.. I'd say the Russians decided to shake things up and at this point may be wondering whether they can contain it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bit daft.. Of course the US is going to warn the Russians, they had an agreement in place to do essentially that, and attacking Russian forces on the territory of a Russian ally whilst bombing an airfield would be pretty catastrophic and lead, somewhat justifiably to a major escalation, massively to the detriment of US interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, it also wanted out of a political union that didn't fit well, so the rationalisations aren't that far removed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably, that's going to court at the moment, I can't see them saying anything different though.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's broadly how I'd read it, a notification being a one time statement of intent that kicks off a process that leads to an exit.. I could just about see that negotiation leading to some other form of association, but not allowing for withdrawal and re-notification.  That said, things tend to take on a different meaning when it comes to treaties and international law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha..  OK that does work. 

(You remoaning git, etc..) ^obviously </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case I apparently misunderstood your usage of the daily struggle meme.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think a huge number of leave voters are terribly keen to see the UK reversing the leaving process in the first place though.. If anything a decision that it could be reversed at any point would be a negative (both in negotiation terms and in a domestic political sense), it keeps the uncertainty about whether the UK is actually leaving rumbling on..  If anything a very small number of remain voters might be concerned if they thought it was likely to be reversed and so they still had the opportunity of re-fighting the referendum, rather than having to kick off an unpopular 'rejoin' campaign.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 20:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really... But it's interesting given the Irish court case and just how much of a procedural shit show this looks like it might be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barnier lobbied to stop May withdrawing article 50 in two years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barnier lobbied to stop May withdrawing article 50 in two years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1.2m Sheffield Tramlines takeover bid revealed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably the best case scenario, although it is one that depends heavily on viewing it through the lens of the current US political narrative. You do however have a major problem if that narrative is wrong or skewed excessively.

I wouldn't discount the idea that the US acted as it did because Trump wanted to be seen as resolute where Obama had been painted as weak, yes he informed the Russians before, but that doesn't suggest a coordinated approach. In that context, this response also makes sense, and it does mean that there are now more risks in both Russia and the US operating in Syria. If the next incident is a Russian shoot down of a US air strike you have one hell of an escalation..

People are assuming a level of coordination and cooperation between Russia and Trump, intended to press a particular political outcome, I'm not so sure that it isn't far more one sided than that and so far more dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...there seems to be a bit of a divergent message coming out of the Labour Party on this from various people. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There seems to be a bit of a divergent message coming out of the Party on this from various people.. 

*Edit: Actually... Emily Thornberry is doing a good job pushing a single narrative that ties the divergent positions together, well somewhat anyway...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeremy Corbyn: US missile strikes on Syrian airbase risk escalating the civil war still further </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeremy Corbyn: US missile strikes on Syrian airbase risk escalating the civil war still further </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree but in my opinion is the right desicion for the EU population to decide in this way.

Quite possibly, but that argument has to be made to people in Europe, and at the moment, it really isn't, largely because it would boost euroscepticism and create more opposition than already exists..

 Imagine EU to fucntion like a real state with its own army. 

Yeah.. I see that as a bit of a problem, although less so now that the UK is leaving, and I do think closer integration is likely and probably necessary.

Im just citting some arguments that Merkel thinks too.

Sort of, based on what has been said in public she is certainly for further integration, but the detail there falls quite a long way short.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 14:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but again, that's just the way it is.. Scotland has a route to independence and Catalonia basically doesn't (in terms of self determination anyway..), it makes a UDI from Scotland less justifiable (unless things change significantly..) and more justifiable for Catalonia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this period of world history EU should function like a federal state due to certain type of threats.

That should really be up to the people who make up the EU, and frankly it doesn't seem that popular an option..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose the difference between Scotland and Catalonia is that  for Scotland there is a political process that can lead to independence, we have seen one referendum and there is likely going to be another at some point (and indeed probably another one at some time after that if there continues to be support etc..), Catalonia on the other hand doesn't, which you could argue justifies a push for a UDI given the lack of alternatives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, fair enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that relevant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vladimir Putin says US air strikes on Syria army 'illegal' and badly damage relations with Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Key point:

**"We reaffirm our commitment to the UN-approved principles for a Palestinian-Israeli settlement, which include the status of East Jerusalem as the capital of the future Palestinian state," the ministry said.
"At the same time, we must state that in this context we view West Jerusalem as the capital of Israel."*
v
*Moscow's announcement comes as the new U.S. administration is considering moving the U.S. embassy from Tel Aviv to Jerusalem, thereby recognizing the city as Israel's capital.*

*Israel declared Jerusalem its capital in 1950, but Russia is the first nation to recognize it as such, according to The Jerusalem Post.*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia recognizes [West] Jerusalem as Israel's capital </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 00:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as the Anglosphere media is capable of portraying the euro as a project bound to fail because of political uncertainties in one of its members states, the euro will not achieve its full potential as a global reserve currency, to the detriment of all members.

To be fair, the EU is currently talking about requiring Euro clearing to be carried out within the Eurozone, that would also make it an anomaly and unhelpful in terms of global reputation for the Euro and potentially has an impact on its role as a global reserve currency..  In short, it's not just a media issue.

That said, the chances of Le Pen winning in France are incredibly small, and the chances of France leaving the EU and/or the Euro, even with Le Pen are small too (given the damage that could do very quickly to France, never mind the rest of the continent..).  We'll see what happens, but the whole Frexit scenario seems remarkably unlikely, even if the level of support for Le Pen is a little alarming in that context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how I read it too...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be (although I can't see Ukraine joining any time soon..), at which point they will have to balance the benefits of joining with the costs like any other member though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's visa free travel not free movement so it shouldn't have any impact on immigration or indeed create brain drain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably as long as they can get a passport, but if you can identify them at the border you can always refuse entry.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a little bizarre because the UK has additional requirements to the EU and has traditionally had stronger restrictions (at least in part because of things like Rabies being more common in some EU countries and, the pet passport schemes extend beyond the EU too...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like it was a multi-country 'tour' of royal visits rather than a flight to Romania for business, the line from the independent is that he visited Romania, where he has business interests, not that he went to Romania for those business interests, he also visited Austria and Italy as part of the tour.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about what we go through (assuming my gallon to pint conversions are correct..) in about a month for a family of 6.. I wouldn't have anywhere to put it if I bought it all in one go though, and our milk only lasts about 3 days when open and about a week in a fridge anyway (non UHT..). Sounds like this guy was just pissing about though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wondering when we hit peak 'if' on Brexit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wondering when we hit peak 'if' on Brexit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quarter of a million British pets face jail in Europe if Brexit talks fail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 11:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the star has it now - [Heavy traffic building in Sheffield with temporary traffic lights stuck on red
](http://www.thestar.co.uk/news/heavy-traffic-building-in-sheffield-with-temporary-traffic-lights-stuck-on-red-1-8478345) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Trump, the weight of world's problems sink in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So.. The temporary lights on Walkley road don't work.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The temporary lights on Walkley road, betwen South road and Compton street seem to be stuck on red, so if you can avoid it.. Do.

That was my run up to school this morning, on the way up it seemed like the lights weren't changing at all (sat for about 5 minutes before someone took the initiative and just went..) quite a lot of the  drivers were just going for it.. But it meant a lot of traffic on Walkley road down and South road back just sitting..

A lass who was walking up the road stopped, watched for a bit and then started directing the traffic, when I came back down again half an hour later, there was a chap doing the same thing, and he looked like he was handing or about to head off after I passed him.. So cheer if that was you anyway.

Good job everyone, apart from whoever put the lights in obviously.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Works traffic lights on a school run route are stuck on red causing massive tailback, but random pedestrians are taking it in turn to direct traffic to keep it going.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my run up to school this morning, on the way up it seemed like the lights weren't changing at all and some drivers were just going for it.. A lass who was walking up the road stopped, watched for a bit and then started directing the traffic, when I came back down again half an hour later, there was a chap doing the same thing, and he looked like he was handing off to someone else after I passed him..

Good job everyone, apart from whoever put the lights in obviously.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how accurate the assumption is to be honest (there have been other chemical attacks, including immediately after condemnations by US president..), but it's an interesting take on it. If this view becomes prevalent, I do wonder what the administration response is going to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria chemical 'attack': Is Trump partly to blame? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats use Trump's populism against him in fight over Gorsuch nomination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 23:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little bit more than that in terms of the development, for one they are apparently not shit.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new Impossible Foods factory will produce 1 million pounds of 'meat' per month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new Impossible Foods factory will produce 1 million pounds of 'meat' per month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new Impossible Foods factory will produce 1 million pounds of 'meat' per month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any US states have specific storage requirements for firearms?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rex Tillerson's incredibly odd and confusing statement on North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator talks all night as Democrats fight Trump court nominee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Chatsworth house](https://www.chatsworth.org/) in Derbyshire in the UK probably in terms of how often I end up there, great adventure playground, really nice gardens and grounds etc..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of 'fake news' or rather a prevalent meme that isn't based on reality, this has to rank up there.. The US has troops in Eastern Europe, it's currently building up troop numbers in Europe rather after a significant period of reductions and it is doing so because of the perceived threat from Russia.. The US has made a lot of negative noises of late over funding, but it has also reaffirmed its commitment to NATO. That applies to the rest of NATO too, not one member has suggested it wants to cease cooperation, NATO has run and is running fairly major exercises, NATO members continue to inter-operate and share information...

 And your take on it is that NATO is dead and that there is no way 'Trump' would help e.g. Eastern European countries. I'm sure Russia is well pleased by the notion that people believe it, and would love to see it become a reality, but it isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So if you ask 1000 people something, the outcome is concrete? 

No, but if you ask a selected group of 1000 people and weight the responses appropriately and produce an analysis of the responses, you can get a very good idea of what the general view is..

Nah, it's the opinion of a tiny fraction of society who are being compensated for filling out forms that people then take as gospel and use as "evidence" to fulfil their own beliefs. This is how we ended up with Brexit and Trump.

Firstly, you don't generally get compensated for completing a poll and the polling that was out there was pretty good in terms of Brexit and to a lesser degree Trump. The last big(ish) polling failure we had was the last General Election (which may be more appropriate to take into account here given the context) but frankly, it's no where near 'wrong' enough to turn this into anything other than a shit show.

You don't get Brexit and Trump because of polling outcomes, you get Brexit and Trump by not paying attention to polling and what people think, and instead think that twitter might be more accurate.

Corbyn is incredibly unpopular, even amongst labour voters, that seems pretty obvious both from polling and anecdotally.  Whether it's enough to put them off voting for a Labour councillor or MP is a slightly different question (although it seems rather clear that his leadership is having an impact there), but if you are suggesting that this data point, or the many that we have seen in the last while are simply wrong (and on the basis that polling is somehow generally wrong, and twitter more accurate..) are utterly incorrect, then you are essentially ignoring, rather than addresssing a fairly major problem.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably YouGov are after usable data though, not quite the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do we do? Suggest that the current Tory government puts in place a regulatory system, give them the power to decide which newspaper are allowed to publish and which not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but regulation is far overdue.

And regulation is hard to get right, especially statutory regulation (because again, you essentially put the government in a rather interesting position in terms of power over the media..).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are tabloids.. It's expected. The idea of actually banning people from publishing is incredibly problematic though.. I mean by all means take them to court when they lie about something etc.. but banning a paper, regardless of how shit it is, is disproportionate and dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allowing something to spread lies for decades, especially not the hate-filled ones the likes of The Sun publish, is generally not a good idea.

And preventing someone from being able to publish whatever bollocks they want is generally a bad idea too. We have libel laws, anti-hate speech legislation, decent courts and more importantly, lots of other papers and media channels, that should be enough, banning newspapers is a quick way to end up with far bigger issues than some shoddy press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be nice too, but don't hold your breath.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banning newspapers is generally not a good idea, even if they are shite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot to choose from, but [Black Books](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0262150/) has to be up there.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump threatens 'core institutions of American society', says former US Labor Secretary Robert Reich </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deaths feared in Syria 'chemical attack' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beyond shocking, it's vomit inducing.. I should say that they are mostly in somewhat more neutral livery ([more like this](http://www.goyorkshire.com/app/cache/images/Stagecoach%20Supertram-iopts-1000x600-cropped-scaled.jpg)) with a few with specific paint jobs like this one.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's broadly right (wrong on leaving the EU in my view.. but right on the issues of winning over the electorate)  That said:

Populism is actually a massive opportunity for the Labour party, but were not capable of accessing it. My view about the rightwing populism is very, very clear. It can only be defeated by progressive forces building out from the centre.

I'd argue that the Blair government was elected on the basis of populism to a certain degree, it sought to address problems that a lot of people had that could be solved by policies that were, broadly, popular.. The issue isn't populism, it's targeting a relatively small number of people in one part of the political spectrum.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised the Lib Dems did not see a bigger rise after it was triggered.

Given they are broadly pushing the 'find ways to remain' position, I suppose you could argue that voting Lib Dem to remain in the EU became less of a thing with the triggering of A50 rather than more.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think first poll post A50, surprised UKIP haven't gotten lower.

Same here, the party isn't looking to snappy, and their core issue (the one that presumably helped bring in moderate members from a variety of areas..) is essentially dead.  I was assuming we'd see a fairly major drop and UKIP having to shift focus, but so far that hasn't quite happened, and I'm not sure it's just the 'Don't let them reverse direction on leaving the EU' thing is the only driver..

The locals will be interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be the end of the night, rather than the start of the day, in which case just spilling beer is probably better than the alternatives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And abonus - [Metrolink Tram in Manchester..](https://www.flickr.com/photos/subject3078/32897470036/in/dateposted-public/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trams of Europe: Sheffield SuperTram in Sheffield, UK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure we read the same article... Surely this is about the US government using  eminent domain laws to take land away from a raft of people who have property at or near the border? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump vs. American landowners on the border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, not being able to use punctuation like that probably didn't help.. Didn't you find that his delivery switched from rapid and hard to follow to slow and back a bit much? Oh and that the gaps between words were somewhat arbitrary at times.. Might just be the accent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it goes poorly, then maybe, but I doubt it. They currently have a majority of 11, a shit brexit deal is unlikely to increase it.

I'm not sure it'd be that important a factor to be honest, a shit deal (and any deal is going to be called shit by some and great by others) will have less of an impact than the perception of competence and the ability to govern.. I'd love to see a swing toward policy perception, but without any confidence in the ability of a potential government to deliver it's all a bit academic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, as befits the best city in the UK of course.. Someone started trying to turn the white rose red a few hours ago so I think there was a bit of support from the region too.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of these offer a discount if settled within X days, to disincentive that and challenges to these 'fines' generally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump golf course urination case starts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently 60% of UK trade is under EU treaties, either directly with the single market or via EU trade deals with third parties. 

Indeed, that's because competency to make trade deals currently rests with the EU.

While the UK can engage in informal talks any time it likes, it won't be possible to work out the details of any FTA until the future trade relationship with the EU has been determined.

It'd be a factor, but the real barrier is that the EU currently still holds the relevant competencies, and will until there is either an agreement between the UK and EU on how to move forward in the interim or indeed the UK leaves.

And even after that, the relationship with the single market will have an impact on UK trade with third parties.

That depends on the relationship. Outside of the Single market and the customs union whatever origin rules the UK and EU agree on will be relevant, but the EU won't be setting UK tariffs.. The EU obviously will be responsible for any tariffs that apply to the UK for UK/EU trade, but the UK isn't about to hand over tariff setting beyond what the WTO agreements are to the EU.

that would preclude a close relationship with the single market because the EU would have to protect itself against dumping through the backdoor.

Right.. And that applies to any country that the EU trades with.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay for hospital corners..  That said, this feels like it took about 10x longer than the demo we got in a 16 man room and weirdly a lot less instructive. Might just be the cadence and tempo that the instructor is running with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sheffield](/r/sheffield) managed to keep it's little spot throughout ([here](http://imgur.com/a/6kojy)), which was nice.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think all can be forgiven when you use a sensible date format.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the barrier there will be that our exit and transitional terms will have an impact on any deals anyway, sufficient to cause some issues at the very least.  Discussions and preparatory work seem sensible and somewhat inevitable..  The UK/EU deal and transition are going to be pretty important in that regard and I'd sort of assume that the UK will be talking there too, well before the exit deal is final, but I suppose we'll see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long will UK wait for EU's green light to talk about trade? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. set to clash with Russia, China over U.N. meeting on human rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to say, Place has ended, and the Sheffield bit was there at the end, in full, about halfway through the colour change...

[Quick screen shot here in case /r/place disappears...](http://imgur.com/a/6kojy)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there an image of the final thing anywhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In self-driving car race, winners get all the way around track </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/Yorkshire - 1,777 subscribers

//Lancashire - 271 subscribers

Who knew they had that many internet connections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think most people do, it's not so much the total numbers, but the progression, I mean the reality is that the likes of Ford, VW AG etc.. are going to probably end up dominating the Electric market, but Tesla gaining a foothold is pretty impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thread on the 'sheffield' place [here -](https://www.reddit.com/r/sheffield/comments/632zky/putting_sheffield_on_rplace_5_minutes_at_a_time/?utm_content=comments utm_medium=hot utm_source=reddit utm_name=sheffield) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone is trying to turn the White Rose Red next to /r/sheffield on place.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone seems to be trying to turn the white rose red.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was suggested elsewhere, so I've set up an /r/Sheffield Discord channel for anyone interested and on Discord. No particular intention as to how to use it or anything else, so have at it if you like that kind of thing..

*(This time with discord spelled correctly..)* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An /r/Sheffield Discord Channel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm.. Just saw that sorry, may have slightly set it back.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was suggested elsewhere, so I've set up an /r/Sheffield Dischord channel for anyone interested and on Dischord. No particular intention as to how to use it or anything else, so have at it if you like that kind of thing..

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.. Seems to be happening now (although someone is still occasionally reverting it to green... They might get the idea as it goes..).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> though someone is stopping any blue from moving to be around the 'sheffield'.

I think I may have started that.. I figured green on blue might look a bit awful.. The alternative might be to convert the Sheffield to white and then throw the blue around it (assuming no SUFC supporters take that as a slight..). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apart from the somewhat amusing musing of using RAF Akrotir and in flight refuelling to increase the time over target for air strikes against Spain^^1, this should hopefully go some way of killing the idea that Spain is going to do anything aggressive one way or another.  The issue of Gibralter in the context of the UK leaving the EU is a diplomatic one, no-one is going to be starting any wars..

^^1 FTA :*If we really wanted to do something, we have got RAF Akrotiri in Cyprus, and there would be no problem flying from the UK because it is closer, and you could refuel in the air to give you more time over the target.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gibraltar dispute: Michael Howard's claim UK could go to war with Spain is 'hilarious', says defence expert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 15:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted here and in /r/business because I figured it'd be interesting, the /r/business thread seems to have gotten more [traction](https://www.reddit.com/r/business/comments/632jxv/tesla_delivers_quarterly_record_of_25000_vehicles/?utm_content=comments utm_medium=front utm_source=reddit utm_name=technology inc) and discussion of the figures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lithuania fears Russian invasion as Kremlin misinformation campaign aims to destabilise Baltics, say officials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lithuania fears Russian invasion as Kremlin misinformation campaign aims to destabilise Baltics, say officials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, sort of, Reuters being accurate I suppose.. Still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure tbh, given we'd essentially be talking about a comparably large calibre muzzle-loader that isn't using a cartridge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good man.. Just about cleared up that purple mess on the left and there seem to be a couple of three people around.. Which is interesting given it's 4am... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In case anyone is playing along - Sheffield on /r/place is here.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure it quite qualifies... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTA:

*Kossman infuriated parents by telling their children that Adam is not real. She noted that Judaism, Christianity and Islam share the myth, thinking it would help build up tolerance for other faiths. She also inadvertently showed kids a classical painting of the first couple as imagined in the Garden of Eden  nude.*

Apart from the core issue, it's also somewhat amusing that people see showing kids a fairly famous, classical painting of a religiously inspired scene as something that should be a problem for 9 year old's. To be clear, it's [this painting by Reubens](https://thenypost.files.wordpress.com/2017/04/peter_paul_rubens_004_141891559.jpg?quality=90 strip=all w=344) and the original hangs in the Spanish national art museum.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adam and Eve lesson gets teacher cast out of religious school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to go and keep in in place - https://www.reddit.com/r/place#x=968 y=660 Is the link will get you there without pissing about too much..

*Edit:* *Just looking at whose blocks have survived and make it up, looks like 20+ of you, including (but not limited to.. /u/MotchSmedley /u/tenterhooked /u/acutely-cute /u/TheFamousUnknown /u/DMKitsch /u/Jack323 /u/PonderousPigeon /u/capn_andy /u/jaguarfemme /u/SuperFreakonomics /u/KernKernson /u/TeeJayPow /u/Precourser /u/GuyWhosNotThatGuy /u/Chaggers /u/sbirkenfeld /u/Dyfed_ /u/Ezayy /u/vtelgeuse u/itscebb
/u/Chineserose /u/WDB40 /u/tgarron)*

*So well done... Be interesting to see how long we can keep it..* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly, but to be honest I'm not sure, the UK has been on the periphery of the political project  Even if you deal with the elephant in the room on  immigration issues (which frankly we should have done and could have done..) you still have a slew of other issues. If the EU did manage to push for more integration,which I'd argue is necessary for the block, you'd still end up with building resentment. That would have lead to a crunch point either way at some point, and the solution then would have been the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that doesn't mean we can't rejoin the single market at some point which is basically what we had just without the political institutions.

That'd certainly be easier, be interesting to see how it would go down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'll just take a moment to channel a stereotype...](http://imgur.com/a/V8yEo) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is he so sure? Give it a few years and demographics suggest there would be a pro-EU majority. Of course a lot can happen over the next few years, but he's way too arrogant considering how close it was.

It's an opinion on his part, putting aside that he's a bit of a dick,  he's probably right. I doubt the demographic shift are going to guarantee anything, there is more support for the EU amongst younger people, but I doubt that that is an entirely 'sticky' political view.  Then we have the issue of joining being a different argument to remaining, there was a lot of soft support on both sides of the argument, but I don't think even half the remain vote would push to join the EU, potentially under quite different circumstances in the near future.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't even considered this before, although I initially assumed it'd fall under Section 58(2) of the Firearms Act 1968 given you could argue that a canon would be a curiosity and so not subject to the provisions of the Act...  That it falls into the same area of regulation as shotguns really is a (really quite cool..) oddity.

Oh and the size limits are also interesting, we found a civil war canon ball a while ago with a diameter of around 2 inches, likely fired by a falconet (a civil war cannon) which would have a barrel length of around 48 inches.. Curious to think that you could own something that could fire it under the regs..

Oh and video about the ownership of cannons without any footage of a cannon.. Come on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IRS.. I think he's already picking one with the EPA and half the other TLA's out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IRS chief is unexpected survivor in Trump era </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla delivers quarterly record of 25,000 vehicles in first quarter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla delivers quarterly record of 25,000 vehicles in first quarter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I don't think it's as likely as people state it is that we would lose our EU citizenship. 

That seems pretty unlikely and presumably would need action from the EU to make it possible, I don't see the UK government going after it and certainly not offering concessions to make it happen, doubly so if the EU are looking for reciprocity.  I mean you'd be giving UK citizens a whole slew of rights across the EU that no EU citizen would have, and it'd be at the behest of the EU. It'd be great if it happened, but I don't see it happening.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britain expresses regret over 'disturbance' during Saudi aide's London visit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kelly McParland: It's lonely at the top, and Trump keeps making it even lonelier for himself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coastguard say County Down kayaker alarm was elaborate hoax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if Hungary breaches EU rules, then there are sanctions that can be applied.. That isn't the same as not being allowed to be critical, or to present any given policy.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman who filmed her maid falling from a building and didn't try to help 'detained by police' in Kuwait </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be like kicking out a Catholic priest who claims God is evil.

I wasn't aware that EU membership required blind adherence to any particular dogma.. Surely if Hungary, has a different view of what the EU should be (whether you, I or anyone else agrees with that or not) then they have every right to push for that view.. It's a union of sovereign states after all, not a religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd agree that the argument that we need a *new* centre ground party is a bit silly really, the Lib Dems exist and there are many centrist Labour and Conservative MPs that should hold that ground, but it seems that neither the government nor the opposition seem interested in fighting for it in a lot of areas at the moment..

That'll be costly for Labour in upcoming elections, and potentially a bit of a boon to the Lib Dems too, but I do wonder to what degree.  After all, a real real threat from the centre would likeley (hopefully..) result in more centrist government policies and opposition policies (in theory at least, the current leadership of opposition may disagree..). So essentially the current Issues with the Labour party exacerbate the issue, the lack of opposition coupled with the party being associated more and more with positions that are quite a long way from the centre left (as well as the Damage done by elements of Momentum, some of the very pro-Corbyn types and indeed Ken Livingstone ). 

All that said, I don't think that the Lib Dems seem very centrist when it comes to the EU, and there are some severe limits on how far the Lib Dems can push their current position without looking a bit daft, right now I'd argue that they would have a very hard time convincing anyone who voted leave that they were a safe pair of hands to negotiate or carry out an exit from the EU.  Quite the reverse in fact. 

With that in mind, I'm not sure that the Lib Dems are the best party to fight a Tory hard brexit, it's the equivalent of going to the far left against a Tory government, it cedes the centre ground, it doesn't occupy it. The Lib Dems would have to be credible as a party that will take the UK out of the EU on better terms than the Tories (or Labour) to really take that centre, and I don't think they can. They'd alienate far too many of their own members and especially their new supporters if they did (well, unless any exit essentially changed nothing bar the name of our membership, and even then that'd probably cause issues..).

We don't need a new centre ground party to fight a Tory hard brexit, we need centrist MPs of all stripes to hold the government to account and ensure that the terms on which the UK leaves the EU are the best they can be for the UK, taking into account the views of  both remain voters and leave voters.  That would mean accepting the practical realities of the process of leaving and selling the notion of the UK outside of the EU, on the terms that the Lib Dems are happy with.

I'm not sure if that's possible, which is unfortunate, because the alternative could be a bit nasty and will likely take a long time to sort out.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tech firms force government backdown on weakened encryption demands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That wouldn't have made the problem go away though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bread

Bread dogs are generally pretty safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VIDEO: Sheffield universities' darts derby cancelled after 'drunken' fights break out in crowd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police shoot dogs after man and woman bitten in Bolton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose the repeated attempts to kill them, whilst not being terrorists would be a start, plus there have been some leaks and discussion of how this is supposed to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To be fair the last referendum was under a completely different setting. Pro Britain = Pro EU. Now is the opposite.

To some degree, but not on the scale that people are suggesting... I mean if you look at Scotland now and the likely routes after independence, there is a good argument to say that Scotland wouldn't join the EU, it'd go the EEA route.  You will note that polling has hardly shifted since the EU vote and doesn't look like it's going anywhere unless something else changes..  So yes, some things have changed, but that doesn't change the fact that there was a referendum, and indeed that people in Scotland don't seem to want another one, and that their voting intention hasn't changed a lot even if there were one soon.

 As Germans we have  mostly because of WW2  a totally different approach towards history and nationality and to me it is contemporary whereas the British feel stuck in time.

You'd have a point if you said that the UK perspective of Europe is different to the German one, and that both are shaped by WWII. The UK doesn't see the EU as a guarantor of peace, it doesn't see it as a necessary progression from the horrors of WWII, both at least in part because it was neither occupied nor the aggressor in that war.  That's not a harking back to Empire though.

As I said since Brexit some people seem too proud and too sure to be on the right side. No questioning at all. Just victorious

People who have been arguing for the UK to leave, campaigned to leave and voted to leave will see it as a victory and no doubt believe that they are on the right side.. But that's in line with what they have been working for and what they think.  That's not really unreasonable.  It is unreasonable to ignore the views of anyone else, but to be honest a lot of the issues there are that the loudest voices have been talking about simply not leaving, or reversing the decision, or indeed running another vote in the hope of achieving either..  

We have to be very careful to find the right balance for the UK and the EU.

We do, and it should be a close relationship, but with the UK firmly on the outside of he political project. That's achievable and I think probably fairly acceptable to most people in the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something very drastic had changed. 

.. A lot of things have changed, but I don't think they will result in a massive reversal of the current political fortunes of the Liberal Democrats, especially not in the context of the Lib Dems doing better than Labour in a General Election.

 There are a lot of naysayers at the moment but lib dems membership has exploded since the referendum

Labour Membership exploded somewhat more drastically fairly recently, it hasn't been mirrored by their electoral chances though and polling doesn't suggest a huge swing to the Lib Dems either.

 people right now are identifying them as the party against brexit so with the shifting of people's opinions I think the crawl back of the lib dems willbe the major talking point of 2020.

I don't doubt that the Lib Dems won't see some improvement in some areas, but frankly I don;t think Brexit is going to be as important in 2020 as it is now, and I would also argue that the Lib Dem position on it at the moment is going to start getting harmful rather than beneficial, arguing for remain is one thing, blindly doing it when the UK is on its way out is another, arguing to rejoin would be something else altogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buses to replace trams on Sheffield routes as Tram Train work begins in Tinsley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millicent Fawcett to be first woman statue in Parliament Square </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecuador's new president will tackle economy... and Julian Assange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 15:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not just change the colour of all issued passports from that point onwards.

I think that's the general idea (assuming the colour is changed of course..).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 14:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nor have I, and I doubt anyone is going to make you.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  any Tory Prime Minister would.

I'm pretty sure any Prime Minister would, or they would very, very quickly cease to be Prime Minister. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> April 1st was yesterday.

I did check that.. the Posting date is the 2nd though.

No government can be so dumb to waste so much money on such a petty thing when the NHS is collapsing.

It's the renewal of a contract, so it's not really new spending by the sounds of it, and whilst the NHS clearly needs a funding boost and a reversal in the current trends of how it is managed, it's not collapsing. Not to mention its not the only thing Governments need so spend money on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd expect Labour to take a beating in 2020 unless something changes, but the Lib Dems aren't even going to come close to recovering where they were in 2010 in terms of seats unless something very drastic changes.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just before anyone goes too far overboard on cost etc..

*The Home Office has invited businesses to apply for the 490 million redesign project, with the new passports set to come into existence in 2019  although it stressed this is because the current contract is ending, rather than because of the exit process.*

*A Home Office spokesman said: We are launching the procurement process now to ensure there is sufficient time to produce and design UK passports from 2019 when the current contract ends. *

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post-Brexit plan to spend 500m 'bringing back blue passports' is already under way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say Fascists and everyone thinks Right-wing Nazis.

Very true, given that the Nazis were Fascist.. It goes a bit beyond that of course, but it is a major example of fascism.

. Maybe they should actively teach about Stalin, Mao, Castro, Polpot, Chavez, and the other Left-wing Fascists that took us even longer to defeat.

They do don't they? I mean Stalin certainly, Mao and Polpot certainly are major examples of extreme ideologies, or authoritarian implementations, the same goes to a lesser extent to Castro and Chavez, but of course they weren't fascists... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem there is that talking about how shitty the club is, isn't grounds for being kicked out in this case, and frankly it'd be a bit alarming if it were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking if he is can be used to start a discussion though, can't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wait until someone insists that Fascism was defeated in Europe at the end of WWII.. Still, give the benefit of the doubt, comment as you'd like to be replied to (mostly..) and all that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be a little clearer, VW was originally established in 1937 by the German Labour Front (Deutsche Arbeitsfront),  which was the NAZI trade union organisation that replaced the various independent trade unions that had existed.. Hugo Boss was a member of the  German Labour Front and Nazi Party as well as a sponsoring member SS, and IG Farben (Bayer at the time...) had similar party ties. Essentially all of these private companies were so enmeshed in the state during the period that they are almost textbook examples of economics and industry in a Fascist state.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair to the people that do make that assumption, it's a very common misconception and one that gets pushed rather often. I think the most common response is something along the lines of 'well North Korea claims to be a Democratic Republic but is neither' but that doesn't generally help move the debate further..  Rather pleased with the response I got actually, if only I had more upvotes to give... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While there are a few interesting arguments that the Nazi regime did in fact have some socialist characteristics..

There are good arguments for it, I think when you are an authoritarian regime, there is a some reliance on populism that can often result in some traits you'd also associate with some forms of socialism almost regardless. It sometimes gets pretty twisted though, and at the end of the day, National Socialism is (together with its Spanish and Italian counterparts) almost seen as the definition of (one type..) of Fascism.  Not to mention fairly opposed to the Socialism and indeed communism by the definitions accepted then and now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 05:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Sorry fucker, if you wanted fair you probably shouldn't have posted a clickbait headline and then debating semantics in the comments. People meet tit for tat.

Fair in the context of the role of the President.. But feel free to read that how you want. As to tit for tat, I think I've been pretty clear don't you? 

You're wrong,

No.. I'm right

and it's obvious from the downvotes. 

I don't think downvotes mean what you think they mean..

So based on your continued willful ignorance I'm going to report this post as spam and suggest others do the same.

Feel free, but it clearly isn't spam, you may want to read the sidebar rules too.. Maybe add a comment when you report it to make your intentions and objections clear, you could perhaps outline what particularly offended you.

If you didn't have an ulterior motive going into this then you would have been more responsive to reason and logic from the other guy in this comment tree.

I discussed it with them,  I'd argue that's responsive enough, I do however disagree with them, which is unfortunate, but it does happen.

You have fun though.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
