<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4647</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if he cared about the truth he would tell it. He wants to lie and he doesnt want to get sued. All around a douchebag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even if he wasnt a total nut and asshole he would be at a disadvantage. The fact that he throws away his so called views when they become liability shows how much he believes in. He wont win the kids, he will just kill what little credibility he has </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money doesnt buy happiness. There is a reason a lot of rich people are bitter and angry. They have no love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He sells anti-gay frog repellent, male enhancement pills, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jones was always prorussia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No he isnt. He picks up every conspiracy that fits his agenda and test it. He does the spam tactic, spam lots of them and a few stick. Those that fail he drops or he drops them when it gets inconvenient.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia learned the hard way you cant buy american fascist. You can give them money but when russia needs their help they will betray russia. It is what trump did after russia gave him billions and stole the election for him and it is what trump will do. Their is no loyalty among fascist

In the past alex needed russia to make fake news but they learnes russia's methods for brainwashing and no longer need russia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Him and trump are bff. All actual conspiracy types turned against alex a long time aho for being a fraud and then turned on him again for being a trump shill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When has fake news not been highly upvoted on /r/t_d? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong. His support of trump and putin show he doesnt care about transparency, individual rights, etc. Furthermore he is basically one of the shills he rallies against. 
He blindly pettles any conspiracy that benefits his fascist agenda. If challenged he drops it. He refuses to even consider events, like russiagate, since they hurt his agenda.


If he believed what he preached he would need to kill himself. So no there is no proof he believes what he says,  and his lawyer confirmed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colbert is not a might. He is a comedian. He doesnt present himself as some fighter for truth. 

He just makes fun of republicans. If alex jones is doing the same approach he is making fun of his audience and other conspiracy theorist while ripping them off. He certainly does not admit this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selling products that will save you from turning into a gay frog or from dmt vampires from other dimensions. Im not making this up either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Only one making stuff up is alex jones. You would think he would be less angry since he gets lots of money for stuff he just makes up.

There is plenty of reason to believe he doesnt drink his own koolaid and just makes it up to sell overpriced vitamins that will save you from gay dmt frogs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was no secret colbert is satire. If alex jones is a satirist making fun of conspiracy theorist he is brilliant but i dont think he is that. He actually wants people to take him seriously so he can sell snake oil. 

Bad comparison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He cant have cake and eat it. Either he is a nut or he is fraud. He either loses his kids or his fans. 

And if you like his show it isnt about conspiracies. It is about selling snake oil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe he is a bitter and angry fraud that sells koolaid but doesnt drink it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt it. I dont defend dictators and trump. Guy is pure scum. Acts like he wants transparency and truth and than exposes himself as a propagandists for fascist like trump and putin. Fuck him. He is just trying to make money by taking advantage of feeble minded and crazy people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly given how much he yells and how angry he is he clearly isnt happy. He also needs to stop threatening to beat other people up. It shows depression. 

I have a hard time believing he believes himself when he gets his lawyer to say he doesnt believe what he says and people that do are nutjobs. 

Also he is not consistent in his views and seems to jump onto things and make them up and than drop them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money!=happiness

I realize republicans cannot understand that and that is why they feel empty and dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racism motivated Trump voters more than authoritarianism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burying 'Trumpomania,' Kremlin TV says Trump scarier than North Korean leader: russia is angry at trump for taking billions of bribes from them and then betraying them the same way he betrayed america </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burying 'Trumpomania,' Kremlin TV says Trump scarier than North Korean leader: russia is angry at trump for taking billions of bribes from them and then betraying them the same way he betrayed america </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> brutal new poll shows that fewer and fewer people believe Trumps lies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> brutal new poll shows that fewer and fewer people believe Trumps lies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> brutal new poll shows that fewer and fewer people believe Trumps lies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This brutal new poll shows that fewer and fewer people believe Trumps lies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thing he believes in is money for himself and fascism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Voters in a Swing District Wonder When the Winning Will Start: they have yet to see trump win once </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of money helps. He is a typical con artist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All alex needs to do is tell the truth that he is a fraud. Sure it will end his show but it seems like his life is pretty shit anyway. He has made millions of his little act so he can quietly retire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps big problem is he doesnt know what hes talking about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps big problem is he doesnt know what hes talking about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hes playing a character: Alex Jones lawyer says Infowars host is a performance artist and not really a nutjob revealing that he is a phony that exploits stupid and crazy people for money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Putins Moscow, a Pliant Press That Trump So Craves: The altright and Trump want to make the USA more like Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Voters in a Swing District Wonder When the Winning Will Start: Swing voters who voted for Trump overwhelmingly regret their decision after seeing Trump is failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which state sends the most tax dollars to the IRS? Hint: Its not a state: Last year, the District of Columbia paid Uncle Sam $37,000 per person in federal income, payroll and estate taxes. The next closest was Delaware, at $16,000 per person </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which state sends the most tax dollars to the IRS? Hint: Its not a state: Last year, the District of Columbia paid Uncle Sam $37,000 per person in federal income, payroll and estate taxes. The next closest was Delaware, at $16,000 per person </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I am saying they didnt fire the cops for the right reason. They fired them only because they couldnt let them off the hook like the 90 times in the past. They were nailed with too much evidence. Im saying even if they knew they were guilty but the evidence wasnt recorded they would have let them go. In this case it was recorded and there was no way to excuse them without being international news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg, right over your head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure the IRS made it so few people can access his tax returns in the DB and it properly shows all types of alerts whenever they are accessed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~germany~~ America first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *tear down the wall* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> george soros pays me in reddit karma, sucks to be you protesting for free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Soros travels through time to pay people in pesos to protest because he is evil ~~jew~~ globalist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they didnt do right thing. These people were so flagrantly caught that even Sessions couldnt protect them. The department would have buried it if it could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get it. 

On the right is church on Easter since clear there are way more people on the picture in the right. Whoever, has picture on left is clearly a loser. Whoever brought those people out in the picture on the right is clearly a winner. ive never seen so many people in one place. I am not even sure if there are that many people on Earth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this happened in space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also, most railroad crossings generate noise too. Even if you cany see the train you should hear it and the warning noises they added.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is right of every American to never have to stop for pedestrians or be delayed for a few seconds. You monarchist communist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IS is horrible to everyone, including the people who they claim to represent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly bombing civilians around them more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Obama is secretly a Muslim IS member who helped them. Only brave Trump is fighting them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it is great how he is killing even more civilians than Russia now, who kill civilians with impunity. Lots of stuff to make him look stronk and lots of dead civilians. Pretty awesome sauce.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is why America is not great we dont have enough giant bombs that are only useful in very limited situations  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is because Russia is ran by racist, fascist, and theocratic Christians who hate non-whites, non-Christians, and liberal and progressive values. They are also a corrupt oligarchy where a few rich people have all the wealth and anyone who complains about this can be arrested, beaten, tortured, and/or killed. Basically GOP paradise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> free land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that is navy yard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess too. Looks like VA between WV and DC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Good. We deserve this, and let's learn as a country the consequences of idiotic politics the Republican party has been.oushimg for the last ~~decade~~decades.**

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> likely the last person he talked to was Ryan who told him to ax it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tis a silly place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still Australia's fault. You are guys are total cunts. I blame the drug war over there on Australia too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are probably a few as pets and such.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Green really fell off the map </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump administration isnt even going to pretend to be transparent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even Canadians are skipping trips to the United States after the Trump travel ban: people suddenly have an unsettling sense that the United States isn't as welcoming a place as it once was. One industry expert pegs the projected lost revenue for 2017 at $7.4 billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even Canadians are skipping trips to the United States after the Trump travel ban: people suddenly have an unsettling sense that the United States isn't as welcoming a place as it once was. One industry expert pegs the projected lost revenue for 2017 at $7.4 billion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even Canadians are skipping trips to the United States after the Trump travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They recently started to devolve into this 

http://cdn77.sadanduseless.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/04/slav9.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump cant even pressure his own party to repeal Obamacare or lower taxes, the only things Republicans talk or care about, so I eagerly await his failure in NK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the funny thing is nobody was talking about Russia here, except this person who seems to be panicking over a scenario only they thought up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf are you talking about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isnt just Trump but the GOP voters in general. They vote corrupt politician after corrupt politician that hurts them economically and destroys their family, jobs, community, and country. As long as they profess to be GOP and Christian they are ok with this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is part of the conservative experience to never admit you are wrong, regardless of how bad things are going, and deny reality. 

Conservatives even do change their views to go against old views they have they just wont admit they were wrong about old views. If there is a picture of 10 million cheering for Obama and 10 cheering for Trump if they are asked who has more people cheering for them they will say Trump with a straight face knowing it is bullshit but refusing to admit it, forever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go to /r/t_d and ask them who wants to betray America for Putin, they will line up to work for Russia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Challenge accepted - Jeff Sessions 

He would fight 99% of the country if it meant imposing his KKK views on America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are both in the know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that reference!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always nice when people like you see their mistakes and own up to them. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always nice when people like you see their mistakes and own up to them. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit. Flip off a cop in Russia and they won't just flip you off back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not expert on this so I might trigger someone but I believe a unbalance in the force creates problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always nice when people like you see their mistakes and own up to them. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they want us to obtain it legally maybe produce enough so we can buy it without a 100% markup or more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always nice when people like you see their mistakes and own up to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You Cleary don't understand my point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol like I said libertarians live in delusion. Communism is not what they want but that or fascism is the end result of what you advocate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It began. Compared to the rest of Europe Russia was mostly far behind with a very small % of its workforce working in actual industry. 

If we are going to count the progress of industrialization as something positive than ussr  was a great success since stain vastly increased the % of workers I'm industry and output, even during times of war and chaos. Ussr is the biggest example of rapid industrialization after China in the 90s. 

As for Russian civil war, that was happening regardless of lenin. The elite in Russia controlled too much wealth and the vast majority had too little compared to them. The result is always revolution. That should serve as lesson to rich in america. It could be a fascist or a communist revolution but the elites will lose it all due to their greed. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He still drives the alright. His libertarian ideals are impossible to implement and what he tries to implement just results in inequality and poverty which fuels fascism and the altright. I agree he talks in a more sane matter now but what he believes is still crazy and results in fascism. He doesn't support fascism directly like Bannon sure but he supports it equally indirectly by promoting ideology that is insane. 

The end result of libertarianism is communism or fascism. They live in a randian  fantasy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is still a nut. He fired someone for having an abortion and pays people to teach false history. He is still a radical libertarian. He is just toned down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did actually but decades later. However, there were other factors at play. Wwi, civil war, stalin, and then wwii all happened. So it is hard to say if it was better or worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My generation has to choose between a child or a career. We cant afford both </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rich in Russia brought ussr  on themselves. Their greed destroyed them and they lost everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gop base behavior </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally I don't agree.

Gop believes in no privacy, broadcasting personal issues, and judging people. They and their supports should be held to those standards and every detail of their life should be public and held against them always. 

This should apply to politicians  with this view and people who vote for them. 

Meanwhile people who believe in privacy and focusing on issues should not have this applied. 

I am sure they are such pillars of virtue that they will still come out looking better under close scrunity they give americans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Gop  believes personal issues, lack of privacy, and moral judgement should be norm so we are just applying what they say they want to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At home, rebel Republican lawmakers pay no price for defying Trump: Republicans who spit in trump's face and told him to fuck off are met with applause and cheers but quisling Republicans who work with trump face voter wrath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At home, rebel Republican lawmakers pay no price for defying Trump: Republicans who spit in trump's face and told him to fuck off are met with applause and cheers but quisling Republicans who work with trump face voter wrath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At home, rebel Republican lawmakers pay no price for defying Trump: Republicans who spit in trump's face and told him to fuck off are met with applause and cheers but quisling Republicans who work with trump face voter wrath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At home, rebel Republican lawmakers pay no price for defying Trump: Republicans who spit in trump's face and told him to fuck off are met with applause and cheers but quisling Republicans who work with trump face voter wrath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At home, rebel Republican lawmakers pay no price for defying Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are considered class traitors by the gop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more they win the more they lose. 

They are getting more money but in the process they are destroying millions in America and tens of millions over the world. Trump won in part to backlash against them even though trump is their pawn. 

They are building the guillotine slowly with their own wins. As they screw over 99% of the world and get richer while we get poorer what happens? What is result in long run? Result is fire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why spend the money on improving education when we can spend more to give worse education but make the investors rich? -the gop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have their gilded age but it is about to end and the new backlash against them  will make them wish for the good old days of the new deal. 

They can only get a short term win hut in the long run they male things worse for what they want. They need to cooperate not try to control when they are small minority or they will face an angry mob .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gilded age is what caused social reform and higher taxes for them. Their battle against progress will result in the loss of their wealth, European aristocracy learned this the hard way. 

Maybe the rich right now won't reap their consequences but their kids will.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *they hurt my feelings by not letting me institutionalize racism and theocracy, and implied my ignorant opinion is not equal to actual science while trying to help with me government assistance because there is no jobs or hope where I live*. Liberals are evil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is why most trump voters voted for trump. Trump hurts them economically, socially, and culturally while stripping them of rights. However trump voters are very tribal and feel those *edumucated  city liberals with their separation of church, science, and tolerance* look down on them and trying to oppress them by improving their life and giving them education. Trump voters vote to hurt others not to help themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump who keeps dropping national secrets on twitter and on TV because of what he sees on Fox and friends is clearly the right choice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took wwii to destroy the German at right. Wwi wasn't enough than decades of communist occupation. 

The alright wants to create a situation that ultimately destroys them. That is how the extreme right always works. You can never best progress, maybe slow it down temporarily but the backlash will speed it up in the long run. That is human history. The only way for the right to win is to destroy humanity, barring that they will destroy themselves as progress crushes them like the instincts they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You work for us: Arizona Sen. Jeff Flake faces hostile town hall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spending blind: Shocking education report shows taxpayers pay millions for subpar charter schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could go wrong? Alabama Senate votes to give local church its own armed police force </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could go wrong? Alabama Senate votes to give local church its own armed police force </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could go wrong? Alabama Senate votes to give local church its own armed police force </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More TrumpRegrets every day: Now the hard-right nationalists are losing their religion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More TrumpRegrets every day: Now the hard-right nationalists are losing their religion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More TrumpRegrets every day: Now the hard-right nationalists are losing their religion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More TrumpRegrets every day: Now the hard-right nationalists are losing their religion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More TrumpRegrets every day: Now the hard-right nationalists are losing their religion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More TrumpRegrets every day: Now the hard-right nationalists are losing their religion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Trump adviser and russian spy Carter Page held 'strong pro-Kremlin views' along with the rest of the Trump administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Trump adviser and russian spy Carter Page held 'strong pro-Kremlin views' along with the rest of the Trump administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Trump adviser and russian spy Carter Page held 'strong pro-Kremlin views' along with the rest of the Trump administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Trump adviser and russian spy Carter Page held 'strong pro-Kremlin views' along with the rest of the Trump administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Trump adviser Carter Page held 'strong pro-Kremlin views', says ex-boss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican congressman tells his constituents that because hes rich, he doesnt work for them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 13:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You care about this way too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly eating and drinking. Also not paying or fights. Or seeing bottles of pies . Vast majority is eating and drinking though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I was saying Russian hooligans work out a ton, practice mma, and practice street fighting so they can fuck up other fans. 

One it isn't a positive thing. They aren't trying to be mma world champions just street fighting champs.

And there is a reason the Russian hooligans crushed English hooligans last time they met. The Russian hooligans are like a paramilitary. I don't view it positively. If it makes you feel better in positive comparisons UK almost always beats russia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not many. I see way more rule breaking on metro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Is Our Most Helpless President: Even in the White House, Trump keeps playing the victim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Is Our Most Helpless President: Even in the White House, Trump keeps playing the victim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Is Our Most Helpless President: Even in the White House, Trump keeps playing the victim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump just realized North Korea is a complicated issue: After listening for 10 minutes, I realized its not so easy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump just realized North Korea is a complicated issue: After listening for 10 minutes, I realized its not so easy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump just realized North Korea is a complicated issue: After listening for 10 minutes, I realized its not so easy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British spies warned US intelligence that Trump and team were Russian spies 2 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British spies warned US intelligence that Trump and team were Russian spies 2 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British spies warned US intelligence that Trump was a Russian spy 2 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is fleecing America, and the Department of Justice is letting it happen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is fleecing America, and the Department of Justice is letting it happen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a technical standpoint that would be easy to do with driver behavior having cretins license plates. 

However, the joke would be lost on America and most of the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mentally ill man set to die in Arkansas 'conveyor belt' executions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mentally ill man set to die in Arkansas 'conveyor belt' executions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Bannon doomed? It hardly matters  Jeff Sessions is much better at white nationalism and wants to undo civil rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Bannon doomed? It hardly matters  Jeff Sessions is much better at white nationalism and wants to undo civil rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the gop  started a class war on the poor to drive them from the city and how it is party of a larger gop and trump agenda of waging war on the poor in the whole country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Rich Seized Control of New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump sparks first protest in space: Space networks screw-you message to Trump flies 90,000 feet high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas Doesnt Want Trumps Wall Either </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump sparks first protest in space: Space networks screw-you message flies 90,000 feet high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump sparks first protest in space: Space networks screw-you message flies 90,000 feet high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump sparks first protest in space: Space networks screw-you message flies 90,000 feet high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no he listens to any idea from the last person. He he had a good advisors and that person could block everyone else that could be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it all makes sense. 

Whoever can get access to Trump is president. 

He is demented. His mind is failing. He can easily be controlled, but the control can be undone by someone else. 

Basically whoever controls President is de facto President. Right now it is mostly Kushner. In the past it was Bannon, who in turn seems tied to Russia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, only several people with very close ties to Trump had all kinds of shady ties to Russia that they tried to hide. Some even being investigated by the FBI. Surely it is angry at defeat and not something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like Trump is the puppet of the last person who could talk to him alone, so Putin is that powerful if he could get access to Trump without interference. 

There is some people with ties to Putin that had access to Trump like Bannon, Flynn, Mannofort, Alex Jones, etc. They are being pushed out. I dont think they are Putin puppets as much as fascist or just corrupt and aligned with Russia over ideology, white christian ethnonationalism, or for money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I believe there is among the right. Now that Russia is pissed at him maybe that will go away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin is more of a threat directly, but the problem with Trump is that he is is inconsistent. He has no ideology or belief to him. he is intellectually lazy and just goes with whoever has his ear for the moment. He doesnt want to invade parts of Europe, and likely never will he could do something extremely impulsive without any thought to the consequences. Maybe even WWIII. He would rush right in, and it could come out of nowhere. 

He is not reliable. 

Putin is sneaky, but you know what he wants and is trying to do. He is playing a game but is aware their consequences. He has bad intentions for France but if you stand up you know he wont do anything impulsive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> English Hooligans vs Mexican fans. Oh boy would those English be in a world of trouble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian hooligans arent much better, but the Russians at least can fight really well. Instead of fat drunken louts they MMA nazi types. They arent drunk hooligans as much as paramilitary fascist who rekt anyone in their way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al Gore was pretty awesome. He had election stolen from him. 

Kerry was decent, but fake news and manipulating patriotism defeated him. Obama was real awesome. 

Really the only bad Presidental candidate was Hilary. She isnt even a bad politician per se but the Republicans have spent 2 decades to spread irrational hate of her and the anti-elitist mood was not in her favor. 

*edit* also a massive Russian propaganda effort to discredit Clinton and the FBI stepping in to help Russia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush is looking pretty good these days for a Republican.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is why ivanka is now his personal assistant. She monitors who can influence him and calls in jared if there is a problem,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hated Dubya so much years ago, but compared to how bad Republicucks have gotten I would gladly see them all replaced  by him. He seems like a pillar of good Repulicanism. Not that he was a good leader, far from it, but for a Republican he was good. Hell nixon even looks awesome these days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has no mind. 

He is a demented old man. It is the people who control him. Bannon is being kicked out, who was pro-Russia by his son in law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the theory here in America is that he has dementia and this anti-NATO pro-Russia stance was Bannon who is being replaced by his son in law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> until he changes his mind. Dont worry he will change it back. if there is one thing you can count on from Trump it is inconsistency  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He will fund it by cutting taxes for the rich </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be praising him for saving NATO from himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bannon is against US intervention in ME, dislikes Jews and Israel, and seems to have a positive view of Assad and Russia's support of him. 

Nazis tend to like Syria and Iran because they dont like Israel. I dont see why Bannon would put down Hitler and Syria, two things he likes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a 3rd possibility that involves a combination of those 2.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt 5. is the case. He likes Assad and Russia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he is clearly demented. That is why he keeps bringing up his inauguration vs Obama. take a look at what happened with Ryancare, jared was skiing in Aspen and Trump had no clue what he was doing. He kept asking Ryan if the bill was good and Ryan told him it was great. Same with bannon, Bannon can control Trump.

Basically the last person who talks to trump can control him. That is why Ivanka his now his personal assistant, to limit access. 

Jared is our new President, and Trump is his proxy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it depends on how you take them. I think if you are prescribed a medical dose and take it as needed, not all the time, it isnt too bad. If you are abusing them, probably.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id quit it isnt good for your brain

http://www.livescience.com/19867-cocaine-ages-brain-shrink.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Oakland was pretty hot. They were a popular team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Win a nobel prize for going to war?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> doubtful. He doesnt give a shit about his people, that is the hallmark of the regime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IDK I doubt he cares about these 600k people. Most likely he is removing all the poor from the capital.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $3000? Wow a realistic budget for DC, usually these post are something like where can I get a place on 14th and U for $1000? 

For $3000 a month you will be fine, or $2000 for a single. My recommendation is live a little further out. This may come as a surprise to you but Georgetown has some good deals on rentals for over $2000. Or VA as others have said. Other options are Admo and dont discount union station. If you are willing to take 1-3 metro stops or a small bus ride you will have better options.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Popville poster publically rekts driver who almost hit them becoming DC's most passive aggressive badass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> best GTA game. You would get generic looking luxury condos, a small urban area full of yuppies, gridlock traffic, and endless suburbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Trump have abandoned all of his campaign promises by the 100-day mark: At this rate of three flip-flops a day Trump will have a completely different policy platform while some of these reversals are probably better than his previous positions hes still be Trump so everything will still be bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Trump have abandoned all of his campaign promises by the 100-day mark: At this rate of three flip-flops a day Trump will have a completely different policy platform while some of these reversals are probably better than his previous positions hes still be Trump so everything will still be bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Trump have abandoned all of his campaign promises by the 100-day mark: At this rate of three flip-flops a day Trump will have a completely different policy platform while some of these reversals are probably better than his previous positions hes still be Trump so everything will still be bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Trump have abandoned all of his campaign promises by the 100-day mark: At this rate of three flip-flops a day Trump will have a completely different policy platform while some of these reversals are probably better than his previous positions hes still be Trump so everything will still be bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Donald Trump have abandoned all of his campaign promises by the 100-day mark? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is kinda right in that Democrats today are like pre-reagan Republicans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really hard to get fired. I know people with fed jobs who are literally Russian spies and in the pocket of Russia and still haven't gotten fired </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he didn't kill her after </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude Petworth happened years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The super rich benefit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol they won't get it cut. Just younger people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple didn't fall far from tree with ryan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ss  already pays shit. It won't disappear for boomers but for millenials  it will  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump ruined hired a bunch of movement conservatives who think hes a sucker and keep manipulating him to make stupid and embarrassing decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump ruined hired a bunch of movement conservatives who think hes a sucker and keep manipulating him to make stupid and embarrassing decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
