<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2574</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New gaming keyboard. Filco Majestouch with Cherry Reds and DSA Dolch keycaps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New gaming keyboard. Filco Majestouch2 with Cherry Reds and DSA Dolch keycaps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feels like these are in every thread now, but I still love them. Filco Majestouch2 with DSA Dolch keys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 09:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the typical "I was here first" elitism that also gives way to things like "real gamers" and "real games".  Ignoring the fact that gaming has been more or less mainstream for over a decade now (if not longer), large parts of GamerGate have this incredibly myopic sense that *they* are the gamers.  That *they* are the audience.  They are unableor unwillingto accept that there were people playing games before them, and that there are people playing games after them.

It's this sentiment that gives rise to ridiculous claims of "ignoring your customers" and "attacking your audience".  Because that self-inflated sense of importance, of being capital-G Gamers, means that necessarily all others must think and act as they do.  

Because paramount to your average GamerGater's sense of identity is that because they self-identify to a group, all others self-identifying to that group must feel the same way.

The unfortunate corollary to this is that anything to preserve that ego is seen as positive, and anything that diminishes that ego is not only seen as a negative, but also as a sweeping attack on all who self-identify with that group.  

Indeed, the primary outrage amongst GamerGaters isn't so really personal outrage, but outrage *on behalf* of other gamers.  Hence why that outrage is so often fueled to a larger than life state.  They are not fighting on behalf of self, they are fighting on behalf of the Gamer ego, extended by fiat to all the other imagined Gamers in the world who are wronged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 09:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TotalBiscuit complains about lazy and pseudo-intellectual position, then proceeds to write lazy and pseudo-intellectual screed about thing.

Surprise factor: zero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 06:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read a ton of wuxia novels (mostly in Chinese, tho), and watched probably more iterations of The Condor Trilogy on TV from both Hong Kong and Mainland China than I really care to count. You've honestly covered most of the immediate suggestions that came to mind.

(I'd note that while the classical Wuxia of Jin Yong might be defined primary by its martial focus, the wider world of wuxiaincluding works by Gu Long and Liang Yushengoften features charactesr and narratives that are much more focused on politics, or mysteries, or even slice of life.)

But with that said, a few more, though some stretch your core requirements of martial focused wuxia a bit:

**Deathstalker Cycle by Simon R Green**.  More pulpy sci-fi than fantasy, perhaps, but has a pretty well populated milieu with plenty of fascinating characters.

**Red Country by Joe Abercrombie**. This novel isn't standalone, and requires reading The First Law to understand much of the subtext.  But it's also remarkably similar in narrative structure and tone to many wuxia novels.

**The Magicians by Lev Grossman** 

**Nightside novels by Simon R Green**

**Cycle of Fire by Janny Wurts**

**A Wizard of Earthsea and its sequels by Ursula Le Guin**.

(A few **Discworld** novels are also remarkably similar to some wuxia stories in both scope of milieu and narrative.  They're all great, so I'd just recommend the entire series.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 23:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but he decided that the highest value a man can subscribe to is calling out people on the Right and doing the Lefts work for them.

This guy isn't part of GamerGate.  GamerGate is full of left-leaning progressives, I thought everyone knew that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 21:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   best programmers are also some of the least socialized people (at one company I worked at, one of the programmers would literally hover around the cubicle of every woman who was hired for HOURS just to 'get to know them') and that kind of comes through loud and clear in this piece.

I'm pretty happy that the kind of behavior you describe is generally no longer tolerated in mature companies, no matter how good the engineer in question might be.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 21:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW, Vox Media's Polygon brand page also calls out audience segmentation:

http://www.voxmedia.com/brands/polygon#audience

It's not quite as MALES FUCK YES gung ho as IGN's corp page, but it similarly calls out the 18-34 male demographic as important and desirable to advertisers.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 21:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's what she was going for, but expressed it poorly.

(And for the record, the Green Lantern is a stupid stance to take on this beacuse that hero and mythos expressly and explicitly allows Green Lanterns of all race, nationalities, genders or species) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day this will happen to harassers of non-celebrities, but always nice to see someone get what's coming.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yankees fire employee over vulgar tweets about Curt Schilling's daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 22:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 23:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little concerning that experienced game dev Mark Kern does not appear to know math, or basic idiomatic English for expressing numbers.

(Then again, maybe that explains Red5 *rimshot*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 18:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's fine. It's only a "divide" because GamerGate has taken a "agree-or-destroy" approach to civil discourse and rational disagreement.  As the industry (and overall readership) grows, there are necessarily going to be sites that lean one direction or another on issues.

You see the same in traditional news sources (ie, NY Times vs Wash Post)

It's not a bad thing, though I could buy the argument that it's not a great thing either.  

But practically speaking, sites need to find their audience (and via that, their revenue) via differentiation of content and voice.  In the current media climate, it's near impossible to survive solely from factual news reporting.  Sites need a voice.

Sometimes the voice adopted might be personally offensive (eg, The Escapist), but whatever.  I'm okay with that. It's only crossing the line if Escapist adopts a GamerGate stance and encourages the active destruction or malicious interference of other sites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 18:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not understanding programming or something as simple (for devs) as GitHub speaks a lot to.. wherever the hell his game is right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Founder of Mary Sue joins Polygon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 17:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "One of my hopes for this industry is that someday TotalBiscuit will find the one field-of-view slider that has always evaded him: his own." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 20:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 15:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular reminder that despite being active for a little over a week now, Mark Kern's petition only has gathered 2700 votes.  The petition to remove Adam Baldwin from Supanova got 4000 votes in 2 days.

So who wants Mark Kern to speak?

Not very many people at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 17:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being the first in a neighborhood to have a Playstation was a point of pride.  Being the first kid in your neighborhood to have a C64? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 17:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part?  10 years ago, *it was 2005*.

Kid, you didn't live through the 80s and 90s of gaming.  You *already missed* arguably the two greatest decades of gaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 09:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they can fix their Facebook page (https://www.facebook.com/EscapistMag) while they're at it, which amazingly still stays:

 The Escapist covers digital culture with a **progressive** editorial style, with articles and columns by the top writers in and outside of the digital entertainment industry.

Emphasis mine.

http://i.imgur.com/750x1l2.png

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 04:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That *Jango_the_Blue_Fox* user's comments, aka The Bra Denier belongs on something like /r/cringe.   It's that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know your coworkers so can't speak to them, but I've had similar conversations back in 2008 when Hillary was running against Obama in the primaries.  

Maybe there is an undercurrent of sexism, but Bill being "back in the office", so to speak, is a not unimportant allure for a lot of folks.    

Where it veers into casual sexism, I think, is when people refuse to believe that Hillary is able to run the presidency herself without Bill's guiding hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I called you a racial epithet why won't you just shut up and cry like you're supposed to" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 18:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm going to comment in a thread about Social Justice Nuts and complain that this person saying that GamerGate is about fighting against social justice screeds is wrong.  WRONG.  It's actually about ethics, you social justice nut." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 18:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I stand corrected.  Though, I haven't really seen any of those pubs push for it recently, so not sure where the outburst is coming from this time around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 18:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most stupid thing is that there weren't even that many people asking for it.  IIRC, it was basically one blogwhose entire premise is talking about PoC in video games and mediawho made a post about it.

Daniel Vavra proceeds to then blow it completely out of proportion, acts as if every publication in the known world is gunning for him to put historically inaccurate PoC in his historically accurate computer simulation, and engages in what is, as far as I can tell, a persecution-complex fueled whine-fest of epic overreaction.

(EDIT: /u/Coltorl- points out below that though the request was made on one blog, several gaming pubs picked up on it)

(EDIT 2: It looks like the two articles in question on Kotaku and Daily Dot were more about the vast and pretty hateful over-reaction to a seemingly benign question on the MedievalPOC site, rather than actual serious requests on the part of press for Daniel Vavra to include PoC in his game.  So my original point stands.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 07:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Polygon mods have had the unenviable duty of moderating GamerGate raids, and IMO they've done a pretty admirable job of it.  Obvious trolls and diehard gators get shut down pretty quickly, and in general the community seems to have learned that certain things won't be tolerated, so they aren't attempted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 05:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no problems with Gators having their own site, or their own favorite destination.  NicheGamerand its brethrenpretty much already serves this purpose.

I'm more sad that Escapist was once a fairly respectable gaming publication, with good writing, and smart videos. 

It's like watching TechTV get turned into G4TV into whatever it was during the last few moments of its existence, except faster and over the course of 6 months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 03:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In human society and among actual wolves, the path of a loner is riddled with hardship.  

*In real life and among actual wolves, ethics in journalism are paramount.*

 This is designed to be a young male friendly place on the internet, to counter-balance all the corruption and all the misandry found on other gaming and geek culture websites.

*This site is designed to be a young male friendly place on the internet, to counter-balance all the other places online that are not friendly to young males.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 02:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was a smart lawyer (I'm neither of those words, so who knows), his contract with the Escapist would be a veritable fortress of binding obligations and departure penalties, given how many views he draws with his videos.

The question is, when does Yahtzee's contract run out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular reminder that this is the publication where Alexander Macris personally conducted interviews with devs, and then pushed through the article with the byline **Escapist Staff**.  

The Escapist Staff had no real involvement in the interviews or the selection of interview subjects. It was basically an attempt by Macris to hide behind a publication byline to lend his set of interviews the weight of a publication's credibility.

It was not only cowardly, but incredibly sketchy, when it later came out that Macris donated money to one of the devs that was interviewed.

It was basically a disaster for all involved, was the first major step in drowning The Escapist's reputation in a gutter of pandering and shit, and at the center of it all is what appears to be an unrepentant Alexander Macris.

Who, in an Escapist forum thread complaining about their latest hiringsI mean non-employee potentially regular contributors (http://www.escapistmagazine.com/forums/read/18.871054-A-professional-objective-apolitical-future-for-The-Escapist?page=9#21836458
) wrote:

 Lizzy and Brandon Morse are writing articles. They are not employees or news writers. As I've said elsewhere, we've downsized on both employees and news writers and aren't staffing up right now.

 Nor are they writing political work for us. Josh and I are quite serious that we don't want the Escapist to be political. That means we don't want it to be left-wing OR right-wing.

Which, of course, makes total sense given that Morse has no real history of game writing, and his main claim to notoriety and relationship with gaming is his political and cultural views on feminism, gamergate, and everything in between.

*So what's going on with The Escapist?*

My guess is that Alexander Macris is either (1) showing his true colors and sympathies now that Greg Tito and other writers are gone, or (2) desperately pandering to a reactionary extremist minority in order to boost page views.  I almost prefer option 1, because option 2 is just depressingly sad for a publication of Escapist's once sizable stature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 23:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gl all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 19:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet another person in a long line of people who claim that the "games press is shitty" because something they made or were involved in didn't get a great reception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 06:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the funny thing: in the beginning, press outlets *did* take some of the issues of ethics from GamerGate supporters seriously.  In fact, both Kotaku and Polygon *both* acknowledged that their stances on Patreon needed some changing, and modified their ethics policies.

So yes, Mark Kern, the press did address ethics -- or at least those parts they felt were realistically relevant and true.  

But you know what?  That was over *half a year ago*.  And surprise, surprise, GG is still on going and the increasingly strident and desperate pleas for "ETHICS"while openly mocking feminists and "SJWS" and similarly other "no-really-we're-left-ring-progressives-ignore-baldwin" actionshas not abated.

So what did the press learn from that?  That GamerGate is truly about a lot of things, but ethics isn't one of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 14:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes the incessant behavior is on the part of the person dishing out the harassment.  If I see a Twitter account harassing 100 people with 100 tweets, each individual target may not be undergoing incessant harassing, but the Twitter account is certainly engaging in harassment.

(eg, if you look at the timeline of many GamerGate supporters, there's a history of continual harassment, even if the target may shift) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 14:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I got hired by Escapist!"

"In my immediate next tweet, I will retweet Milo and make fun of Feminism."

http://i.imgur.com/P66iaxx.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 09:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It was horrible, and one woman was so badly harassed that we decided to take her picture down from our site...and she never wants it there again.

Ugh, that's horrible and shitty.

 This petition is not just about yellow journalism in gaming press, but also about how such journalism does nothing to solve this type of harassment. Instead, it drives people apart, trying to put them into boxes or labels and pit them against each other for nothing other than traffic and profit. To solve these issues, the press has to bring us together, positively and constructively, with serious journalism. 

Okay, fine, I'll hear you out on the "serious journalism" that will address the harassment your employee received.

 Kotaku and Polygon, lets not start with "games are bad and getting worse" lets start with "games are great, and can even be better."

Wait. What?  Mark Kern, did you try that with your employee?  **"Hey Jane, I know you've been harassed in terrible ways by our community, but remember, games are great!  Let's figure out how to make them even better!"**

Seriously, did you?

No?

Maybe because it's a completely toothless stance to take that fixes nothing except maybe help a boss who doesn't truly care about his employee's harassment*and want to try to stop it from happening to others*to sleep better at night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 3 days, Mark Kern's misguided petition only has a little over 2000 signatures. What does this say about GamerGate's size? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 09:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of 2/19: https://archive.today/rSOn7

That it is a tattered remnant of its height of support.  That it is fractured, more chaotic than ever, more confused than ever, more unsure than ever of its goals.

If Mark Kernmaybe the highest profile developer to engage the GamerGate crowd in an actual call to actioncan only get ~2000 signatures after 3 days of soapboxing, of constant unironic flagellation of a supposed media-induced narrative, then GamerGate's actual political power for change is microscopic. That, even relative to their prior tiny size, they are now even more a completely irrelevant drop in the bucket compared to the gaming population at large.

(For comparison, the petition to remove Adam Baldwin from Supanova hit 4000 signatures in 2 days) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 16:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, about that "with us or against us" narrative...

https://twitter.com/Totalbiscuit/status/522292390061948928

 When the dust settles, remember who it was that fed their own readership to the wolves. I will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 20:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, yes, you're right. Typo in my thread title _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 20:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Storify of their tweets:

https://storify.com/idolminds/raspberry-pi-gamergate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember GamerGate going bonkers over Raspberry Pi and their "anti-consumer" stance? They've sold over 3 million units. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 20:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously guys, [I don't understand why 7 million people a month](https://www.quantcast.com/polygon.com) visit a site that is so blatantly anti-gamer.  Am I missing something here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why doesn't Amazon directly sell Nintendo consoles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 16:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind the sound of the stock tips, but what were the new tips you tried? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 08:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually had these a year or so back, but returned them because the price/value was a bit high for me.  But now that they are in the $250-300 range, I couldn't resist.

For my tastes, lovely bass with some incredibly sumptuous female vocals.  

It's a little larger than my current go-to portables (Senn IE80), but the fit is comfortable once I got used to the increased sized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JVC FX850 - Just received these a few days ago! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 08:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 07:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely a guilty pleasure.  Felt almost like if a younger Simon R Green tried to write a novelization of a shounen anime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 16:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading between the lines, I wonder if there was a call from Riot going "Um, guys, WTF" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garena Philippines drops LGBT restrictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 16:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garena Philippines drops LGBT restrictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 16:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-04 06:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, what's the point of placing a woman character  into a cold weather stage if she's not in a tank top.  My best female friend told me that it's just not very realistic at all.

Anyway, having read through your very long and insightful post, I can tell that you are being very serious, and display an obvious passion for gaming.  Not like Crystal Dynamics.  Going to boycott them now.  The status quo is there for a reason, its just capitalism.  If SJWs really wanted something like that, why don't they start their own country or something.  Like a Marxist country.  I don't think that's ever been done before, so maybe finally SJWs would try something _new_.

I don't really  mind that the original is influencing the new one and that trauma plays a part in the game, but at least make it objective.  I mean, what is trauma, really? According to the 17th century philosopher scientist Sir Jain Bain of the Boors, trauma is really just this gaze that we look at shadows at the back of a cave in a tree, just a reflection of the insecurities of the people looking inside the tree.  Why can't developers be more confident and just do what they want.

I think her boobs are fine.  You don't want to go overboard with boobs, like really I think her boobs are probably the right size.  I hope there's an option to remove the coat though, because what's the point of giving a female good proportioned boobs if you can't see them at some point.

Anyway, I'm pretty neutral in this and don't really care about any of it, but just my thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 18:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the same Jace as this monkey http://www.reddit.com/user/jace_neoreactionary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 09:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post has reminded me fondly of "The Big Game" in Myth Directions.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 07:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warded Man
Travelers Gate

if you liked Belgariad, there's also mallorean, elenium, Tamuli. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 09:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a supposed IT manager, I hope you never use the "simple and easy!" line with your employees without putting more thought than the amount you've demonstrated here.

Ammo count is stored as fractions because different weapons have different magazine and reserve ammo sizes.  If ammo was stored as flat values, switching from a 1 magazine rocket with 3 reserve rockets to a machine gun would give you 1 bullet with 3 reserve bullets.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 09:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one thing i never understood about the "conspiracy" is that in order for the conspiracy to make sense, the smallest atomic unit of time in the modern world must be "day".  Or maybe "5 days".

Because there's no other explanation for how an article, reactions and reposts and subsequent unrelated articles that were published over a course of *days* could be considered "coming out at the same time" and "coordinated". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PewDieDie quote appearing on Techland ads for Dying Light: "The quote, which reads 'I love this game. Its sooo awesome!' was taken from the incredibly popular YouTuber's playthrough of a demo of the game during VGX 2013, which appeared to be an advertorial video solicited by Techland themselves." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 09:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is your regular reminder that beyond gamers, remember that novels, television and cable are dead too. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 09:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just judging by article titles right now, but in this fast paced modern world, that should be enough.

http://www.theguardian.com/books/2014/may/02/will-self-novel-dead-literary-fiction

http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2014/02/tv-is-dead-now-what-103670.html#.VMnxYmTF_41

http://motherboard.vice.com/read/hbo-killed-cable

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edge Online being rolled into Games Radar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 18:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 16:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited for this assuming 250 of those 300 hours aren't collection and fetch quests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 06:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even "products" aren't evaluated objectively.  Plenty of reviews mention "feels like a BMW" or "not as elegant as expected from Apple" or "Leica still has my heart" or "this American car does not *feel* like how an American car should". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 06:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even car reviews have an element of emotional resonance.  Hell, phones too.  I've ready many car reviews from many places where a car "not feeling BMW-ish" or "an interior not at the level I expected from Audi" carries significant weight in the final analysis.

Even things like cooking knives and pots and pans can sometimes have emotional resonance with reviews.  Plenty of "this lodge pan is as good as my Le Creuset but *it's no Le Creuset*.

Pens have "ink feel" and "flow", phones have "ease of use", "overall experience", hell digital camera reviews have things like "this Leica *feels* like a Leica".

It's utterly silly to expect a reviewer to take the.. reviewer out of the review.  It's not possible.  Beyond a strict factual description of technical specs and dimensions, an aspect of emotional evaluation of the product gets injected at some level into every single review I can think of for pretty much any product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 16:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too, wish Joystiq people the best.  On the other hand, for all the shit that Kotaku gets, they are bringing in traffic.  

I'd rather Joystiq had done a little more of what Kotaku has done if the other option is them closing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 18:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm waiting for the Gamespot/Metacritic/GiantBomb/IGN/CBS Interactive are all headquartered in SAN FRANCISCO panic post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also TIL "Meninist" is a thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buzzfeed tagging "we are a 100% feminist website" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he's already started in some places.  re: Yahtzee's PC Master Race article:

http://i.imgur.com/OsrVcST.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 16:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of feel like their money troubles mightve been one of the reasons they did go full gator.  Macris's own personal views on GG combined with a need for more readers led to a series of unfortunate events for the staff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 16:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on Sterling's current Patreon numbers, getting out of there is looking more and more like a great move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Escapist in trouble, Greg Tito leaving: "Due to budget cuts at Defy Media, the parent company of The Escapist, Game Front, and GameTrailers, a large number of my colleagues have also been let go." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 16:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test with imgur og:image </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 20:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test http og:image on verge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 20:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robotoki closes shop, Human Element on 'hiatus' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 18:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 22:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not explicitly -- but he did retweet and respond to scalzi's whole pinapple pizzagate mockery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 09:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If nerd icons  who have come out against GamerGate like Felicia Day or Wil Wheaton or hell, Neil Gaiman and Joss Whedon haven't done anything, what makes you think Gabe saying something will help?

Each time, in each case, the first response from the core GG group is always "well I never liked that person anyway" or "well they are talking about harrassment, not GamerGate" or "they just don't understand what GamerGate is about and have been misled by mainstream media"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 17:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I am super curious to see how Joystiq's reviews will be received in the future, I don't really mind scores.

I mean, we have scores in book reviews, in film reviews, in tv reviews, in restaurant reviews, hell, between Yelp and Amazon, pretty much anything you ever pay money for is tied to a quantitative score.

I am loathe to accept that for whatever reason, the general gaming audience is somehow incapable of dealing with scores.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 17:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I am super curious to see how Joystiq's reviews will be received in the future, I don't really mind scores.

I mean, we have scores in book reviews, in film reviews, in tv reviews, in restaurant reviews, hell, between Yelp and Amazon, pretty much anything you ever pay money for is tied to a quantitative score.

I am loathe to accept that for whatever reason, the general gaming audience is somehow incapable of dealing with scores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 18:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is a ton of fighting in the story, but Kenshin is all about not wanting to fight and preserving his vow not to kill anymore.

The problem wish Kenshin as a pacifist vehicle however, is that the manga/anime is billed as an action/shounen work, so inevitably despite not wanting to fight Kenshin still does it. Nearly every time.

And it definitely does not satisfy the OP's request of "do not also betray their morals as a necessary ingredient for the protagonist's victory?"

Kenshin basically engages in (true, non-fatal usually) combat in every encounter eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 18:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sheer *fun factor*?  **Deathstalker** and **Nightside** books by Simon R Green (which, pound for pound, are probably the best guilty pleasure books I own), **Glory Road** by Heinlein, **Vlad Taltos** books by Steven Brust

Others with perhaps more lasting influence/literary merit that are also great reads: **Dune**, Vance's **Dying Earth** books, Wolfe's **Book of the New Sun**, **Lord of Light** by Zelazny, **Jack of Shadows** by Zelazny, **His Dark Materials**

And more recently Max Gladstone's **Craft Sequence** is a really refreshing take on science and magic and how the modern world might work if magic was real and well known. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 10:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming you've already read (or passed on) the sequels to Ender's Game and Old Man's War:

- **Armor** (John Steakley)
- **The Lost Fleet** series (Jack Campbell)
- **Vorkosigan Saga** (Lois McMaster Bujold)
- **In Fury Born** (David Weber)
- **Troy Rising** series (John Ringo)
- **The Moon Is a Harsh Mistress** (Robert Heinlein)
- **Deathstalker** books (Simon R Green)
- **Empire of Man**books (David Weber)
- **The Forge of God** and **Anvil of Stars** (Greg Bear)
- **Ciaphas Cain** Warhammer 40k books (Sandy Mitchell)
- **Gaunt's Ghosts** Warhammer 40k books (Dan Abnett)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 10:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My picks/hopes (mostly hopes and dreams I admit): 

**TV**: 

- Dresden (but maybe better than Sci-Fi's attempt)
- Discworld (I'm imagining a BBC series a la Dr. Who with a wide ensemble of rotating characters. Hopefully as enjoyable as the few Discworld specials they made)
- The Dark Tower 
- The Chronicles of Prydain
- The Magicians
- Night Angel trilogy
- Nine Princes in Amber


**Film**: (not necessarily series, but also standalone films)

- Good Omens
- Coldfire Trilogy
- Perdido Street Station
- Red Rising
- The Paper Magician </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 09:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There was even a source on ghazi that said the CEO of Intel spent time looking at this. 

FWIW, The NY Times article that features quotes from Intel's CEO from a p hone interview specifically mentions Intel pulling ads from GamaSutra (and by extension, GamerGate) being a reason for Intel's diversity push. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 09:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know when I was 6 I wasn't a gamer but two years later when I was 8 I considered myself a gamer.

Did you also know if you don't claim to be a gamer by at least 2010, you can no longer ever claim to like games ever again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anita is actually a strategic genius who invented video games and the Princess in the Castle trope so that she could talk about them 30 years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know Nintendo based the original Samus sprite in Metroid on the mother of video games, Anita Sarkeesian?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a tactic I can get behind </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard from my friend that Anita claimed she was the real inventor of video games.  Man, why is Anita such a scammer.

Prove to me she didn't claim that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 would live in your house.

It also varies way more than I initially thought unit to unit.  A volume that would be safe at one apt I lived at would have the neighbors come knocking at another.  One apt I lived in was so bad that adjacent units could hear normal volume talking between my roommate and I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once I saw Folsomdsf on the street and heard the quote "man, I sure hate oranges". Show me proof it didn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 19:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody's got an Xbro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 16:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's as if they are in high school and still live with their parents and don't realize that "thousands in funding a month" translates to very little real world expendable income. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 09:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's interesting how snow makes the playset look inviting, and fog makes it look horror movie creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 09:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After many, many years of apt/condo/shared living, here's the key to doing what you want to do: talk to your neighbors.

Seriously, that's all there is to it.  Work out schedules.  Neighbors sleep at 10pm? Okay, don't pump the bass at midnight.  Neighbors tell you that weekends are fair game? Blast that music.  Have a party on a Friday that you think will run late with music going? Just tell your neighbors and work out a date.  

I've rarely found people super un-accommodating provided some common sense courtesy and respect for shared living is shown.

If the neighbors are friendly, and you are worried, I've also found it helps (if they're willing) to actually go into your neighboring units and see how much sound leaks out. 

It's mutually beneficial.  They get to see how their noise habits affect you, and you get to verify what levels of volume gets tranferred to adjacent units. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 08:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on to your butts because here are a few blasts from the past that, while not really quite classic quest fantasy, were all fun reads for me and books from the 80s and older:

Prydain Chronicles -- LLoyd Alexander

The Belgariad -- David Eddings

Dying Earth -- Jack Vance

Myth Adventures -- Robert Lynn Aspirin

Vlad Taltos novels -- Steven Brust

Chronicles of Thomas Convenent -- Stephen R Donaldson

Discworld books -- Terry Pratchett

Valdemar books -- Mercedes Lackey

Thieves World  -- Robert Lynn Aspirin (and many others)

Elric and more -- Moorcock

Conan -- Robert E Howard

Dark is Rising -- Susan Cooper

Shannara -- Terry Brooks

Nine Princes in Amber -- Zelazny

Riverworld -- Philp Jose Farmer

Riftwar Saga -- Raymond Feist

Icewind Dale, Crystal Shard -- RA Salvatore

Deed of Paksenarrion -- Elizabeth Moon

Fionavar Tapestry -- Guy Gavriel Kay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 07:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few suggestions:

Deeds of Paksenarrion

Mists of Avalon

Black Magician

Gate of Ivory

His Dark Materials

Mistborn

Throne of Glass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 07:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Please Intel, reconsider your **$300 Million pledge** because do you really want to support insert someone I disagree with" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game, set, match. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 07:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 23:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm saying whether or not it has existed in the past has no bearing on what authors can do in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 22:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fantasy. I just made it up.  

Replace healing ward with heal spell, heal charm, heal chant, special innate ability, whatever else you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 22:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Gerald Tarrant**.  The Coldfire Trilogy does a lot of things right, and its primary antagonist is one of them.  I was rooting for him the entire way.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 22:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Planetary**

**Chew**

**Sandman** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 22:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's why scifi is more egalitarian: Because they don't need to worry about those issues because science fixes them. Magic on the other hand rarely is as advanced as the science.

That... doesn't make anysense.

Science solution: better healthcare

Fantasy solution: I cast a ward of healing on you, now you feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 22:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Night Watch* and *Small Gods* are both at the top for me.  

I also have a soft spot for *Interesting Times*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a tough call.  Both Pinsof and the scammer in question were in the wrong.  

IIRC he was never explicitly blacklisted, but his firing was quite public (and made all the more public by his tweeting at the time), so I'm not sure how he expected it to go down without some professional repercussions wrt his general trustworthiness, credibility and ultimately employability, deserved or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the way I generally think about it, Giant Bomb is to the standard Gaming Enthusiast press the same way that Top Gear is to the standard Motoring press.  I don't go to GB or Top Gear for news, I go to them to watch the antics of the personalities involved within the context of my favorite hobbies.

I go to Polygon/Kotaku/IGN/Gamespot/etc for news, reviews, etc the same way I go to MotorWeek, Car and Driver, Autoblog, etc for the same things in cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people also don't really want to be video personalities or be in front of the proverbial camera all the time.

Not saying that's what Klepek did, but I've known many like that.  They might even be good at it, but they just didn't like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 21:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Campbell is definitely a guy that looked like an almost reasonable member of GamerGate in the early stages and then quickly descended into madness.

Auerbach and to a certain extend Kain also followed the same trajectory, though didn't go quite as deep into the crazy as Oliver Campbell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 17:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI, the opinion section officially started in January with the hire of Kuchera.  It didn't initially have the About Page or the existing opinion piece branding.  Part of the motivation for having that about page and the general big giant OPINION branding in giant letters is that despite an article obviously being an editorial due to tone and title, and despite an article living in the opinion section and written by the opinion editor, people were still constantly mistaking it as news/representative of Polygon as a whole or of staff not involved with the piece, and sending in nasty emails or engaging in pretty terrible behavior elsewhere.

(I've found this sort of selective myopia on what is or isn't an opinion to be mostly based on how much you disagree/agree with the opinion, and also, sadly, mostly universal and separate from any specific GamerGate traits)

So well, when relative subtlety doesn't work, just hit them on the head over and over again that it's an opinion piece.  It's unfortunate that it feels like little like a Caution: Hot warning on coffee, but it sometimes does help because the response can just be: read the giant white letters and read this page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 08:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want paragon levels :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 08:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Destiny is a flat circle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't be the only one that basically wants Total War: Homeworld, or whatever that amazing fusion of games would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One immediate reason that pops into my head is new player acquisition: from what I think you're describing, holding land would be a beneficial/interesting system for long-term players, but would steadily make the context more and more complex for new players.

DUST does appear to be an exception, though one that perhaps isn't all that surprising considering its EVE pedigree.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 07:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps an alien from the Great Zipper Galaxy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Max Scoville joins IGN as new host </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 20:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd only be unethical if they claimed in their Patreon that they wouldn't accept other forms of revenue or advertising, which they haven't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in their defense, that number is still rising.  when I posted the link, it was hovering around $800.  As of this moment, it's around $1800. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right -- I don't think very many people outside of the GamerGate kool-aid drinking populace really believed the drivel that Xbro was spouting.  I was using him more as an example of a case where, IMO,  I think you can legitimately ask someone's employer if they are happy that this is how they are being represented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 18:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those wondering what happened:

http://www.patreon.com/kindafunnygames

They are quitting and starting a podcast.  Looks like for now they are seeking monthly funding through Patreon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 16:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revision3 is also no longer a thing in gaming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 16:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Perhaps you should clarify that this guy doesn't represent the views of the rest of the company?

So, like, I get your sentiment. I really do. It's immensely frustrating when someone from a company that is big or that you like says something you disagree with.  But the whole "do you want this person representing your company?" thing is stupid.

It should be obvious by now that unless you are specifically saying something about your company and some part of your company's stance, you are always, *always* speaking for yourself.

This doesn't need to be called out.  (And in any case, the EthanJamesPetty has it called out in his Twitter bio that his views don't represent Ubisoft)

Of course, in cases like Xbro, this is different.  Xbro specifically, explicitly stated what he thought the opinions of others in the Microsoft were on GamerGate.  In his role as an employee of MS, he was, in multiple interviews, *actually* speaking for portions of the company.  He used his employer as a platform to amplify his views and position.

Which is why I don't mind people worked up about Xbro but think that just because someone says something disagreeable on Twitter -- without bringing in their employer -- it doesn't mean its a reflection on their company.

(Obviously, I'm not including instances where a person makes direct threats to others. In which case, IMO, if someone wanted to say to their employer "yo, look at what this person is doing", fine by me, stop making personal threats.  But AFAIK, Ethan James Petty never did that.  He has some views on Twitter I think are befitting of assholes and people I probably wouldn't like, but I never saw the kind of tweets that exemplify why GamerGate is so venomous.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 22:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rogue Legacy is probably my Vita game of the year, in terms of both hours played and fun per hour gained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 22:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Giving absolute numbers also gives absolute metrics for success and a baselines for comparisons between various games, publishers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-02 11:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poorly. All too often, I get burnt out on side quests, and never manage to finish the main quests.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 19:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantasy occupies as much if not more shelf space than a genre like Romance at places like B N in my experience.  And I wouldn't consider Romance to be unread.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 23:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, many of the opinions there are not wrong.  I think many genres have underwent phases of the incestuous "written by fans for fans" periods, often to their detriment.  

I don't agree that it's happening with Fantasy right now, but there definitely seemed to be a slate of me-too copycat novels in, for example, young adult fiction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 22:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's less about gear for me at the office than music.  I absolutely cannot have music with vocals in them if I want to concentrate when working.  So I tend to play instrumentals or electronica, etc.

(Or, because its words i don't understand, some bad Asian pop music -- my secret weakness) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 22:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had them for a while when I accidentally broke the cable on my IE80 and was looking for a (flimsy!) excuse to buy new portables.  Ended up returning them, however.

I liked them a lot. I had no complaints about the sound.  The real issues where they they jutted out of my ears quite a bit (both when wearing straight down and wearing around the ears).  It made it hard to do things that I've gotten used to doing with my IE80s (that are relatively flush with my ears) like lying down on one side or put my head on my shoulders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 22:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was initially hesitant about the brown and gray colors because I was afraid it was going to be more brown and silver.  Worries were unfounded however, because it is an IMO gorgeous light gunmetal gray.

I'm running this at the office off of an Fiio E10 connect to my laptop.    Currently, it's hooked up to an AKG 271 and an ATH-M50x.

Really liking the MDR1A so far. By far the most comfy headphones of the bunch I wear (though the 271 comes in a close second due to the self adjusting headband and velour pads).  

In terms of sound, I find the signature and overall tone very pleasing.  The bass is just right for me (the 271 was very much lacking in that regard, while the M50x was pretty good).  Obviously haven't put many hours into it yet, but early imprssions are positive.

(Photo taken with a friend's Fuji X-T1 that he just purchased.  So aside from headphone lust, I now have a whole new set of camera lust feels I need to deal with) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Sony MDR-1A came in the mail today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 22:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 19:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, I mean people who might be at first underestimated or seem unassuming but are in reality super accomplished or badass.

Not so much wimp turned badass, but rather someone who was always badass but hid it in some way.

Ron's mother in Harry Potter would be a good example in [Deathly Hallows](#s "when she kills bellatrix") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some "Hidden Badass" characters/books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 08:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And by Hidden Badass, I mean something like this: http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/HiddenBadass

A few examples of things I've read that fit the bill:

Ari Marmell's Conqueror's Shadow and Warlord's Legacy

Abercrombie's Red Country

Kingkiller Chronicles satisfies this somewhat, with the present day POVs.

"The Sweeper" from Pratchett's Discworld novels.  Most notably in Thief of Time.

Jim Butcher's [Codex Alera](#s "Fade")

(From film, Taken and The Equalizer are obvious examples) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 08:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simon R Green's Nightside books

Vlad Taltos novels by Brust

The first couple Discworld books by Pratchett.  If you like them, the rest feature different POVs but are all equally good.

Brent Weeks' Night Angel books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 08:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Leviathan Wakes** by James SA Corey

**Old Man's War** by John Scalzi

**Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy** by Douglas Adams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 07:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would've thought that acting like a complete asshole online would be a detriment to finding a job in a field where many people are internet saavy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 09:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Old Man's War sequels are great.

There are no sequels to Forever War.  There have never been any sequels to Forever War.  Forever War will always be a standalone book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 09:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Expanse books by James S.A. Corey had some great audio book adaptions.  

(The novels themselves rank among my top Sci-Fi series of the past decade or so)

If you're looking for more pulpy stuff, many of Simon R Green's books have audio versions.  I remember listening to the entire Deathstalker series via audio books, and they were awesome.

(Simon R Green is also, incidentally, IMO vastly underrated for the sheer entertainment value present in both Deathstalker and the surprisingly rich Nightside novels) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
