<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5813</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually palmed my face when I saw this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> But...that's what anchors do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 16:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WDIS] DeAndre Hopkins or Andre Johnson? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 14:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To the Motherland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 19:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He was asking for it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 23:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 21:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize you used this sub for news. Google it yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, Kanye. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 16:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 01:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I could help you; missing football is something I can't handle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 19:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First and only time. Yeah it does hurt the image, but I don't foresee this being a common occurrence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder if she realized after, but I tried my best to look like nothing was out of the ordinary... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 18:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 22:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Got a great deal for it on Craigslist ($400). Worth every penny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 22:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. I didn't realize the controller had any form of memory (flash I'm assuming). Pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 22:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I installed it last week, just getting around to posting about it. Do you know what it was for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Controller Update? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 21:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This poster at work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 19:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-15 03:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presidential pardons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 16:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out. Confirmed for lots of research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 16:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a better joke than the original shitpost. Illitch is a parasite on the city, refusing to build parking garages so his empty gravel lots on his vacant, completely non-developed parcels can collect outrageous event parking fees.

That, and his pizza is terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-10 16:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google or YouTube Slow Roll. That will tell you all you need to know.

I'm a Detroit resident and cyclist. I'd never want to live anywhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 22:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lions will win the NFC North. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sign actually reads "Eggs". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 22:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 23:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former guy with dandruff here. I found that all I had to do was leave any regular moisturizing shampoo in for 5 minutes or longer and it all went away. Most men put it in and wash it right out, that's a no-no.

Also, don't but that 2-in-1 shampoo conditioner crap. They should be completely separated. Same process with the conditioner as the shampoo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 15:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time posting on this subreddit, thanks for the tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 03:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the response! Why a sardonic sense of humor specifically?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Casual] What is your age, sex, country, and the one feature that you find most attractive about the opposite (or preferred) sex? (All) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 00:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to understand how these features change as people age, and what differences can be seen based on location as well. It can be anything: Money, a certain look, a certain personality, etc. It's all fair game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 00:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took the poll aspect out. Now it's just curiosity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 00:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, but what rule of this subreddit did I break exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 23:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. Time to repost under the correct title... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 23:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Did not know that subreddit existed. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-26 23:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure whether to upvote or downvote... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 20:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bust out laughing every time I see this referenced, which is often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 17:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not lose 7-0 in Premier League exhibition matches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm from Holland, isn't that veird?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://np.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1y6lhe/what_is_the_worst_thing_someone_has_said_to_you/cfhtedq </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 00:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You like that, you fucking retard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 17:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in downtown Detroit. I love the city and can give you some first hand tips and recommendations. I'll try my best here.

-Detroiters don't like Greektown. It's safe for out of towners, but the bums and beggars know that that's where the surbanites and tourists go. Part of the bad rep of the city comes from that entire experience alone. If you want some legitimate Detroit goodness, here are my recommendations:

-Park Bar: Great atmosphere, excellent location relative to Ford Field. Great Mediterranean food, if you're into that sort of thing. Excellent beer selection.

-Foran's Grand Trunk Pub: One of my favorite spots, and is more of a localized gem as opposed to an out-of-town haven. They have a ton (a TON) of Michigan brews, excellent game day specials, and great food. The bar has a legitimate old school feel to it, and is only a couple blocks to the game. Good access point between the field and the river (the river walked has been completely revamped and is quite pleasant).

-Bookie's Bar and Grille: Nice double decker building with a patio on the rooftop. A free bus to the game. A few pretty good beers, solid prices as well. A little off the beaten path per se, but still downtown. I walk there from my place frequently.

-Mercury Bar/Slows: Obligatory tourist destination (Slows specifically). I don't frequent it often because of this, but the food always seems to get fantastic reviews, even on a national level. I'd expect a near hour wait here though, so plan accordingly if you decide to go here.

Fancier options include 24grille (great wine selection, little unknown high end restaurant/bar in the Westin Book Cadillac, along with another bigger one called Roast, which I feel is overrated), London Chop house (has a cigar bar, if that's your cup of tea), and Texas De Brazil (every cut of meat you can think of).

Things to do:

-Walk the river, it really is nice.

-Visit Campus Martius right smack dab in the middle of the city. There is always something going on there.

-Get a famous coney dog at American or Lafayette (Lafayette FTW).

-Hit up a casino. Greektown feels like gambling in my parents basement. I would advise Motor City if you wanted to see some over the top style.

-Do touristy things. There are small niche shops all over the place. There's always some quirky items at any of these locations. Walk as much as you can; it's not dangerous, I promise.

-Go bar hopping in Corktown. You can snag a bus to the game from there if you choose that as your destination before the game as well.

Well, that's what I got. Hope it helps some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 15:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Win: Tall, thin, attractive, intelligent guy.

Loss: Type 1 diabetes since 7 years old.

I call it a wash. Things could be way worse and diabetes has probably also helped me stay thin. Looking at how my brother has turned out makes me feel much better about my situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 22:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, glad I came home early from work today. That's crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 22:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the point of publicly posting my regret like it was some monumental climb? If I ever get to that stage, I'd have fallen a long way. I've had to walk 25 flights to get to my place when the elevators were being serviced and I didn't complain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 whole flights? After BRUNCH?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-11 20:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 16:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Areas to live: Corktown, Hamtramck, Woodbridge, Downtown, Indian Village (if you have that kind of cash), New Center, and Boston Edison.

News: Deadline Detroit, Detroit News, Detroit Free Press, Metro Times, Motor City Muckraker, Preservation Detroit, MLive

Climate: Living here all my life, the winters are cold and the summers are hot. I love that I can own both a snowboard and golf clubs in this state. Detroit was rated the country's safest city based on natural disasters; the lakes help keep them away. The summers average around 85 degrees, the winters hover around 10 degrees or so. To put it one way: you will never be bored climate-wise.

Jobs: I am an engineer and have companies begging me to talk to them. I make six figures and I'm not out of my mid twenties. It depends on your degree, of course, and unfortunately I can't give great information on liberal arts jobs, but there are plenty of other small time jobs all over the city.

All in all, I love it here and have no desire to ever live elsewhere. The people are friendly, the city is in a progressive transformation, and loyalty to the city is fierce. I'd defend Detroit to my grave. Good luck on your decision.

EDIT: Realized I titled one of the districts incorrectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 02:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I know of, but possibly? I'd be curious if you could link it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> His dad gives him a hickey in place of nipples every night while he's asleep. You know, so he isn't abnormal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 22:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 22:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/nocontext </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When this shit happens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 20:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just received a reminder for a meeting at work...over one year late. Thanks Outlook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 17:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 01:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha, as good of a reason as any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 01:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm half English. I'm living on a prayer at this point to equalize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rocky Patel Vintage 2008 Cameroon, Woodford Reserve, and England vs. Italia. It's a beautiful day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 00:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 21:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well sonovabitch! I tried accessing it through the program itself. I'm going to go pretend I didn't do anything technologically stupid today ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 20:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have that menu for some reason. Samsung GS5 if that makes a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 19:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> scene selection..I can't seem to find any settings or unlock areas otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 17:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great, but the "reddit" code doesn't seem to be working for me :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 03:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is held late in the evening through the night. Usually starts around 7PM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 02:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every Monday there is a bar that is selected along with a starting point. People ride there, imbibe for a little bit, then ride back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 21:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the turn-out has been impressive. Detroit is a beautiful place to ride, it's been nice to see that so many others have discovered that as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 16:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a "serious note"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've experienced Redditors' doubts when I talk about Detroit having a very large bicycling community. This is a typical turn-out at Slow Roll, an event that happens every Monday. [x-post from videos] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 15:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've experienced Redditors' doubts when I talk about Detroit having a very large bicycling community. This is a typical turn-out at Slow Roll, an event that happens every Monday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 15:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 18:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/nocontext </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 18:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why hello there!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 21:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it funny that Joe Louis Arena is still up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 16:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So move there then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 16:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I was writing this in the back of a taxi and didn't have the ability to fact check, but I'm willing to bet that you're way closer than myself on that one. Beers affect my memory recollection ability, so my apologies for that.

EDIT: Autocorrect fails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 03:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Metropolitan and city are not one in the same. After the era of white flight, population in the city had declined test over year for a long period of time. The city is under 700k residency for the first time since the 50s, with the square mileage to fit NYC and LA within it's limits combined. The lack of many tall buildings is also due to the gothic architecture of the time which didn't allow for extreme heights when the city was becoming industrialized. So tl;dl Toronto is much bigger and newer at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 03:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 01:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 00:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My high rise on Washington Blvd. I consider it one of the best views in the city, I was glad I held out for an east side view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 00:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. Hence why this isn't more than mildly satisfying... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The perfect-perfect pump. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 21:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The beautiful city of Detroit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 21:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 21:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved to Detroit last year, and I would do it again 100 out of 100 times. If it helps you understand, I am the type of person who can't sit still; I need something to do at all times. I have not spent a single day bored in this city. 

From Slow Roll, to Come Play Detroit, to DCFC, to the Copa Cup Detroit City soccer league, to the many bars within walking distance, to the phenomenal food, all the way to the festivals and events throughout the city essentially every week: There is something to love in this city no matter who you are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 17:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a theory that he was left off so Klinsmann could evaluate and give experience to the younger players in "the group of death" because they realistically don't have a chance to advance. That way, when the next cup comes around those players will have experience and will make for a much better shot in 2020 where Donovan will absolutely not be playing in. Keep in mind that Klinsmann just received a 4 year extension, so he has no reason to "win now". His real evaluation will be the next WC, not this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meditating Baby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 17:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 16:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By looking at the construction of a spoke in a wheel, the correct answer absolutely is the top spokes. The inner rivets along the rims are only held in place by the spoke being screwed in, thus pulling it snug to the rim wall. There is nothing preventing it from moving it towards the tire tube. Therefore, compression is not used for support, only tension. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 18:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Type one Diabetes and the inability to gain weight (6'4" 170 lbs; finding small-tall shirts is a challenge). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 15:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fudge". 

Cue the stoned grin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you for the translation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 23:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-11 21:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I had this issue too. It has to do with your Outlook account having a child setting on. I don't remember where I found the info to get it taken off, but you should be able to find it by wading through the settings. Best of luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 17:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My motherfucking sides. This is brilliant. Long Live Harold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 16:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was nice weather for the game yesterday (finally). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The old man would be proud. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 15:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 15:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone likes that lamp more than the old man. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 15:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's one of us. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 21:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These park jobs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 19:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 17:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's truly underrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 00:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I found their food to be delicious, personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 20:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met a couple of the guys who live in the penthouses in the Westin, 24grille is their preferred happy hour spot. I took solace in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
