<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3447</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Angela Merkel's visit to Washington postponed because of impending winter storm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A company owned by the family of Jared Kushner, U.S. President Donald Trump's son-in-law, stands to receive over $400 million from China's Anbang Insurance Group, that is investing in a Manhattan building owned by the Kushners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German Chancellor Angela Merkel has postponed her trip to Washington to visit with US President Donald Trump due to a late-winter storm expected in the Northeast US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A company owned by the family of Jared Kushner, U.S. President Donald Trump's son-in-law, stands to receive over $400 million from China's Anbang Insurance Group, that is investing in a Manhattan building owned by the Kushners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama lawyers move fast to join fight against Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama lawyers move fast to join fight against Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Rodrigo Duterte of Philippines said he has told his country's military to assert Philippine ownership of a large ocean region off the country's northeastern coast where Chinese survey ships were spotted last year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi forces are facing the final battle to defeat Isis in the country for good as elite troops engage in a gruelling building-by-building fight in the last few extremist-controlled neighbourhoods of Mosul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egyptian Prosecutor Orders Release of Ousted President Hosni Mubarak </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook bars use of its social data for surveillance tools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pipes in New Zealand's capital are leaking a million litres (220,000 gallons) of water a day as a result of the powerful November 2016 earthquake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas lawmaker ridicules anti-abortion measures by filing anti-masturbation bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the news article:

Tests on his blood in France found no evidence that he had been poisoned but Kara-Murza insists there is no other explanation.

He said: I have absolutely no doubt that this was a deliberate poisoning, that it was intended to kill because, as I mentioned already, the doctors told my wife that its about a 5% chance of survival. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Russian political activist claims Vladimir Putin has poisoned him twice in two failed assassination attempts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Catalan leader Artur Mas has been banned from holding office for two years after organising an illegal independence referendum in 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump expected to announce vehicle emissions rules review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The European Court of Justice (ECJ) will determine on Tuesday whether an employer can prohibit staff from wearing the Islamic headscarf in the first case of its kind before the EU's top court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sturgeon declares she WILL call a fresh Scottish independence referendum for 2018 in response to Brexit as she blames PM for forcing her hand by not getting Scotland a special EU deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what if the ghosts follows him to wherever he goes, what will be his next move? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While him and his wife were feeling Ghost, their child didnt care, was busy running round the house and having fun.

From the article

He told Veja magazine: "I felt something strange there. I wasn't able to sleep right from the first night. The energy wasn't good.

"Marcela felt the same thing. Only Michelzinho, who went running from one end to the other, liked it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discovery of Earths Oldest Fossil Suggests Life Elsewhere in Our Solar System </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discovery of Earths Oldest Fossil Suggests Life Elsewhere in Our Solar System </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being bullied during childhood might have lifelong health effects related to chronic stress exposure -- including an increased risk for heart disease and diabetes in adulthood, according to a research review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican Steve King suggests Muslim children are stopping our civilisation being restored </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John McCain tells Donald Trump to prove Obama wiretap claim or else retract it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President of Brazil has reportedly moved out of his official residence because of ghosts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aides to U.S. President Donald Trump on Sunday attacked the credibility of the nonpartisan agency that will analyse the costs of a replacement for Obamacare, as the White House sought to quell opposition from many Republicans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A British intelligence agency has told political parties to protect themselves against potential cyber attacks, citing allegations that Russian hackers tried to influence last year's U.S. presidential election. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cairo's population is set to grow by 500,000 this year, more than any other city in the world, adding to the pressure on an Egyptian economy struggling to recover from six years of political turmoil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 34 people were killed and 17 injured in northern Haiti late on Saturday after a bus crashed into a parade of pedestrians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists develop 'Trojan horse' molecule to fight crop fungus linked to cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists develop 'Trojan horse' molecule to fight crop fungus linked to cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China is working to develop a new spaceship that can both fly in low-Earth orbit and land on the moon, the announcement comes shortly after the US announced plans to fly two private citizens around the Moon by late 2018, under private aerospace company SpaceX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China is working to develop a new spaceship that can both fly in low-Earth orbit and land on the moon, the announcement comes shortly after the US announced plans to fly two private citizens around the Moon by late 2018, under private aerospace company SpaceX </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobel peace prize winner Malala Yousafzai has told an education conference that she has received an offer to study at a UK university </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bear has been killed after it escaped from its enclosure at a zoo in the northern German town of Osnabruck. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of Americas most high-profile prosecutors is considering refusing an order from the attorney general to resign, and instead demand that President Donald Trump fire him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Countries around the world must augment controls over the use of pesticides for they are causing 200,000 deaths a year due to poisoning, UN experts have warned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man and woman have been publicly lashed in Indonesia for allegedly having sex outside of marriage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The family of a repair technician killed in an auto parts factory accident is suing five robotics companies they say are responsible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 12:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family of technician slain by factory robot sues everyone involved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 12:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 30 people were killed by two bombs in the Syrian capital Damascus on Saturday targeting Shi'ite pilgrims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 12:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dutch Prime Minister Mark Rutte on Saturday barred a plane carrying Turkey's foreign minister from landing, saying his visit would be a threat to public order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 12:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European countries have stopped mass rallies by top Turkish politicians to attract support for a constitutional referendum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article, it appears to be part of the transition process, nothing to fight over.

Read:

"U.S. Attorney General Jeff Sessions has asked the remaining 46 chief federal prosecutors appointed by President Barack Obama who have not already resigned to do so "in order to ensure a uniform transition," the Justice Department said on Friday" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remaining 46 U.S. attorneys hired by Obama asked to resign - Justice Department </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three families who helped shelter former U.S. National Security Agency contractor Edward Snowden in Hong Kong in 2013 after his mass leak of information about surveillance programs have asked Canada for asylum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police in Kosovo have seized more than 2m fake banknotes in a taxi, in what authorities say is the largest seizure in decades </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US President Donald Trump has invited Palestinian leader Mahmoud Abbas to visit the White House "very soon" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. military said on Friday it plans to forge ahead with building the THAAD missile defense system in South Korea, separating the issue from a political crisis in Seoul that saw President Park Geun-hye's removal from office on Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone here know this law please?

"The office of the chief medical examiner said that details of his death were being withheld to comply with international law"

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this mean the cause of death is "top Secret"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexican forces have detained a high-level member of the Italian mafia in Mexico wanted for drug trafficking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pope Francis has sent 100,000 euros ($106,090) to the poor in the ravaged Syrian city of Aleppo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alphabet's self-driving car division Waymo seeks to completely block Uber's autonomous vehicle operations, according to new documents filed in federal court Friday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The US state department has instructed New York City's chief medical examiner not to disclose the cause of death of Russia's ambassador to the United Nations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael T. Flynn, President Trumps first national security adviser, acted as a foreign agent representing the interests of Turkeys government in exchange for more than $500,000 during last years campaign even as he was advising Mr. Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France issues two more arrest warrants over Paris attacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook is using AI to identify suicidal thoughts -- but it's not enough, experts say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook is using AI to identify suicidal thoughts -- but it's not enough, experts say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google gets go-ahead to break ground on new futuristic HQ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People smuggling in Europe comparable to the illegal drugs market, warns report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Several injured' after man goes on axe rampage at Dusseldorf station in Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poland warns of disunity across the EU after Donald Tusk reelected European Council president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swallowing just a few drops of a new vaccine could protect against the deadly Ebola virus. The new immunization is not meant for humans, but chimpanzees and gorillas, for which Ebola is a devastating disease as well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scotland could hold an independence referendum in the autumn of 2018, just months before Britain is due to leave the European Union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkey Seeks FBIs Help to Restore Deleted Messages of Russian Ambassadors Assassin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish prime minister promises to speed up trial of jailed American pastor swept up in a crackdown after an attempted military coup last July </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Purported U.S. airstrikes kill 14 civilians, including some children on a village east of ISIS de-facto capital in Syria, activist groups said Thursday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two people have been killed and two others injured after a road bridge in Italy collapsed onto a motorway that ran beneath it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nigel Farage visited the Ecuadorian embassy in West London on Thursday morning - but refused to say whether he had met with WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks to provide tech firms access to CIA hacking tools, its founder Julian Assange said Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As Xabi Alonso retires from football, here is one of the best goals football has ever seen scored by him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 13:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadas foreign minister says Russia is spreading disinformation about her grandfather </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kenya to hire foreign doctors to get public hospitals running again after talks failed to end a strike that has crippled healthcare for 94 days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two UN workers who were among 11 Malaysians banned from leaving North Korea have flown out of the country, the UN says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 20 die in suicide attacks on wedding in Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At least 110 people are reported to have died so far as a result of severe starvation and famine in Somalia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video: Lionel Messi amazing reaction after Sergi Roberto's winning Goal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
