<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1922</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 21:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the Muslim is using double standards by applying one logic to himself and another one to his opponent.

Because the Muslim never followed the same logic as the atheist to begin with. Why would he use the atheist's flawed reasoning for himself? Watch the video again. The Muslim in the video DOES claim that you can be certain about things, the atheist in the video does not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 00:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's not that Muslims don't believe that you can't be certain about anything.  The Muslim in the video used that argument (incorrectly) to prove his point.

The Muslim showed very clearly to the atheist that he can't assert that God doesn't exist. The Muslim in the video does claim that you can be certain about things, the atheist in the video does not.  In the end, the atheist realized his mistake and accepted it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 00:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad that bias is preventing you to see what just happened. Muslims don't believe that you can't be certain about anything. That's just the conclusion the atheist reached in the conversation and therefore he was wrong in his assertion about God not existing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 05:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another rephrased topic just asking about your favorite movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 11:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need a book to understand it? Doesn't that prove the point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 12:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, yeah I highly doubt you received that message from regulars of r/Islam.  Unless you're willing to show proof.   If someone sends you spam, you block them.  The mods can't do anything about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 04:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debating on the internet is usually pointless.  It often  turns into people trying their hardest to prove others wrong.  If you want to understand the opposing view better or have someone understand your view better, have a dialogue. In a dialogue, people are far more likely to look at the opposing view with an open mind and change their original position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 00:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The assumptions are backed by facts. 

How do you know he was traveling alone and what his urges were?

 Astaghfirullah at your blasphemy.

lolwut. 

 Yes, so let him admit that he made the account to seek a halal wife.

Because he DID NOT make the account.  There was no need for him to make the account.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 00:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  1) He is alone, thus has the urge.
 2) Away from his wife, so no risks.
 3) Fewer people know him in Australia.

You are now making assumptions on how he was feeling and what his intentions were. You are not all-knowing.

And he said that it's allowed to seek another wife which is Islamically allowed, or are you a progressive who thinks that polygamy is haram now? His argument illustrated that using a website like Ashley Madison makes no sense, since there is no point to cheat on your spouse, you can always look for a second wife.  This is just more proof that he has no need to sign up for an account on Ashley Madison. 

Looks like all your arguments have been exhausted. I hope you learned something today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 23:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yet again you have failed to explain the fictional hackers intentions.

I have already said comments ago, we do not know the hacker's intentions. This would lead into speculation, which you seem to be  good at.

It's much harder to believe that Hamza, instead of making the account from the conveniency of his home, decided to wait until he went to Australia right before a Islamic seminar to make the account using his public address and then never use the account for anything ever again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 23:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you don't "manually" pay for subscriptions each and every month.

Exactly. So there is no proof that he used the account in UK. Your earlier comment "And then when he made subsequent payments, his location was from UK" was meaningless. You still haven't read the article. We already know the account was made in Australia, we know the emails went to spam folder which he explained. The only thing the hacker would need to do would be to sign up for it once with credit card info. He would NOT have to travel to UK to pay. Can you please accept your mistake here and move on?

 that doesn't mean anything since he only acknowledged that oddity but never defended himself against it. 

He doesn't need to defend it. He never made the argument. Do you know what a straw man is?

 Indeed the simplest explanation is the correct one. Mr. Tzortzis was looking for some zina to do.

This is clear slander and is against Islam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 22:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like you moved away from your last point, that's good.  

 the ashley madison account in hopes that it will get hacked? 

This is a straw man argument. Hamza even said himself that the hacker couldn't have known that Ashley Madison was going to be hacked. No one is claiming that the hacker wanted AshleyMadison to be hacked EXCEPT YOU. 

 Really? If they hacked him for money, they should have used it, 

This is nothing but speculation. We have almost no idea who the hacker was or what they wanted to do or what else they did.  You can't rely on speculation to consider someone guilty of a crime.

 If his deen is tied to your deen, who am i to stop you

You do realize that backbiting and slander is haram, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 22:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone find her Facebook account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 22:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I am saying subsequent PAYMENTS were made in UK

Have you ever used a credit card online before? He was charged monthly.  You keep ignoring this point.

 meanwhile the first PAYMENT was made in Australia, on the same date when he was in Australia.

Which was mentioned in the article. Did you bother to read it? His credit card information was taken in Australia. How is this proof that he was manually paying for it every month in the UK? The only way for you to prove this is if you can show that he used the account in UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 22:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the tech industry. I know quite well what an ip address is and like i said before, the Australian ip address was already discussed in the article. You clearly have no proof that the Ashley Madison account was used in  UK because it was NOT used in UK. It's sad that you can't accept your own mistake, but whatever it's your choice to believe whatever nonsense you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 21:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And then when he made subsequent payments, his location was from UK.

He was automatically charged every month. Have you ever used a credit card online before? You would need proof that the Ashley Madison account was being used in the UK.  Where is this proof? 

How old are you? It feels like i'm talking to a kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 21:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The information released shows the ip address when the account was made and date as well.

Yeah, it was explained in the article Hamza referenced. What's your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 19:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those points have been refuted months ago. 

 And the fact he deleted the comments and then even his "rebuttal" was deleted as well is insane. He is stretching the facts a bit too much:

Yes, because he was receiving more attention than he expected. thousands of people were raiding his facebook page, including media outlets. He was receiving a lot of hateful comments. What did you expect?

 But since they magically knew Ashley Madison is going to be hacked, they quietly paid for it.

No one said that the hackers knew Ashley Madison was going to be hacked.

 How the hell could he not know he is paying for something? It shows up in your monthly bill you know.

He already explained that on his facebook, this happens to thousands of people by the way.

 He says he has filed a police report, but when the users asked him to show him the report, he refuse.

There is no need for him to show you the report.

 His account was created when he was in Australia, and it matches with the information on where the account was created. Oh hackers did that.

His credit card information was taken in Austrailia, the rest of his information was already public knowledge. The person who made the account used his public information including his public email address. 

 The hackers traveled with him to Australia to sign him up to the site. And then came back with him to UK again to pay for the site to make it look like he paid for it.

That's a strawman argument. The hacker wouldn't need to travel anywhere and Hamza never claimed such a thing to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 05:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's funny is that ex-Muslims like you who "studied" Islam before they left it,  actually think i'm in the wrong here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 16:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think OP was referring to the fact that ALL Muslim majority countries are literal fucking shit stains on the world map. They were shit stains long before ISIS or the Syrian Civil War.

Again, try learning more than a century of history. 

 So those medieval fucked up barbaric punishments aren't facets of Shariah Law?

There is no such term as "shariah law" and what does chopping off hands have to do with economic prosperity or societal degeneration? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 04:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "*Time has proved the exact opposite*" lol, it looks you're saying this after the recent Syrian migration. Try learning more than a century of history before making such a silly statement.  I guess Assad was a role-model Muslim ruler, and groups like isis weren't formed because of what happened in Iraq a decade ago, but rather they formed because of their love of Islam...

"*Muslims say that not following Islamic laws will lead to economic and societal degeneration*". Really, we say that? What the heck is "Islamic laws". Let me guess, you mean chopping off hands and stoning adulterers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slavery: A Past   Present Tragedy (Live presentation starts soon) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 01:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 23:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could give you answers for the first two if you are willing to consider theism again, but the third one seems more arbitrary. It's not like Muslims believe they shoot some kind of 'worship projectile' that has to hit a target for their prayer to be counted. Muslims never saw it that way, rather they have to pray together and are told to face one direction. It's like someone arguing that if you face a wall or a chair, your prayer doesn't count because you were supposed to face kaaba. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 02:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I went back to the Imam who first took me in and asked a load of questions, and he never had any satisfactory answers.

Can you give an example of a question that you had? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 23:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He already mentioned this years ago. He even had that long article about it on his website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 19:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the pope go and meet her, or did she go out and meet the pope? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 18:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People are surprised over this? What did you guys expect from the Pope to say to her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 01:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're an Atheist, why did you ask me to show proof that the Quran is from God? If you don't believe in God, then obviously you won't believe God revealed a book to humans. This is just simple logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 04:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  one must first believe it is written by God to see the proof that it was written by God.

That's not what i'm saying.  I'm trying to figure out what type of proof would convince you that this is a revealed book. I asked you twice already, do you believe God exists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 21:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can't help you with basic literacy.

Okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 21:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> .... What are you talking about? Are you the same user as 1121231234 and are you an atheist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 19:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If I accepted the view that a book could be divinely inspired, what proof would you show?

As mentioned before, if someone believes that God does send revelation to humanity, then the person would need to study the Quran with an open mind and contemplate over it.

 What is the challenge? Can it not be translated into English?

It doesn't matter.  If you don't believe a book can possibly prove itself to be Divinely originated, then logically you won't accept any proof the book makes for the argument. I'm not even sure if you believe in God, do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 16:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well i can't show you a proof from the book if you don't think a book can possibly prove itself to be Divinely originated.

 I'd be looking for a specific proof that isn't people's reaction to a text.

Everyone goes through their own unique journey in life and will have a different reaction to the text and it's arguments.  You will react, regardless of whether or not you believe, so i don't know what you mean here.

 Is that reason based on logical steps to defining reason

Do you believe in God's existence? There is a challenge in the Quran i know of, but i don't think you know classical Arabic and i it wouldn't matter since you don't believe a book can prove itself to be divine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 16:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What would be the evidence in a text that it was divinely written?

I already gave a general explanation twice now. People are guided by different ways and different verses can push them to accept Islam, but you appear to be looking for some specific type of proof. Can you give an example of how a text can prove itself to You that it was divinely originated?

 The problem with the the last line is it sounds like you are condemning atheists for not believing

I wasn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 06:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  an atheist would look for proof that a human couldn't have written it, that it is different from other holy books

Yes, you can use reason and contemplate over a book to determine if it was man-made or if is Divinely originated.  Some people for example who have read the Quran, have concluded for themselves that it could not have been written by a man. There is a lot more that can be said about this subject and there are other proofs that are used, but a prerequisite is that a person should be sincerely searching for the truth and must be willing to accept something even if it goes against his desires/ego. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 04:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good way to determine if a person is a true prophet of God is to check the book that was revealed to him. Does the book explain the purpose of life, does it give us more knowledge about who our Maker is, does it guide us toward good and move us away from evil, does it provide good lessons, stories and parables that we can benefit from, etc. We need to use reason and take time to contemplate over the message to determine if it is indeed the word of God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 03:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What I do find useful about debates is that when my arguments are challenged, I'm forced to think about them from a different angle to propose counter arguments. I may even form better arguments as a result, and gain more understanding about the positions I hold. I also see it as a healthy mental activity, if you're interested in it.

That's part of the problem with debating. When someone's argument is refuted, they will often attempt to rationalize their old position from a completely different angle or bring in a new related subject into the discussion turning it into a longer convoluted debate. They will never be able to admit that they're original position was wrong, and they will become close-minded toward the opposing view regardless of what they say. 

If someone is planning to debate me for the sake of mental exercise, then that's a good reason not to debate such a person.  If you want mental exercise, do math problems or something. If you want to understand the opposing view better or have someone understand your view better, have a dialogue. In a dialogue,  people are far more likely to look at the opposing view with an open mind and change their original position.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 03:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debating on the internet is usually pointless. I just came across a recent [atheist circlejerk topic](https://www.reddit.com/r/exmuslim/comments/3lyvq2/muslim_vs_exmuslim_debate_does_allah_exist/) on /exmuslim where they were "debating" Muslims.  The same sub gave me -12 downvotes when i said a person should use reason to determine the validity of the Quran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 20:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atheists have been fuming over this story the last week. I've read so many jealous comments on reddit about all the attention Ahmed is getting, it's ridiculous. We get it, he didn't invent the clock, it's not his fault the media embellished his story.

There are so many people that still insist that it was intended to be a hoax bomb.  I'm not an expert but if you're going to bring a hoax bomb, wouldn't it be better to bring fake dynamite instead of some circuits inside a pencil case? And wouldn't it be better to have a countdown timer instead of a clock display that displays time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 20:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's a difference between learning from good non-muslims, and one of the biggest corrupters on earth and misguiders.

You can learn from any person just like you can learn from any teacher in school. Obviously we don't learn religious practices from the pope, but can learn other things.

 Plus, let's say all of what you're saying is correct, it's still not an excuse, just because others are doing wrong doesn't validate your wrong doing.

What exactly is my wrong-doing here? 

Can you at least admit that you have a terrible way of correcting people?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 05:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is hypocritical for you to say that i  should explain how Op's beliefs are wrong when you have some of the worst explanations on this sub when correcting others.

The first post of yours i linked to  shows how you completely dismiss the entire audio without listening to it.

The second post shows how terrible you are at explaining things. Don't you realize that when you say something like *"It's well known that Islam allows us to have slaves, back in the days, when we would kill the infidels, we would take their wives as slaves"*, then people on this mostly Western-forum are going to misunderstand that? You should have explained what a slave was in the past, what rights they had and how "slave" is different than the modern understanding today. "Infidel" is not even an Islamic term, but you should have explained the conditions that were used before engaging in battle by Muslims of the past and the rights the captives had, etc.   The way you explained it made it sound like that Muslims could have just killed whoever they wanted in the past and enslaved their wives.

Those were just two of your posts, but there are  other examples of your terrible explanations. Don't you ever think to yourself that perhaps you're being downvoted on this sub because what you're saying is wrong or poorly explained?

[Here's something you just posted today](https://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/3li13e/what_can_we_learn_from_pope_francis_as_muslims/cv6s963). It makes you sound childish, of course you can learn from non-Muslims just like how we go to school and learn from non-Muslims.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 01:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad how so many people are butthurt that this 14 year old boy is getting all this attention.   It's not his fault the media is embellishing his story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 01:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad how butthurt so many people are over this.  It's not his fault the media is embellishing his story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 01:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad how so many people are butthurt that this 14 year old boy is getting all this attention.   It's not his fault the media is embellishing his story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 23:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I  think it'd be better if you take the time to explain how these beliefs are wrong, instead of just being aggressive like that.

I find that funny coming from you. I've seen your post history with  [posts like this](https://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/3hz7av/feminism_in_islam_fatima_barkatulla_40_mins_on/cubxw7x) or [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/3ece8j/no_islam_is_not_inherently_misogynistic_heres_why/ctdnpbj).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 22:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like just another ex-Muslim who knows very little about Islam.  

*" I don't think there's a sky man that created us we evolved from animals before us. Also the concept of heaven and hell fire is messed up.  Allah is supposed to be the all mercifull but uses hell fire to threaten his servents"*

*"To live life and not worship a god that I don't have to be scared of and to relax knowing that I will go to hell if I disobey a dictator allah. No offense again"* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 19:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been asked many times before.  I think we should have flairs for countries or general religion flairs like: "atheist", "christian", "muslim".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 02:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that the Arab world was even more religious 1000 years ago. They just didn't see a conflict with science and religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 20:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a letter the school sent to the parents.](https://i.imgur.com/3Sq5o09.jpg) Turns out, they were only concerned for the child's safety lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 15:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But i thought you didn't believe in the existence of God, so obviously you won't accept the Quran.

Interesting how my comment gets -11 downvotes for saying that we should use reason to determine the veracity of the Quran. Just goes to show how rational this sub is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 04:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Muslim here. 

You don't have to rely on miracles or visions like that. God gave you a brain, you can use reason and contemplate over scripture.  You should pray to God sincerely from the bottom of your heart to show you the true path wherever it is. Then you should read the [Quran](http://legacy.quran.com/) and contemplate over it's message, and decide using reason whether or not this is indeed the word of God. Here is a [intro page to Islam](http://www.whyislam.org/islam/islam-explained/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 02:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meteorites contain iron, and some early civilizations used this iron (and not iron from the Earth) to make tools and artifacts: 

http://www.nature.com/news/iron-in-egyptian-relics-came-from-space-1.13091

I'm not sure about the picture you have though, scientists have different theories regarding Earth's early formation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 04:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another sensationalist story that does not deserve attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 06:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% serious.  More people are converting to Islam everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 06:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully someone can give you a informative answer, but the short answer is that Islam really is the Truth. That's why more people are converting to Islam in the West. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 17:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they now have to respond to the false report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 03:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/europe/saudi-arabia-offers-germany-200-mosques--one-for-every-100-refugees-who-arrived-last-weekend-10495082.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 03:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have solid evidence that they stole finances and resources from Syria? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 02:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even read it? It was a response to the numerous accusations that Saudi did  nothing for the Syrians.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 02:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saudi Arabia is misunderstood so much by the world. They now have to explain that  offering Germany 200 mosques was meant to be a  charitable gesture.  

And they are hated so much by the world too. Look at the thousands of comments on reddit, news forums and social media, celebrating or mocking the deaths of people who died in the crane incident. It's disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 19:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell him that you won't lie for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 12:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was more important because her decision affected more people, but you do have a point, that story got more attention then it deserved too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 03:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this news? Aren't there any  more pressing matters in the world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 20:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone is free to use this video without worrying about copyright infringement since the gorilla is the one with the camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 18:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because God is all powerful doesn't mean that He will do something that doesn't befit Him, like begetting a child, or committing sins or creating a rock so heavy that cannot be Lifted by Him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 19:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Honestly, you don't even need to read a refutation.

That's what i thought at first. But then i realized that i would be ignoring the the large magnitude of Islamophobes, some of them with degrees, who would be more than willing to believe this claim and use it to criticize Islam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 01:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Zakir's style. He has good memory, rumor has it that he memorized the Bible (probably not true though). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 18:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're comparing a speech with written material? This is just a small segment of a larger lecture and we don't know who the original audience is. It's not always easy for a person to give a speech while giving all the exact sources and references, especially when there are many references to list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 06:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is an important issue, and it got 5 upvotes already. The problem is that the the topic post seems very vague and interpretative.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 05:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly do you mean by "leaders", like an Imam? I would say to look for another authoritative figure in  your Muslim community that you can trust and tell them about the problem. You can start some kind of sister council if it's that serious, but you also need connection to some people on the men's side too that you can trust.  Every community is different. One masjid i go to has a box that anyone can write their complaints and put in, and it's read by the Imam (whom the community trusts) and that's good enough for them. Right now, the way you are describing the problem seems really vague. Physical abuse is very serious, but you need to look for strong evidence and testimony  if you want to take this further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 04:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I saw the way he was looking at me and it did not make me feel comfortable at all.

that's it? I thought you meant there was some type of physical abuse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 00:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. By the time the police come, the kids leave. And when the police leave, the kids come back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 19:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  He should be held responsible and so should Stalin for his actions.  I just find it strange that some people don't agree with Bush being responsible for the deaths of thousands of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the picture](http://d.ibtimes.co.uk/en/full/1455394/paolo-porpora.jpg?w=220). It's not bad, I'd probably be willing to pay $5 for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 18:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never even heard about this before. Person is being threatened for being on tv, so let's give him some more attention and more news coverage, that'll solve everything... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 17:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a slow punch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 17:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But i wouldn't say no. So my question still stands: Did George Bush kill thousands of Iraqi and Afghani civilians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 17:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did George Bush kill thousands of Iraqi and Afghani civilians? If your answer is no, then why would you think Stalin is guilty of mass murder?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 16:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did George Bush kill thousands of Iraqi and Afghani civilians? If your answer is no, then why would you think Stalin is guilty of mass murder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 07:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's when the What Would You Do crew stepped in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 06:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

So as the new kid it was a little tough getting into the flow of things at the school. My name would always be mispronounced (even though it is spelled how it sounds), I would always hear comments like terrorist, Osama, sand nigger, AYRAB, even some interesting ones like dune coon. Kids would say them out loud in class and the teacher would act as if they did not hear a thing. But I put up with it, there was nothing else I could do... But I never learned how to brush it off, it always hurt.

When I finally found a group of kids that were the LEAST ignorant I started speaking to them in class. I was asked by one of them, "Are you parents illegal?" as a joke, and I replied "Yeah we are all fresh off the boat obviously." We went on with the day and nothing exciting happened. But it was all coming to me the next morning...

I arrive to my first class of the day about 20 minutes late (Counter-Strike was more important than school). As I sit down in my chair there is a knock at the door, a counselor peeks his head in and points to me and says, "I have to take him out for a little while." to the teacher. I remember an overwhelming sense of joy for being pulled out of that terribly boring class but that joy quickly turned into confusion.

As I walked down the hallway alongside the counselor I asked him for the reason why I was getting out of class? He just replied "We have a few things to talk about." When I sat in the chair in front of his desk he leaned forward looking me right in the eye and said, "There are accusations that you father is going to do harm to some students tomorrow." I was flabbergasted, I quickly replied, "Are you being serious?" Still looking into my eyes he said, "We got information from students that overheard you, they said your father was coming to the school tomorrow to quote "Kill all the white people."" I told him that not only was this accusation ridiculous but obviously somebody just trying to target and harass me. He said he would have a talk with the other students and get back to me, so he sent me back to class.

A few hours passed and I was in my 3rd class of the day when the counselor peeks his head into the room and pulls me out again. I ask him if the situation has been cleared up and he says that we have to go through a few steps to fix this. In my head I was thinking, "FIX WHAT? I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING!" But I went along with it, I had no choice.

He walks me into the main office where I sit around waiting to talk with the principal. He walks out of his office and beckons me in, I sit across from him, with the assistant principal standing in the background, and he starts speaking about the accusations against me. At first it sounded like he understood I was being targeted but then he stated, "Even though this might just be harassment I need to make sure you understand the consequences." He waited for me to reply but I couldn't, I was too terrified of the helpless position I was in right now. He pulls out a manilla folder and pulls some papers of out them and begins to explain...

The first words of the explanation were, "According to the Patriot Act..." I saw this coming, I had dreaded it and now it was upon me, I was going to be detained, my family is going to be taken away, these kids have just destroyed my ENTIRE LIFE. But there was more, he continued, "Any suspected threats to our safety or the safety of the homeland can be dealt without due process of law." He stopped and explained, "That means they can take you and your family for any reason." I began crying as he finished that sentence, but it didn't phase him he continued, "This is a very serious thing you have done RawadSquad, the consequences are very real. In fact you can even be expelled." At this point all I kept saying over and over is, "I'm sorry but this is all a lie, these kids just hate me." After a minute or two the men looked at each other and said, "Let's see if we can fix this, we have arranged a meeting with the students who overheard you and their families." I got up and was escorted out of the door.

On the other side of that door was my father, with a confused look on his face. Apparently they had contacted him and told him to come speak with the principal as well, which they did as I waited outside. The principal explained the Patriot Act to my father as well believe it or not. When my father exited the room, the principal and assistant principal followed behind, and they directed us to an adjacent room, this was where the family meeting would take place. 

I walk in to see two girls (Caucasian) and one of their mothers is there, and the other girl's father is present. We all sit down around the table and the first thing I say is, "Why would you make up a lie like that about me? Why do you hate me, because I have a different skin color?" My father grabs my arm and tells me to settle down, but the girls reply, "We heard you saying all this stuff yesterday, your parents are illegal." I was dumbfounded, I hadn't even remembered what I had said that previous day, I was even more amazed that they eavesdropped from across the room to hear that. I replied back, "That is not true, it was a joke and why would you say my dad is coming to kill all the white people tomorrow? Where did you get that?" They both stated that they had heard me say it as well, which is a COMPLETE fabrication.

Some more discussion went on in the meeting that I forget about but I remember my father apologizing to EVERYBODY in the room in my behalf and even offering proof of his citizenship, it was the most humiliating moment in my life, I can't imagine how a proud man like my father dealt with it. The meeting ended after we all apologized, even though the girls apologies were disgustingly shallow.

I remember the car ride home, my father and I broke down into tears. Our family had almost been torn apart, all because of ignorance and hate. A joking response to a racist question almost got my expelled, and almost had my family detained. That day I realized that the actions of very few on 9/11 had changed my life forever. 

[Original comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/spwhw/muslims_of_reddit_how_much_did_your_life_change/c4g5zqf) (wasn't me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 06:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand why some people there talk about family problems or life as an apostate. What i don't understand is some of the users who are completely obsessed with hating Islam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 06:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand why some people there talk about family problems and life as an apostate. What i don't understand is some of the users who are completely obsessed with hating Islam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslims of Reddit, how much did your life change after 9/11? Crosspost (X-post/AskReddit) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 06:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 06:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [gif](http://i.imgur.com/XAq719l.gif). That could explain why he doesn't smile often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 17:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's insulting to suggest that I form my opinions off of google search results of other people's opinions.

This gif doesn't have to be about you.

 Some of us think reason trumps faith, and that's why we don't understand why you or anyone would choose your faith.

No one said that you have to give up reason to accept Islam.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 20:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living in a land that follows ideals of Islam united under a khalifah sounds nice, but that's all theoretical.   I'm not sure i understand where exactly you're going with this. How exactly are you going to carry out this idea of yours? 

And keep in mind that no matter how you choose your policies, there will almost always be a number of Muslims who disagree with each of your points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 06:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slavery was an institutionalized practice for many parts of the world, [including in Africa](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Slavery_in_Africa).   Slavery took on many forms and [Islam had it's own rules.](https://www.reddit.com/r/islam/wiki/slavery) It's very easy for a person to say today that "slavery is wrong and evil" but to go back in time and overturn a integral part of a civilization would be a radical thing to do and could actually cause more harm to the society.

Slavery has been outlawed by unanimous consensus and it's hard to imagine how Muslims can export slavery back into our time in a Islamically valid way.



 If Islam in a pro-slavery religion, I am done

That's a quite ironic statement to make, especially considering how many slaves accepted Islam in the early history. One of the things that encouraged slaves to this faith was how Islam lacked a hierarchical structure.  Even in recent history, a large percentage of African slaves that were brought to America were originally Muslims.

[Islam, Slavery and the African - By Abdullah Hakim Quick](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dcbWt27UieA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 21:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be really careful when learning about recent events from VICE news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 05:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone likes being praised or approved of, but i see this as only a problem if you start performing wrong/haram acts for the sake of pleasing other people. I think this is harder for teens facing peer pressure but it can get easier once we get older, once we realize how irrelevant other people's thoughts are about us.

http://productivemuslim.com/teens-part-1/

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=73kHTs-Mk-U </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 21:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those that can't see the article:

---

Kansas loves them some voter fraud hysteria. From going to the Supreme Court to try and make doubly-sure that non-citizens cant vote in their elections to setting up a voter fraud website where citizens can report every kind of voter fraud except the kinds that have actually happened in the state, Kansas is on the forefront of voter fraud readiness and protection.

Except, perhaps, when it comes to the machines they use to record their votes.

According to the Wichita Eagle, Wichita State mathematician Beth Clarkson has found irregularities in election returns from Sedgwick County, along with other counties throughout the United States, but has faced stiff opposition from the state in trying to confirm whether the irregularities are fraud or other, less-nefarious anomalies.

Analyzing election returns at a precinct level, Clarkson found that candidate support was correlated, to a statistically significant degree, with the size of the precinct. In Republican primaries, the bias has been toward the establishment candidates over tea parties. In general elections, it has favored Republican candidates over Democrats, even when the demographics of the precincts in question suggested that the opposite should have been true.

Clarksons interest in election returns was piqued by a 2012 paper released by analysts Francois Choquette and James Johnson showing the same pattern of election returns, which favor establishment Republican candidates in primaries and general elections. The irregularities are isolated to precincts that Central Tabulator voting machines  machines that have previously been shown to be vulnerable to hacking. The effects are significant and widespread: According to their analysis, Mitt Romney could have received over a million extra votes in the 2012 Republican primary, mostly coming at the expense of Rick Santorum and Newt Gingrich. President Obama also ceded significant votes to John McCain due to this irregularity, as well.

You can read the paper in full here.

Voting machine, via Wikimedia Commons

While Clarkson has found the same statistical irregularity in a number of localities, her efforts to confirm whether they amount to fraud have been centered on Sedgwick County, Kansas, due to the localitys use of Real Time Voting Machine Paper Tapes, which provide a paper trail that other localities dont have. However, her efforts to verify Sedgwick Countys election returns have been repeatedly shut down.

She first requested a recount of the 2013 election, but the timeframe in which a recount could have been requested had passed. She then requested the machines computer records from the Sedgwick County registrar, which told her to kindly shove off and sue Secretary of State Kris Kobach if she wanted the records so badly.

When Clarkson initially filed her lawsuit requesting the paper records from the voting machines, her suit was denied because a judge ruled that the paper records constituted ballots, shielding them from the states open records law. This ruling is suspect at best, given that the paper records to not have voters names assigned to them; they only record when and how a ballot was cast for recount purposes.

She then sought a court order giving her access to a sample of voting records in order to check voting machines error rates. This order was ignored by the Secretary of States office, despite their being legally required to respond to her within 30 days. The office later said that they didnt realize they had received her request.

Given Kansass professed diehard commitment to combatting voter fraud, one would think that they would be all for analysis into whether the integrity of their elections have been compromised. Apparently youd be wrong.

--- 

[Mirror, alternate link](http://americablog.com/2015/08/mathematician-actual-voter-fraud-kansas-republicans.html?utm_source=feedburner utm_medium=feed utm_campaign=Feed%3A+Americablog+%28AMERICAblog+News+%29)

---

edit: thanks for the gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 21:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the companions of the prophet (pbuh) lived in our time, they would have acted based on the circumstances of our time. Different actions for different contexts. Certain Salafi groups can't seem to grasp this thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 21:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every country makes mistakes just like how every Muslim makes mistakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 05:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of Muslims in the West are delaying marriage or can't even get married. If only there was some of kind of program or event where hundreds of Muslim couples can be married off at the same time. Get the process finished with and move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 03:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socrates is more likely to be a prophet than Mirza Ghulam Ahmad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 14:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you read about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 03:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They consist mainly of 2nd generation Americans from upper class or upper middle-class backgrounds. You can't ignore the obvious issues with this.

Is this true? I didn't know that and i honestly didn't realize it would be a issue to sign up to take the class for free.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 01:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are don't have the money, you can still take part in many of these programs after you sign some forms or be sponsored by someone.  And these aren't the only resources you can use to learn Arabic, you know.

  The rest will be condemned as being bad Muslims and not 'gaining' (read, 'paying for') knowledge.

??? Why would someone be condemned for not being able to do something they don't have the financial means for?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 23:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is nothing compared to what students pay for college courses. Why do we have this double standard where we should only be expected to pay for secular knowledge but not Islamic knowledge?  If this is too expensive for you, like it is for me, then there are also free resources for us out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 23:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From my experience almost half the students that attend an Al-Maghrib class don't even pay, or at least they don't pay the full price.  And Islamic teachers should get a decent paycheck so they don't have to rely on getting another job.  Just look at how much more expensive college classes are. The prices that Al-Maghrib and Bayyinah ask for are far cheaper in comparison.  

 you're not going to humiliate yourself asking for free money when it's not an absolute necessity for life.

I would imagine masjids and Muslim communities  feel much worse when they beg for money, because they have to say it openly to everyone. Whereas if you want to take a class for free, you just talk to one guy and sign some papers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 13:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahmadiyyism shares a lot of the same beliefs with mainstream Muslims but they add another prophet which is completely sacrilegious and they  interpret the Quran and hadith very differently. I have personally studied their religion and found many problems with it that contradict mainstream Islam.  I made one of my topics [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/islam/comments/1vltgo/some_questions_for_the_ahmadiyya_community/).  I recommend watching [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E-yRFudnT9A) of a Muslim explaining the differences and why he left ahmadiyya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 18:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My comment was in response to the Prophet's tomb, (pbuh).  **The news article you brought up about "Saudi plan to remove tomb of Prophet Muhammad" is misleading.**

 like i said earlier its different from one school to another. the same article has this comment.

Yes and the same article discusses that. Don't just skip to  the comments on the bottom of the article.  

 The realities of history, the truth of demolishing many archaeological sites, historical locations, and other damages to the two holiest sites in Islam is something that is concrete, recorded, and undeniable. There is no doubt, a time, a place, and a discourse that must be had on the destruction of historical sites (I plan on writing a critical analysis of the destruction and preservation of historical sites in the Haramain). However, many do not know about the existence and the work of the organizations to preserve historical sites. In fact, the Center for Historical Studies and Research of Madinah has an entire division that oversees preservation of archaeological sites in Madinah, makes recommendations to the government body overseeing expansion, and I have personally witnessed the director signing 18 sites to be preserved in the future expansion of the Prophet allallhu 'alayhi wa sallam (peace and blessings of Allh be upon him)'s masjid.   Another organization that does the same in Mecca is called the Al-Furqan Islamic Heritage Foundation, and many other organizations exist both in Mecca and Madinah that work to preserve historical and archaeological sites as best as they can.  But what must be realized, what must resonate, is that there is no doubt that this strategy of manufactured journalism to sow discord is prevalent and strategically placed.

---

 When the facts are pointed out to many that the article contains false information, most seem to not care, the reality is we can't forget that Saudi did or but in Saudi type rhetoric is spreading. Even academics that lay claim to scholastic standard, even journalists, even educators many are falling prey to the exact intention of the article the sowing of discord.  For many equating Saudi to not just a government but to an ideology that pigeonhole others is becoming comfortable, again. The they and us is something that spread through the discussions on social media, no matter which spectrum the person belonged to. The standing and representing movements rather than Islam again reared its ugly head Many are letting their feelings dictate their rationaleit doesn't matter if the assertions in the article are false, there is injustice that needs to be spoken against, and criticism that needs to be made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 18:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That same story about the supposed removal of the tomb keeps popping up in the news and has been debunked

http://muslimmatters.org/2014/09/03/of-tombs-madinah-and-manufactured-journalism-the-reality-behind-the-independent-article-on-the-prophets-grave/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 02:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea. I personally don't have a problem with OP posting this article here as long as he tells others that this is an ahmadiyya article, especially when the article says that  "true Islam" is to follow the Ahmadiyya khalifah.  OP should know that deceiving people is wrong and i am quite aware the tactics used by Ahmadis to invite people to their own faith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 21:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we stop posting these Ahmadiyya articles disguised as Muslim articles? And before people start downvoting, **read the article for yourself**. 

 "On the other side, we see His Holiness the Khalifa of Islam, Mirza Masroor Ahmad, who is head of the Ahmadiyya Muslim Community. Under this Khalifa, tens of millions of Muslims in 206 nations are united into one community of Muslims and are dedicated to observing justice, engaging in dialogue, and maintaining involvement and service to local communities."

 " the Khalifa of Islam presents the true Islam that has a proven history of conquering radicalism with peace. "

For those that are not informed, the Ahmadiyya community  teaches that mainstream Islam is inferior to their religion and that what they teach is peaceful and "true Islam". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bro discussing Shia-Sunni theology has always resulted in hatred and ignorant debates. I think it would be much better to talk about common grounds or maybe remove misconceptions if there are any.

Exactly.  And WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO LOOK INTO SUNNI-SHIA DEBATES DURING LAST NIGHTS OF RAMADAN?!?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aisha (ra) said: O Messenger of Allah! What if I knew which night Lailatul-Qadr was, then what should I say in it? He said Say - (Allahumma innaka affuwwun tuhibbul afwa fafu annee) 

O Allah You are The One Who pardons greatly, and loves to pardon, so pardon me. [at-Tirmithi and Ibn Majah with a Sahih Isnad]


[Explanation of dua](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uQyLyV0ooy4)

[Audio: dua repetition](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fJnxCVNXd6o) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short dua, say it many times during Laylatul Qadr </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 02:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 18:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like i said before, "chance" is not a thing or a being. It doesn't create or give life. Randomness is what we refer to something that already exists, that doesn't seem to have a pattern or order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 01:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already know that you don't believe in God, but then how do you explain your existence? random chance isn't an answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
