<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject331</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would I know? Is this some kind of cruel joke? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 16:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone wisely said: I hope everyone who voted for Jill Stein because "both parties are the same" have enough healing crystals to replace their health insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cook walked out of a bathroom without washing his hands. No thanks, I don't want escherichia coli with it

EDIT: a lot of people are telling me that he probably just washed his hands in a kitchen handwashing station. Thank you. I still think that he should have done that in the bathroom as well out of respect for people who saw him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some motherfucking poetry right there my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flater420 uses a very good metaphor to explain net neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 13:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what helped you become happy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 01:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew I would find this comment, I looked for it, and I found it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't fight with a pig. you'll both get dirty and the pig loves it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you're right. Unless you're going to lose your health insurance. In that case, well, you're fucked, chicken little </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe remember to fucking vote, next time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The damages they can do in two years, tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not American, and I sincerely wonder: why are you so obsessed with big or small government? What does that actually mean? Lower taxes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A-hem

http://www.wsj.com/articles/trump-visa-ban-also-applies-to-citizens-with-dual-nationality-state-department-says-1485628654 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that even constitutional? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ma s, votiamo lei, vediamo che succede! Del resto le stiamo soltanto affidando una capitale di tre milioni di abitanti con mille problemi gravissimi. Che dai vuoi che faccia in cinque anni?

Vediamo che succede! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 18:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 27yo male, Ice Cream routine for the past two months. Diet and protein intake should be in check. Thank you if you can help me out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I'm 27yo male, been following an Ice Cream routine for the past two months. Diet and protein intake is in check. Should I just correct form? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bench plateau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't seem to progress on the bench press, and the surprising fact is that my plateau is embarrassingly low (83lbs). What am I doing wrong? Could it just be that I have to keep eating (I still am pretty skinny). Thanks to anyone who can help me with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gente che sta male e deve tornare a casa di fretta capita pi spesso di un caso su un milione... e comunque, io sono sempre del parare che gente che guida male  meglio averla davanti che dietro! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 00:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://np.reddit.com/r/AdviceAnimals/comments/1kbhcn/i_gain_strength_from_their_tears_and_anger/cbnhvxv/


non fare stupidaggini e fallo passare. non puoi mai sapere il vero motivo per cui ha fretta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anybody likes that abortion exists... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what should be Hillary Clinton's political target? I mean, what the hell was the party thinking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump 2nd term </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puoi essere fiero di quello che hai fatto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ehm... 2012, Emilia Romagna. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 11:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aspettiamo u/TheEarthquakeGuy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 10:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Furtive fallacy. You can never win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 10:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do not believe the *first* thing they hear: ignorant believe the version that most simplifies reality and agrees with their bias.

The world is scary, bad things happen to good people, sometimes innocent people get terribly sick and die: you can either educate yourself on epidemiology (years of study), read books, go to school, or just watch one youtube video and repost a blog entry on your Facebook wall. If you're very ignorant, mentally lazy and also dumb, you'll prefer the second option: Big Pharma just wants to make money! your kids are autistic because you vaccinated them! they're hiding the real cure to cancer!

I think it's a combination of just world hypothesis and furtive fallacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just watched this episode! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> poche regole nella vita: non guidare ubriachi, tenersi in allenamento, non leggere i commenti agli articoli di giornale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> il grande giornalismo del corriere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come quella volta che ho lasciato la macchina sul marciapiede e ho dovuto pagare 10 centesimi di multa. Stangata! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lived in Rome for twenty years, I disagree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the internet everyone will tell you to speak English. Very few people you meet on the street will actually speak reasonably good English, at least in the South. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 23:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 22:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to sound like an asshole, but... shouldn't good mental health be a prerequisite for being a pilot? I mean, it might be that I'm not suffering consequences from such a discrimination, and I don't understand the issue... but it just sounds like it makes sense to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Texting and driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most dangerous thing people mindlessy do all the time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 00:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, we do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
