<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4592</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hotels and Restaurants Reap the Benefits of U.K. Consumer Boom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austria Says Eurofighter Deal Cost $1.2 Billion in Damages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bayer, Syngenta Clash With EU Over Bees Amid M A Charm Offensive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andrew Puzder withdraws as a labor secretary nominee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UBS France Said to Be Charged With Harassment Amid Tax Probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eurovision 2017: Organising team quits en masse - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm foreigner too and I have been asking the same questions for past few months. Basically it boils down to this:

President Trump is viewed as a problem by both Democrats and Republicans. Democrats I don't have to explain, Republicans are little more complicated. Lot of his policies go against the unhindered capitalism and free trade deals they like so much, unlike most of them he does not have a problem with LGBT people, he used to be Democrat for a long time and not so long ago used to support universal healthcare. Last but not least he does seem to be actually insane.
All and all he is not your traditional Republican and party leadership didn't want him to succeed in primaries, much less become a president.

Now in order to get rid of him he needs to be impeached, for that he needs to be guilty of treason, bribery, or other high crimes.

Here comes the fun part, what is and isn't the high crime is technically defined by the Congress. And Republicans have majority in both chambers.

But all it takes is few "swing votes" and Democrats will take care of the vote, and conveniently, they will also receive most of the blame from Trumpists while Republicans can claim that it's a stab in the back by Democrats.

Unfortunately, the moment Trump loses presidency his Vice President Mike Pence become president. And believe me that guy is maybe sane, but he is still an asshole. But an asshole that will do what Republican party wants from him, unlike Trump.

Right now both Democrats and Republicans are trying to build as strong case against him as possible. Otherwise he might slip away or make someone take the blame.

Still, both Republicans and Democrats hope that he can be tamed or subdued. At least a little bit. Republicans are afraid of backlash from Trumps supporters who will inevitably feel betrayed, while Democrats secretly hope that Trump breaks Republican party into pieces and liberals will be so angry at him that they will show up at elections two years from now. Because turnout is notoriously low when it comes to midterms and liberal voters.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a shitshow, no discussion. 
But more importantly this shows that Trump can be opposed and that the system can beat him.

What is important now is to keep the pressure on and take him out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to be that guy but maybe the problem is that unlike young people the old people vote almost every election.

Maybe the millennials (technically my generation but I live in Czechia) should try that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 11:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats left of the bridge is right now well below the street level, in fact few pieces are in local basements, one arch actually IS a basement.

Even this arch is actually almost never seen since its under several buildings, these days its mostly used as haven for tourist boats.

Anyway there are several other remnants, two sculptures, one which is used as way to measure flooding risk called Brad, no one know who it was, some say the architect. 
The other one is inside the old guard tower on left bank of the river. The tower is now connected to the one build for Charles bridge.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 22:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the academy refused him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this above my table when I was a tech. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is gulag talk tovaris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remains of Judiths bridge - first stone bridge in Prague 1172 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greek Central Bank Chief Warns Bailout Delay Risks Rerun of 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia green-lights health clinic for treating Kremlin top officials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitler lookalike arrested in Austria - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Switching Debt to Francs Would Cost France Dearly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post-Brexit Boost for U.K. Would Be EU Capitulation, Kern Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey look, the fake news go both ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, that's one of many reasons why Mass Effect 3 wasn't my favorite in the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From weakness of the mind, Omnissiah save us,
from the lies of the Antipath, circuit preserve us,
from the rage of the Beast, iron protect us,
from the temptations of the flesh, silica cleanse us,
from the ravages of time, anima shield us,
from this rotting cage of biomatter,
Machine god, set us free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG get over it. I get it you don't want to be reminded about that shit, nothing wrong with that. 

But don't turn this into issue of century, I think right now both Germany and USA have much bigger problems than singing wrong stanza in an anthem. 

An Anthem which, btw, Germans barely sing apart from sports events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone acquainted with Tennessee legislative climate say how broad is support for this law and how likely it is that it's going to pass?

I know its a conservative state but that can mean a lot of things these days.

So to reiterate: Is it likely it's going to pass?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF is imperial wizard? KKK really seems like LARP gone horribly wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 16:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably fake news, but even if real it seems reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 15:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1:So if the evidence does not support your case you discount it?
Ok, maybe you know more than that guy, still it would be nice if you pointed out what was wrong with his methodology.
The one you liked actually shows that C++ is faster and curiously does not include data for programs compiled using GCC on Windows. Because of that the data is incomplete and basically worthless. Not to mention the fact its over a decade old.

3: Yes he uses large number of objects but considering how little data they contain it shouldn't impact memory much (Note: I haven't seen report from his profiler or his code I am kind of shooting it the dark here).
One way or another he doesn't need to insert/delete data from it, all he needs is data retrieval from what is essentially fixed sized structure and some basic arithmetic with it, followed by overwriting of data. 
Essentially just get/set operations which are faster in arrays.


5:Seeing that this simulation took more than hour (I think OP wrote that somewhere) I think that he calls the constructors in every iteration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aperture Science </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1:I guess it depends on the purpose of the application and your skill, however especially when it comes to relatively simple mathematical operations and arrays (which is the case here) the C++ does have an edge.
https://benchmarksgame.alioth.debian.org/u64q/compare.php?lang=gpp lang2=java

http://blog.optionscity.com/java-vs.-c-performance-face-off-part-ii

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Java_performance#Program_speed

3:Depends on what you want from them. In this case the size is set before the execution, therefore more advanced stuff the Lists implement is not necessary. 
You can do just fine with the array.

5: He has over three hundred thousand of them, if the constructors are not optimized properly he will get lot of wasted cycles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Saudis would prefer the pipeline not standing.

Since their oil competes with that from Dakota. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well ArrayList still implements lots of stuff that is not really necessary for this kind of work, for example Serialization and stuff it inherits from List. I will try to look up some analysis but intuition tells me that its still less efficient than simple array. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [SDL](https://www.libsdl.org/) is good if you are writing in C++, it might be an overkill but it's multi platform and well documented.

There are other options like [Cairo](https://www.cairographics.org/) and [GTK+](https://www.gtk.org/),  finally you might try OpenGL, but that's seriously overpowered. It might be interesting learning experience however.


Anyway, if you can you should take a look at method calls your program makes, most IDEs have some helpful features when it comes to that, that way you can figure out where are you spending most resources. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work.
If you want some tips here is the stuff I found out while implementing my cellular automaton, which is in principle same thing:

1. Use compiled language, C/C++ works best. You will have to use third party graphics library but you will get lot of efficiency compared to JAVA.

2. Make sure you only check neighbors you need to check, there is no reason to check neighbors of the same type.

3. Simple data structures like arrays are more efficient than lists.

4. Compute results for entire field at once, not in series like you seem to do. Otherwise you will get weird results.

5. If you use objects to describe individual pokemon consider alternatives, it is very resource intensive when you consider what you need them to do. Try simpler data structures. Especially when all you need from them is basic math.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if I should be happy that I write like native english speaker, or sad that I write like Donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For start the pipe is going to be under the lake Oahe, about 90 feet below the lake in fact, on both sides it will have automated valves.

The USACE conducted assesment and found the pipeline to be safe , the Fish and Wildlife service also concluded that pipeline
 will have either "No Effect" or "May Affect, But Not Likely to Adversely Affect" on
listed species. 

Last but not least, right now the oil is shipped by trucks, which is one of least save and ecological solutions, so unless you want stop the crude production entirely, which, let's face it, is kind of hard sell for people who work there, it's better for the oil to be shipped by pipeline.

Anyway, the report goes into way more detail, you can find it here:
http://cdm16021.contentdm.oclc.org/cdm/ref/collection/p16021coll7/id/2801 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to say this but I am on the pro-pipeline side in this.
I have read the reports, I looked at how the negotiations looked and I checked the economics of the thing.

All things considered it is not as bad as some make it out to be, frankly I would be more concerned about Trumps cabinet picks and some of the legislation in the Congress than about this.
But I'm not american so it's not exactly my business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so happy that I live in a country with universal health care.
It's not always a place to be proud of but this is one of the things we do right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And people wonder why Zionism exists. 

Almost as if Jews had reason to believe that only government of Jewish state will actually stand by them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This idea often appears when people discuss Japanese interment camps in USA.

I once talked with a guy who seriously believed that FDR would send Japanese to gas chambers if he didn't have space for those camps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, every country should do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guardian keeps finding new rock bottom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 12:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but isn't that a good thing? I mean they are breaking the law right, by overstaying their visa aren't they?

And btw I really think that we should focus on how many of them are paying taxes.

To be honest as a european the thought that people want illegal immigrants astounds me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 10:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Austin is overwhelmingly Democratic with Democratic mayor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 11:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is where the hosts are made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 22:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried it with 2.6.3 and it still crushes, guess I will have to stay with Christian rulers.
Edit:It seems to happen with sedevacatists too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fight her on state level, if feds don't finance public schools than states must. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this will fall on deaf ears but here I go.

Americans, you live in federation, your states have huge power over your lives. You do not have to rely on DC to handle everything, if you don't like federal governments policies, if you truly want to help the poor and unfortunate:
THEN YOU MUST START AT THE STATE LEVEL.

If you approach the problem from top-down it will only get worse, vote in state elections, municipal elections and push for local policies to solve your problems, don't wait for entire federation to get its act together.

If you do that nothing ever gets done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like fake news to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are just removing the subsidies that deformed the market and caused unsustainable development of solar power for fucks sake read something about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I mean. This was no split second decision or heat of the moment deal. This was calculated cruelty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 23:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that AtE is only compatible with 2.6.1, thats why I downgraded to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MAKE COMBINE GREAT AGAIN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I am not surprised. 

Although I would like citation from more reputable source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get that, that's why I mostly stand on side of the cops in these things, especially when it comes to split second decisions.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF? Now I'm usually on side of the cops but this crosses the line ...twice!  
I can get over people loosing nerves or getting confused, but this is just unnecessary cruelty.

I sincerely hope that the cops are brought to justice, shit like this is making all cops look bad and undermines the system itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 16:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me guess, this event fires on planet Cadia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 11:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the extra empire submod, and so far it seems to happen only with Americanists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game crashes when I click on religion tab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 00:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much what the title says, I'm wondering if its a compatibility issue. 
The game version is 2.6.1 and I have all the DLC except for Council, Reaper and Sword of Islam, so I don't know whats wrong.

Does anyone have any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A* is pretty good and common algorithm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need optimal solution for Traveling Salesman, especially in a video game. All you need is approximation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy, that's not good. Not saying the SPD/Schulz is bad but I don't like another variable in the mix.

I don't agree with Merkel on lots of things but she is stable point of EU politics, something we need now more than ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is case study no. 50, done by Royal Commission into institutional responses to child sexual abuse.
[Case study 50](http://www.childabuseroyalcommission.gov.au/case-study/261be84b-bec0-4440-b294-57d3e7de1234/case-study-50,-february-2017,-sydney)

Many other organisations (religious and secular) were investigated and others are going to be. 
Sadly (as far as I know) only Catholic church had comprehensive report done at the end. 
Others have only individual reports and related materials.

Some interesting data from the case study 50.

Overall proportion of priests who were alleged perpetrators
Priests overall  weighted average Percent

All Catholic Church authorities with priest members 7.0%

Diocesan Catholic Church authorities 7.9%

Religious Institutes with priest members 5.7%

Archdiocese/Diocese  weighted average Percent 

Archdiocese of Adelaide 2.4%

Diocese of Ballarat 8.7%

Catholic Archdiocese of Brisbane 9.3%

Diocese of Bunbury 7.8%

Catholic Archdiocese of CanberraGoulburn 8.4%

Diocese of Lismore 13.9%

Diocese of MaitlandNewcastle 7.9%

REPT.0011.001.0006

And finally 

Number of alleged perpetrators 
12. A total of 1,880 alleged perpetrators (diocesan and religious priests, religious brothers, religious
sisters, lay employees or volunteers) were identified in claims of child sexual abuse. 

13. Of the 1,880 alleged perpetrators identified: 
a. 693 were nonordained religious (37% of all known alleged perpetrators), being 597
religious brothers (32% of all known alleged perpetrators) and 96 religious sisters (5% of
all known alleged perpetrators)

b. 572 were priests (30% of all known alleged perpetrators), being 384 diocesan priests and
188 religious priests

c. 543 were lay people (29% of all known alleged perpetrators)

d. For 72 known alleged perpetrators (4%) the religious status was not known.


To reiterate: other organisations are investigated, including schools, prisons, Scouts, YMCA, medical personnel and many others. Please do not forget about these victims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 7% is the number across entire clergy, some organisations had more, some had less. If you can not understand that I have to suggest reading up on statistics or at very least reading the report I gave you link for.

Again to reiterate the 7% is NOT an average it is literally 7% of all priests in Australian Catholic church. Which you would know if you read that report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you stated it wrong. 7% are probably molesters, not 80% like you implied right now, not even 20% like you stated.

In both cases you were incorrect and I wonder why are you so unwilling to admit that.
So I will ask you, did you read the report itself? Or are you just quoting the article?

Because if you did read that you would know you are wrong and you are probably graduate of "alternative facts" school of statistics.
And if you didn't read it I honestly do not understand why, if you are truly so interested in the matter I imagine you would spare 10 minutes of your time to read about the findings of the commission. 

Finally, I am deeply sorry that you interpreted my insistence on facts to be my acceptance of child molestation. I hope that you do understand that it was a wrong impression and I am sorry that my conduct caused you to adopt such belief.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's acceptable targets, essentially some organisations, people etc. can be targeted more easily than others. Often it's due to their wealth, power, fame you name it.

For example: try criticizing political system in China and then political system in USA. You will get very different results.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you read 40%?
The analyses came up with 7%, please read the actual report and not the article.
Here you go: http://www.childabuseroyalcommission.gov.au/exhibits/261be84b-bec0-4440-b294-57d3e7de1234/case-study-50,-february-2017,-sydney </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you read 40%?
The analyses came up with 7%, please read the actual report and not the article.
Here you go: http://www.childabuseroyalcommission.gov.au/exhibits/261be84b-bec0-4440-b294-57d3e7de1234/case-study-50,-february-2017,-sydney

First on the list, all organised in tables according to order, time and place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a drop off but I'm of the opinion that its just until the victims gather courage.

Anyway here is the data.
http://www.childabuseroyalcommission.gov.au/exhibits/261be84b-bec0-4440-b294-57d3e7de1234/case-study-50,-february-2017,-sydney

Its the very first on the list.

Interestingly, none of the other 49 investigations into other organisations (secular and religious) gathered so much attention.
All of them are on the same site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As for Catholics they just fund and enable the rape.

Following that line of reasoning watchers of BBC and Hollywood movies do the same.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but sadly data is the last thing that matters in these things.
People have tendency to simplify, it is much easier to just be outraged than actually try to understand the problem.

To make things worse church is treated as a single entity by most people, no matter where the priest is, where he works, what order is he part of or how the congregation looks like, all that will appear in the headline is Catholic church.

On the other hand when it comes to say, football club or school, there is much more nuance because not all schools or clubs are part of same organisation.

To sum it up: humans look for patterns, it's what they do, even if those patterns imaginary like face on mars or astrology, people cling to them because they make world easier to understand.
And in this case it's easier to say that Catholic Church is full of child molesters than to say that child molesters appear anywhere they can molest children and organisations involved tend to sweep things under rag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if it had real computer terminals with deranged librarian AI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you read the study its about 7% of all priests, now assuming that about half of priests involved was never reported by anyone it would still be about 14%, that's still less than 20% you are implying. 

That does not mean its any less horrific, it just means that your data is inaccurate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is case study no. 50, done by Royal Commission into institutional responses to child sexual abuse.
[Case study 50](http://www.childabuseroyalcommission.gov.au/case-study/261be84b-bec0-4440-b294-57d3e7de1234/case-study-50,-february-2017,-sydney)

Many other organisations (religious and secular) were investigated and others are going to be. 
Sadly (as far as I know) only Catholic church had comprehensive report done at the end. 
Others have only individual reports and related materials.

Some interesting data from the case study 50.

Overall proportion of priests who were alleged perpetrators
Priests overall  weighted average Percent

All Catholic Church authorities with priest members 7.0%

Diocesan Catholic Church authorities 7.9%

Religious Institutes with priest members 5.7%

Archdiocese/Diocese  weighted average Percent 

Archdiocese of Adelaide 2.4%

Diocese of Ballarat 8.7%

Catholic Archdiocese of Brisbane 9.3%

Diocese of Bunbury 7.8%

Catholic Archdiocese of CanberraGoulburn 8.4%

Diocese of Lismore 13.9%

Diocese of MaitlandNewcastle 7.9%

REPT.0011.001.0006

And finally 

Number of alleged perpetrators 
12. A total of 1,880 alleged perpetrators (diocesan and religious priests, religious brothers, religious
sisters, lay employees or volunteers) were identified in claims of child sexual abuse. 

13. Of the 1,880 alleged perpetrators identified: 
a. 693 were nonordained religious (37% of all known alleged perpetrators), being 597
religious brothers (32% of all known alleged perpetrators) and 96 religious sisters (5% of
all known alleged perpetrators)

b. 572 were priests (30% of all known alleged perpetrators), being 384 diocesan priests and
188 religious priests

c. 543 were lay people (29% of all known alleged perpetrators)

d. For 72 known alleged perpetrators (4%) the religious status was not known.


To reiterate: other organisations are investigated, including schools, prisons, Scouts, YMCA, medical personnel and many others. Please do not forget about these victims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankly I would be more worried if he "had" a plan and started working on it right away. Now that would be a real cluster fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, what did I do to you to call me that? I just pointed out that current Trump-hysteria obscures real issues.

Which, when you think about it, is kind of what happened during the elections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, how many wars he started? How many ecological catastrophes he caused? What was it that he actually did that caused real damage?

Sure he is an asshole and that travel ban was a dick move, but all things considered it mostly just affected image USA and frankly that was bad for some time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 21:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West talks a lot but does way too little.

For example Libya, it's right across the sea from most developed nations on Earth, nations that helped depose local dictator, you would think that they would be interested in fostering local democracy, providing military, economical and political support so that the place didn't turn into another Syria.

Guess again. Right after Gaddafi died they turned their back to local problems. And then they started to wonder why are Libyans unable to stop migrants and are sailing en mass to Europe.

Sure they could step in and help, but soldiers could die, kids could get killed in misplaced strike and it would look bad in the press.
So they decide to do nothing, just send the locals some money and condemn the worst groups, but nothing substantial.

Make no mistake I do agree that Muslim nations should do more. But I also think that right now all west does is glorified PR move dedicated to one goal: improving ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 78 000 SPACE MARINES?!!!

That's legion grade force rivaling Ultramarines. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what did Obama, Hollande, Merkel or Cameron do for Rohingyas? Or Yeminis, Assyrians and others? When it comes to ignoring genocides Trump follows long standing western policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But remember: Trumps latest tweet is the real news of the day! /s

But seriously people, there are genocides going on RIGHT NOW, and the world is more concerned about asshole who so far made mostly superficial damage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Posters critical of Pope Francis appear around Rome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 08:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, de jure it's still Ukraine and de facto it's split between Ukraine and Donetsk separatists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fillon got sabotaged by someone. Possibly Russia, there are similarities to Hilary when it comes to him.
So right now it looks like it will come to either Le Pen or Macron.

Macron is as left wing as humanly possible without being outright communist, some of his economic policies are, lets say bold, Le Pen makes no secret out of her pro-Russian tendencies.

One way or another I can't see this thing going well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not getting your child vaccinated should be a punishable offence.
Family like this is worse than no family at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly they live mostly in Donetsk oblast. But they survived centuries under hordes, turks, Hitler and Stalin. I don't think they will fall now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some towns in Czech Republic (and rest of Europe as well) turned the old Jewish cemeteries into parks and took the masonry as cheap decorations, AFTER holocaust.

Only in last few years is attention finally paid to dozens of these places. I walk next to one almost daily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, just wow.

I have to contribute fun fact of my own: There is about 100 000 Pontic Greeks living in Ukraine right now.
Yep, descendants of Theodoro and Trebizond are alive and (relatively) well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked it up and it looks like its ruling dynasty of... Nogai.

That zero diplomacy makes even more sense now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That zero diplomacy is because no one in entire Europe speaks his dialect of Tamazight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. All things considered, the medieval rulers acted very similar to CK2 players, especially when it comes to gravelkind inheritance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 11:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Formed Rome, conquered Europe, Africa and near east, by the time I got to India I just couldn't go on.

So I disabled Iron man, typed in observe and watch second collapse of empire.
I enjoyed that more than conquering Scandinavia and Russia combined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 11:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kebab autophagia. 

Jokes aside, I have see stuff like this happen from time to time, one time it happened to Mongols.

That's when I learned to fear Nestorians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 10:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is pretty historical however. There is a reason why Lothair (oldest son and imperial heir of Luis the pious) got almost exactly the same strip of land in treaty of Verdun.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest its the same in most countries, even in Europe the Norway is an exception. Most of the time our prisons are overcrowded and underfunded just like yours. 
With the added benefit of Islamists recruiting among the inmates, at least in countries with large muslim minority. 

Thankfully Czechia dodged that bullet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. All that talk about being humane is easy when we don't see what happens behind the bars.

Not every country has Swedish prisons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job Singapore. That pig deserved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They usually record it. Look it up on LiveLeak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most don't care about it, some oppose it on moral grounds.

Personally as a westerner I would prefer caning to long term prison for most offenders.

If you throw a guy in prison for a decade all you accomplish is him becoming even worse criminal. He does not contribute to society in any way while imprisoned, he does not reform and it certainly does not help the victim.
Usually he loses his family and home not to mention his job.

On the other hand if you beat him up in public he will remember it for rest of his life and can return to his previous life without delay.
His family will not abandon him and he actually has a chance of becoming productive citizen.

So all things considered, I would support such punishment for some criminals.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French soldier shoots and wounds knife-wielding attacker at Paris Louvre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 11:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iranian-American, lives in California, teaches at Stanford, finished studies on Harvard. Just for clarification.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The target is mainly composed of water ice and volatiles.
Its negligible gravity well and lack of atmosphere mean that it's of limited use apart from component materials.

Recommendation: Kinetic strike, possibly using another moon as improvised projectile. Opposition will be completely annihilated with just moderate investment. As a bonus, the resource extraction will be much easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. In the end the judgment is not ours to make. 

Pretty much all religions agree that there is a higher justice, independent of the one humans have, proclaiming that you know how it will act is dishonest at very best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? White people have to pay for college just like everyone else and, lets be honest, few programs target them specifically.

Anyway, whatever helps people get through broken american college system is good in my book. It doesn't make Milo a good guy but it certainly doesn't make him any worse than he already is.

There are other issues we should focus on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 10:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prions are much more durable than bacteria however. 
Unlike them they can not be destroyed by heating them to boiling temperature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he has Caitlyn Jenner as a VP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to actually stop shit like this break the peoples bubbles. Don't let content filters define what is and is not true, don't let the radicals to isolate themselves in their little cysts of hatred.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musks Trump Outreach Is Angering The Resistance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that we should all focus on what is truly important, crime was committed, suspect was detained, wounded are being treated, people showed compassion.

All in all, despite the shooting, despite the vitriol we should all find comfort in the fact that system still works.

And furthermore I would like to remind everyone that no matter who is the attacker and who is attacked the state should always act in same way. 
I am no supporter of rampant immigration (I am Czech not American), I do believe Islamism is a threat the western politicians underestimate but I also believe that fearmongering and decisions based on feelings rather than facts are the answer. 

I do not think that Trump will help the situation with what he is doing and I do not believe he has best interests of Americans in mind. But I do not think that Merkel has the right answers either.

What I do think however is that we must take violence as the very last option and that crimes, no matter the perpetrator, must be prevented or failing that punished.

And I think it's a shame that people prefer their narrative to justice.
That goes to all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 11:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> History education in Czechia is also pretty funny.

"No, we are not going to study the Napoleonic wars/HRE/Mongol khanate/Ottoman empire/KuK monarchy/Charles V/pretty much anything we need the time to study the 20th century."

This is almost literally what my teacher told me, no kidding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meaningless? The people in the town hall decide how to use millions of dollars, how to maintain infrastructure and where people can build their houses.

If you treat municipal elections like they are meaningless you get Flint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people just don't know that.

People like the idea of Malcolm, not the racist and borderline terrorist person he really was, but the idea of the guy who was opposed to evil of racism and helped Civil Rights movement succeed. 

Every nation has someone like that, Czechs have Masaryk, Indians have Ghandi, person who is more of a symbol than a human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 11:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "extreme vetting" is basically just reiteration of current policy.
Trump will simply relabel existing laws and give them some populist facelift while letting administration to continue as usual. 

For example, his recent ban on travel is mostly cosmetic, the countries on the list have very weak ties to USA and most Muslim migrants don't come from them.

The real result is that the voters are pleased and status quo carries, more or less, on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 11:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually decentralizing it would be the worst decision possible.

You see, local authorities, councils and such, are elected and beholden to very small selection of the public. Most people don't vote in elections and even less people vote in municipal elections, so you mostly end up with town being controlled by very small group of dedicated voters.

Accidentally, people who are dedicated to voting are often also very, shall we say, convinced that their views are right. After all they walked all the way to booths to prove it.

And so, local authorities are inclined to follow wishes of these narrow groups rather than to do what is actually good for the children or what is even sensible.

If you decentralize education you put the authority over curriculum , teachers ,and ultimately, pupils, into hands of the most radical and convinced elements of the communities in question.

If, on the other hand, you centralize the decision and policy making, you ensure that all the varied groups with their interests and opinions are represented and you prevent the most radical of them from dictating the policy.

To put it into layman terms, the more idiots are yelling at each other, the less they yell at reasonable people. And the reasonable people have time to actually work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 20:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the guy either but you make it sound like Civil war round II.

Not saying that his policies will work or that they are reasonable, moral or even sane but so far most of the damage he did was just by getting elected not by his decisions in office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia Day: Deputy PM Barnaby Joyce rebukes critics - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 12:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 11:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if you coated the artificial part of the interface with organisms mimicking the normal neural cells, that were at the same time adapted to live on surface of said interface, you could use them as a translators of sort.

Or at least a protective layer for normal neural cells to prevent scaring of the tissue.

But that's way beyond of what this paper suggests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite him being an asshole I do think that is correct response.

Because whatever the local government is doing it does not work and that's exactly when the government should intervene. 


PS: I do get the hypocrisy involved btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, Olaf is not that kind of a person.
That being said he does have more sides than the one we usually see.[book spoilers](#b "Even evil has loved ones. If you read the books you know.")

However you must understand that he has more than monetary reasons for trying to hurt the children. Sure the money is a biiig part of it, but there are other ways to get rich, especially if you are a bad person like he is.

Also he [book spoilers](#b "is not the greatest evil in their world) and the people that [Book Spoilers](#b are fighting him often employ, lets say questionable methods"). 

Furthermore [book spoilers](#b "it is heavily hinted if not outright stated that he was not always completely bad and that he was actually pushed to become so by... a very, very unfortunate event.")
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I learned that random guys on internet know more about what defines Aborigine than Aborigines themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a nice Doritos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 13:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually if you try to vote without state issued id (it's not entirely free BTW) in Czech Republic you will get figuratively thrown out of the voting room.

When I told my dad that americans can just walk in without any proof of identity he though I was messing with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
