<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3471</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 08:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im 22. My dad disappeared when I was five. Fucked up, right?

It turns out that our definition of fucked up is limited by just how much life has decided to crush us. 

Its been just me and my mom ever since. Flashes of memory and fleeting emotions, undoubtedly marred by the flow of time, are all that I have left of my dad. I figured my apathy was his penance for leaving. 

So I lived with Mom until I graduated college. She was the only one there for me.

I felt kind of guilty taking a job in Nashville and leaving her halfway across the country, but she understood. She always did. 

It meant moving away from the only home I could remember, though. It was surreal enough packing up our house; it was as though I was disassembling the foundations of existence itself, pulling apart things that I did not know could be undone. 

Thats when I found the videos. 

We never realize just how much stuff we own. Its because when we move past a certain phase in our lives, we think that the material possessions disappear as well. 

Think about that last part long and hard. Do it now.

Some bells cannot be unrung, and some fires cannot be unburned.

I was digging through the endless possessions in our attic. I did not realize how much of myself had been left behind, how living means turning part of yourself into a ghost, until I dug through it all.

It was in an unassuming box.

There were three VHS tapes in there. They were all unlabeled. 

The digging made me nostalgic. My mom wasnt around at the moment, so I couldnt ask her about it. 

It wasnt hard to find and old VCR and an even older TV in the attic. To my surprise, they worked on the first try.

I put the video in. 

Fire lit.

The screen showed a poorly-lit room. You can instantly tell from those old VHS tapes when youre looking at a home video, and not a movie.

This was not a movie. 

There were two men crouching in the corner of a cage. They were naked.

One was my dad.

I could tell he was on the verge of tears. He glanced up, gave a desperate look to the camera, and shuffled forward. He made a pleading gesture with his hands, and the video cut out.

It was quickly replaced with another scene. The angle was identical, and it never shook, so it was clearly sitting on some sort of a tripod.

My dad was on his knees in front of the camera. When he looked up, I nearly puked. He was still naked and caked in dirt. His frame had become much more skeletal, and he was openly weeping. I could hear his sobs. 

Then he began to speak.

Pleeee-ee-eease, he begged through the tears. The other man in the cage, also naked and dirty, rolled silently back and forth in the corner. Please, dont, he wheezed through gasping sobs. Please, Nancy.

Gravity shifted. Nancy is my mom.

He continued to pump his interlocked fingers up and down in front of him in a begging motion. Ive never seen a human look so miserable.

The video cut out again. When it started up, it was of the same scene.

Clearly, time had passed.

He was more gaunt than ever. My father and the man next to him sat utterly transfixed, staring at the camera with empty eyes. I began to wonder if the tape had stopped, or if they were dead. Then my father leapt forward and started growling. He grabbed the chain-link bars of the cage in a white-knuckle grip. He started chewing on it.

The video cut out one more time. When it came back in again, my father was sitting on his haunches. He was no longer looking at the camera. Instead, his face was pitched forward, stuffed with something that he was eating. It was oozing through his fingers.

The liquid was so dark that at first I did not realize it was blood.

My father was eating ravenously, as though he had long been starved. As he was chewing, he slowly pivoted his head around and looked into the camera.

I dont know how to describe what I saw. When a person looks at you, theres a humanity that can neither be denied nor described. You know, based on what you see, that the person behind the eyes is interpreting the world around them in a million tiny ways that links them back to you.

His eyes had none of that.

He looked at the camera the same way that youd stare at a sign in a foreign language. Or a purple sunset. Fuck, I dont know. Something that wasnt sharing the world with you.

He continued chewing unabated. The blood poured freely down his chin.

It was only then that I realized the other man was no longer in the cage.

And here I am in the attic, seventeen years later.

Which brings me to a very important question: precisely what in the blue fuck do I do?



UPDATE:

Ive decided to come clean to my mom that I found the tapes. Shell be home in a couple of hours. I want to give her a chance to explain herself before I show them to the police or anyone else. I mean, shes my mom, right? Whats the worst that could happen? Doesnt she deserve at least a chance to explain whats going on? What do you guys think? 



Part 2 is [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/68s3fs/wtf_part_2/) .... fuck me.

[Part 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/68zna0/wtf_part_3/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hell is What You Make of It - Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had them write their experiences to share. Because once a story is written, it becomes true forever. 

You can read my account of the beginning of Jakes experiences [here.] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6185uw/hell_is_what_you_make_of_it/)

-J



**Lacys Story**

Four years after I discovered the truth about my son was the worse day of my life.

Casey was the classic good kid as a young boy, but he started to slip in high school. I found out who he really was when I had to bail him out of jail a week after his high school graduation. 

Despite my wishes, he did not go to college.

He would disappear for longer and longer periods after that. It tore me apart to watch my only son unravel in front of my eyes. I blamed myself, I blamed Casey, I blamed the husband that lost a battle to cancer when our son was five. I had tried helping him, paying for rehab, yelling at him, pleading with him, crying to him, slapping him, kicking out, welcoming him home, and doing nothing.

In the beginning, I wanted desperately to know where he would go when he disappeared. As time wore on, I realized that I really didnt want to know at all. 

When the police called me the last time, I could tell right away that the tone was different. Part of me knew immediately; part of me had known that this outcome was predetermined, and that only the timing was left to fate.

I didnt cry when they opened up a drawer in a chilly morgue. His body was badly mangled, but it was my son. I caressed his twenty-two year old face for the last time, but felt mild surprise that I could do so with a certain academic detachment. I felt a stress behind my eyes, and vaguely realized that my mind was going through a seismic fissure. Something deep was breaking  not in my world, but in myself. It was too fundamental to be addressed with something as pedestrian as tears.

The next days were hard to distinguish from one another. It took nearly a week for me to realize that I was adjusting to life without hope, and that had changed my lifes trajectory. I decided to test that theory.

I found myself standing on the edge of a bridge. Below me was the place that I had first gone to pick up an unconscious Casey. At the time, I had not known whether he had passed out from drugs or violence. It took another year for me to realize that there wasnt a difference. 

It was on the edge of that bridge, wondering what fate lay below, when I finally cracked. I screamed, and thats the last that I remembered before the Change.

I found that I was still standing, but in a different place. A man sat in front of me, foot tucked up near his waist, elbow resting on his knee, a long, thin cigarette in his left hand. His sandy brown hair looked unkempt in an intentional sort of way. The collar of his trench coat was flipped up too high in an irritating sort of way. 

To be perfectly honest, Lacy, even I didnt think that it would end up like this. He turned his eyes toward me; they were a cobalt blue. I thought he would go for the boy. He took a deep drag contemplatively, then let it out with a soft sigh. A man once told me Theres no point in saying what Im looking for  my most valued possessions are all things I never knew I needed at first. Well, I suppose theres a mirror of that on the other side as well. The saddest things I see are the unexpected.

He sat quietly for a moment, the smoke gathering in the air above him. His cigarette stayed long. 

Why am I here? I didnt know why I asked the question, but did not really care, either. Not anymore.

The man held the cigarette between his index and middle fingers and pointed his hand in my direction. Lacy Delora, aged forty-six, current denizen of a curious bridge, I will show you something different from either your shadow at morning striding behind you, or your shadow at evening rising to meet you.

He leapt down from his perch, revealing a doorframe behind him. There was no wall in which it resided; it was simply a freestanding edifice.

Doors are kind of my thing, the man smiled. Come take a look.

I took three steps forward and he pulled it open. 

The other side of the door led somewhere impossible. It was a grassy median of a busy thoroughfare, outdoors and noisy. But the door was in the middle of an otherwise empty room. 

My confusion quickly dissipated when I saw what was on the other side.

Casey!

I sprinted at the door, but bounced off of it, as though an invisible wall held me back.

Ah, ah, ah, the man said. This is a seeing door, not a changing door. All this already happened. Whatever happens can never be undone. Thats the most important rule. He put his cigarette back into his mouth. Sorry, I guess I should have explained that. 

He didnt seem too sorry, but I hardly seemed to notice.

I watched in horror as my son  looking worse than ever  lurched, slightly stumbling, across the median. He had an evil look on his face, almost lecherous, and I realized with horror that he was advancing on an oblivious man. I could see what he was about to do, and wondered with terror if one of them would kill the other, and did not know which way to hope.

I gasped as another man, from seemingly nowhere, dashed forth and lunged at Casey. My son pulled a knife, but it was too late.

I knew what I was about to see, but could not turn away. 

The collision was mortifying. My son was tossed like a rag doll up into the air, and bounced twice on the ground. Three more cars ran him over without stopping before traffic ground to a halt. No one else seemed to get hurt, but I my attention was elsewhere. 

All I could think about was that I wished Id jumped before seeing my sons death.

Why? I whispered. Why would you do this?

The man slowly closed the door. It clicked shut.

Because, he actually sounded sympathetic this time, it was unfair. You never had a choice. You couldnt have known that Caseys after-school tutoring sessions were where he first got introduced to substance abuse. Even he didnt know that he was depressed, and youre not a mind-reader. And he made the wrong choice at every turn through his own volition. And you

Here he looked genuinely sad. 

You didnt even have a choice in his pregnancy. He was quiet. But you loved him just the same, didnt you? You- here he opened the door again, never got to choose.

The scene behind him was different this time.

There was a short hallway, with a man napping in the corner.

I recognized him. It was the man who killed Casey. 

This, my mysterious host now handed me a .22 caliber pistol, IS a changing door.

I stepped through it. He followed.









**Jakes Story**


I awoke to the snap of a gun clip.

I looked up blearily from his uncomfortable nap. Janus was not much of a host; but when I was offered the chance to sleep in a dingy hallway, I reasoned that it would still be the least bizarre thing to happen to me today. I had suddenly felt a wave of sleepiness, and was quickly out.

Now there were two people in front of me. Janus was closing the rooms only door behind him, while a frail woman who looked to be about sixty stood looking down at me. 

She was the one holding the gun. 

Um.. hi? I propped myself up on my elbows.

Before this happens, she nearly whispered, you have to know who I am.

My mind raced as I slowly climbed to my feet. I looked to Janus for help, but he stood stoically in front of the door, arms folded, omnipresent cigarette clenched by thin lips.

Janus this is not what I chose

You chose to kill Casey! the woman was suddenly shrieking. 

I am  confused. Please maam, the gun, put it down. I dont know a Casey. Im a stranger here myself.

I watched you throw my son in to traffic!

Shit.

To be honest, I had been wallowing in the sense of being a do-gooder. I really had thought Id beaten the system, had tricked the trickster and saved two lives at no cost. 

In retrospect, I could see how murdering an anonymous criminal might have consequences. 

The woman was advancing slowly toward me. Okay, I thought, youve beaten the odds once. Piece of cake.

She was trembling, the barrel of the gun in constant motion. She reminded me for a fleeting moment of the man (boy?) I had tossed into traffic, and how fragile he had seemed.

Maam, listen, please. You may not believe me, but I swear whatever you saw was NOT me. I was advancing slowly, almost imperceptibly, never breaking eye contact. I dont know what happened to your son, but I just lost my wife. It was hurtful beyond what I thought I the limits of pain were. It got better when- 

I suddenly snapped my gaze over her shoulder in the direction of Janus, who was quite still.

She turned her head around, immediately and unconsciously, just as I reasoned a highly stressed person would do.

She fell backward easily, just like her son did. It was easy to take the gun from her hand.

The woman shot up immediately. I flashed glances between her and Janus, the latter of whom was still standing motionlessly, smoke enwreathing his head again.

She had a crazed look plastered on her face, and something knowing flashed behind her eyes.

Janus would be no help. This was all about choices, wasnt it? She chose to come here, and she was choosing not to walk away

The woman began to walk toward me. I slowly began to step back.

Dont move! I aimed the gun at her head and held a steady hand. Stay right there! my voice trembled even if my hand did not. 

What the fuck was I going to do? This woman obviously came into the room with the intent of murdering me. She found me in my sleep. She wouldnt even back down when I had a gun pointed at her face. I would never be safe as long as she was alive.

My back bumped against the wall.

Last chance. I stood fixed; so did she. For a moment, neither one of us wavered.

I didnt have a choice. Right?

I pulled the trigger. It clicked. 

I pulled several more times. Nothing. 

The woman closed the final step separating us and took the gun in a nearly maternal way. My troubled son forced me to involve myself with worse things than this, she explained, holding the gun out to her side. During that time, I became more than familiar enough with guns to know how to unload a clip and clear a chamber.

I was locked in place, thunderstruck.

I gave you an gun, she went on, her voice just beginning to crack, to give you a choice. So that you would know the weight of being a mother. Of having a life in your hands. She released the hint of a forlorn gasp. I made sure the gun was empty so that, no matter what you chose, you would get to live with your decision. 

She threw the pistol violently to the ground. My hell is that as long as I walk on this earth, I will never escape the fact that I could not save my son. Yours is the fact that you have to live with what you were going to do to me. You chose to pull the trigger when I was unarmed. You would have been just as safe if you had let the gun fall. The only difference is what you did to yourself.

She turned and walked gracefully away. 

She made it thirteen steps before collapsing into a crouch on the ground. The cracks in the dam finally won; every tear she had held back started to spill. 

I was sick. I had the gnawing thought in the back of my mind that the past minute would change me in a way that could never be fixed. My knees wobbled.

Janus locked eyes with me, but continued to stay silent. 

I realized vaguely that I had yet another choice in front of me. 

I slowly walked forward, taking care to step over the discarded pistol. I advanced on the hunched-over woman, who was now shaking with all of the frailty and fragility that I had initially ascribed to her. 

I sat down and wrapped my arms around the mother of the man I had killed. She grabbed my torso with such ferocity that I thought she was attacking me after all. But she rocked back and forth instead, heaving gasping sobs as she did so. I rocked with her, too empty for tears.

Janus let us sit in silence for some time. When the woman had quieted, he smiled. 

Theres nothing left in this hallway, he explained, turning around to grab the doorknob. Now lets see whats behind door number three.
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
