<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6396</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking at Sardinian DNA for genetic clues to an island's - and Europe's - past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking at Sardinian DNA for genetic clues to an island's - and Europe's - past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is from September 2016, fyi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Photoshopped from [this picture](https://www.reddit.com/r/mildlyinteresting/comments/2ehca2/triple_rainbow/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is a controversial book among historians. 

It's really not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hammerstedt (2005: 51-52) surveyed 190 examples of trees cut with a stone ax from Europe, North America, South America, and New Guinea. Trees ranged from 1 to 73cm in diameter with a mean of 17cm. He found that the mean time of felling a tree was just 25 minutes. I'm not sure how that compares to metal axes, however.

* [Hammerstedt, Scott William. Mississippian construction, labor, and social organization in western Kentucky. Diss. The Pennsylvania State University, 2005.](https://etda.libraries.psu.edu/files/final_submissions/5899) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps if they show no evidence of a function, the very act of construction was the purpose for the earthworks. When you need to build something that large, you need other people to help out or the project will take forever. And when you bring people together you have opportunities to share stories, recall history, play matchmaker, trade items, throw feasts, and strengthen the bonds of family and friendship all under the guise of this construction project. At least, that's what Wesley Bernardini argues for the Hopewell mounds in Ohio in his 2003 paper

* [Bernardini, Wesley. "Hopewell geometric earthworks: A case study in the referential and experiential meaning of monuments." Journal of Anthropological Archaeology 23.3 (2004): 331-356.](https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Wesley_Bernardini/publication/223951764_Hopewell_geometric_earthworks_A_case_study_in_the_referential_and_experiential_meaning_of_monuments/links/559e9a0408aeed377e5798ba.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v432/n7020/full/nature03146.html

Carbon samples taken in the Pativilca and Fortaleza areas dated from before 3500 BC suggesting a Late Archaic root for the Norte Chico civilization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They had metallurgy, but had not yet entered the bronze, or what we would typicalyl think of as metal working (smelting to create alloys, they only had heating and hot/cold hammering techniques of metals found in purish forms).

Mesoamerica and South America had bronze. They also were experts at alloying gold, silver, and copper together to create gold looking items with far less gold than what was needed and vice versa for silver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference between Mann's book and Diamond's book is that Mann doesn't try to offer explanations or create overarching hypotheses about the past based on cherry-picked information. Diamond does just that and that is why academics rag on his book. No one rags on Mann's book because it is a survey of research and the literature at the time he wrote it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We need to encourage imagination so we can figure it out.

I agree with this if you mean encourage imagination to find solutions to problems using physical, collected data from a secure context. 

I disagree with you if you mean encourage imagination to create fanciful stories based on a vague and weak associations with actual data in order to sell these stories to the public for a profit, as Hancock does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  From there please consider checking out Graham Hancock and Randall Carlson

They are pseudo-archaeologists who write fiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubtful. There's too much textual, artistic, and physical evidence of dirt bikes, what they do, and why people do it for any real debate to occur in the future. Archaeologists are not some group of bumbling idiots that poke around the dirt and are confused when they find an object. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3,000-Year-Old Child Footprints Found at Site of Ancient Egyptian Palace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 18:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that doesn't mean they did not continue to prosper. They just didn't have trees.

Tainter's paper and McAnany and Yoffee's book chapter cover quite well what a collapse is, what happens during a collapse, and who did or did not experience if you want to give them a read.

* [Tainter, Joseph A. "Archaeology of overshoot and collapse." Annu. Rev. Anthropol. 35 (2006): 59-74.](https://origins.asu.edu/sites/default/files/archaeology_of_overshoot_and_collapse1.pdf)

* [McAnany, Patricia A., and Norman Yoffee, eds. Questioning collapse: human resilience, ecological vulnerability, and the aftermath of empire. Cambridge University Press, 2009.](http://www.langtoninfo.com/web_content/9780521515726_excerpt.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Europeans were lucky enough to find that civilisation wheezing it's last. 

Easter Islanders were doing quite well until Europeans showed up. It was only after the arrival of Europeans that Easter Islanders began "wheezing it's last" breath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't exactly new research. [Clark L. Erickson](https://scholar.google.com/scholar?q=Erickson+%2B+bolivia+%2B+earthworks btnG= hl=en as_sdt=0%2C23) has been researching the earthworks in Bolivia's Amazon rainforest for a few decades now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For clarification, there was no Maya empire. The Maya were a collection of city-states with a shared culture and language family. No one city-state dominated all the others, though large alliances can and did form.

Further clarification, the Aztecs and Maya are also in North America. North America extends from the Arctic to Panama, after all. But I am guessing you meant people north of the Rio Grande. In that case, perhaps the section [Technology and Civilization in the Americas](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/nativeamerican#wiki_technology_and_civilization_in_the_americas) from our FAQ will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there! You may consider asking this question on /r/AskAnthropology since this topic deals primarily with prehistory and possibly deep prehistory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 20:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Beta v1.0 Tariacuri will focus on Western Mexico

If you need any input, let me know. I study West Mexico </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a number of books in the /r/AskHistorians [booklist](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/books/americas#wiki_andean) on Andean pre-Columbian history that may interest you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 02:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, in some cases people were buried in a flexed position. People were also buried [supine](http://i.imgur.com/KtBOEWd.jpg) or prose if the burial space was large enough. There are even cases of [bundles of bones](http://i.imgur.com/DASucAu.jpg) being placed in burials as well as cremated and semi-cremated remains placed in ceramic vessels. Despite the focus of burials in [shaft tombs](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/43tvqk/do_the_burial_sites_of_the_shaft_tomb_cultures/) during the Late Formative to Classic periods in this region, there is a surprisingly wide arrange of burial types across Nayarit, Jalisco, and Colima. What I have not seen in the literature is the mention of mummy bundles. If West Mexico has mummy bundles my guess is that they would be from the Epiclassic or Postclassic periods with the introduction of more stereotypical eastern Mexican cultural practices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I should have clarified. I thought you were asking about the difference between agriculturalists, horticulturalists, and pastoralists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Faunal and floral remains in hearths, residue analysis of pottery, stable isotopes in human remains, and recovered tool types can try and answer this question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or radiocarbon dating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  more significant in Western Mexico, particularly in the Oaxaca region

Do you mean southern Mexico? ;p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pompeii unveils Roman kiss for Valentines Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://kernaia.com/purepecha/

It's out!

http://kernaia.com/mixteco/

And they have Mixtec! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mexico can be fun and interesting. There's a lot that we still have not found in West Mexico. I know I've had a great time finding [guachimontones](http://i.imgur.com/WLGl8lv.png) around the Tequila valleys of Jalisco in Google Earth. I've even tried to find some of the guachimontones located in the Bajo at sites like La Gloria. [Guachimontones](http://i.imgur.com/ms4Ats5.png) are somewhat easy to spot, though, since they are round and stick out from the landscape. The square buildings on the hill around the Palacio de Ocomo at Oconahua, for example, are difficult to spot with the combination of vegetation, inadequate resolution, and unsatisfactory lighting in Google Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I changed the title because the [press release by INAH](http://www.inah.gob.mx/es/boletines/5901-pequena-ventana-a-panteon-prehispanico-tumba-de-tiro-hallada-en-la-ciudad-de-colima) makes no mention of a feather headdress. I think this was an interpretation on the author's part and it is in error. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient, Untouched Tomb Yields Horned Figurine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I changed the title because the [press release by INAH](http://www.inah.gob.mx/es/boletines/5901-pequena-ventana-a-panteon-prehispanico-tumba-de-tiro-hallada-en-la-ciudad-de-colima) makes no mention of a feather headdress. I think this was an interpretation on the author's part and it is in error. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient, Untouched Tomb Yields Horned Figurine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The app that's teaching the world an indigenous Mexican language </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should have checked their website before I made my first post because . . .

http://kernaia.com/purepecha/

It's out!

http://kernaia.com/mixteco/

And they have Mixtec! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunting tools tell how first people in Denmark lived </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The app that's teaching the world an indigenous Mexican language </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The app that's teaching the world an indigenous Mexican language </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just learned about this app called [Lets Learn Nhuatl](http://www.konbini.com/en/lifestyle/the-app-designed-to-teach-the-whole-world-the-indigenous-language-nahuatl/), an app designed to teach Nahuatl. I'm not sure how the Nahuatl taught in this app differs from Classic Nahuatl scholars look at in the early colonial period yet, but it should be interesting and fun to check out. The article also mentions that an app is in the works for Purepecha, the indigenous language spoken in the Michoacan region and the former Tarascan Empire, the rivals of the Aztecs.

/u/Ucumu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 16:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, Hancock's ideas are built on poor, cherry-picked pieces evidence and he creates a persecution complex to dupe people with poor critical thinking skills into believing his ideas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That idea has been [refuted](https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2016/12/161219115304.htm), just like all of Hancock's ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is There a Secret Chamber in King Tut's Tomb? A Final Hunt Will Investigate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hey, I was involved with this but not really. I did lab work in Genoa with Julien and Claudine in 2014. It was an amazing experience and I kind of wish I did work in Italy rather than Mexico. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Dakota tribe says running out of options to stop pipeline </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 16:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion but perhaps the section [Water, Wine and Beer](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/health#wiki_water.2C_wine_and_beer) from our FAQ will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 11:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there are [so many more](http://tlatollotl.tumblr.com/post/142930176516/tlatollotls-beachless-yucatan-vacation) sites than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  remember that post about the Roman coin in the Japanese fortress?

Do you remember how that coin dates to centuries before the construction of the fortress? And that it doesn't indicate Rome trading with Japan, but that the coin itself saw continued use as currency or an oddity as it traded hands moving its way eastward? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unearthed London Skeletons to Be Displayed in 'Crossrail' Exhibit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you going to visit any other Maya sites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should cross post to /r/StrangerThings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The old world was into domesticating animals (very significant)

Natives had domesticated animals, dogs, turkeys, guinea pigs, llamas.

 densely populated cities (also a little significant)

Cahokia? Teotihuacan? Tenochtitlan? Cusco? Mayapan? Chichen Itza? Chan Chan? All cities

 The Europeans had already suffered through various plagues

As did Native Americans. They did not live in a disease-free vacuum, they just lived without Old World diseases.

 the Native Americans got hit with all those plagues at once.

They were hit with successive waves of disease, they were not hit with everyone all at once. It took a century just for the Basin of Mexico to go from a few million to less than a million people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Because the Native Americans, etc live in smaller tribal groups rather than larger cities

You might want to rethink your notion of how Native Americans lived. Don't confuse Plains peoples in the 1800s with all Native Americans in North and South America. I could list a number of dense urban centers in Mexico and South America, but you may try to brush that off. So instead, I would say look at the American Southwest, the Mississippian peoples, Southeastern peoples, and the sizes of Native towns in the Northeast. Cahokia, especially, should stand out with its population in the tens of thousands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Persistent tropical foraging in the highlands of terminal Pleistocene/Holocene New Guinea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High-precision radiocarbon dating of political collapse and dynastic origins at the Maya site of Ceibal, Guatemala </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Archaeologists find 12th Dead Sea Scrolls cave](https://phys.org/news/2017-02-archaeologists-12th-dead-sea-scrolls.html)

* [Dig in Cambodia unearths 1,000 year old clay furnace that extracted iron from ore](https://www.cambodiadaily.com/news/dig-unearths-ancient-furnace-in-hunt-for-cambodias-past-124687/)

* [Shifting monsoon altered early cultures in China, study says](http://popular-archaeology.com/issue/winter-2017/article/shifting-monsoon-altered-early-cultures-in-china-study-says)

* ['Monumental' building complex discovered at Qantir in Egypt's Nile Delta - Ancient Egypt](http://english.ahram.org.eg/NewsContent/9/40/257745/Heritage/Ancient-Egypt/Monumental-building-complex-discovered-at-Qantir-i.aspx)

* [Archaeologists, engineers race to save 650 year old tomb from being submerged when Turkey dam is completed](http://www.dailysabah.com/travel/2017/02/06/archaeologists-engineers-race-to-save-ancient-tomb-from-being-submerged)

* [General   Princess's 6th-Century Tomb Found in China Filled with Figurines of Warriors, Camels, Oxcarts   Drummers: An inscription states he won battle with the Yi barbarians. His wife is described as modest   chaste. It is not known why they were buried at the same time.](http://www.livescience.com/57766-tomb-of-chinese-general-princess-found.html)

* [Study shows Pre-Columbian builders managed Amazonian forests](http://popular-archaeology.com/issue/winter-2017/article/study-shows-pre-columbian-builders-managed-amazonian-forests)

* [Abu Dhabi archaeologists unearth rare, well-preserved Stone Age house](https://archaeologynewsnetwork.blogspot.com.au/2017/02/abu-dhabi-archaeologists-unearth-rare.html#2YB41MrjHmxEFyxU.97)

* [Excavations in Tlos, Turkey ](http://www.hurriyetdailynews.com/excavations-in-turkeys-southwest-reveal-anatolian-food-culture-.aspx?pageID=238 nID=109377 NewsCatID=375)

* [Warrior treasures: Saxon gold from the Staffordshire Hoard](https://www.archaeology.co.uk/articles/features/warrior-treasures-saxon-gold-from-the-staffordshire-hoard.htm)

* [After an 11 year hiatus archaeologists get set to dig at Masada, the natural fortress where Jewish rebels staged their last stand against the Roman Empire in 74 CE](http://www.timesofisrael.com/archaeologists-get-set-to-dig-at-masada-after-11-year-hiatus/)

* [New discoveries from Bulgarian show that Celts and Thracians lived together and assimilated](http://archaeologyinbulgaria.com/2017/01/09/celtic-shrine-discovered-in-bulgarias-sboryanovo-showing-celts-mixed-with-ancient-thracian-getae-tribes/)

* [Skeletons, artefacts found at Wiang Lor prehistoric site](http://www.bangkokpost.com/news/general/1193176/)

* [2,000-year-old sex toys found in China](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-4187752/2-000-year-old-sex-toys-China.html)

* [Roman house with ornate mosaic and hypercaust discovered in Leicester](http://www.heritagedaily.com/2017/02/and-home-with-underfloor-heating-among-new-evidence-discovered-from-leicesters-roman-past/114069)

* [Scientists unlock secrets of oldest surviving global trade map ](https://phys.org/news/2017-02-scientists-secrets-oldest-surviving-global.html)

* [300-yr-old shipwreck tells the story of a bloody war between Sweden   its neighbors - The Blekinge is thought to have sunk in 1713, at the height of Sweden's war with Russia   its allies.](http://www.ibtimes.co.uk/ancient-shipwreck-tells-story-bloody-war-between-sweden-its-neighbours-1604499)

* [Baltic hunter-gatherers began farming without influence of migration, ancient DNA suggests](https://phys.org/news/2017-02-baltic-hunter-gatherers-began-farming-migration.html)

* [Ancient Egyptian's Baboon Obsession Laid Hidden Within Luxor Tomb](http://www.seeker.com/ancient-egyptians-baboon-obsession-laid-hidden-within-luxor-tomb-2232890200.html)

* [From 13,000 years ago more than 600 Solar-Aligned Pictographs at the Paleoindian Site of Painel do Pilo along the Lower Amazon River at Monte Alegre, Brazil](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0167692)

* [Archaeologists find 25 skeletons in medieval Cambridge friary - BBC News](http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-cambridgeshire-38735157)

* [Boat from the tenth century recovered from the bottom of lake Lednica in Poland](http://scienceinpoland.pap.pl/en/news/news,412172,wielkopolskie-boat-from-the-tenth-century-recovered-from-the-bottom-of-the-lake-lednica.html)

* [Archaeologist raises $900,000 to recreate ancient sites in VR while waiting for PhD results](http://venturebeat.com/2017/01/29/australian-architectural-startup-raises-679000-to-rebuild-ancient-sites-in-vr/)

* [Climate change drove population decline in New World before Europeans arrived](http://popular-archaeology.com/issue/winter-2017/article/climate-change-drove-population-decline-in-new-world-before-europeans-arrived)

* [Ancient women found in Russian cave were close relatives of todays indigenous population](http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2017/02/ancient-women-found-russian-cave-were-close-relatives-today-s-indigenous-population)

---

And this one is in Spanish, but I wanted to share it anyway

* [Pequea ventana a panten prehispnico, tumba de tiro hallada en la ciudad de Colima](http://www.inah.gob.mx/es/boletines/5901-pequena-ventana-a-panteon-prehispanico-tumba-de-tiro-hallada-en-la-ciudad-de-colima) - ""Small window" to pre-Hispanic pantheon, shot tomb found in the city of Colima" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be pedantic, but the Aztecs and Maya are North American Native Americans.

That being said, perhaps the section [Pre-Columbian Trade and Contact](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/nativeamerican#wiki_pre-columbian_trade_and_contact) from our FAQ will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps you could clarify your question? The Aztecs and Maya are Native Americans after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 03:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! That's a really good article and it is one of his favorites to have people read. All of his articles and book chapters are on Academia.edu and Researchgate.net if you want to read more of his stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 02:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most available books on the area are

* Foster, Michael Stewart, and Shirley Gorenstein, eds. Greater Mesoamerica: The Archaeology of West and Northwest Mexico. University of Utah Press, 2000.

* Townsend, Richard F. Ancient West Mexico: Art and archaeology of the unknown past. Thames and Hudson, 1998.

* Beekman, Christopher S. and Robert B. Pickering. Shaft Tombs and Figures in West Mexican Society: A Reassessment. Gilcrease Museum, 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.inah.gob.mx/es/foto-del-dia/5900-foto-del-dia-peralta-guanajuato </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peralta, Guanajuato </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pequea ventana a panten prehispnico, tumba de tiro hallada en la ciudad de Colima </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pequea ventana a panten prehispnico, tumba de tiro hallada en la ciudad de Colima </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shifting monsoon altered early cultures in China, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have any questions or want further reading, just let me know. I'll be more than happy to answer/provide info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps this previous topic will answer your inquiry.

* [How did the early humans deal eith the Toba super-eruption?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/43fg09/how_did_the_early_humans_deal_eith_the_toba/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the gild! You didn't need to do that, I was just happy to answer.

If you're interested, I have several topics (and a podcast episode) on AskHistorians where I talk in more detail some of the things I've mentioned above.

* [How much contact did the cultures of far west Mexico have with central Mexican cultures during the Classic Period?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/1s4xv1/how_much_contact_did_the_cultures_of_far_west/)

* [Has there ever been archaeological / written evidence to identify the "lost home in the north" of the Aztecs?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3atv2y/has_there_ever_been_archaeological_written/)

* [How much do we know about the Teuchitlan Tradition's societal structure and how it was reflected in the layout of their settlements?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/5ek0pf/how_much_do_we_know_about_the_teuchitlan/)

* [Was There Ever a State in West Mexico Before the Tarascans?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/5e7c20/was_there_ever_a_state_in_west_mexico_before_the/)

* [Do the burial sites of the shaft tomb culture(s) allow us to differentiate between 'common people' and nobility or royalty? If so OR if not, what does that tell us about Western Mexican cultures?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/43tvqk/do_the_burial_sites_of_the_shaft_tomb_cultures/)

* [For a civilization like Classical western Mexico, how much can we learn about daily *life* when our sources relate almost entirely to *death*?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3s5fih/for_a_civilization_like_classical_western_mexico/)

* [Did all meso-american cultures practice human sacrifice?](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/53usws/did_all_mesoamerican_cultures_practice_human/)

* [AskHistorians Podcast 049 - Shaft Tombs of West Mexico](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3rrpe3/askhistorians_podcast_049_shaft_tombs_of_west/)

* [AMA by my advisor](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/2g82cl/i_am_dr_christopher_beekman_ama_about_formative/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  For the sake of scale/context, how big is that dome on the left

The dome measures about 37.5m in diameter, 8m in total height. The entire structure, from platform to platform, measures approximately 99m. This circular arrangement of platforms around a patio space and central structure we call an altar is called a guachimonton.

The naming can get confusing. The site in the picture above is called [Los Guachimontones](http://imgur.com/a/kt0HJ) and is named after a district in the town this site is located near. Each individual structure, however, is called a guachimonton. The town is called Teuchitlan and we named the culture who built these structures the Teuchitlan culture.

At Los Guachimontones there are eight guachimontones and two ballcourts. There is a sister site located further up the hill with five guachimontones and one ballcourt. The immediate area of these two sites makes this the largest site in the Tequila valleys.

There are about 50 or so guachimontones in the Tequila valleys with one in the Bolaos canyon to the north, one by Puerto Vallarta,  one by the town of Comala in Colima, one in the western area of the Atemajac Valley (where Guadalajara is), and several in Guanajuato to the east. There's supposedly one in Nayarit and another at La Campana in Colima, though I've never seen pictures or drawings of it.

 Speculatively, why is this not discussed or researched? Funding? Interest? Not sexy enough?

Jalisco, Nayarit, and Colima are known more for their large and small, hollow and solid [ceramic figures](https://www.google.com/search?q=shaft+tomb+figures source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwjagrfHwf7RAhWni1QKHXCCBuoQ_AUICSgC biw=1536 bih=736) and dioramas that are attributed to the shaft and chamber tombs the dead were buried in at that time. Gong as far back as the Early Formative (1500 BC to 800 BC), the people in this widespread region buried their dead in these shaft and chamber tombs. The earliest ones are located at El Opeo in Michoacan by Lake Chapala. This cemetery consisted of simple chambers dug into the ground with a short staircase to reach them. The chamber would be sealed off and the staircase back filled. The tradition continued through the Middle Formative (800 BC to 300 BC) in places like [Mascota](http://www.famsi.org/reports/03009/03009Mountjoy01.pdf), Jalisco with simple chambers and simple vertical shafts to reach those chambers. It wasn't until the Late Formative and Early Classic periods (300 BC to 550 AD) that shaft and chamber tombs became more numerous and more elaborate. [El Arenal](http://imgur.com/a/mMrco) is the largest tomb known to date and was 17m underground with three well carved chambers dug into the soil for the dead. Unfortunately, the tomb was partially looted before Corona Nuez and a few later Stanley Long were able to document it.

Because these tombs are underground and have little to no surface indicators, almost all of the thousands of ceramic figures in museums across the globe were looted. A lot of this looting was opportunistic in which a farmer finds a depression in his field, digs down a couple of meters, robs the tomb, and sells it to someone in the city who then sells it to museums or art collectors. Some looters made it their job to go around and find these tombs using long metal bars to punch into the ground to try and find a chamber. This looting, however, is not new and has been occurring since the late 1800s. So, too, has the creation of fake ceramic figures been an industry/occupation in this region which casts doubt in the authenticity of the figures in museums today.

Because of this looting, the volume of figures, and the fact that guachimontones are not spectacularly large like pyramids in eastern Mexico or even the yacatas in Michoacan, no one really bothered to take a look any surface architectural remains. Adela Breton was the first one to [document these guachimontones](http://imgur.com/a/Cq3gv) in a letter to a friend. While she published the photo of the mound being looted (possibly an altar from a guachimonton) as well as photos and watercolors of the figures recovered from the mound, she never published her sketches of the site. As a result, the most anyone really did when documenting surface architecture was note that there were mounds. If you look at that first [picture](http://i.imgur.com/Koqc02r.jpg) in the El Arenal album, you can see the arrangement of an altar and platforms that is typical of a guachimonton. But no one recognized it as such. It wasn't until the 1970s that Phil Weigand and his wife noticed these things for what they were when they saw the guachimontones near the town of Ahualulco. Weigand and his wife did some amazing work from the 70s to the 90s doing a lot of small scale survey work, [site map drawing](http://imgur.com/a/AGQ5R), photos, surface finds, etc., but a lot of their work has remained unpublished or published in obscure sources. I had heard that Phil was ridiculed by colleagues who studied other parts of Mesoamerica saying he didn't find anything or that it wasn't important, which drove him towards publishing in obscure places or not publishing at all. He's been vindicated and was able to procure the funds to restore the Los Guachimontones site, but he did not live long enough to see the study of these structures really take off. Phil passed away in 2011 and the study of guachimontones is still trying to take off.

I was drawn to this area because of the unique structures. I thought about continuing with Maya studies in my undergrad until I learned more about the Tarascans in Michoacan. They were so different from the Aztecs and I thought that was intriguing. But then I learned about the Teuchitlan culture and was blown away by how different they were from everyone else. So part of the lack of investigation is interest. Another part has to do with colonial history. 

When the Spanish arrived in the Jalisco region, Nahuatl speakers had invaded and completely changed the region. We can pinpoint this at the end the 500s/early 600s when drought gripped the region. This same drought effected Teotihuacan and most likely drove Nahuatl speakers out of marginal areas on the border of Mesoamerica that could not continue to support agriculture. Areas like Zacatecas or Guanajuato. These people fled southward and created a ripple effect. Those that stayed behind just created more people for later migrations in Mesoamerica at the start of the Early Postclassic and Late Postclassic. The Aztecs were the third wave of migrants that occurred at the beginning of the Late Postclassic. Many of the people in the Basin of Mexico when the Aztecs arrived were second wave migrants. And the Toltecs (and maybe the Pipil of El Salvador) appear to be first wave migrants. 

But because of the drought and the influx of these migrants in Jalisco, the people stopped building guachimontones. They stopped burying their dead in shaft and chamber tombs. They stopped making ceramic figures in earlier period styles. Instead they adopted the more typical Mesoamerican monumental architecture with stepped platforms. They buried their dead in pits or box-shaped tombs. They brought in other art styles for ceramics, figures, etc. It was a complete change to the point where Epiclassic and Postclassic sites were built away from Late Formative and Classic period sites. You don't see sites with a long chronology going back from 1492 to 300 BC. You see sites that are either 1492 to 550 AD or 550 AD to 300 BC+. There's some kind of breakdown in which the people in the area were either all wiped out (unlikely) or completely rejected everything about their culture in favor of this new culture without ever revisiting their old one (loss of faith?).

When the Spanish arrived they arrived to a region made up of tiny city-states with multiple languages and multiple cultures. Sometimes these languages/cultures coexisted within one area and other times there were fierce rivalries between two neighboring towns. But because there was no large empire or state it was hard for the Spanish to control the region. The Spanish were frustrated because they wanted riches and these people did not produce riches in sufficient quantities like the Aztecs or Tarascans. So many of the Spanish resorted to legal and illegal slaving and sold many people off in the slave markets of Mexico City. Eventually a number of these groups set aside their differences, banded together, and rebelled. They used the Spaniard's own unawareness of cultures and languages to openly organize so that when they rebelled, they rebelled as one. This became the Mixton War of 1540 to 1541. Ida Altman has a [great book](https://www.amazon.com/War-Mexicos-West-Spaniards-1524-1550/dp/0826344933) on this topic. Tragically the early and successful resistance of the Natives was broken by the Spanish. And as punishment the Spanish killed many people, enslaved many more, and decimated the culture and language of these people. So we don't have things like the Florentine Codex or Relacion de Michoacan to turn to because the Spanish never bothered to document all the groups in this area as well. And when people wanted to document the cultures and languages of the past, the cultures and languages had either disappeared, were replaced with Spanish culture, or was culture brought by Aztecs, Tarascans, and Tlaxcallans that were made to settle in this now emptied region of the country.

So with not much in the way of Postclassic/contact sites to study, no pre-hispanic writing to turn to, sites that didn't fit the norm for the rest of Mesoamerica, and hard to find tombs, interest and research just hasn't been the same in West Mexico as it has in eastern Mexico.

Hopefully I can help change that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's fascinating as we're finding more and more examples of Pre-Columbian culture that didn't build in stone or easier to find remnants.

The [structures](http://i.imgur.com/d69q8K8.jpg) I study in Jalisco, Mexico did not become widely recognized until the 1970s (though they were reported as eary as the 1890s). Even now, they are not widely discussed or researched

 massive and large-scale human labor projects not just in the Americas but in Asia and Africa as well.

One of my favorite things to tell people about are the [Walls of Benin](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Walls_of_Benin) which you can see encircling parts of the modern city of Benin today. They are massive and certainly were not an easy accomplishment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Monumental' building complex discovered at Qantir in Egypt's Nile Delta - Ancient Egypt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article - http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/01/31/1614359114 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Impact of pre-Columbian geoglyph builders on Amazonian forests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Impact of pre-Columbian geoglyph builders on Amazonian forests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study shows Pre-Columbian builders managed Amazonian forests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're focusing on history from around the world and want to be super cheesy, you could go with Ourstory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://monarobot.tumblr.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, different artists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could email her and probably purchase a print

http://monarobot.tumblr.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, this is all a Maya art style. That's what Monarobot does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 04:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bar is 5 so two bars is 10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forget that the bronze phallus, if used as a dildo, is going into an acidic environment. And acid is not kind to bronze. Perhaps the acidic environment left unique usewear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is by [Monarobot](http://monarobot.tumblr.com). I have an [Imgur gallery](http://imgur.com/a/ZZtY5) of all the ones she did l, but I haven't updated it in while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not polishing as in polishing the bronze to make it smooth and look nice. Polishing as in wear from repeated use. Even polished metal will exhibit more polishing in areas that come into frequent and repeated use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How do you know those stone tools were used as sex toys? It could as well be their version of a crucifix (there are several instances of penises being religious symbols), decoration (we have examples for that too) or a joke item.

It really depends on the context in which these found, examples from the same time period, and the presence or absence of use-wear. Not everything can be boiled down to religion. If these bronze phalluses show use-wear (i.e. polishing) it may very well have been practical items rather than symbolic items. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a press release from the Asian Art Museum in San Francisco that was cited in the Daily Mail article,

http://www.asianart.org/press_releases/77# </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These were cited in the article,

http://www.asianart.org/press_releases/77#

http://www.chinanews.com/cul/2011/06-10/3101815.shtml </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pence Defends Trumps Criticism of Judge Who Blocked Travel Ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 19:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, why not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/AskHistorians as their own podcast

https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/podcast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a shame because a look at the paste can help determine whether it is authentic or not. I won't claim to have seen ever kind of Mesoamerican artifact, but I will say that I have not seen anything like this before. My gut tells me this is just a tourist item.

Out of curiosity, the green color is somewhat odd. Is that a result of the lighting, a pigment, or is the ceramic itself green? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Most Native Americans, especially pre-Columbus, were still semi-nomadic hunter/gathering societies that relied directly on their environment.

Most Natives were agriculturalists, not hunter-gatherers.

 In the more semi-arid regions, such as the American south west, the people had to adapt to their surroundings and anthropological records show that their diets consisted more of small game and seeds/berries

American Southwest Natives farmed. There is an extensive system of irrigation canals where Phoenix is today. The people at Mesa Verde constructed breaks on the plateau their cliff dwellings were built into in order to capture and retain water for farming.

 the people living in the Great Plains, or more fertile areas, were found to have lived off of big game and more sustainable flora.

The Plains peoples were hunter-gatherers and some groups in the Pacific Northwest and California were, as well. But up and down the Mississippi, the Southeast, Appalachia, and the Northeast the people were farmers. The farmers may have supplemented their farming with hunting and gathering, but it does not make them hunter-gatherers. Would you characterize Americans in the 1700s who had a farm and supplemented their farming with hunting and gathering as hunter-gatherers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps the section [Disease in the Americas](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/nativeamerican#wiki_disease_in_the_americas) in our FAQ will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, is it glued together? If not, post a picture of its paste (the side that shows the inside of the ceramic). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/ArtefactPorn/comments/5s2hug/os_one_of_two_han_dynasty_era_bronze_sex_toy/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion, but perhaps the section [Ancients' views of static electricity](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/science#wiki_ancients.27_views_of_static_electricity) from our FAQ will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Article](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-4187752/2-000-year-old-sex-toys-China.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Article](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-4187752/2-000-year-old-sex-toys-China.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Article](http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-4187752/2-000-year-old-sex-toys-China.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Han dynasty era bronze sex toys found in a tomb in Jiangsu Province near Shanghai, China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] One of two Han dynasty era bronze sex toy found in a tomb in Jiangsu Province near Shanghai, China [306x459] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] One of two Han dynasty era bronze sex toy found in a tomb in Jiangsu Province near Shanghai, China [634x357] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2,000-year-old sex toys found in China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2,000-year-old sex toys found in China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never Alone (Kisima Initchua) is a puzzle side scroller that explores the history, mythology, and beliefs of an Inuit group in Alaska. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, no problem. If you would like books on more specific subjects let me or one of our other pre-Columbian flaired users know. The book list is a list of general histories and as a result do not dive into too much detail (like iconography, household archaeogy, ceramic production, textile products, etc.). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you checked out our [book list](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/books/americas#wiki_latin_american_history) located in our sidebar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost a hat here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roman house with ornate mosaic and hypercaust discovered in Leicester </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists unlock secrets of oldest surviving global trade map </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible. But the only places I know of that were using metallurgy at this time are in Central or South America. Central and South America have been hypothesized as the locations from where metallurgy spread to Mesoamerica, but I am not aware of any hard physical proof linking the two areas together. There is circumstantial evidence in the form of bell shape (and I think tweezers shape), but nothing from Central/South America in origin found in Mexico. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around the Great Lakes for sure, not sure about anywhere else. And that was 6,000 to 3,000 years ago. I haven't heard of any native copper working in Mesoamerica prior to 600 AD. That's why it surprised me. Perhaps /u/Ucumu can chime in, he knows more about metallurgy than I.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 15:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Im reading the chapter The Shaft Tombs of Parcelas 12, 19, and 25 and their Inhabitants: Funerary Considerations of the Recent Archaeological Finds in Colima by Marcos Trinidad Zavaleta Lucido and Rosa Mara Flores Ramrez in *Shaft Tombs and Figures in West Mexican Society: A Reassessment* (2016). On page 67 they are discussing the remains found in a shaft tomb that dates to the Comala phase (0 AD to 400 AD). This is what they say,

 Likewise some of the bones showed the remains of red pigment and of adhered metal, surely from the copper beads that were found in the interior of the tomb.1

What, what, WHAT?! Copper beads in the tomb?! But metallurgy wasnt introduced to Mesoamerica until sometime after 600 AD. But they had a note! And the note says,

 Even though the a remains recovered from the interior of the tomb indicate that it was utilized solely in the Comala phase, it is not possible to rule out a later reuse of the tomb during this phase or that the offerings were deposited at the same time, until other tests, such as residual collagen, are carried out.

So its possible the copper beads are from a later period. But then, it looks like they may in fact be from the same period as the tombs. Thats a big find despite the brief description. I think Zavaleta and Flores are waiting on those tests to confirm the dates of the tomb before making the big announcement. Im sure they are going to get some push back for their findings, but I hope their evidence holds up. I had an inkling that someone was going to find metal in a shaft tomb at some point, I just didn't think it was going to be so soon. I'm going to keep my eyes peeled for their publication on these beads because I think it is going to be huge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abu Dhabi archaeologists unearth rare, well-preserved Stone Age house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Im reading the chapter The Shaft Tombs of Parcelas 12, 19, and 25 and their Inhabitants: Funerary Considerations of the Recent Archaeological Finds in Colima by Marcos Trinidad Zavaleta Lucido and Rosa Mara Flores Ramrez in *Shaft Tombs and Figures in West Mexican Society: A Reassessment* (2016). On page 67 they are discussing the remains found in a shaft tomb that dates to the Comala phase (0 AD to 400 AD). This is what they say,

 Likewise some of the bones showed the remains of red pigment and of adhered metal, surely from the copper beads that were found in the interior of the tomb.1

What, what, WHAT?! Copper beads in the tomb?! But metallurgy wasnt introduced to Mesoamerica until sometime after 600 AD. But they had a note! And the note says,

 Even though the a remains recovered from the interior of the tomb indicate that it was utilized solely in the Comala phase, it is not possible to rule out a later reuse of the tomb during this phase or that the offerings were deposited at the same time, until other tests, such as residual collagen, are carried out.

So its possible the copper beads are from a later period. But then, it looks like they may in fact be from the same period as the tombs. Thats a big find despite the brief description. I think Zavaleta and Flores are waiting on those tests to confirm the dates of the tomb before making the big announcement. Im sure they are going to get some push back for their findings, but I hope their evidence holds up. I had an inkling that someone was going to find metal in a shaft tomb at some point, I just didn't think it was going to be so soon. I'm going to keep my eyes peeled for their publication on these beads because I think it is going to be huge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltic hunter-gatherers began farming without influence of migration, ancient DNA suggests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Egyptian's Baboon Obsession Laid Hidden Within Luxor Tomb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 22:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would support a feature like the one you suggested. And I'm not saying that just so more people will ask about my area of expertise ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change drove population decline in New World before Europeans arrived </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient women found in Russian cave were close relatives of todays indigenous population </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The journal article is [here](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0169524) if you're interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 19:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Tomb of Ramesside-era royal scribe uncovered in Luxor](http://english.ahram.org.eg/NewsContent/9/40/257292/Heritage/Ancient-Egypt/Tomb-of-Ramessideera-royal-scribe-uncovered-in-Lux.aspx)

* [Midcontinental Native American population dynamics and late Holocene hydroclimate extremes](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep41628)

* [Oldest Prostate Stones Ever Found Suggest a Man Was in Agony 12,000 Years Ago](http://www.seeker.com/oldest-prostate-stones-ever-found-suggest-a-man-was-in-agony-12000-yea-2228584491.html)

* [Ocmulgee Mounds Historical National Park Expansion Bill (HR 538) passes House. Park Lands will preserve 2800 acres to the initial 702 acres.](http://www.macon.com/news/local/article129705059.html)

* [Want to Be a Space Archaeologist? Heres Your Chance](https://www.wired.com/2017/01/want-space-archaeologist-heres-chance/)

* [2,000 year old glass-making workshop in Poland](http://scienceinpoland.pap.pl/en/news/news,412821,the-oldest-glass-making-workshop-in-poland-is-approx-2-thousand-years-old.html)

* [38,000-Year-Old Cave Art Found In French Cave](https://www.yahoo.com/news/38-000-old-cave-art-095835071.html)

* [Coins discovery 'will re-write' Anglo-Saxon history](http://www.msn.com/en-au/news/world/coins-discovery-will-re-write-anglo-saxon-history/ar-AAmmGlU?li=AAgfYrC ocid=mailsignout)

* [Archaeologists discover wreck of a 1,800 year old Roman ship near the island of Cabrera, south of Mallorca - "To our knowledge this is the first wreck in Spanish waters that since the sinking by no human hand has touched."](http://www.hotrecentnews.com/news/antique-ship-wreck-found-in-mallorca/20802)

* [4,000 BC-800 BC artifacts of Stone, Bronze and Iron Ages found in Angus, Scotland dig](https://www.thecourier.co.uk/fp/news/local/angus-mearns/349023/angus-dig-finds-ancient-artefacts-international-importance/)

* [Wyoming Wildfire Reveals Massive Shoshone Camp, Thousands of Artifacts in Native American site likely used for as much as 2,500 years](http://westerndigs.org/wyoming-wildfire-reveals-massive-pre-contact-shoshone-camp-thousands-of-artifacts/)

* [The ancient Indus civilizations adaptation to climate change](http://www.heritagedaily.com/2017/01/the-ancient-indus-civilizations-adaptation-to-climate-change/114027)

* [Ancient Mayan Superhighways Found in the Guatemala Jungle](http://www.seeker.com/ancient-mayan-superhighways-found-in-the-guatemala-jungle-2219303581.html)

* [Gold. Jewels. Armour. These are some of the riches uncovered alongside the remains of an ancient Celtic priestess near the Danube River in Germany ](http://www.news.com.au/technology/science/archaeology/excavation-of-celtic-priestess-grave-reveals-gold-gems-armour/news-story/b049ae418cf6f29c16811c93fcaf33c1)

* [Oil, gas drilling rights near Chaco Canyon sold for $3M](http://www.santafenewmexican.com/news/local_news/oil-gas-drilling-rights-near-chaco-canyon-sold-for-m/article_f7727a6c-9694-5116-bf39-7cf492dee240.html)

* [Foundations of three Roman houses found under Chichester park.](https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2017/jan/26/foundations-of-three-roman-houses-found-under-chichester-park) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tomb of Ramesside-era royal scribe uncovered in Luxor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Midcontinental Native American population dynamics and late Holocene hydroclimate extremes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 14:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a good point, Earth would just be easier. Isn't the resolution for this program better than Earth? That would be just one advantage. There are sites in Jalisco that I have been to that you cannot see on Earth, for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How much looting is done/abetted by locals in that area?

It's dropped off since the 70s, but still occurs from time to time.

 looters being local to the site they're looting

I think they were local to the region with people going around Nayarit, Colima, and Jalisco

 I also don't think looters would take the time to look up images just because they've not been looted yet when as you say Google Earth can help you incorporate so many factors so easily to find potential areas.

Perhaps. But if money is tight and you need the cash, you may do a little research before you go out looting.

 The kid "finding a lost Maya city" points out the other problem, that satellite images only identify anomalies and do not help interpret them. Parcak's attempts at finding a Viking site faced the same criticism that the evidence for the site dating to that time period was only circumstantial.

Yeah, I've got 50 or so pushpins on Earth of things I think are buildings, but I'm waiting to ground truth them at some point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article - http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0169524 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oldest Prostate Stones Ever Found Suggest a Man Was in Agony 12,000 Years Ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Late Pleistocene/Early Holocene Evidence of Prostatic Stones at Al Khiday Cemetery, Central Sudan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who works in an area that has experienced looting for over 120 years (Jalisco, Mexico) and pokes around Google Earth looking for sites in that area, I would be hesitant in reaching out to the public to find things for me. If you are savvy at all, even a small 100m x 100m square with any features can be found on Google Earth no matter how you rotate or flip the image. When that story last year about the kid who found a lost Maya city in the jungle using Google Earth broke, it took me all of 15 minutes to find the exact location of the images in the articles. Maybe looters are not as savvy as me and won't be able to find the locations of these things, but I would still rather not chance the possibility of giving them more places to loot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to Be a Space Archaeologist? Heres Your Chance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who works in an area that has experienced looting for over 120 years (Jalisco, Mexico) and pokes around Google Earth looking for sites in that area, I would  be hesitant in reaching out to the public to find things for me. If you are savvy at all, even a small 100m x 100m square with any features can be found on Google Earth no matter how you rotate or flip the image. When that story last year about the kid who found a lost Maya city in the jungle using Google Earth broke, it took me all of 15 minutes to find the exact location of the images in the articles. Maybe looters are not as savvy as me and won't be able to find the locations of these things, but I would still rather not chance the possibility of giving them more places to loot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to Be a Space Archaeologist? Heres Your Chance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fossilized tree and ice cores help date huge volcanic eruption 1,000 years ago to within three months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 17:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 20:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always room for discussion but perhaps the section [Native American Genocide](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/nativeamerican#wiki_native_american_genocide) from our FAQ and this [recent topic](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/5pyxx8/genocide_of_native_americans/) will answer your inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 14:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Aztecs are Native Americans. Any peoples living in the Americas before 1492 or descended from Native peoples and are living today are Native Americans. I'm only speculating, but your co-working may have a certain perception of what constitutes Native Americans based on media portrayal. Many people think of Plains peoples who used horses to raid American towns and forts and fight the Union army, like the Comanche or Apache, as the only kind of Native American since they are commonly portrayed in Old West films. There is, in fact, a wide range of Native peoples who all lived many different lifestyles before and after the arrival of Europeans. Many of them were agriculturalists who made no use of the horse since the horse had not lived in the Americas for several tens of thousand years before their reintroduction by European conquerors after 1492. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ancient Indus civilizations adaptation to climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 13:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Mayan Superhighways Found in the Guatemala Jungle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Mayan Superhighways Found in the Guatemala Jungle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Mayan Superhighways Found in the Guatemala Jungle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been to Jalisco, Puebla, Oaxaca, and Yucatan and have never had to drink Coke from a bag nor seen someone who drank Coke from a bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oil, gas drilling rights near Chaco Canyon sold for $3M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 02:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be interested in this section of the /r/AskHistorians FAQ

https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/nativeamerican#wiki_technology_and_civilization_in_the_americas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 03:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apocalypto

A city would not be some wondrous thing to a villager. The Maya did not practice the volume of sacrifice depicted in the movie. The art and architecture is not 100% Postclassic Maya. You have some Classic Maya and Aztec influence.

I could go on. The movie was kind of a mess

And don't get me started on Indiana Jones </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * [Cops seize 3,500 stolen artifacts in suspected art-trafficking ring](http://www.nbcnews.com/news/world/police-seize-3-500-stolen-artifacts-arrest-75-suspected-art-n710866)

* [Archaeologists find 3,500-year-old jewelry workshop](http://cphpost.dk/news/danish-archaeologists-find-3500-year-old-gemstones.html)

* [Archaeologists uncover new clues to Maya collapse](https://phys.org/news/2017-01-archaeologists-uncover-clues-maya-collapse.html)

* [Archaeologists discover man whose tongue was replaced by a stone - Roman British skeleton found buried face down in Northamptonshire has tongue mutilation seemingly unique for the period](https://www.theguardian.com/science/2017/jan/23/archaeologists-discover-man-tongue-replaced-stone-roman-britain?CMP=twt_a-science_b-gdnscience)

* [2,700-year-old goddess statue discovered underwater in Turkey](http://www.dailysabah.com/history/2017/01/22/2700-year-old-goddess-statue-discovered-underwater-in-turkey)

* [Authenticating the oldest book in the Americas](http://news.yale.edu/2017/01/18/authenticating-oldest-book-americas)

* [New research examines ancient Roman trash from Pompeii to to understand the relationship between ordinary Romans and their stuff: Find signs that objects were well-worn, re-used, and possibly recycled](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2017/01/20/truth-garbage-new-research-examines-ancient-roman-trash/96815766/)

* [Isis destroys tetrapylon monument in Palmyra](https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/jan/20/isis-destroys-tetrapylon-monument-palmyra-syria?)

* [Hell Gap archaeology site wins national recognition](http://www.wyofile.com/column/hell-gap-archaeology-site-wins-national-recognition/)

* [Treasures from 2,600-year-old grave of Celtic princess in Germany reveal their secrets](http://www.ibtimes.co.uk/treasures-2600-year-old-grave-celtic-princess-germany-reveal-their-secrets-1602047)

* [Ancient Sundial Shaped Like Ham Was Roman Pocket Watch](http://news.nationalgeographic.com/2017/01/ancient-roman-sundial-pork-clock-pompeii-archaeology-science/)

* [Lost Dark Age Kingdom Uncovered in Scotland](http://www.seeker.com/lost-dark-age-kingdom-uncovered-in-scotland-2201671707.html)

* [Iceman Oetzi's last meal was 'Stone Age bacon'](https://phys.org/news/2017-01-iceman-oetzi-meal-stone-age.html)

* [Evidence of a lunar observatory built in the Shetland Islands, long before Stonehenge and the Egyptian pyramids.](https://drive.google.com/open?id=0Bzp1DG8V0H7SeVNYN25rR3BOVjA)

* [3,500-year-old Greek settlement](http://en.protothema.gr/65-byzantine-tombs-unearthed-in-ancient-greek-city-in-turkey-photos/)

* [Massive Burial Ground Unearthed at Medieval Monastery in Sudan: The remains of at least 123 people have been excavated at a series of four cemeteries near the ruins of a medieval Christian monastery in Sudan.](http://www.livescience.com/57553-burial-ground-unearthed-at-medieval-monastery.html)

* [The First Humans May Have Arrived in North America 10,000 Years Earlier Than Previously Thought](https://www.yahoo.com/style/first-humans-may-arrived-north-174630739.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops seize 3,500 stolen artifacts in suspected art-trafficking ring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Dakota GOP will declare 'state of emergency' to repeal voter-approved ethics reform law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 13:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The artifacts did not come from space, the iron used in the artifact did. What a click baity title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 22:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an old article. They got to the end of the tunnel and found nothing.

Also, this shouldn't be tagged as Aztec. Teotihuacan is not Aztec </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Quiero excavar la tumba y publicar la informacion. Pocas tumbas han sido excavadas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obsidian and Blood by Aliette de Bodard - fiction

The Florentine Codex by Friar Bernardino de Sahagn (okay, this is 12 books, but still)  - nonfiction

Aztec Warfare by Ross Hassig - nonfiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 12:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mexico is not a part of [Central America](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Central_America) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 05:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you find a shaft tomb, let me know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I somewhat disagree with the term collapse, but that comes from having read Tainter's and Mcanany and Yoffee's work on collapses and what it truly means. I am intrigued by Inomata and his team's dates which chronicle the site history of Ceibal. Inomata has done some great work on Middle Preclassic Ceibal and I don't doubt that he has done great work with this topic as well. I do wonder how these radiocarbon dates will shift the discussion on collapses and what they mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeologists uncover new clues to Maya collapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeologists uncover new clues to Maya collapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeologists uncover new clues to Maya collapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 02:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have your parents visited Los Guachimontones yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you visited Los Guachimontones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know a whole lot of articles on the subject, to be honest. But I know a few. I haven't read all of them

John Pohl has an article in Arqueologia Mexicana

For reference - https://dialnet.unirioja.es/servlet/articulo?codigo=3972281

Cabrero has an article on it, though I haven't read it

http://revistas.unam.mx/index.php/antropologia/article/download/13091/12424

And Michael Mathiowetz has a lot of stuff on Aztatlan as a whole

https://www.academia.edu/7460240/_2014_Recuperan_importante_acervo_fotogr%C3%A1fico_sobre_la_arqueolog%C3%ADa_costera_Aztatl%C3%A1n_Important_Photographic_Collection_Recovered_on_Aztatl%C3%A1n_Coastal_Archaeology_Authors_Mauricio_Gardu%C3%B1o_Ambriz_and_Michael_Mathiowetz_

https://www.academia.edu/4424564/_2013_The_Aztatl%C3%A1n_Culture_and_the_Puebloan_World_Assessing_the_Role_of_Postclassic_West_Mexico_in_Southwestern_Cultural_Change

https://www.academia.edu/19576200/Weaving_Our_Life_The_Economy_and_Ideology_of_Cotton_in_Postclassic_West_Mexico

https://www.academia.edu/11260113/The_Bringers_of_Cacao_Portrayals_of_New_World_Primates_in_the_Art_of_the_Aztatl%C3%A1n_Culture_of_Postclassic_West_Mexico_AD_850_900-1350_

https://www.academia.edu/9291672/One_Thousand_Years_of_Cacao_Cultivation_and_Ritual_Use_in_Nayarit_Mexico_AD_900_to_present_

https://www.academia.edu/5156244/The_Origin_of_Mitote_Ceremonialism_in_Postclassic_West_Mexico

https://www.academia.edu/3688297/The_West_Mexican_Origin_of_Cacao_found_in_the_Ancient_American_Southwest

https://www.academia.edu/2368697/Solar_Ceremonialism_and_Human_Sacrifice_The_Aztatl%C3%A1n_Tradition_at_Chacalilla_Nayarit

https://www.academia.edu/2368554/The_Aroma_and_Nectar_of_Flowers_Floral_Symbolism_in_the_Art_and_Ritual_of_the_Aztatl%C3%A1n_Tradition_of_Ancient_West_Mexico

https://www.academia.edu/2368649/Cultura_Material_y_Religi%C3%B3n_en_el_Antiguo_Occidente_de_M%C3%A9xico_Documentando_las_Colecciones_de_la_tradici%C3%B3n_Aztatl%C3%A1n_en_los_museos_de_los_Estados_Unidos_y_M%C3%A9xico </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you do decide to go to Yucatan and visit some sites, I wrote [this post](http://tlatollotl.tumblr.com/post/142930176516/tlatollotls-beachless-yucatan-vacation) on a whole week's worth of sites you can visit while bumming around Yucatan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 12:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if anyone else has except Thompson and now Miller and Coe.

While this could very well be an ambitious forgery, I think it passes too many criteria to be a forgery. Between the age of the paper, the method of construction, the method of decorating, the iconography, and the paint used, to me it is authentic. For a forger to do all that they would have had intimate access to a real codex, know of iconography before anyone else, have found blank pre-columbian paper that dated to the correct time period, and know what it meant and how to use it, and have figured out Maya Blue without telling anyone. 

Occam's razor, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 12:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that the Aztatlan culture of Nayarit had Mixteca-Puebla art before the Toltecs and Mixteca-Puebla area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 12:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hassig says in his 1992 book, that if Chichen Itza's population density was the same as Dzibilchaltun it would have a population between 15,625 to 33,250. The median population would be not much larger than Mayapan 

https://books.google.com/books?id=0X3TExVt0EYC pg=PA128 lpg=PA128 dq=chichen+itza+population source=bl ots=cxmt9ZF_OR sig=GbxzVvJofH_la0pozLwh9dZUrUA hl=en sa=X ved=0ahUKEwj42976z9XRAhVIw1QKHfWICHQQ6AEItQEwFA#v=onepage q=chichen%20itza%20population f=false </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are. The wiki article on the Dresden says that it could be a copy of an earlier codex. 

It could also simply be artistic choice to include a more Central Mexican art style than a Maya. It may have been thought of as foreign and exotic and thus had more power and prestige. But I'm just guessing. If artwork was the basis for establishing empires, than the Aztatlan culture of Nayarit created an empire reaching Oaxaca and Puebla since the Mixteca-Puebla style appears earlier in Nayarit than in Central Mexico. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 03:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  just inferior

:(

Have you seen the LiDAR map of the site? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is cooking bad? I can see not cooking every day because you make a ton of food and then eat leftovers. But why else shouldn't you cook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 22:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know of Mayapan and some of its history. I just haven't seen much of its art or artifacts. Marilyn Masson was one of my professors in undergrad and she told me plenty of the city. We just never discussed the artwork.

She once told me that people call Mayapan a knockoff because of two reasons. The first, Mayapan's Castillo and Caracol are smaller. The second, Mayapan looks worse than Chichen. I don't recall her discussing why the size was smaller, but she did discuss why its appearance was worse. Chichen was built with cut stone and very little of it was plastered over. Mayapan, however, went back to using plaster to covers its buildings and thus did not need to invest in the time and labor for cut stone. She thought it was unfair to call Mayapan a knockoff just based on its appearance.

Somewhat related, the main pyramid for the Itza Maya of Nojpeten supposedly looked like the Castillo from Chichen and Mayapan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a Postclassic book which means the International style was very common in Mesoamerica at the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it is a Postclassic book. Chichen Itza does have a lot of International style art. I don't think I've seen enough of Mayapan to know for sure how International their stuff is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I love this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authenticating the oldest book in the Americas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authenticating the oldest book in the Americas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 19:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are tourist items that are kinda sorta based on actual Maya art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Decides Who Counts as Native American? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. 

Wrong culture, wrong piece of art, wrong kind of calendar.

The Maya Long Count, the calendar people were obsessed with, doesn't end. It counts up from the point of creation, not down to a point of destruction. It is made up of five different cycles of days. One of those cycles was like our millennium and it was completed in 2012. We are now in a new cycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 13:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Native Americans do have a "European" component to their DNA that is very ancient. I say European because it shows up in modern populations. However, that same component has been found in Siberians and Siberian remains that are thousands of years old. Since Siberians are the closest related populations to Natives, this suggests that there was a split sometime in the Old World before people reached Siberia. One group went northwest to Europe, the other continued northeast to Siberia.

Native Americans also have traces of Denisovan DNA which suggests that their Old World ancestors had some intimate interaction before reaching the New World. Europeans have almost no Denisovan DNA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 04:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are three new books out if you're interested, all produced in part by the Gilcrease Museum.

There's *Shaft Tombs and Figures in West Mexican Society: A Reassessment* edited by Christopher Beekman and Robert Pickering. You can get it on [Amazon](https://www.amazon.com/Shaft-Tombs-Figures-Mexican-Society/dp/0981979998/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1484968216 sr=8-1 keywords=shaft+tombs+and+figures).

The other two you will have to call the museum and have them send it to you. There is *West Mexico: Ritual and Identity* and *The Visual Guide to West Mexico Shaft Tomb Ceramic Figures* both of which are by Robert Pickering and Cheryl Smallwood-Roberts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 03:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, another with an eye for West Mexican figures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a resource that lists unique chemical compounds for foods that one can look for when conducting a liquid chromatographymass spectrometry test of ceramic vessels. So if you were going to test a vessel to see if it was a pot that was used to cook beans, is there a unique chemical compound for beans that you can look for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tacos. The only good tacos come from Mexico </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hell Gap archaeology site wins national recognition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outraged Westerners look to Trump after Obamas EPA refuses to pay claims from Gold King Mine spill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 17:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 16:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Spanish is not that great, to be honest. But it sounds like the accusation stems from McGovern giving unpublished data to a brewery.

There also seems to be an issue with Laura Almendros from INAH-Colima who has been accused of plagiarism, not providing proper credit, and not seeking the required permission from authorities to send ceramic sherds to McGovern which he then tested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any of you study organic chemistry? Or know someone who studies organic chemistry/is an organic chemist? A friend of mine is wondering if there is any sort of database containing biomarkers from plants that you could look for in a residue analysis test. Like how you would look for theobromine for evidence of chocolate. He's specifically looking for squash, beans, manioc, vanilla, and honey.

---

Somewhat related, Patrick McGovern from UPenn has been [accused](http://www.reforma.com/aplicacioneslibre/articulo/default.aspx?id=1026093 md5=bd656f9abcb2601e6439ba848c77f250 ta=0dfdbac11765226904c16cb9ad1b2efe lcmd5=b0cd43729c025bf9127ad6d0ef91f2ce) (Spanish, lo siento) of plagiarism, breach of contract, and a violation of the code of ethics on some work related to Capacha vessels by Patricia Colunga, Daniel Zizumbo-Villarreal, and Fernando Gonzlez. I guess McGovern gave the details of a residue analysis to some brewers who wanted to recreate the 3,500 year old distilled drink and this action was a big no-no. I have written about Daniel Zizumbo-Villarreal et. al.'s 2009 study [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3dynjb/what_kinds_of_alcoholic_beverages_did_the_native/) and [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/2z0p4w/saturday_reading_and_research_march_14_2015/cpeo5r7/?context=3) if you are interested. While I found the experimentation fascinating, I was hesitant to charge forth proclaiming that the Capacha culture actually had distilled spirits without any sort of residue analysis. But if McGovern, Colunga, Zizumbo-Villarreal, and Gonzlez did do the tests and did find evidence, this does change our understanding of alcoholic beverages in Mesoamerica. And it makes me question whether the [claims](http://mexiconewsdaily.com/news/mezcals-history-is-older-than-thought/) of distillation by two researchers working in Oaxaca are not so far-fetched as I first thought. Hopefully when all this mess between McGovern, Colunga, Zizumbo-Villarreal, and Gonzlez is sorted out, we can get our hands on a published article of the results to judge for ourselves whether the claim for distillation holds true or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 15:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any of you study organic chemistry? Or know someone who studies organic chemistry/is an organic chemist? A friend of mine is wondering if there is any sort of database containing biomarkers from plants that you could look for in a residue analysis test. Like how you would look for theobromine for evidence of chocolate. He's specifically looking for squash, beans, manioc, vanilla, and honey.

---

Somewhat related, Patrick McGovern from UPenn has been [accused](http://www.reforma.com/aplicacioneslibre/articulo/default.aspx?id=1026093 md5=bd656f9abcb2601e6439ba848c77f250 ta=0dfdbac11765226904c16cb9ad1b2efe lcmd5=b0cd43729c025bf9127ad6d0ef91f2ce) (Spanish, lo siento) of plagiarism, breach of contract, and a violation of the code of ethics on some work related to Capacha vessels by Patricia Colunga, Daniel Zizumbo-Villarreal, and Fernando Gonzlez. I guess McGovern gave the details of a residue analysis to some brewers who wanted to recreate the 3,500 year old distilled drink and this action was a big no-no. I have written about Daniel Zizumbo-Villarreal et. al.'s 2009 study [here](https://np.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/3dynjb/what_kinds_of_alcoholic_beverages_did_the_native/) and [here](https://np.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/2z0p4w/saturday_reading_and_research_march_14_2015/cpeo5r7/?context=3) if you are interested. While I found the experimentation fascinating, I was hesitant to charge forth proclaiming that the Capacha culture actually had distilled spirits without any sort of residue analysis. But if McGovern, Colunga, Zizumbo-Villarreal, and Gonzlez did do the tests and did find evidence, this does change our understanding of alcoholic beverages in Mesoamerica. And it makes me question whether the [claims](http://mexiconewsdaily.com/news/mezcals-history-is-older-than-thought/) of distillation by two researchers working in Oaxaca are not so far-fetched as I first thought. Hopefully when all this mess between McGovern, Colunga, Zizumbo-Villarreal, and Gonzlez is sorted out, we can get our hands on a published article of the results to judge for ourselves whether the claim for distillation holds true or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treasures from 2,600-year-old grave of Celtic princess in Germany reveal their secrets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 14:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if you scroll down a bit further you get this,

 The terms "Stone Age", "Bronze Age", and "Iron Age" were never meant to suggest that advancement and time periods in prehistory are only measured by the type of tool material, rather than, for example, social organization, food sources exploited, adaptation to climate, adoption of agriculture, cooking, settlement and religion. Like pottery, the typology of the stone tools combined with the relative sequence of the types in various regions provide a chronological framework for the evolution of man and society. They serve as diagnostics of date, rather than characterizing the people or the society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The archaeological evidence is not gone because humans do not live exclusively on the coast, even if they live on an island. If people had migrated to the islands earlier there would be evidence of it inland. So far, no such evidence has been found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 05:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not necessarily. People, culture, and history is not a game of Civilization in which everyone follows a predefined and set tech tree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That seems less likely to me. Why don't these populations show up in the genetics of native north Americans?

Maybe they do. I'm not a geneticist. All I know is that all Native Americans, North and South, have their strongest roots in Siberia. I also know that minor genetic markers today were once [more widespread](http://www.sciencemag.org/news/2015/11/inca-child-mummy-reveals-lost-genetic-history-south-america) in the past. Unfortunately Europeans brought diseases that wiped out a lot of genetic diversity in the Americas. 

 We already know that people in the ice age were capable of sea voyages due to the date that humans arrived in Australia and other pieces of evidence.

A short hop across a channel is not exactly crossing the entire Pacific ocean with thousands of people to populate an entire continent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Stone Age refers to a period of time, not a level of technological advancement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they weren't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice to doubt and all, but Monte Verde is clearly a pre-Clovis site away from the coast. It has excellent stratigraphy and excellent preservation which is why so many Clovis-first archaeologists got upset when the carbon dates came back as 14,000 BP. New work at the site has pushed its date back to 18,000 BP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
