<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's certainly one way of handling it lol! 

I'm too much of a goody-two-shoes to put off my coursework and I still manage to be nearly late sending it in! XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt this way a lot when I first started my degree. I think you can't predict what will happen, but if you're doing well right now, I think that's a pretty good sign. There's also usually lots of things universities have in place to support you if you're finding something difficult. I don't really believe in 'failure', I think if something goes wrong there are always ways around it or other options, and to me nothing in life is wasted. 

It's maybe easy for me to say, but have faith in yourself. I think pretty much everyone feels like this sometime, and I'm sure that's not actually going to be the case. What degree is it you're doing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately for me, my course is currently part-time (though it's full-time from next year) and I study from home, so I don't think I'm as swamped with coursework as some. With that being said, I've found as long as I structure my work time carefully and prioritize, I can keep on top of it quite easily. It's honestly not horrifically stressful like I thought it would be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the paper about exactly? 

I think the boring parts of study are the worst. Difficult essays with a deadline I'm fine with, but for me reading Hard Times was so boring, I found it one of the hardest parts to get through (the ending was good, though lol).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, how I envy you! XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I try and stay ahead as much as possible. I start my work a week or so before the course starts, and try to keep things at that pace the whole way through. Though for my last assignment, I was about a couple of minutes off the deadline before submitting. So, my bad. -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
