<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9124</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 06:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H01vpMdzX7U yay!! let me know if you have any feed back or suggestions for my future ones ;) thanks y'all for all the awesome support for the first one you rock,  dont ever change  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you look like the red lady in game of thrones! so pretty :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 03:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try writing pages. 3 pages everyday ( preferably in the morning or before something stressful) Of what your thinking, feeling, scared of, excited about for that day or specific event. It helps get the ideas and the thoughts out from circulating your head and on to a page.
Anxiety for me in the non expression of an emotion or feeling. Some times its inappropriate to say or do something in the moment. So express it on the page.

Just get out it man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 01:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> urban decay is my fav! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 22:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EYE LASHES GURL OMG I LOVE THEM!!! what are they?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 17:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha awe thanks! ill be making some more soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since tutorials are all the rage now, i started a series of my own. My idiot make-up. I was a makeup artist before im just incredibly inappropriate in front of a camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since tutorials are all the rage now, i started a series of my own. My idiot make-up. I was a makeup artist before im just incredibly inappropriate in front of a camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 22:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is my BIRTHDAY :) i spent my last day as a 22 year old recording this little diddy with my best friend (featured in video) CCW :) let me know what y'all think </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 18:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is my 23rd birthday. I spend all day recording this little diddy with my best friend (featured in the video) all day yesterday. It was a super fast shoot and edit but i figured id share it with y'all :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 18:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 18:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!!! Im gonna make this into a series ill let you know when i come out with the next one. In a few days or a week max. AND THANK YOU :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since tutorials are all the rage now, i started a series of my own. My idiot make-up. I was a makeup artist before im just incredibly inappropriate in front of a camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 16:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will release a new one this week i guess! so many positive responses :) and yes lets be the bestest of friends ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) Im down for more friends, i lack in that department haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! i figured i couldnt be the only one! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 05:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shall ! im so happy you liked it! ill let you know when i make a new one, ill try to do so in a few days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 19:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats kinda what inspired me actually. I love hannah hart! thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
