<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3591</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The recipe mentions chilli twice.  Did you mean garlic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 03:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing you could try is to get it thinner first.  And then apply the plastic spatula once it's in the pan.  A good way to do this is to take the sausage and lay it on a fairly big piece of saran wrap.  Then place an equally big piece of saran wrap over the top.  Use your rolling pin to roll it out into one big flat piece.  If it's too big for the pan, use two pans or do two batches and then combine into one after browning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a white cannelloni on the left?  Or weird Bechamel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burrito Supreme is the supreme of burritos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no places to stay in Tuscany.  Don't even try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corn and tomatoes sound like a great addition.  Both so sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 00:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/QzGWYShgmfk?t=37 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a luge/bobsled team car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it's got peppers.  Maybe it's more of a mexican lasagna. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 18:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been to Destin.  I really like it.  It was October, and they had the fish rodeo thing going on with concerts and stuff.  Beautiful weather also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, you guys are fucking with me.  There's no tape, and whatever, it came into contact with the fucking coolant hose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 01:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the brisket is a tough cut of meat.  You can't just cook it like a sir loin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, FML.  Here's a video of scrapping stuff I'm still buying parts for:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YY9To39qMAE

I'd love to have all of the windows and door hardware as well as the drivetrain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you use to annotate .pdfs?  That would be useful if I can convince my IT dept to install on our pcs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I regularly go to the catalogs section on https://www.napaprolink.com/ to verify/select parts.  Especially with Ford light truck exhaust stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Advanced just converted our CarQuest since the buyout a couple years ago.  Still the same people and they have some idea of the buses/trucks that they have been dealing with for the last 25 years.  So our Advanced is still a-ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use this: https://www.napaprolink.com/
To make sure that I get the right part every time.
Props to the Autozone that opened up.  I can get parts the next day with no freight.  They've got some sort of awesome deal with FedEx.  edit can/can't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny, I was at work yesterday (Saturday) and had a request from the night shift for an air compressor for a Gillig.  I could not find the parts book, and Gillig isn't there on Saturdays, also these 15 year old POS buses are fairly new to us so we didn't have any history for the air compressor.  I left it for the guys on Monday, FFIO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a reverse hemi in picture 4.  The other cylinders aren't like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't sound like much, but I made this once and it was EPIC.
http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/guy-fieri/braised-pork-ribs-and-italian-sausage-recipe2.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol @ overcooked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your plate has pictures that are pixelated.  What are you hiding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, tomatos?  How about some cheese? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 23:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not air tight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but, I'm only going to be here for a minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I'd sue them in small claims court.  They won't show up, and it will be dismissed.  Save all of the paperwork because the next time you park in one of their facilities they will tow your car and fuck it up.  Then you can sue them for the big bucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> either that or get a lawyer and counter sue.  You can probably counter sue them yourself.  Also, be aware of laws regarding collections if they keep phoning you.  You can add that to your countersuit and get damages.  Record all phone calls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they say that you "will be taken to a county court", that means that they will get the cops to shoot you in the back and kill your dog as well.  just pay it, and keep on truckin' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you never put your skis on the rack with the tips forward, do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been snowing a lot here over the last few days.  So, I've been in 4wd.  c/s car doesn't go like it used to when stopped and wheels cranked. 
/in 4hi, idle doesn't over come drivetrain when wheels are cranked and snow is piled up.
//punched myself in the dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pins, they're threaded pins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Change your oil at the parking lot for the open space that the county bought for $6.6 million from the rich guy that owns the ranch and kept the best/only good part of it for himself.  Use a drain pan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His arms weren't even above his head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of guys have died gauging petroleum tanks.  So, right next to the well is a steel tank that the petroleum goes into.  You have to climb a ladder to the top and open it up and gauge how much was produced or shipped or whatever the level is. They think that when they opened the top the gasses inside overwhelmed them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that was a fun little rabbit hole.  The part 2 had two Jeep 4 doors, and an F250 4x4 diesel, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 15:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's bad, fuck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 03:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I've never seen a cable operated caliper.  Well, on a road vehicle anyway.  Bicycle, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 03:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who drives an Audi Q5 and steals stuff off of porches for a living?  What has this world come to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 03:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want a stable friendship, get a horse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a Guards Red 1986 944 once.  I had it for 10 weeks and some jerk t-boned me.  Mine had about 70000 miles.  Great car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there must be something out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 04:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about this post, but it seems like the Nashville hot chicken uses a lot of powdered spice in a sauce that they pour over after frying.  I've never tried it though, could be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 03:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chicken tinga.  Put the tomatoes in a saute pan on the stove. Heat till they start bursting.  Add red onion sliced into sliver moon shape, and whole cloves of garlic peeled. Cook till onion is translucent. Transfer to blender/processor, add chipotle peppers w/adobo and salt. Buzz it up. A little chunky is fine. Add mixture to baked, pulled chicken, mix it around, boom Chicken tinga.  Use as a filling for tacos, tamales, burritos, etc. /stolen directly from the DDD feed on food network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a place in Leadville that actually has a good Tenderloin Sandwich.  Not sure if it's from frozen or homemade.  I get a hankering for one every once in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok then.  I like lamb a lot.  Would give it a go 4sure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does Big Vern's Krispy Ring entail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's pasta inside that pizza?  Wow, good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some of our ski-doos have engine mounts that look like that.  They've broken many times, and our guys hardly ever roll them over at all, lol
edit: thankfully the bracket breaks and not the engine block. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trail rated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great.  That one on the left blew his achilles tendon though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get tipped out anywhere?  Because I saw on another /r that waiters and waitresses are tipping the cooks now (sharing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 02:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been a server, but no I've never tried that one.  Seems like it might should be a thing though if you're not going to get along at all for a pleasurable experience.  Maybe the manager should handle it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people who have important discussions (meetings) have shifty eyes and always know when there's someone coming to their table.  And they quit talking.  It's always like that in the books that I read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you just go to the hostess at that point and suggest that she be re-seated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. Are you closed on Tuesday and change the oil Thursday night? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, she's on a diet.  I thought it looked more like a "chicken pot pie" but then looking more I thought maybe potato with the scrapes on the top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that seems easy enough.  Somehow I got an aversion to squash young in life, so I've never tried the spaghetti squash but I've had others recently that are fine.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kale is de-sprouted Brussels sprouts.  ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, I'm not going 1000 miles to try that combo.  I'll be happy if my local has the McRib!  Lurv those things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> risenscreenskrit I guess it's the same thing.  My hearing is fine, I just don't do good with words.  Especially ones from another language that I've never. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We used a quarter when I was growing up.  Whomever got the quarter got good luck.  And a quarter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw a guy on youtube change the oil on his Pontiac w/italian salad dressing (out of date).  He didn't add enough before starting and it died within minutes, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure no.  Maybe just add it after you flip the steak and let it sit on top while it finishes and leave it there when you serve.  I could be wrong though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, there's shepherd's pie on the left, beef roast on the right w/yorkie, and half a chicken w/potato and veg and yorkie for yourself?  Looks great!  What did they serve with the shepherd's pie though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom usually makes fudge this time of year.  It also has a detectable un-dissolved sugar look/texture to it.  Not sure if it's the same recipe.  I don't mind the look though, it tastes great.  Hopefully you get some replies from people familiar with the recipe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see why you shouldn't.  I can see some pesto underneath to pep it up, good job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No view of the curds?  Anyway, the bun looks sad but the brat might be ok.  How did it taste? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always end up with so much extra veg because the brisket shrinks so much.  I wish I had a dog who would nom the extra veg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it looks quite good.  Not sure why the downvotes on imgur.  How did you prepare the squash?  Also, it looks like more than just sausage, what did you do there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What potato type would you suggest?  Seems to me russets would break down somewhat in a soup... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burger in USA vs. Burger in Belgium.  I think the difference was horse.  Anyway, young stupid me should have ordered something different in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like shrimp and sausage (kielbasa?) gumbo.  I was expecting more liquid in the bowl.  However, this is chunky and I like chunky.  Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might not have heard me correctly when I said I want all of the kimchi and meat dumplings that you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks very good.  Can you detail the cooking process for al pastor that you used? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What flavor coke would you like, pop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't they the same as your Heinz Beanz?  Or look for Hunt's or B M brands.  Or anything that says Boston Baked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 04:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did chef Ramsey pave the way for the Trump presidency by not really being PC, WhyBePC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 04:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Gene Masseth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there a cooler for the tire? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks tasty!  http://getinmybelly.com/jalapeno-cheddar-chicken/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that the mods assign that.  Not sure though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That tater salad!  What eggs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 15:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a ham on there also! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 10:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kasstopf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh, fancy!  J/K I love mac and cheese.  With a nice steak on the side, even better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 938G Cat loader in the shop again because fuel gauge doesn't work properly. No picture because of forum rules. Details inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 05:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we've had this loader for quite a while and for the last three years the fuel gauge hasn't worked properly. The story I got was that when it was full, fine, then as you ran the machine the gauge would stop going down and hold on 3/4th full. Well, we try to replace the fuel tank sender. Ordered the wrong part, sent back and try again (big job). Replace sender, nope doesn't work. Trace the wiring, determine it's the engine ECU. How about we replace the instrument cluster for the third time in three years? Nope, doesn't fix it. Order the engine ECU, receive the wrong one because engine S/N. Tape on the box says you can't return it. Order the correct ECU and finally that thing is fixed. Most expensive fuel gauge EVER! ($10,000 est.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and your neighborhood has adhd and cuts the lawn twice a day, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not catfish, but that could work just fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I googled and it seems like it can be goat, beef or pork.  What's this one? Looks very tasty! I bet the liver gives it an earthy flavor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great, I think you just used the wrong tag. No big deal, probably should have been [PRO/CHEF] or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think corn is a good idea. From a can it's pretty sweet, so that would be nice. I've done potato on pizza also. Might have to pre-cook that a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 02:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I'd call that a donut, I think I'd call that delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The egg looks perfect for a sandwich! I prefer them looser for other applications like CFS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 01:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a crappy tratianno or something one at Walmart. The enamel just came right off in chips. Then I got a Lodge one (like $50), and it's much better. I've had it over twice the length of time (4 years). It's so easy to use, and you can convert any slow cooker recipe to do in the dutch oven. Plus you can brown your meat in it first without dirtying another pan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 01:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of easy to get wrong though since it comes from thermOworks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed that I can buy un-cooked corn tortillas in the grocery lately. Maybe having a fresh cooked tortilla would make the difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 12:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you could make up your own way to do it. Offhand, make a chicken noodle soup without noodles. But make it thick, with less stock, maybe some cornstarch slurry to thicken at the end. Then put some bisquick knobs in while baking at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 11:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, to some degree. You wouldn't want to be rolling down the highway/road with the window down though. Source: My ex had a Sentra w/studs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UserName checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 18:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more headlight fluid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
