<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8068</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The forest trail in ReMake did it.

The interiors of Commando Island in RE4 - dark, ruined, the weird growly thing Saddler's army ganados did was freakier than the villagers (Zealots weren't even unsettling imo). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find a tall building. Hide on the roof. Let the zombies dry out, wait for the rot to finish them.

BOWS - im ded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Depiction of the Drow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The idea of the drow is intriguing - but much of what I've seen of the dark elves in Forgotten Realms' Menzoberranzan doesn't strike me as all that plausible.

Now, Jarlaxle's Bregan D'aethe is a bit more reasonable - they're still chaotic, but focused on making bank to keep their lifestyle going. Do you all have any other novels/quick-n-dirty writeups on how to make the drow a feasible foe, as opposed to chaotic "how are these things not dead yet?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say sit back and let the drow do themselves in. In a war of attrition, discipline will win out over all the arcane and infernal magic the drow could muster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All employ-ees

All employ-ees

All employ-ees

That needs to be in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u stink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not Light Sultai?

That's a nice looking list though OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 06:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know if these were too outlandish for a bunch of different human cultures, or if they would be better recognized as alternate races, like the suggested gnomes, lizardmen etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an interesting perspective. I couldn't put my finger on just what it was with RTR that made it..lesser than our first strip. But the plane felt smaller on the second go-around than the first.

*

Historically, Tarkir could become Kami 2.0. Replace Kami vs Humans with Elementals vs Dragons...humans disgruntled with the dragons deify elementals, making them a threat to the dragons...let the other human societies develop more into a palatable version of Kamigawa. Complete with ninjas, rakshasa in place of oni and naga in place of the ogres that worshipped the oni etc.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, its when they act like whatever they resemble. If I have some lionfolk, then a male might regale his companions with the time he slaughtered a rival, the rival's offspring, and took the rival's mate as his own. The others would likely be aghast while the lionfolk doesn't think twice about it.

Aesthetically I change the bauplan ever so slightly - make 'em a bit strange looking. My dragonborn, for example (the D D things with scales and tits in the case of females from 4E), have a muscular tail that counterbalances their broad chests, thick necks and large, blunted snouts. The lionfolk I mentioned above might have broad shoulders, a large trunk tapering down to a narrow lower body and limber, muscular hindlegs.

Stuff like that OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could've done better on the DTK end of it, but it was the most fun I've had with worldbuilding since Innistrad 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it did anything better than 1R +2/0, I might consider it in Dragon Stompy due to Chalices and Jittes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Tarmogoyf is back in Standard boyos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shifting Races? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I've drafted up about three different peoples. I'm not sure if they'd be better served as say...genasi, dwarves, and...trolls perhaps, or if they still work fine as human cultures.

Preface - I know there's genasi of differing elements and all, but the one I've got that most fits the genasi are a sea-based culture...

**Geddlith**  A limber, light-boned folk who owe their calcified skin to the balance struck by their God Primeval Reshrith and its sorcery of Armageddon (which burned out the veins of magic  within that neck of the world). The Geddlith are practitioners of lithomancy, crafting magic-resistant swords imbued with their own special sorcery. This is their primary source of income. The Geddlith are an industrious people that used their skills in lithomancy and wire-fighting to settle their region of Tundra. (or, should these be dwarves instead of calcified humans?)



**Zuhyd**  A stocky folk whose fish belly pale skins are marked from birth by seafoam glyphs resembling either a drake on wing, a storm of faeries, or a carplike elemental.  The glyph forms demarcate the Zuhyds role in their society, though their mind-rending magic gives them upward mobility despite their birth glyphs. Battles of the mind allow the victorious Zuhyd to take on the glyphs of the loser. Zuhyd make their way whaling, serpenting, and harvesting the seas; they are nonviolent in their captures, preferring to attack their preys mind rather than inflict physical violence on these great sea behemoths.

Their desire to make their earnings without spilling the blood of their targets is driven by a fear of their capricious God Primeval Hydrei. The Zuhyd believe that the blood would wake Hydrei; while the God Primevals central head encouraged the Zuhyd to abandon It in so that they may thrive, the other two heads cried out for blood. So, to avoid waking a God Primeval that would help as readily as it would hurt them, the Zuhyd make it a point to no spill the blood of their kill in the seas. (or, should these be genasi given the blue glyph thing that ties them to the sea?)


**Krolothra**  A tall folk whose society is built around the hunt. They wear the hides of their kills while the essence of the beasts live on in the hunters mindscape. The Krolothra believe themselves to be speakers for the beasts whose essence inhabits their mindscape. Krolothra ensure that no part of their kill goes to waste  the meat and organs are used for food. Hides are cured and stored until the Krolothra has taken down five different beasts  then the hides are used to create the Krolothras distinct armor.

Krolothra, once fully armored, then leave their treetop villages and hire on as mercenaries in foreign companies. They seek causes that they believe in and return with trophies of their service. These are the source of friendly competition between Krolothrai  the winner of such competitions usually claims the mate of the loser, then the loser and his or her offspring are killed and eaten. It is believed that the loser and his/her progeny will be reborn from the forest, after having sojourned through the victors mindscape and gained self-improvement from the victors life experiences.

The Krolothra trace this practice to their God Primeval Thragkhro  who, once fallen, beseeched the Navajko from which all humans of Flamedroi trace common ancestry, to partake of her flesh. From this the Navajko gained wisdom, and strength. This is the Krolothra justification for their savage treatment of the submissives. (Or, should they be trolls given their size and affinity for beasts?)

*



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 18:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banefire Berserkers - Banefire Berserkers is a mercenary army comprised of berserkers (fighters), artillery (mages and munitions), and dragonspeakers (shaman responsible for controlling the pit dragons).

Armageddon Dawning - An army comprised of Stonesplicers, hailing from the continent Jesojutei. On their own, the Stonesplicers aren't intimidating - tall, but lean and willowy with calcified-white skin brought on by the hardships of their homeland; they have survived literal armageddons caused by the wars between the efreet and djinn. Their talents are in their ability to craft magical blades on the spot. The army is comprised of mystics (the actual forgers), tabernacle magi (wizards whose enchantments can lock up an enemy's automatic weapons), and the exalted (can summon angels).

Wild Razers - The Wildrazers are a large, earthy folk that dress themselves in the hides and scales of their kills. Wildrazers are pure mercenaries, seeking coin for whatever cause they deem worth their while. Their records as mercenaries are discussed within their tribe, often as a source of competition among members of the tribe.

The Tide Sculptors - The Tide Sculptors are psionics often brought in to prevent conflict by scrambling the brains of warmongers. They are distinguished by their pallid complexions and vibrant blue tattoos mimicking the gyri and sulci of the human brain. Their mind-rending leads to further infighting among a given warmongers' lackeys. Thus Sculptors employ their talents to create conflicts that let them fully explore the human psyche by observing the actions of their target and the target's underlings.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does that mean she's gonna fleece the rebellion for a swanky beach house? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stakes are subjective. The Eldrazi posed a threat to the entire plane, but I also didn't care what happened to Zendikar and its inhabitants.

I prefer stuff like KTK/DTK where you have a bunch of warbands post-apocalypting it up. Now that's fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That justification is weak as hell. Did it come from a comic book or something lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if the renegades didn't play stupid games, they wouldn't win stupid prizes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the Renegade movement as being justifiable. I've been rooting for Tezzeret since *Test of Metal*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoogland's done well with a mono R sneak deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 04:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A young man gets his wish when he joins the marines and gets sent on a secret mission to uncover a nuclear warhead deep in enemy territory. A warhead with which the marines may bring a last hold out of rebels to heel by obliterating the rebels' greatest benefactor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 03:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one plays Faeries as a tribe anymore.

*

I would like to see something done with Viashino. As it is, you can build around their bounce ability with [[Pandemonium]], but its still a limited application. I would personally like to see them settle as red's midrangey tribe, at CMCs of 3 (2R being my preference) with artifact fetching abilities so as to make them Dragon Stompy friendly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 04:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Just get it done." is the basic M.O. for its use, for those that use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 04:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doo-dad like this: "oo oi!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 04:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Industry. At the end of the day, many of my scattered ideas come down to pushing through the blood, sweat, and tears to build something that makes you, the individual, happy and prosperous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 22:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have necroburners - a framework of metal containing an artificial heart, magically melded to the skeleton and hide taken from large reptiles in my setting. They're essentially vehicles, albeit powered by a magic link between the artificial heart and the reptile's preserved nervous system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 16:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The countries comprising my continents are designated as either Holdings, Clutches, Bivouacs, Outposts, or Palaces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 16:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak for everyone, but the dynamic bores me. In the case of my material, they would be redundant when you consider the variety of humans I'm running:

**Frontierfolk** - Alloys of dragonscale and iron that form, keloid like, along appendages most often used in spellcasting.

**Tundrafolk** - Glyphs or upgraded epidermis reflecting magic use:

  *Mind Sculptors* - Glowing blue glyphs resembling the gyri and sulci of the brain.

  *Stoneforgers* - Calcified skin, giving them an alabaster or chalky white appearance with a lighter bone structure and longer limbs. 

  *Wildspeakers* - A more simian appearance with a rough, earthen cast to their skin.
  
  *Abyssal Veil* - Their blood is blackish in appearance, signifying the presence of a patron demon inhabiting their body. They have a greyish look and a more muscular build from the demon having consumed their fat for sustenance.

*

So really, that makes the elves, dwarves, and orcs superfluous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 08:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jace? Hot damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 02:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frontier was never going to be cheap. It's a way for stores to offload bulk from past Standard formats.

Are there any Modern decks running [[Jace, Vryn's Prodigy]]? That might account for the price, somewhat. [[Anafenza, the Foremost]] is listed at $3.99 on scg you cheapskates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 03:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, do continue. I finished Fool's Fate (or whatever book three of the Tawny Man trilogy is, I forget) and felt it would've been nice to have had that as part of the conclusion in Assassin's Quest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 04:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Efreeti**: They're a monastic order of firefolk that temper their draconic gifts with cold logic. There are two denominations of efreet - the Oju and Tei.

*Tei* - To their mind, they must use their gifts of Primevals' fire to give lesser creatures hunted to extinction a last great hurrah. Thus, their magic, extremely destructive, uses Primeval fire to denature the fabric of reality. From these burning gashes come great old behemoths from the days of yore. The world corrects itself by dragging these creatures back to their proper time period, but not before they get to taste revenge against humankind.

*Oju* - Oppose the reckless destruction of the Tei efreet. They blend logic with compassion and chose to focus on what the Primevals did right: the angels and the sorceries of clear judgment employed by the Primevals near the time of their downfall. The Oju are a folk eager to employ their talents in angel-summoning and cleansing the present day evils that, flourishing, appear to them as monuments to the cruelty of the primevals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primevals - the greatest of the great; they descended from a foundling race called the Foreshi. They possess all the viciousness of their ancestors, except on a grander scale. Their primary prey was the Primordials.


Regents - the progeny of the Primordials; these out-competed the Primevals, driving their ancestors into extinction. The Regents were brought down by idols of sticks and stones to which they were bound by their neanderthal servitors. There's magic that lets you summon Regents, though the sorcerous emanations that roll from them in waves warps, slashes, and crushes the surrounding environs, or may raise the dead or trigger religious frenzy.


Pit Dragons - the lesser of the dragons; these are manufactured by the shaman on the continent of Thundermaw in the Thunderbreak Clutch (one of the many countries on Thundermaw). Pit dragons were instrumental in the founding of Thundermaw - in the past there was a Dragon War in which Thunderbreak agents worked to acquire as many Regent Idols as possible; from these they learned how to create the pit dragons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Cavern of Souls]] -- Eldrazi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, they wanted to publish official names for wedge decks like your WUR Control/Midrange/X in modern to go with stuff like Jund, Grixis, Naya, Bant and Esper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 08:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I think of possums, I think of the whole "playing dead" thing they do to evade predators. Given that "death" is somewhat a part of the possum, I can see where zealotry could be used to define your oppossumen.

Perhaps they've got a zealotry that glorifies death in one way or another, one that ties more into their defense mechanism of playing dead rather than poisoning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 08:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vaik - Bipedal reptiles, wingless, whose weight is counterbalanced by a length tail. They believe that nature gives them the tools they need to thrive in a vicious world - its up to the solitary Vaik to figure out how best to use those tools to chase their passions.

Ketzalku - Serpentine reptiles with atrophied wings that're born with an ingrained fear of dragons and the Vaik. They utilize their psychic venom to get the right blend of juices - guilt and fear - flowing through their prey so as to have a viable host for their eggs.

Efreet - Simianlike beings of fire and lavarock whose inhuman sense of compassion was forged by the fires of draconic tyranny. Their rebellious magic rips the very fabric of time, bringing forth behemoths they believe were unjustly extincted by the Primeval Dragons.

Engineers - Green-scaled apelike creatures that practice a bloody Children of the Corn sort of elemental worship. Seeing the horrors the dragons, angels, demons and humans, they believe elementals are the inheritors of the world.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 07:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. If someone really likes them, they'll find a way to make them fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 07:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is.

My efreet tend to rip the aether to let critters unfairly extincted by nature have a last hurrah...these critters tend to be very large, and very destructive. Even through the world's magic sucks the critters back into wherever the efreet sorcery nabbed them, these prehistoric beasties can do some Dunwich Horror Yog-Sothoth tier damage.

Fortunately its easy to deal with efreet - you just slug 'em hard enough on the back of the head while they're spellcasting and they're out cold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salamence Question - Looking at Expanded </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 06:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long time ago I built a deck around Salamence from Ex Dragons, and later Salamence Ex from Ex Deoxys. Now I see a couple of Roaring Skies dragons, Reshiram and Hydreigon EX, that could be boons to either Salamence Ex/Mega Salamence Ex from the new box set, or the Roaring Skies Salamence...

So which of the two Salamences is most viable for Expanded - the Ex or the full-line utilizing the Roaring Skies Salamence?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 04:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vaik - dragonoids, about fifteen feet in height, though they walk on two legs, their weight being counterbalanced by a long tail.

Ketzalku - feathered serpentine dragonoids, about seven feet in height

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merkel's got a job to do - Hillary thought she'd have a job to do. They shouldn't be worried about "web troll abuse." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's bad news for CNN/MSN, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs [[Dark Confidant]] and [[Snapcaster Mage]]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuk dat shit. Slivers all the wayl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 09:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Animate Dead]] + [[Worldgorger Dragon]] + [[Sliver Queen]] looked hellafun. You could also use [[Ambassador Laquatus]] or [[Oona, Queen of the Fae]] in lieu of [[Sliver Queen]]. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Member [[Rainbow Efreet]] ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who da fuk plays Charbelcher in skred? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 06:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I've been telling this scrub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Orochi**

Orochi are the end result of a human choosing to act as host for a naga hatchling. The hatchling - thrown off out of the naga's mountain nest for whatever reason - integrates with its human host, changing the host in order to survive. At the end of this process the host appears green-skinned with a reticulated pattern, red-eyed, and with an extra set of arms mimicking the vestigial wings common to all naga hatchlings. Most orochi, driven by the naga hatchling's desire to thrive, are single-minded in their pursuits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I thought it was that supplement store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 08:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like sh1t. Should be RE6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 04:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, its been fun on my end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 08:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Savro

A shaman whose fragile self-image, despite his somewhat muscular physique, is rooted in a struggle with childhood obesity. He believes in taking care of oneself first - then you worry about everything else. Having been raised with the expectation that he would be used as fodder for the pit dragons, Savro neglected his body and focused solely on the mind.

As he neared adulthood, ramifications of Savro's decision hit him like a raging thraghorn...during an attack on his village by the vaku lizard-beasts, Savro saw his father, an accomplished shaman, drop dead from a heart attack. In the aftermath Savro came to accept that death is a natural part of the life cycle but that he had the power to mitigate that...by training the body as rigorously as he had trained the mind.

In finding his new path, Savro found the confidence to fully enjoy his passions while employing magic based around death and decay. His broad-framed build is muscular, though not unrealistic, and he wears the hides and skulls of the reptilian vaku whose attack triggered his father's heart attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the writing. Some of the mechanics were off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone got thrashed in modern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sneak

Sneak's an ifrit that, like all ifrit, can burn through the aether with its magic, freeing monstrosities from the dawn of time - gargantuan wurms, demons of legend, even the Dragon Tyrants of yore; nothing is off the table where the ifrit style of magic is concerned. Only drawback is, these chaotically-conjured beasts are dragged back into the aether (part of the world's innate defense mechanisms) in the blink of an eye.

That's all right - the blink of an eye's all the time it takes for these displaced beasts to do some major damage.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make them god-devouring maggots, as they were originally intended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liliana is going to do what's best for Liliana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ahriochi have jade hides patterned like a lizard's skin. They've developed the skill of empathomancy and used it to shape cities that match their emotional state. Within their cities the Ahriochi pursue vices - food, drink, or fighting. Their primary food source are the elementals drawn by the magical radiation coming from the Ahriochi use of emphathomancy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use them as proxies for guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make them work with the theme, either as an extreme or intermediate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kalitas Meta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 06:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what meta does [[Kalitas, Traitor of Ghet]] function best? Same question, but for [[Huntmaster of the Fells]]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From *Forge of Darkness*- Urusander's Legion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I first encountered Moorcock's work in 2009 via the Del Rey reprints. I enjoyed *The Stealer of Souls*, *Stormbringer*, and *The Sleeping Sorceress*. I found Sailor to be the weakest of his Elric novels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta give that title to *Stormbringer*, sir. ;)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First book is like walking into a crowded pub where everyone's engaged in an intriguing conversation. You're the guy in there trying to make sense of it all - and it does come together, but you don't get much in the way of exposition to bog down the flow of the plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 06:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I just suck at variance, but before I came to Jund, I was on the Skred game - and it seemed like I kept drawing hands where I'd be loaded on Snow-Covered Mountains without any way of really protecting my threats.

So I would say discard is pretty good vs the Skred game. It was my achilles heel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not your buddy, guy.

Blood and souls for the All-Consuming Oni of Chaos
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Robert Howard's prose in the Conan stories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Roland Deschain**

He's driven toward achieving his goal. He's not letting anything get in his way. This makes him a bit unpredictable in the sense that he'll probably act predictably, even when the predictable choice may seem morally unlikely. Its a flaw of his character that I enjoy almost as much as his grit and determination to see his quest to its end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 07:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 98% sure that's a joke. Friends taking the piss out of friends and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 06:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NBC also told me that I wouldn't have to wake up to a Hillary loss. Would this make them one of the "Fake News" outlets that you hear about from CNN? I would rather hear this from CNN before I get excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 06:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Obama promised us that his administration would be on the the most transparent in our history. We got the transparency he promised, and via this, educated votes took to the voting booths to make their decision.

We are a nation that values transparency and honesty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *A Wizard of Earthsea* touches on a lot of the big mainstays of the genre. Its a book I would liked to have read when I first got into it.

My main pull into fantasy was *The Gunslinger* by Stephen King. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt the same about Kaladin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, except there's the part where they hypothetically say "its a virus." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 15:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last leg of Roland's quest in The Dark Tower. Such an emotional journey for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arkahc is my suggestion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Its a biological impossibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just put up both sides doing their thing. One wants better for her people but never asked if they wanted it. Another wants to use the one's war for profit and incidentally helps bring it to an end. And a third party employed by the warmonger seeks to balance the scales, albeit not necessarily by bringing peace -more by putting the dispossessed in a position of power, stepping back and letting them do their thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 01:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Frontier seems like a place for bad standard decks to find refuge. For me there's really no appeal, but if you've bought into standard and want to keep using your cards with a higher probability of wining, this seems like the plae for you.

Real talk though, is Frontier an official format recognized by WOTC, or is it an unofficial format made by the players? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 01:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to be better. Scott McGough, Cory Herndon, J Robert King all turned in some really good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've seen a couple of modern videos showcasing D T fwiw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I play my Modern Jund deck in Frontier? If not, then Frontier's not worth my time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I got that far. I remember the first choosing ceremony, where a prospective rider confronts their dragon, and thought it was pretty cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see OP is trying to cope with not having a fully-fueled Jund deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know Hobb's a big name in dragon fantasy (I'll say no more, it would spoil too much for those who haven't read her), but it felt like she spent a good 300-ish pages per novel beating around the bush before getting to the meat of her plots (its the strength of those that helped me persevere through the opening fluff) - whereas with McCaffery, it seems like she gets right to it, based on Dragonflight.

I am excited about the SF touch - I love when it creeps into my fantasy. That's another part of my attraction...

...and since I'm speaking on dragon fantasy, I should also mention I've read Wizard of Earthsea...should I go on and finish out this series too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will do. Just looking at the Whelan covers, they look like compound eyes. Kind of insectoid.

That's cool. I'll probably end up reading the Pern books between Kharkanas novels if I end up enjoying them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading Erikson's *Forge of Darkness* - I believe a reread of *Toll the Hounds* will be in order once I'm done with this one. On the whole, I'm enjoying Forge though it is a different beast to his Books of the Fallen where prose is concerned. Erikson's penchant for a wide cast of characters is still in play, but it feels easier to get acquainted with everyone in this series opener as opposed to *Gardens of the Moon*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dragonriders of Pern Question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had an old Ballantine Books omnibus of the first three Pern novels sitting on my shelf for a while now. I've been itching to read some good SFF with dragons, having already read Erikson's Malaz and Martin's Ice and Fire (and kinda hit a block where I had to put aside Hobb's Dragon Keeper to scratch my Malaz itch with a Bonehunters reread lol).

Do these novels come recommended? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the first book didn't do it for you, I'd hesitate to encourage you spending time on the subsequent volumes when there's a wealth of other fantasy you could be sampling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 14:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Wyatt's **Draconic Prophecies Trilogy**. I don't play DnD, but these novels presented Eberron as a fun little setting I'd like to known more about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 13:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is my favorite, storywise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 02:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The League that Doc is talking about is mostly concerned with maintaining some kind of balance of equilibrium. It sounds like your guys just like killing. So you should be alright, though the League of Shadows isn't all that well known to the general public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 02:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Cult of Entropy Inevitable** - A cult found in the coastal bayous of Eberrai that was founded by an Takejukai expat. The founder discovered shrines of petrified wood and stone dedicated to the Foreshi, a foundling race of the setting. The cult forged compacts with the Foreshi, gaining the creatures' assistance in exploiting the fossil fuel rich lands of Eberrai.

They figure that if the goods are there to be gotten, they may as well get 'em because someone will eventually.

**The Sajin Sages**

The Sajin is an order of mage-monks that used their clout to begin a worldwide enforcement of an edict that required magic users to hone body and mind in accordance with the Sajin scrolls. Scrolls given to them by the jackal-apes from which the Sajin claim humankind has descended.

The Sajin soon relaxed their edict when it left many urban regions unable to deal with gangsters that had made compacts with the oni, gaining the demons' magic and thus getting the upperhand on the various law enforcement agencies that would combat them.

Today the Sajin are focused on continuing education, a blending of science and holisticism in an attempt to open magic to all that wish to learn it without the need of demonic bargains, or hiring out various underworld groups.

**The Trepanation Triad**

The Trepanation Triad is an organization that rose when the Sajin began the worldwide enforcement of their edict. This organization harvested the CNS of skilled mage-monks for study, producing miraculous drugs that would allow almost anyone to access the world's magical veins.

For the most part, they have become defunct with the relaxation of the Sajin edicts.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 02:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. This is close to my take on the combination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selfishness isn't inherently evil. You gotta take care of yourself first.

*

My main critique is that this focused more on the undeath aspects of BG. When I look at BG, I see a color combination that understands the rules set forth by nature, understands the necessity of those rules and is willing to use all the tools available to accomplish its goals by either bending or warping the rules...but never outright breaking them.

*

It seems like TM's leaning more toward explaining the flavor of the guilds' mechanics - like he did with Dredge here. That might be a good starting point for the subsequent videos. Focus on the guild mechanic and how it ties into the guild colors.

Could we get something for the Shards after this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine with it - rolls off the tongue better than most setting-specific swears and gives the old middle ages/Renaissance a contemporary feel. In the grand scheme of things, I've never really given it much thought or attention. Use it where it's appropriate, more or less.

*

In one of the Malazan novels, I think there was a line like "its fucking raining dragons," which I liked. I also remember that one from Reaper's Gale mentioned in this thread. Great scene, and the line didn't take me out of it anymore than their solution for the dragon problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the hierarchy of dragons, you have Primevals -- Regents -- Pit Dragons, with PDs being the bottom of the foodchain.

The Regents are unique in that, conjuring one, require an offering. Regents conjured through this method are somewhat translucent - you can see the silhouette of the offerings struggling against the dragon's inner flames.

It was a neat visual I stole from some Suicide Squad concept art for Incubus - in one the demon didn't have any armor/metal, so you could see the shadows of the people he had been feeding on within the flames. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jund here. Been waiting to see how my favorite set of enemy colors works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got some three-foot froggy looking cavemen that used sticks and stones to bring down an empire of primeval dragons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fong Ling and Bruce McGivern are my choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is themed around industrialism and capitalism - things that tend to be vilified, going back to Sauron and Mordor, or simplified in the case of Goodkind's work (haven't read any of it, but I've read about it).

Part of the theme is that power isn't good or bad - its there to be used.

A third part of the theme is that fear is the ultimate enemy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 22:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GRRM plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
