<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3000</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I see this sub decided to get super judgy yesterday.

Appearing offline has been feature put into social apps (especially types of messengers) forever, it doesn't seem too much of a request to have said feature when it has been provided to work as it should (blocking others from being able to tell you're online).

And all the shit thrown at OP, geez you're telling me if someone's SO is a bit insecure/immature they need to break up? Sure a talk may be needed but that's up to them (OP in this case) not the collective mind of the internet.

Tl;dr appearing offline isn't a new feature made for consoles and is a feature any social platform should have and should work as intended.

Also stop being judgemental pricks because you want to force your views onto OPs relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 01:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would call them, I bought a PS Vita game from my old ps3 on accident once. I called and they removed the license from my account and gave a PSN credit for what I spent. Granted I never even started up the game since I don't own a Vita, but they definitely can do refunds.

I'd just be nice when calling and hope you get a nice representative. I may have also have had a really good experience with the only time I needed a refund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 26 here, started at like 4-5 with my mom's NES, then got an N64 when I was 6...(pretty sure I was 6, it was the Xmas it was released).

Now gaming on my PS4 and XBone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 11:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest going for it this is my comment a bit down/a reply to someone else

"I my first playthrough of DA:I was my first ever DA game, that being said terms like "The Fade" and etc I caught onto very fast. Without ever Googling any lore by my 15-20 hour mark I had forgotten I never had played any DA game before (15-20h is a long time, but my playthrough was like 76 hours so in context it wasn't that long).

It's an amazing stand alone game that may have you a bit out in the dark at first with terms and lore, but you should catch on really fast and should be having so much fun during that time (if you're like me) that it isn't too much of a bother to take time to take everything in."

I know A LOT of people suggest getting through The Hinterlands (first real zone) ASAP, tbh I feel like the only person on earth that enjoyed the zone.

Anyway I know this is a long tldr post but I hope you decide to try it, it is an amazing game. And afterwards if you're like me you'll want to go back and try 1/2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 11:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I my first playthrough of DA:I was my first ever DA game, that being said terms like "The Fade" and etc I caught onto very fast. Without ever Googling any lore by my 15-20 hour mark I had forgotten I never had played any DA game before (15-20h is a long time, but my playthrough was like 76 hours so in context it wasn't that long).

It's an amazing stand alone game that may have you a bit out in the dark at first with terms and lore, but you should catch on really fast and should be having so much fun during that time (if you're like me) that it isn't too much of a bother to take time to take everything in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ps4 on its last legs, should I get a slim or pro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 10:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upgrading, slim or pro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 10:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 09:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God I love this game, I mainly lurk and I've seen it mentioned tons of times, like every game suggestion thread. Bit surprising it hadn't been mentioned yet though (before ths post, I know I'm a bit late).

The Last Of Us was the ps3 gem for me.
So far Until Dawn is the ps4 gem.

Edit, grammar and spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 08:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went down the rabbit hole? You crawled down it and murdered a family of bunny hookers. 

That being said you have a good point, though you may have conveyed it a smidge too well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 08:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why doesn't this have more upvotes? Best use of the phrase ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 08:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In no way is this criticism, I'm honestly just curious.

But what about profanity is so bad it by itself would make you leave? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 11:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd find it a bit unnerving, but probably not enough to recall it a few years later (not trying to say anything against you, just trying to put into perspective where itd fall on a creepy factor for me).

With that being said, I'm a 26 year old guy who's pretty big and probably has very little to worry about when it comes to abduction/murder/rape/etc and when I get into stents about reading unsolved cases and all that jazz I can get pretty paranoid myself. 

When you delve into the weirder side of things/strange disappearances that happen I think becoming paranoid is pretty easy. 

But if it makes you feel better it was probably a benign event that happened that was just a bit unnerving in the way it played out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems a lot of people rate games on $/hour. Personally if it's a REALLY good story I'll settle for around 2$/hour. Otherwise I feel ripped off if I don't get at least a dollar an hour. It's why I love RPGs so much, otherwise I wait for massive price drops. I love The Last Of Us, I knew I was going to love it. Still waited till I could pick it up for about 20$. Yeah the developers want good money for their time spent, but I don't wanna be raped on price for an 8 hour game either. I only really buy RPGs that I know I'll put 60+ hours into at full 60$ price. 7 Days To Die, Minecraft, Skyrim, Dragon Age:I are some of the best money well spent on games I have ever bought. Hell even The Last Of Us I've played through like 5 times, and the sequel may be one of the very few exceptions I make to the 2$/hour max.

Edit: Only things I go to the theater for are Star Wars nowadays. I don't go because it's such terrible money ratio. I'll wait till it's out on Blu Ray and price has gone down to 10$, and then I can watch it as much as I want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this as "when I lived in Antarctica".... No clue why, I had go reread it like wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FOR THE HORDE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 00:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just don't volunteer as tribute... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 10:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOT saying I agree with this, but to quote Scrubs "Every one of our parents does considerable emotional damage. And from what I've heard, it just might be the best part of being a parent." - DR. Cox

That being said, my parents weren't so great. I mean I was a little shit, but a lot of it was crying out for attention from them. In retrospect I have a good deal of respect for my mom and stepdad. They were far from perfect, but I was even further and they put up with way more shit from me than a parent should have to. My relationship with my mom has improved ALOT since I became an adult and I take responsibility for my part, as my mom did for hers. Now my stepdad... I still love him, he stepped up when my bio dad disappeared (who I now have a good relationship with) but I put him and my mom through hell and burnt my bridge with him. But live an learn, I like to think I'm a far better human being now.

Edit: I agree with a lot of people here, too many to list everypne/thing I do agree with. But I think the situation is complicated but we know a lot more about psychology now and hopefully we can become better as parents as generations go on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 04:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just spent like 40 minutes looking through the sub. What I learned is Uber drivers seem to hate other Uber drivers more than customers. Also Lyft is the devil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shouldn't of stepped into the rabbit hole! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you happen to work for Umbrella Corp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My question is, how many people have told you their standards for hired murder? Or the perhaps part, have you maybe seen something about on par? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Costco is amazing. I have friend who worked there for like a decade nearly, he regrets leaving. He wanted to get into caring for people with disabilities (still does work in the care management field), but he misses Costco a hell of a lot. Gets paid similar for harder work, which he knew/expected but he didn't expect to get treated like absolute crap by every employer he's had in the field. Considering he had worked for Costco since getting out of Highschool basically  he found out how most companies treat their employees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, just don't feed the troll. When you feed the troll they win, no matter what. But on topic, shits horrendous. It amazes me that some companies seem to have just lost all sense of ethics or morals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
