<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6524</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No she breaks her wrist a lot and the doc has that scalpel pattern down pat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are upset about it going on for mere months when we had to listen to emails, Benghazi, and Obama being a Kenyan born Muslin for YEARS.....and what did they all produce? NOTHING! You are hands down one of the biggest idiots I have seen from the_donald, and good lord, everyone here knows just how much that is saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well....we won the offseason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, those high taxes really stifled the industrial revolution.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are fucking insane, dude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just beat the game. I did all the content minus the top ranked hunting ground medals on every challenge and it took me 65 hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is to me. Its a subjective term anyway. I really cant believe the pettyness of people downvoting the shit out of me for this though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course that is fine you feel that way!! Do you think The Last of Us was overhyped too? Because this game gives me the same feelings I felt playing that game, which I consider the goat of games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never doubted the people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow nice one. I feel like that could easily happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't get past your mom smoking cigs while punishing you for weed. I just cant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think we will either but I want it to happen more than ever now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna suck when you have to delete your account in order to not own up to this bet! lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is the only main FF character I ever disliked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a hotel restaurant. This kid was getting ready for his 3 hour trip home in the car. All I could think about was how awful it must have been for him sitting in a car after that happened. God I still feel bad and its been almost 20 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you 100%. I think that the RB pick should come in the later rounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless his idea of a friendly contract is the league minimum or barely over it, I'm all set....and I hope BB would be too. 

I really think a younger set of legs from the draft will be all this team needs for the RB position next season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at 60 in 4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be a mistake to not choose horizon.

edit: shouldnt have worded my comment like an arrogant douche, but it really is one of the greatest games of all time....and I am someone who pretty much exclusively only plays JRPGs. 

edit: why have most of the downvotes come after my edit? Because I admitted to wording something wrong or because I consider a game good and you all dont? Childish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 15:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are going to be in trouble if we don't bring him back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> brb making new account to downvote this comment again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally.  Plz no broncos or jets. I'd love houston. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only kiss top commentors  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are both destined to meet at the bottom of comment chains for eternity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude your name  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya ruined it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, why'd you do it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a 15 year old busser, I accidentally spilled boiling hot tea water down the back of a 12 year old kid.

He screamed, I said I was so sorry and I was running to get a manager as I backpedaled away.

I got the manager. I went to the kitchen. I stayed in the kitchen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I desperately hope Romo doesn't go to a team I hate so I can root for him with everything I got.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 19:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright well your view makes a bit more sense. I will be honest I was assuming you were fairly young, which was my mistake. 

I apologize if you stated it already, but did you play it when it came out, or many years later down the road? 

Either way, I should be more accepting of other people's opinions when they are vastly different from my own. 

I loved the PS2 generation as well, but for me, the SNES/PSX eras were my absolute favorites. I totally see what you are saying about the "experimental" stuff going on at the time, however you can easily make a case for experimental stuff going on in each generation since. It wasn't until The Last of Us just last generation that storytelling in a game finally reached equal ground with other mediums. Note that I am not talking story specifically, but storytelling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a Patriots game about 10-15 years ago, I went around the stadium picking up pepsi caps. It was insane how many were thrown on the ground. I ended up having every single pocket of my pants, sweatshirt, and jacket stuffed to the brim. I think I got something like 3000 points from the 15 minutes of walking around. 

I got a leather jacket with them that has the Pepsi logo...never even contemplated wearing it once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually teared up at one of the first sidequests in the game (the one with the old woman who would not speak with Aloy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 14:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got a curve in your pants? I have had a right angle in mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just sounds to me like you have something against the 16 bit generation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We may even have a chance at going to a super bowl! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cooks may be just the push we need to finally get over the hump as an organization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because eggs are different sizes? Also...if you are separating egg whites...do it into a measuring cup and stop when you get to whatever you need....

edit: I think you didnt notice that the recipe said egg whites, not eggs, else Id agree with you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What more could you ask for in a 16 bit RPG than you get in Chrono Trigger? It literally has everything, and everything is done incredibly well. I just dont get some people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STOP TRADING IN ALL YOUR SHIT AT GAMESTOP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This person gave a negative review to a recipe because they find measuring ingredients hard to follow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got hot snakes, bro? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 13:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes got hot snakes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like nut spoons because I enjoy being able to eat multiple nuts at the same time, all while maintaining a healthy level of sanitation and safety.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you had to hunt for them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% of Tom Brady's comeback wins come after the Patriots are behind in the score.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [http://i.imgur.com/1OMou7n.gifv](http://i.imgur.com/1OMou7n.gifv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I first read that as you have a white board of all your white-male guests  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resign? Last I checked that is against the law and he should be brought up on charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 12:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't u have a country to run into the ground, donald? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was that Tom Brady inbounding the ball? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> woah dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that berseria has come out, the answer to this question should always be berseria. Zestiria is weak as far as tales standards, however, since it takes place after berseria, playing it afterwards is probly more fun than those of us who played it first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 34, gamer my entire life, proud to say I have never let an issue as minor as that effect me in any way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 15:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U lived with people like this, I have a feeling u can't be much worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Place is beautiful in 2D, though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 21:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time I have been so into a game in every aspect since The Last of Us, and nothing else is remotely close. And I have enjoyed the fuck out of several titles since then.

No way in hell this isn't GOTY.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fucking shit man. Go read a fucking book. Holy shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He likes that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 14:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish someone would just offer him more money than he can refuse to come back full time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Educationally savage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As if I needed another reason to despise bill polian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone eli5 why they want to trade cousins? I'm out of the loop on this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love it if vii rings was the boat under that cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd do you if she was my sister </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My loins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat too much, sex too little </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much more insane can this man get? 

Find out tomorrow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was his ninja way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does a gif of the whole Super Bowl count as one thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so glorious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta go hit that shit up too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> remind me! 1 month  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its no more "steeling" than the subsidies that corporations receive. Except I am a person and they are not. Learn to fucking spell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here you are yet again ignoring the entire basis of you and I conversing.....you are ignoring what I just told you you did, which was respond in a place where you KNEW it would not be constructive and give you the reaction you received. 

All things considered, I think I actually do feel better after this. I may have a mental problem, but I am still at least cognoscente enough to realize it....you, on the other hand... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ. This is a internet thread about government policy.  I wasn't soooo mean to you for just bringing up how this is not gonna survive. 

You chose to share your opinion not in the thread, but in reply to a comment advising people with depression to not look further as it would hurt their feelings.

Who are you kidding? You can either just say you are an asshole and move on, or apologize for not being very tactful in where you decided to share your opinion on the thread.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And even if you are right, I have a hard time believing you were raised to treat people the way you have treated me. It is not hard to have the opinions you have and not be so awful to someone at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I question even that of trump!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now look at defense spending and the tax differences on the super rich from now and 50 years ago. How about you focus your intense anger at that instead of your fellow human beings who are suffering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also should know it was a combination of 4 years and a team of doctors who all agreed with my diagnosis and my disabikity....seeing as how that doesn't make them any money, I guess all these professionals must have just had a crazy strong desire to let me be "lazy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't really express how much this effects me....it's obvious you don't care about that....but I am a human being, just like the people in your life you care about and wouldn't want others to make feel awful. I'm going to do my best to Ignore this, but please, no matter how you feel about politics, please know there are real hurting people on the other end of these messages.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You show such a blatant level of ignorance to mental health it is truly astounding. Why is it so hard to believe brains can break just like every other part of the body? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And making me feel completely terrible helps that how exactly? I feel like being positive and trying to make me feel better to help get me OFF disability would be a better use of your time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I think the whoosh is yours  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Id say you are in the heavy minority on that. Id bet my life 90% of players would rather have additional content in some kind of way over nothing....and thats what your "do some more battles" idea is. Nothing.

edit: Though I dont understand it, downvote away. I stand by my comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would this look like in a sealed environment? As in in a room with stationary or very slow moving air and nothing else to impact it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My internet feelings =(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Swatchznegger](http://gfycat.com/BoringDeadlyIberianlynx) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? FFX had towns. In the towns there were things to find or do. Also in every single map there were places to explore, while many of them were very small, they still existed on a more frequent basis than 13. 

While they are both linear games, FFX was a much, *much* more "open" linear experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of them encourage attacks on abortion clinics, and I remember a lot of them celebrating the attack on the gay night club in FL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of person intentionally looks for sensitive, suicidal people to try to hurt their feelings?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't believe it till the emojis!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 34 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be happy you werent here during the time in Earth's history where there was twice the amount of Oxygen in the air, resulting in insects the size of cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hated him as President. But I never questioned the fact that he actually cared about the every day citizens of the country, and was a decent human being. 

Trump has made me respect GWB like I never thought I would. I still disgaree vehemently with the policies he took up and some of his decisions.....but I respect the man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 99% of Trump supporters consider GWB the greatest president since Reagan. 

Cant wait to see the crazy justifications that will spawn from this story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you are never the top comment, sometimes you gotta set yourself up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah she is usually all like why is this stranger handing me a stuffed giraffe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should see when *I* give her a stuffed toy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for saying this. I stopped reading at this comment. Seeing things like that would have really hurt me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am on disability for anxiety. 

It took 2 years, and a handful of doctors to have it approved. This isnt a "damn Im really nervous about going to work" kind of anxiety. 

This kind of anxiety is the kind that literally destroys your life. Mine has been.

I had friends, a job, and other social connections.

As it got worse and worse, all of these things faded away into dust, while I was completely helpless watching it all happen. Its like I was watching myself in a movie, not being able to stop the downward spiral I was in. 

Do people seriously think I prefer this kind of life? Do they think I choose to live like a hermit mortified of every single small social interaction that exists in the world?

If I could trade it all in for a 40 hour job, my friends back, and *one* moment of having a clear head....I'd do it in a second.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a game made by the whitest people you will ever see..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ....please never reproduce....not that I think a woman would ever sleep with you with that attitude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/RKOTombstone WE NEED TO SEE THIS REUNION! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get me out asap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
