<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3715</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 19:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, exactly what I was going for ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 19:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 19:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely not the first try. It's the second game in the FRVR portfolio and property the 50+ game I ever made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 19:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triple A games are hard to play on a bus, in bed and um the restroom.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 18:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, hope to have newsletters sorted early next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 18:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this is one of my standard components and will exit across all my games going forward. Here is another example: http://solitaire.frvr.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 18:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 18:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very aware of the network value of my games, and something I am working on underlining with cross promotion, Facebook groups etc. One of the big channels i have yet to explore is Newsletters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iron-age Norwegians liked their bling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 17:58:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 17:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great voice artist from Dubai, Adam Odeh. Here is his [Youtube channel](https://www.youtube.com/user/BandigoPlays) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inventive crows caught on camera making tools in the wild. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 17:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 17:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Here is the relevant quote from the reddiquette**: *Feel free to post links to your own content (within reason). But if that's all you ever post, or it always seems to get voted down, take a good hard look in the mirror  you just might be a spammer. A widely used rule of thumb is the 9:1 ratio, i.e. only 1 out of every 10 of your submissions should be your own content.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 17:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually had to add the tutorial as some people did not understand it. The sound and music was composed specifically for the game fairly late. A model I want to follow going forward, as music that fits the game can really make or break or game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 17:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: I keep fairly good track of how many hours of effort I put into each game. Everything Hex FRVR (Including marketing and for Hex needed engine development is as of right now at 321.5 man hours)
2: As for inspiration, I played a matching game in two dimensions inside of second life years ago. The board where much smaller and it was played in multiplayer but it's the closed I had played before making the game. However during beta, people made me aware of 1010 which seems to be similar and quite a lot more successful than my game.

I will look into doing DMCA takedown notices, got a good service to help making such? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, what's your highscore?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have three major ad providers.

**Mobile**

1: Facebook Audience Network, which I use as primary provider everywhere but China
2: Goole AdMob, fallback for audience network + Chine

**Facebook / Web with ads (Traffic Partners)**

1: LiveStreetMedia ads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a few months in my childhood where I would dream C C Red Alert. And I will admit to once in a while I dream Candy Crush... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I hope to be able to take down the clones that are stealing assets at-least. However the processes seems to be lagging in effectiveness.

My hope is to create a as addictive game more, and use the previous success to make sure I reach even more users before the clones have a chance to catch up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly the addictiveness is a bit short lived. People tend to play like crazy (2-3 hours / day) for about 23-25 days, then become more casual, playing at max 3-4 hours / week.

I am looking into how to make it more addictive going forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, more info over [here](http://blog.chrisbenjaminsen.com/post/132895141632/hobby-startup-kpi-update-8). 

I am now working with a few non exclusive traffic partners   publishers, both in Europe and Asia. If the volume of traffic and eCPM's they are talking about holds true. $600 is just the beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I have come to realise that Hex is actually a really good game, I still hold that it was the sheer size of Reddit and specifically r/Gaming that really made the game. While subsequently I have gotten a fair amount of organic downloads due to the games ratings, it was the power of Reddit to push an app into the app store toplist that did the difference.

Also, thanks! I take your comment as a huge compliment on my game. Comments like that makes me want to sit down and make the next game right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 16:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me re-upload to Imgur.
[Edit: There we go] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Reddit made my simple puzzle game an indie developer success. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a [cross post](https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/3y2ela/hey_reddit_thanks_to_you_my_latest_game_is_a/) from /r/gaming with more information added in for you guys.

**TL;DR of below:** About two months ago I shared [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/3o43f8/what_started_out_as_a_test_ended_up_as_a_crazy/) to r/Gaming about [Hex FRVR](http://hex.frvr.com) and the game instantly took off, peaking at more than 5500 concurrent online. Reddit made my game huge and turned me into a successful indie developer. 

[**Play the game**](http://hex.frvr.com), or read on for a story on the power of Reddit!

For more than a year, I have been working on building a [HTML5 games startup](http://blog.chrisbenjaminsen.com/post/94738198525/lets-make-a-hobby-startup). Initially while having a full-time job, working in my spare time. However in July, after having saved up for a year, [I quit my job](http://blog.chrisbenjaminsen.com/post/123727342642/and-for-my-next-trick-ill-be-unemployed) to Travel the world while working on FRVR 2-3 days a week. 

While I did have a fairly well defined path to success, I was quite sure it was going to be a long hard grind, releasing somewhere between 8-10 games before having a really good business. However a single reddit post was enough to completely change that.

Before I shared Hex FRVR I was quite proud of my previous daily record of 31k visitors. On the day I shared the game, I reached 182k unique visitors and as people kept sharing the game, I eventually peaked at 410k daily visitors a few days later! These days the daily amount of players have stabilised at around 170k. [Here is a graph](https://imgur.com/7d4IlKj)

While that is amazing by itself, it's pretty clear that the gaming press reads Reddit (Hi!) as the game was quickly picked up by [CNET](http://www.cnet.com/news/hex-frvr-set-to-become-the-new-2048/), [PC Gamer](http://www.pcgamer.com/hex-frvr-the-perfect-procrastination-puzzle-game/), [Venture Beat](http://venturebeat.com/2015/10/14/meet-hex-frvr-the-new-puzzle-game-thatll-take-over-your-life/), and many more (Anyone wants a full list?)

Most importantly, the sheer volume of traffic made the game an economic success as well. Even though I only have advertisement in the [iOS](https://itunes.apple.com/app/id1036010745) and [Android](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.frvr.hex) versions, have disabled video ads (I hate those!), and only show ads about 30% of the time, when you start a new game. Hex FRVR still makes an amazing ~$600/day from in-game advertising. Not to bad for a simple puzzle game! [Spoiler](/s "Turn off internet for the app to remove all advertisement for free!")

Where it really did a difference was that initial traffic from Reddit + Reddit users sharing the game, was enough for the game to enter into the top-lists on the Apple App store around the country. In some cases, such as China, taking the #1 spot in Board and Puzzle for several days. The result was more than 400k organic and free downloads over a 5 day period. 

As the game was pretty new when I originally posted. It did have some major bugs bugs and left a lot of features to be desired. However /r/Gaming was amazing at giving feedback and quite a lot of the suggestions and ideas from the [original thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/3o43f8/what_started_out_as_a_test_ended_up_as_a_crazy/), has now been incorporated into the game. Here is a list of the major improvements:

* You now actually get a score bonus for doing combos!
* The game now saves the game state, if you reload or restart the app.
* At scores about 100k the game now becomes challenging for people who are really good at the game (Yes this was a major issue for r/Gaming redditors)
* You can now disable ads in the mobile version with a micro payment (This makes about $500/Month, thanks for the support!)
* The game no longer pauses your own music while playing on iOS!
* I rewrote the mobile versions from scratch, making the games feel like native apps on both Android and iOS.
* Many, many bug fixes. 

However, the success have had one downside. Today there is about 150 clones of the game on the market across app stores. And while I am actually 100% ok with people re-implementing the game, learning along the way and even making a more popular game than mine, about 40% of the games have straight up stolen music, graphics or even the entire game. Fighting that has been tiring and there don't seem to be an effective process for doing so on all platforms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you do have 3 bricks to choose from already. While not a "preview" you have 3x the choice of Tetris already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you make sure you find the game without me spamming reddit? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! If you want more, I [blog](http://blog.chrisbenjaminsen.com) quite a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How high a score did you guys get? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I have not recorded my pupils while playing. I do know that I switch between seeing roundish shapes and sharply defined shapes when playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think to many indie developers embark on the journey without considering the business side of things. While making the game they really burn for, 99% of the time what they do create has little to no market appeal and should be left as a hobby exercise. (Like how you should not quit your job because you love drawing, unless you have a pretty surefire way of monetising your art)

Sadly that's not the way the press is presenting indie developers, mostly because it's only fun to talk about the successes. The successful developers just happened to burn for something that had mass market appeal / or where actually business savvy. The result is that we end up with quotes such as *"Just do what you feel is right, and eventually you will be successful"* which in truth is horrible advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rotating game pieces would be game breaking and really a different game. I might release Hex Rotate FRVR or something where you can rotate the bricks later :)

Have you tried the mobile app as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Happy Holidays to you as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 11:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure how you can play it to much ;) - Absolutely my pleasure. Any feature requests? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 20:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect, I take that as a huge compliment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 20:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally much prefer to have a build once distribute everywhere and have put significant effort into having just that. However for your first game, it's more important to get anything live than it is what platform you made it in. Later you can worry about such details.

If your game is paid, you are basically 90% reliant on Apple features for traffic as paid games are rarely able to get into the top-lists without features. As soon as you have a good test build, send appstorepromotion@apple.com a link, then keep updating them with updates (Even if they do not reply at first, just keep going)

My model is ads between levels with a paid option to disable it. For now that seems to work very well. For not I will stick with it, as free games are easy to distribute (One of the things I am good at)

If you want more, I [blog](http://blog.chrisbenjaminsen.com) quite openly about the company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 20:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you guys loved the original version of the game, here is version 2.6.0 with many improvements! Cross post from [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/3y2ela/hey_reddit_thanks_to_you_my_latest_game_is_a/).

**TL;DR of below** About two months ago I shared [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/3o43f8/what_started_out_as_a_test_ended_up_as_a_crazy/) to r/Gaming about [Hex FRVR](http://hex.frvr.com) and the game instantly took off, peaking at more than [5500](https://www.dropbox.com/s/g9wj6pzdnkxuyxr/Screenshot%202015-10-09%2018.10.29.png?dl=0) concurrent online. Reddit made my game huge and turned me into a successful indie developer. 

[Play the game](http://hex.frvr.com), or read on for a story on the power of Reddit!

Before I shared Hex FRVR I was quite proud of my previous daily record of 31k visitors. On the day I shared the game, I reached 182k unique visitors and as people kept sharing the game, I eventually peaked at 410k daily visitors a few days later! These days the daily amount of players have stabilised at around 170k. [Here is a graph](https://www.dropbox.com/s/ttfattag5wdyyt5/Screenshot%202015-12-23%2017.29.17.png?dl=0)

While that is amazing by itself, it's pretty clear that the gaming press reads Reddit (Hi!) as the game was quickly picked up by [CNET](http://www.cnet.com/news/hex-frvr-set-to-become-the-new-2048/), [PC Gamer](http://www.pcgamer.com/hex-frvr-the-perfect-procrastination-puzzle-game/), [Venture Beat](http://venturebeat.com/2015/10/14/meet-hex-frvr-the-new-puzzle-game-thatll-take-over-your-life/), and many more (Anyone wants a full list?)

Most importantly, the shear volume of traffic made the game an economic success as well. Even though I only have advertisement in the [iOS](https://itunes.apple.com/app/id1036010745) and [Android](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.frvr.hex) versions, have disabled video ads (I hate those!), and only show ads about 30% of the time, when you start a new game. Hex FRVR still makes an amazing ~$600/day from in-game advertising. Not to bad for a simple puzzle game! [Spoiler](/s "Turn off internet for the mobile app to remove all advertisement for free!")

As the game was pretty new when I originally posted. It did have some major bugs bugs and left a lot of features to be desired. However /r/Gaming was amazing at giving feedback and quite a lot of the suggestions and ideas from the [original thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/3o43f8/what_started_out_as_a_test_ended_up_as_a_crazy/), has now been incorporated into the game. Here is a list of the major improvements:

* You now actually get a score bonus for doing combos!
* The game now saves the game state, if you reload or restart the app.
* At scores about 100k the game now becomes challenging for people who are really good at the game (Yes this was a major issue for r/Gaming redditors)
* You can now disable ads in the mobile version with a micro payment (This makes about $500/Month, thanks for the support!)
* The game no longer pauses your own music while playing on iOS!
* I rewrote the mobile versions from scratch, making the games feel like native apps on both Android and iOS.
* Many, many bug fixes. 

However, the success have had one downside. Today there is about 150 clones of the game on the market across app stores. And while I am actually 100% ok with people re-implementing the game, learning along the way and even making a more popular game than mine, about 40% of the games have straight up stolen music, graphics or even the entire game. Fighting that has been tiring and there don't seem to be an effective process for doing so on all platforms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hex FRVR 2.6.0 - Big update to my hexagon shape matching puzzle game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 20:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 19:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dirty minds etc etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 19:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry you can get one more boring ass gym desk job!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 15:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job! Whats the high score among you all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 15:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have considered different game modes, but really scared to break the basic game play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 14:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the best kind of feedback. How long have you been playing and what should I implement next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 14:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really good! How long have you been playing for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, looking forward to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, got a link? Love stories - very far away from the kind of games I make. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! What are you working on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not, the voices are by Adam Odeh, a great guy from Dubai I found on the Newgrounds voice acting forums.

(I wish I had a smooth talking voice like that..!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Focus on keeping the board clear, always having two possible future moves. (Should do the difference) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pleasure! How high a score have you gotten? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, thanks to you, my latest game is a massive indie developer success! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **TL;DR of below:**
*About two months ago I shared [this post](https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/3o43f8/what_started_out_as_a_test_ended_up_as_a_crazy/) to r/Gaming about [Hex FRVR](http://hex.frvr.com) and the game instantly took off, peaking at more than [5500](https://www.dropbox.com/s/g9wj6pzdnkxuyxr/Screenshot%202015-10-09%2018.10.29.png?dl=0) concurrent online. Reddit made my game huge and turned me into a successful indie developer.*

[**Play the game**](http://hex.frvr.com), or read on for a story on the power of Reddit!

Before I shared Hex FRVR I was quite proud of my previous daily record of 31k visitors. On the day I shared the game, I reached 182k unique visitors and as people kept sharing the game, I eventually peaked at 410k daily visitors a few days later! These days the daily amount of players have stabilised at around 170k. [Here is a graph](https://www.dropbox.com/s/ttfattag5wdyyt5/Screenshot%202015-12-23%2017.29.17.png?dl=0)

While that is amazing by itself, it's pretty clear that the gaming press reads Reddit (Hi!) as the game was quickly picked up by [CNET](http://www.cnet.com/news/hex-frvr-set-to-become-the-new-2048/), [PC Gamer](http://www.pcgamer.com/hex-frvr-the-perfect-procrastination-puzzle-game/), [Venture Beat](http://venturebeat.com/2015/10/14/meet-hex-frvr-the-new-puzzle-game-thatll-take-over-your-life/), and many more (Anyone wants a full list?)

Most importantly, the shear volume of traffic made the game an economic success as well. Even though I only have advertisement in the [iOS](https://itunes.apple.com/app/id1036010745) and [Android](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.frvr.hex) versions, have disabled video ads (I hate those!), and only show ads about 30% of the time, when you start a new game. Hex FRVR still makes an amazing ~$600/day from in-game advertising. Not to bad for a simple puzzle game! [Spoiler](/s "Turn off internet for the app to remove all advertisement for free!")

As the game was pretty new when I originally posted. It did have some major bugs bugs and left a lot of features to be desired. However /r/Gaming was amazing at giving feedback and quite a lot of the suggestions and ideas from the [original thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/3o43f8/what_started_out_as_a_test_ended_up_as_a_crazy/), has now been incorporated into the game. Here is a list of the major improvements:

* You now actually get a score bonus for doing combos!
* The game now saves the game state, if you reload or restart the app.
* At scores about 100k the game now becomes challenging for people who are really good at the game (Yes this was a major issue for r/Gaming redditors)
* You can now disable ads in the mobile version with a micro payment (This makes about $500/Month, thanks for the support!)
* The game no longer pauses your own music while playing on iOS!
* I rewrote the mobile versions from scratch, making the games feel like native apps on both Android and iOS.
* Many, many bug fixes. 

However, the success have had one downside. Today there is about 150 clones of the game on the market across app stores. And while I am actually 100% ok with people re-implementing the game, learning along the way and even making a more popular game than mine, about 40% of the games have straight up stolen music, graphics or even the entire game. Fighting that has been tiring and there don't seem to be an effective process for doing so on all platforms.

[Edit: Quite happy to answer any question about the game, business, etc, so ask away :)] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 21:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the latest update, focus on always having two valid moves while making 3+ combos. Should push you over 100k ;)

You can share that with your family whenever you feel like it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 20:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, 15.5k is very very good for your first games. I remember it being around 3-4k on average last I posted it here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 20:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highest validated score for the latest version is 262748 (Quite impressive). As for biggest combo, there was a guy posting [this](https://www.reddit.com/r/gaming/comments/3varx5/i_saw_hex_frvr_on_reddit_a_couple_of_months_ago/) the other day. Pretty much as good as it gets.

I actually have not sat down and determined what the biggest combo possible is. Anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 19:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you again! That goes for all of you. I cannot say that enough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the new video compression strategy from Netflix means for Apple and Amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 19:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 23:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I beat my own score just the other day. Now at 129740!
Always have two possible moves and try to make bonuses. That seems to have done the trick for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 12:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right, there is a statistical chance to get both "Incredible" and "Incredible" at 7. Beyond that there is nothing more.

However I deemed it to happen so rarely that it was ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 12:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The highscore with the current score setup is around 200k :)

How well did you do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 17:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 01:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is for you http://news.stanford.edu/news/2015/december/n3xt-computing-structure-120915.html :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guerrilla grafters quietly grow fruit on SF street trees using latest tech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 01:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Research links creativity and inability to filter irrelevant sensory information </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 01:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musks hyper loop dream is becoming close to reality, a 1 KM test track will be built in Las Vegas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 20:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making Rope - Medieval to Edwardian technique </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 19:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making a traditional Korean inlaid lacquer box [4:37] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 19:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Geminid Meteor shower, best of the year, peaks tonight: Watch it live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 19:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ARM charts out the path to printed plastic chips. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 19:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ARM charts out the path to printed plastic chips. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 19:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The graying thieves who nearly got away with a record heist in London </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 18:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Tabasco Sauce Is Made [5:02] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 18:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's not just the poor who can't make rent. New research from Harvard says that even renters with annual incomes of $45,000 face unaffordable rents in many cities, with potentially far-reaching effects. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 18:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's profiting from $1.2 trillion of Federal student loans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 18:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 90:9:1  the odd ratio that technology keeps creating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 17:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nations approve landmark climate accord in Paris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 04:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists find that walnuts have 21% fewer calories than the Label suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 01:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo touchscreen controller patent offers clues about upcoming NX. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 01:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tokyo police are using drones with nets to catch other drones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 00:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tokyo police are using drones with nets to catch other drones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 00:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I became a morning person. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 00:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cost of average San Francisco rent actually fell (a little) last month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 20:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots are now fighting fires in Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 20:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots are now fighting fires in Australia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 20:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 20:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission Statement: With the country embarking on an ambitious $1 trillion plan to modernize its nuclear weapons, current workers fear that the government and its contractors have not learned the lessons of the past. The article chronicles the past 70 years of US atomic weaponry which so far has resulted in at least 33,480 Americans dead.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irradiated: The hidden legacy of 70 years of atomic weaponry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 20:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building and launching multistage water rockets - [5:58] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 19:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building and launching multistage water rockets - [5:58] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 19:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why hacking DNA is the secret of deep-space travel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 18:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bizarre saga of Craig Wright, the latest "Inventor of Bitcoin" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 18:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faraday Future picks Nevada over California to build a $1B plant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Faraday Future picks Nevada over California to build a $1B plant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dow and DuPont to merge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 22:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyscraper-style chip design boosts electronic performance by 1000x </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the issue is that cooking requires pre-planning. You need to decide what to eat, shop for it, and start cooking before your really hungry. While not that hard, it seems a fair amount of people are to impulse driven to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To see the future of electric cars, look east </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mobile adblocking apocalypse hasnt arrived yet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volkswagen and the blame the engineer game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was being snarky, but is getting away with it due to the developers owning up to their mistake ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the food industry engineers the need to eat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japan's Akatsuki orbiter sends back first Venus images </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 16:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CS:GO Damage Control </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 04:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He Blew the Whistle at JPMorgan Chase, Then Came the Blowback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 04:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Theranos CEO Elizabeth Holmes fend off her critics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 23:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft surface overtakes Apples iPad as top-selling tablet online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 22:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creatures avoiding planks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 22:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New style of police training aims to produce guardians, not warriors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 22:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook to open-source AI hardware design </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 22:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet the woman in charge of the FBIs most controversial high-tech tools. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 18:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surreal painting by Wylie Beckert [20:50] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 18:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milling rocket jet vanes in graphite at Copenhagen Suborbitals - Danish indie spaceflight company. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 18:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walmart introduces Walmart Pay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 18:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I went to help at Calaiss Jungle refugee camp  and what I saw haunts me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 18:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The tipping point: Most americans are no longer middle class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 05:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 21:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People seem to be fairly committed to their respective ecosystems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New clues to Ceres' bright spots and origins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New clues to Ceres' bright spots and origins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission Statement: Americans have been on the move around our country for a long time now. Unfortunately, there's comparatively little knowledge among the reading and research public about what exactly historic trends have been. This ignorance leads to an abundance of casual errors. In this article Lyman Stone goes digging through old Census data back to 1900, and have put together what he believes to be the best estimate of net migration for each state going back to the turn of the century.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A century of migration in the US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 19:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission Statement: What if? is a waste of time went the headline to the Cambridge historian Richard Evans piece in The Guardian last year. Surveying the many instances of public counterfactual discourse in the anniversary commemorations of the First World War, Evans wrote: This kind of fantasising is now all the rage, and threatens to overwhelm our perceptions of what really happened in the past, pushing aside our attempts to explain it in favour of a futile and misguided attempt to decide whether the decisions taken in August 1914 were right or wrong. Its hard enough to do the reading and research required to understand the complexity of actual events, Evans argues. Lets stay away from alternative universes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if? On the value of counterfactual history. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hardly anyone is using Apple Pay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hardly anyone is using Apple Pay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Facebook luring you into being depressed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Cortana: Now available on iOS and Android. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 18:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 04:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great part one, now do more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 04:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission Statement: Researchers say the recent studies carry a broader message about the need for rigorous research in charitable programs. Microcredit has grown into a $60-billion-plus industry reaching 200 million borrowers worldwide despite limited evidence that it actually achieves its goals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microloans Dont Solve Poverty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 04:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 02:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be great with a continuation! Although the two paragraphs in short succession both stating with *I rolled my eyes* thew me off.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Silicon Valley, Stockholm produces the highest number of unicorns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 02:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicago and Los Angeles are next up For Google Fiber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 02:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attack on DNS root servers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do more on that over [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/WritingPrompts/comments/3vyiap/wp_american_satellite_started_transmitting_46/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the WP post becomes big. Looking forward to the stories that does not revolve around aliens or the thing becoming self aware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The smartphone completely changed the Refugee crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The genetic code now has a workable text editor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a [pretty good idea](https://www.reddit.com/r/WritingPrompts/comments/3vyiap/wp_american_satellite_started_transmitting_46/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] American satellite started transmitting 46 years after being abandoned in 1967 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 19:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on a [true story](https://www.thevintagenews.com/2015/10/23/american-satellite-started-transmitting-46-years-after-being-abandoned-in-1967)!

Just found a video with [audio of the signal](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UxqwZ42NyLw)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grand Image Compression Challenge at ICIP 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 18:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vermont utility says it will be the first to install Tesla powerwalls in the US. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 18:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Europe moving toward single unified digital market [Europe] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 18:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 18:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking the same. Isn't it technically better that it's always charging? Assuming your phone battery is full, you will "spare" your internal batter charging cycles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 18:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission Statement: At first glance, there is logic to New York Citys numbered subway lines: 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. The letters, however, are a little less straightforward: A, B, C, D, E, F, G, J, L, M, N, Q, R, S, S, Z. What happened to the H? Or the O? And why in the world there are three S trainsshuttles going between Grand Central and Times Square in Manhattan, between Prospect Park and Franklin Avenue in Brooklyn, and to Rockaway Parkwhen there could easily be an S and, say, a K? To understand how this came to be, we need to go back 111 years, when the subway opened in Manhattan on Oct. 27, 1904. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The history behind New York Citys missing subway lines. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 18:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teens can't tell the difference between Google ads and search results. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mastering coffee delivery, one tray at a time - Design of Postmates in-bag coffee holder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apples new $99 iPhone battery case doesnt measure up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronaut selection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bone-like plastic structures form biodegradeable temporary pavilions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The sports bubble is about to pop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American satellite started transmitting 46 years after being abandoned in 1967 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Qualcomm Is Accused of Violating Antitrust Rules in Europe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welding Low-Alloy High-Strength Steel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 03:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Price is Right - Truly amazing hole in one game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 03:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LeBron James signs unprecedented lifetime contract with nike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 03:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drone nearly collides with helicopter, operator gets caught. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 03:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drone nearly collides with helicopter, operator gets caught. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 03:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drone nearly collides with helicopter in Martinez, operator gets caught. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 03:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the world of Lyft spam on Facebook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 23:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the world of Lyft spam on Facebook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 23:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 21:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission Statement: People who grow up in harsh or unpredictable conditions often unconsciously adopt faster strategies for getting through life, while people raised in largely stable conditions adopt slower life strategies. Griskevicius has used an economic model to understand similar life circumstances and how people's life choices might help them adapt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When destructive behaviour makes biological sense. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 21:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E-Residency in Estonia, Part I </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 21:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 21:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submission Statement: When Alvaro Cerezo, a Spaniard with an unslakable wanderlust and a sun-bleached man bun, dedicated his life to exploring the remotest islands on Earth, he could not have predicted how many hours he would have to spend indoors, making uneasy small talk with local authority figures across Southeast Asia. Recently, NY Times went with him to the office of a provincial government minister in northern Indonesia. Cerezo was there to see about an island. But first came the obligatory schmoozing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to feel like a castaway - One mans wild quest to make the deserted island fantasy the ultimate reality. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 21:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Schwarzenegger: I dont give a **** if we agree about climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 21:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Myth of pristine Amazon rainforest busted: The rainforest was home to millions of people before European arrival. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four reasons the Facebook fortune is going into an LLC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Primitive skills expert Will Lord shows how to create a Danish flint dagger. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first penis transplants in the U.S. will soon help heal wounded veterans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagon says Russian, not U.S. warplanes hit a Syrian army base </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA official warns private sector: Were moving on from low-Earth orbit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was referring to the video's title "Two Inuit men in Canadas Far North choose the site, cut and place snow blocks and create an entrance--a shelter completed in one-and-a-half hours"

I am aware that Eskimo as a term, is a pretty bad one to describe the diversity of people living in the arctic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The K-Cup short squeeze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 20:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
