<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5389</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A super powerful NSA, on auto-pilot. Very nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 12:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys talked AVN and genetics, even gay men's relationship to vaginas. Not even once did someone mentionned or asked for the source. You're loosing it, mates. Big time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quand mme... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are places like this in France </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La normalisation, jusque dans les moindres dtails.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... Tu pensais que je vote FN ou un truc dans le genre? Je suis plutt du genre "stalino-mlenchonien", fan de Taubira, pas effray par le multiculturalisme, etc.

a ne m'empche pas de voir qu'on a un gros problme, dans le style "guerre froide civile". C'est d'ailleurs pour a que je suis Onfray: se plaindre de l'tat du monde sans chercher  le comprendre n'avance pas  grand chose. D'o la ncessit d'couter plus ceux avec qui on est le moins d'accord.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Investi dans des boules quies et des pinces  linge. T'es pas sorti du bois.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Le bruit et les odeurs c'est pas ton truc?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 13:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Faut sortir de la maison des fois, coco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just came here to say that the monarchy is the most narrow-minded, gregarious, cringe-inducing, helter-skelter, harum-scarum, stinking pile of shit-like, backwards, barbarian imbecility an autistic, inbred, rape-born monkey could come up with in the most drunken stupor of his ass-methane suffused, hallucinogenic coma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In France, our bridges are made of upvotes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 00:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **To the Lighthouse, by Virginia Woolf**

Unsettling yet interesting. A third in and still trynig to figure it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Piti, dis-moi que c'est du sarcasme...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah! T'es ici? Je te cherchais dans le thread de l'article LCI o la police nous dit que 10 cm de matraque dans l'anus c'est un accident.

EDIT: pas fasciste, mais visiblement pas prte  tre la "prsidente de tous les Franais".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Et aprs on s'tonne qu'il y ait des meutes en banlieue tous les quinze ans...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You made my day OP!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 03:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of any reasonable situation where I would expose my naked scrotum to a girl armed with a baseball bat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting. Thanks for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fillon c'est un peu comme le mec qui prend une bosse en bagnole, se plante et continue  faire des tonneaux pendant 5 km.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? How was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure most hard-core Trump fans will be crying their eyes out by the year's end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tout simplement magique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk about crossing swords... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Des conseils pour apprter un restant de bloc de foie gras?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boulot, appart et mon permis d'exercice d'avocat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 10:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genre le mec fait des check-check avec les gardiens  l'entre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fillon, cet explorateur audacieux de la friend zone lectorale. 

Merci, mais non merci coco.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 12:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'est dans ces moments-l qu'on regrette la disparition de Philippe Seguin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 12:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last resort appeal in SCOTUS means one thing: Dems need to take a wiz, grow balls, stock up on granola and start filibustering the shit out of Gorsuch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Si cette logique tenait il serait prsident depuis 95 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I mistaken or it's missing Asimov's Foundation trilogy? Isn't Netflix trying to adapt it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> French guy here! A general strike is more a knock out punch than a starting point. But if you can pull it off, well that'll be stuff for History. 

Good luck. Live long and prosper.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 23:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nan mais oh! C'est des cathos srieux ces gens-l! Ils le font par l'opercule de la ceinture de chastet, et avec l'autorisation du pre, s'il vous plat. Pas besoin baissage de culotte par ici!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pauvre Penelope. Tout ce qu'elle voulait c'tait un sugar daddy. Maintenant la presse lui fait bouffer des taloches comme des crpes  Chandeleur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 00:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On rentre dans la catgorie des emplois imaginaires. Du gros calibre tout a.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not know I wanted that. Thx OP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mec, je te paie **l'hectolitre** de sangria si a arrive. (Et je trinque avec toi).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're faced with an administration that lies even about things as painfully plain and obvious as the weather, it doesn't seem far fetched to imagine that the one time they *might* be saying the truth everybody will cry foul.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I'm already exhausted from racking my brain to come up with a punch so original and unexpected. What? Am I made of great one-liners?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  combien de millions ont siphonn les autres en toute impunit. 

Quelle blague! J'en suis dj  compter les milliards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was the American Inauguration... My bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 14:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have not read the book, have you?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fillon c'est un peu comme le mec qui se lance pour le Paris-Dakar et qui fait six crevaisons  30 mtres de la ligne de dpart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 13:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comme disait un clbre trio:


'Mais que se passe-t-il?

Mais que se passe-t-il? 

Qu'est-ce qu'il se passe? ' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Le groupe Facebook de Baroin a aussi t renomm: https://m.facebook.com/FrancoisBaroinPresident/?locale2=fr_FR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Un dput sans permanence... Faut avoir un sacr melon pour oser a.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it and it's one of my favorites. It does seem to me that this is one of these books that you have to read "at the right time". Lost souls looking for themselves are the proper audience for this book.

Some passages of it are immensely poetic, such as that drive from Louisiana to San Francisco. It is also a portrait of an America few remember but which really did exist.

It is full of wonderfully clever observations about manners and the cycles in modern American history. Also full of literary references that shaped the early days of the "counter-culture" and others that betray Kerouac's French Canadian background. 

It exudes so much life. It is vibrant and yearnful,  everything in it "twitch to live and go". Kerouac wrote in two weeks flat, but he spent 7 years on that blessed road to pickle his senses in the zeitgeist of his time. The novel itself was hugely influential. And it bent the direction of American literature at the time. 

This is not a novel you come to for answers: there is a moment in the story where Sal and Dean find themselves stranded God knows where, a policeman comes to them and asks: "Are you guys going somewhere or just going?" 

If you can understand that question, it's depth, then the meaning and purpose of the novel, its importance, will become clearer.             </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I can tell you whose memoirs will not be wanted.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appelez Jean-Pierre Foucault! Il y a clairement quelqu'un qui veut gagner des millions l.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 12:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is some third-world shit right there. Come and tell me again that there is no such thing as "white privilege".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mr. Bissonnette's online profile and school friendships revealed little interest in extremist politics until last March when French nationalist leader Marine Le Pen visited Quebec City and inspired Mr. Bissonnette to vocal extreme online activism, according to people who clashed with him." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quebec City mosque attack suspect known for right-wing online posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all his years, French President Sarkozy did say one sensible thing: if the US pulls out of the Paris deal, carbon tax the shit out of every American export.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first blowjob was a nightmare. She had braces 

Should we assume it was your last or...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came here for the jokes and got an actual, sensible, factual explanation. You sir are tha real MVP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tu attendras encore un peu, je pense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, Macron is an oddity. He's never stood an electoral test until now. He was an adviser in the President's shadow. Then he was an ephemeral minister. The fact that he polls so high is, for me, a complete outlier. 

To be honest, nothing is going on as usual this election cycle. People who were not supposed to win are winning. And winning big. Three 800 pounds gorillas are already out of the race (Jupp, Sarkozy and Hollande). 

I suspect nobody really understands what's going on and the election will be decided the day before the vote is held. 

However, I'm pretty confident Le Pen will be denied the presidency (again).

And no. I don't like him. He's a Sarah Palin with brains but equally empty when it comes to policy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Je ne crois plus  rien depuis qu'on m'a priv de Ccile de Mnibus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dans une lection o tout ce qui tait pris pour acquis est pass par-dessus bord, je me risque  prdire que le FN ne sera pas au second tour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Je pense que le monsieur se trompe surtout sur le sens du mot "privatiser".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world according to Trump, courtesy of the New York Times Magazine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the coolest thing I've ever been made aware of  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you Norwegians! Why do you have to be so nice and friendly all the time? :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Risky business...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ryan "Cocaine Rabbit" Madison. At it, again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did march for women. Doesn't mean I'm not into the occasional racy joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the time you spend on social media each year you could read 200 books </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey mate. I don't want to judge. Maybe you're a bibliophile and you have *tsundoku* which is fine (http://www.latimes.com/books/jacketcopy/la-et-jc-book-hoarding-tsundoku-20140724-story,amp.html). 

But if it affects you socially and financially, maybe you have a compulsive hoarding disorder (https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Compulsive_hoarding). 

Hope it helps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... no one is considering that this may be a before/after picture?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... A little mystery. The real mystery is which will give you diarrhea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck waterboarding. Hot sauce on the pussy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 13:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montesqieu. Nice reference bruh. You know your stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 00:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Est-ce que je suis le seul  penser que ces fortifications ont un style Vauban avant l'heure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 18:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eye roll is a good indicator of pussy quality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Saudi Arabia discretely funds the CIA's clandestine ops so the Agency can evade Congressional oversight, etc.  (Will provide NYTimes source I've read it from as soon as I find it).

EDIT: There you go 'U.S. Relies Heavily on Saudi Money to Support Syrian Rebels' http://nyti.ms/1ONLKkR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 01:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J'allais dire que c'est beaucoup d'efforts pour une si petite marche...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gee, I'm glad he's not *my* president. Hang in there guys. (And join the resistance).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Strange case of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde, by Robert Louis Stevenson** 

Almost through. This is no cartoon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 12:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Du calme cocotte...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 23:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Sentimental Education** by Gustave Flaubert </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bonne question...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sur une chelle de 1  "cause toujours", c'est quoi les chances de Hamon de se qualifier au second tour de la prsidentielle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phew! Thx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 16:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crowd of intelligence officials applauded, raucously.

I pissed myself reading this. Shat myself hearing it on tape. Am I the only one?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day... One day...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 12:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rumor has it her back problems vanished after that scene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 12:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone noticed that the LGBTQ page of the White House website has disappeared? Check: https://www.whitehouse.gov/LGBT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tu parlais de tes impts, ces impts qui finance ta tl, tes partis et mme des journaux que tu ne lis pas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bienvenue en dmocratie, o tes impts financent des partis marxistes-lninistes et le FN. Si tu ne veux payer que pour les choses avec lesquelles tu es d'accord, fais-toi une principaut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with Newt these days? He said he wanted a "congressional committee on un-American activities". Then he said we should lift all ethics requirements to fit Trumps business. Then he said we shouldn't get to hung up on the First Amendment. And now this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 13:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y a des rteaux plus embarrassants que d'autres.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 12:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Baudrillard est sur mon radar depuis un bout de temps. a se lit bien?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 12:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ma contribution: la jolie demoiselle qu'on voit en Bulgarie c'est Nina Dobrev. Elle est du coin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 03:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right?! I hope this is the one reboot that doesn't defile my childhood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montebourg qui arrive  nous citer une phrase d'Aubry sur Hollande pour parler de Macron.

En feu Arnaud!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Donald Trump a un nationalisme chevel" 

Montebourg gagne le prix de la blagounette. Faut avouer que je me suis marr plus que de raison.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> J'espre pas. Y en a marre de se faire plumer par Bouygues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see Jordi's still on MILF duty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 23:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acadmie franaise quand mme...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avec la surpopulation carcrale, on n'a pas le choix. Mme la Cour europenne des droits de l'homme dit que les conditions de vie des prisonniers sont indcentes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he OK back there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pool giant TV. Mos def </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The was my second favorite WTF item </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The view is probably a big chunk of the price. Ironically, it's also the one thing that has nothing to do with the house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yell at your reseller. Top shelf champagne tops at less than a hundred dollars over here. For any increase in price over that blame taxes, greed and yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 14:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you flip the pic upside down and zoom on the eyes and forehead, it looks like the creepiest smiley face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's sleeping on the couch tonight.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I still haven't noticed her face...  (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 16:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like someone nailed her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
