<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3989</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 12:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess i'm sort of the stingy one here, I don't do it intentionally but I have always been really tight with my money and how I spend it. So when I'm out with my work friends I always get the bare minimum of water and the cheapest meal while they feast like kings. 

Now back to them spending too much, they almost never finish their meals so by the end of the meal I always end up taking the free drink there, a plate of chips here and an untouched dessert over in the corner. I could honestly not pay anything at all and be full but I won't stoop that low </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 12:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever i'm presented with an aggressive tailgating driver, I like to think up an elaborate backstory as to why they are trying so hard to weave in and out of the traffic and get to their destination faster. Is he late to his WoW guild meeting? Is his pet turtle late to his vet appointment? 

No, most of the time they're just assholes. But I always give them a smile and wave if i have the chance just to fuck with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 17:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flappy bird. Sometimes the rage helps poop out the constipation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 17:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just panned it in post :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 17:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Ask Jeeves was relevant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 17:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP's mum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] Australia Timelapse Collection (4 In 1) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 08:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 16:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah definitely the better one out of the two, I'm in the process of making a collection so i'll probably do something similar but at night, I think the lights would make it look nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 08:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're trying to find out what you want to do with your life honestly it's just best to keep busy and just do stuff. You're not really going to miraculously find out what you're passion and ambitions are doing nothing all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 08:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never wipe. Save money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 17:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much anything I do while drunk with a girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 14:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Music. But I feel betrayed when i'm practically falling asleep and go oh shit better charge my phone before I crash, then when I lie back down i'm wide awake again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 14:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was born in 1997, but my birthday is in november sooo.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
