<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject943</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Babysitting for the Fitzwillys (Final) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Part 1**: https://redd.it/691whw


**Part 2**: https://redd.it/699a3p


I had never experienced terror as vividly as I did while being dragged down the staircase. 


I was too busy trying to fight Bosworth to notice exactly where I was being taken, but I knew for a fact that it would not be anywhere pleasant. My only calming thought was that maybe they wouldnt find Dylan. Maybe Zander could get the police here before they started searching for him. 

As for my own safety and survival . . . hope had begun to dwindle. 

I didnt care.


 As long as Dylan managed to get out and find some way to put his life back together.


 They threw me into the cellar. It took me a few moments to identify the room from the rows of preserved wines that formed a labyrinth in the mouldy darkness. There were no windows in the cellar. While the upper floor of the house was magnificent in architecture and dcor, it seemed that this cellar was built in a hurry, the poor structural integrity and uneven stonework a jarring contrast from the more expertly-crafted main rooms of the home. I landed against one of the shelves, my head slamming hard against a corner. My vision splintered, pain pounding through my skull where it was still bruised from the week before. I quickly rose to my feet though, determined to not just take whatever they were planning for me. I could just about make out their light-kissed forms thanks to the illumination spilling in through the open door, but it took a while before my eyes fully adjusted to the sudden darkness. 


Margery was still humming the tune to that nursery rhyme, swaying back and forth slightly as she stalked towards me. The most awful thing about Margery Fitzwillys voice was that the tone itself might conjure up feelings of safety and maternal comfort, had it not been laced with madness just below the surface. Even now, her voice began to change, taking on a childlike quality that made the hair on my arms stand up.


 My lovely little flower, so naughty. What am I going to do with you? And such naughtiness right before the party tonight! *What party?*  She began to circle me, her strides long and stilted, her back hunched slightly. She touched the tips of her thumb and index finger to her chin, feigning indecision. My eyes followed her every movement, my fists balled up and ready. 

You were such a wonderful nanny to my Jaime. I shall hate having to punish you.


His name is not Jaime! I screamed back at her. He is not a baby at all and he is not your child! 

Bosworth came striding forward but Margery held her hand out to fend him off. 

Not yet. She cooed. Our nanny doesnt know what shes talking about. She is going to apologise and all will go back to how it once was.


I am not going to apologise! I knew that this was probably not the smartest idea but a week of this horror had outstripped any sense of self-preservation I had left. You can do whatever you want to me but you arent going to get away with it. You arent going to get me to play along with your sick games anymore! I wont do it! 


She clicked her tongue to the roof of her mouth and shook her head in amusement. 

Yes you will. Because you seem a smart girl and you know what happened to the other girls and boys who just werent quite smart enough. You wont make their same mistakes, dearie. Those precious little flowers.


Fuck you, lady. I said dryly.


 Her smile had begun to droop again. Id learned to loathe the slacking of her grin, experience deemed it an omen of something terrible to come. It always was. She suddenly grabbed a fistful of my hair and yanked it back hard. I cried out.


 Apologise! She screamed, spit flying onto my face. 

Fuck off.


 She pulled harder, taking her other hand and pressing her talon-like nails into the skin of my throat. Her voice raised an octave. 


APOLOGISE AT ONCE! 

I pried her claw from my throat and elbowed her hard in the stomach. She fell back shrieking. I decided to make one final, brazen attempt at escape and ran full force at Bosworth. I landed a blow against his cheekbone but it was like he couldnt feel anything at all and I am not a soft-puncher. He simply grabbed me again, spinning me around and guiding me to a chair where he tied me up, my wrists attached to the arms. I didnt go quietly and he must have had a few wicked-looking scratches over his already-scarred face. I smiled a little at that.


 Margery began crawling toward me on all-fours. The bones of her skeletal frame poked through the billowing material of her floral dress, her hair was straggled and there was still blood all over her face. She was still grinning, still lurking toward me, taking on the likeliness of an insect. She swung her head from side to side, the movement growing more erratic the closer she got to me. 

My patience is wearing thin, dear. Apologise. We could still work things out, still be family again.


You are nothing more than a psychotic old woman who ruined the life of another human being but is too blinded by her own insanity to see it. I will never be part of this sorry excuse for a family. And youre either gonna end up dead or arrested by the end of the night.


 She growled, lunging toward me. I raised my foot and caught her in the throat. She keeled over, wheezing, and I prayed to anyone listening that Id crushed her trachea. Bosworth let out an unintelligible scream, then ran to her side. I looked on hopefully. But she still got up. She was laughing through her hissing and gasping, using up any breath she managed to draw in on that ugly cackle. 

Party time! Party time! She croaked out. She was still holding her throat and was beginning to walk out backwards, still staring at me as she laughed, eventually edging out of the door, Bosworth following her. There was nothing but poor light and silence for several long moments, then I heard footsteps. 

Slow, deliberate footsteps. 

A hunters tread. 

Lionel Fitzwilly was entering the cellar, a hammer glinting in his right hand. 

Since I d been in their home, I had never heard him speak a single word. Somehow that was almost as frightening as his wifes constant chirping and singing. He walked excruciatingly slowly. 


There is something oppressive about the waiting silence between the present moment and  your eminent torture. I cant really describe it.  The anticipation of the agony you know will surely follow is so consuming and overwhelming that the only way to escape it is to give in to the numbness of acquiescence. I was going to die. I was going to die here, in this hole at the hands of a deranged old man and his hammer. A million thoughts began to race through my mind. Faces of loved ones, the sound of my friends voices, the dreams I had yet to pursue, unrealised ambitions, the longing for a future unlived . . . it all came crashing into my mind until my thoughts seemed to shatter, then caress the blackness of my mind like stars pressed against a night sky. 

Id always loved the stars. 

They seemed to beautiful, so untethered to the evils of this earth and I wondered, even as I sat there shaking, if what they said was true, if our souls would go on to become one with the celestial once leaving our earthly bodies. 

I hoped so. I hoped for that beauty after these ugly horrors. 


Well, if I was gonna go down, I was gonna down go fighting.


 So, I said casually to the approaching man with the hammer. Is this what usually happens? You do your wifes dirty work for her, watch her torture and remake people? I bet thats what she did to you. Or were you just born a bitch? 


Not my smartest comment but still felt good at the time. By then hed reached me. I tried to kick out at him but he was surprisingly spry for such an old man, and strong too, as he gripped each leg and sat down. He moved the one beneath his weight, trapping it there, then removed the boot from the foot of the other. For the first time, I saw the ghost of a smile play at his lips. 

Lets take a look at these little piggies, eh? He removed my sock. He placed my wiggling foot on the ground, securing it there with his one hand and using the dominant one to hold the hammer. I knew what was happening, but until I saw him rear back his hand, until I felt that first blow shatter my big toe, I didnt believe it was actually happening. 

This little piggy went to the market. He brought the hammer down, hard, and a strangled scream tore itself from my throat as I felt my toe bashed open. He hit my foot again. And again. And again. I could feel the break of the bone, hear the wet slickness of the hammer as it was pulled back from my mangled flesh. It dripped blood on my foot. Then he moved it a little. 


This little piggy stayed at home. He hit the second one. I bit my lip, trying to hold back the screams, but they still slipped out. The pain was incredible. I was panting, trying to breathe through it.


 Ha, thats all youve got? The pain must have killed off the last of my brain cells.

 He suddenly stood up, levelling the hammer with my face. 

Night-night. He said, preparing to hit me in the face. I closed my eyes, steeling myself. 

All of a sudden I heard Lionel grunt and felt the rush of air brush my face as he was knocked to the ground. I opened my eyes. 

Zander was on top of him, struggling with him to get the hammer.

 It only took him a few seconds to grab hold of the thing and hit Lionel against the head with it. It only took a few blows before the old man stopped twitching. Zander got up, breathing hard, face splattered with blood. 

You okay? 

I nodded, wincing at the pain in my foot. Neither of us said anything for several moments. Then, he smiled wryly. 

You know, Teresa, if you wanted to see me again all you had to do was make a date. I appreciate the effort but getting kidnapped by two psychos is a little much, dont you think?


Shut the fuck up and untie me. Thanks, by the way.


Dont mention it. He worked at the rope securing my wrists. Actually, yes, mention it. It was a fucking nightmare getting in here. There are a lot of insane people on this premises. I had to sneak in.


Wait, what? 

He lifted my arm over his shoulder and helped me up. 


Theyre having some sort of party. There are a whole bunch of crazy old people, all bringing adults dressed as babies or small children. 

Holy shit. 

The police arrested them all, right?


No. The police arent coming. 

My heart sank. 

But . . . what? Why? I thought you 


They wouldnt believe me. I sounded like a drunken twenty year old kid making a prank call. I had vague snippets of information, no details, and what I had was already ridiculous enough. I wouldnt have believed me. I wouldnt have believed you if I didnt know you. If I hadnt seen this for myself.


Call them now!


My phones dead.


Youre . . . youre serious? 


He nodded sagely.


So were on our own?


Were on our own.


Damn. 

I could walk but I couldnt put much weight on my left foot. When we reached the light, I nearly passed out. My foot was unrecognisable. The flesh hung off the bones of my two toes. Zander wrapped it up with some material he tore from  his shirt. 

That bastard. He said as he bandaged it up. 

We have to get to Dylan before she finds him. I said urgently.

Zanders grey eyes went wide. Dylans really here? 

I nodded. Yes and theres something very wrong with him, Zander. They . . . messed him up. We need to get him out.


Then were gonna get him out. His voice was certain, blazing with a confidence I was sure was meant to convince himself more than convince me. Where is he?


The nursery. I lead the way there. We did our best to be as quiet as possible. The party was being hosted in the main dining room, so we could sneak past them through the kitchen without being seen as long as we were silent. While in the kitchen, Zander grabbed a knife off the counter. We made it to the nursery which was still dark. For some or other reason, I didnt want to turn the light on. 

Instinct proved correct because when Zander flipped the light switch, there she was. 

It was almost as though I could feel her presence before I saw her, crouched in the corner, cradling Dylan as she sang Three Blind Mice. 

Bosworth materialised from behind the door and knocked me to the side, slamming his foot down hard on my femur bone. I heard it crack, felt the break of bone through skin and I screamed. Zander was no match for him either, and was soon subdued, bloody and held in a lock before Margery.

 She put Dylan aside and crawled towards him, a spoon in her hand, the lyrics to that fucking song still dancing on  her lips. 

Ah, my three little mice. She looked at Dylan, Zander and I all in turn. Then she pressed the back of the spoon against Zander s cheekbone. Little mice but theyre not . . . not blind, are they? 


Despite the agony coursing through me, I dragged myself towards where the fallen knife lay a few feet behind Bosworth because I *knew* what was coming next. I knew what this bitch was about to do.

 I need my three mice blind. She giggled. I had just gripped the handle of the knife when Zander began to scream. 

She was gouging out his right eye with the spoon. 

I could actually hear the disgusting wet sounds and I propelled myself to go faster. From the corner of the room, for the very first time, I could hear Dylan crying. Shed just dug out Zanders eyeball when I reached Bosworth and buried the knife to the hilt in his calf. Then I dragged it down, tearing his flesh. He yelped, dropping Zander. He turned to face me and I slashed out again, slicing his hands whenever he tried to bring them near me. I delivered quick stabs to his legs, trying to get him to fall down, to get him out of the way so I could get to Margery. But I didnt have to. She suddenly began screaming, and both of us turned to watch as Dylan lashed out at her. 

Bosworth looked confused, as though he couldnt process what was happening. Zander lay on the floor, his head surrounded by a halo of blood as he clutched at his empty eye socket. Margery ran out, Dylan chasing after her on unsteady legs. Bosworth slowly walked after them, still looking confused. I crawled over to Zander, bringing his head onto my lap. I looked around and picked up one of Dylans  stretched baby fleeces, wrapping it across his eyes and around his head to staunch the blood-flow.

 He was hysterical.

 I grabbed his hands, bringing them to my face, moving his fingers along the angles and curves of it, telling him that it was ok, I was here and it was going to be fine. I could hear chaos erupting from the dining room.

 I needed to do something, get to a phone somehow. One of those people had to be carrying one. I needed to call an ambulance.

 I reassured Zander that I would be back soon, and dragged myself to the door, across the hall until I could see into the dining room. 

Dylan was strangling Margery in full view of all the guests.

 As though seeing the display snapped something in all of the other children, they all began attacking their captors. It was pure, unabated pandemonium. People were being torn apart by nails and teeth. I could see the years of torment manifest in bloody carnage as screams filled the mansion dining hall. Bodies already lay scattered across the lush carpets, which was quickly soaking up with blood. I crawled to the nearest body, a gentleman dressed in expensive attire that suggested the possession of a phone on his person. I searched his body until I found it and called the police, telling them to send an ambulance immediately.

 I couldnt stand the sight and sounds of the party any longer, so I crawled back to the nursery, finding Zander and waiting with him until I could hear the sirens outside. 

Dylan appeared in the doorway shortly after. He just stood there for a moment.

 Then, he spoke. 

His voice sounded as unsteady as his steps had looked, voice rusted from disuse but still, he made the effort. 

We . . . were back. The three of us . . . 


I could feel tears rolling down my cheeks as I nodded. He came walking over to us slowly, crying himself. Then he sat down beside me and clutched Zanders hand, putting his head on my shoulder, weeping. Thats how we stayed, bloodily reunited after ten years, after unspeakable horrors, each of us bearing different wounds that bound us to that night forever.

 Each of us lending and borrowing strength from each other. 

We stayed that way, unmoving, until the cops finally came rushing into the nursery.

***
I wish I could say it was over. 


But I dont think something like this ever truly ends, not really. 

The Fitzwillys madness had bled into our lives and I dont think the stain will ever truly go away. Well carry that brokenness with us for the rest of our lives. But at least we have lives to live out. 

Were lucky, I guess.

 Zander and I, though certainly bloodier than Dylan, had the lesser evil wounds. We were both set to recover, though it will take months for me to be able to walk properly again and Zander has to have a fake eye. 

But Dylan . . . Dylan was malnourished for years. Besides his obvious malnourishment, the formula they fed him contained hormones that stunted his growth and the doctors had to do extensive tests to figure out how to fix the damage to his body. That too, was minor in comparison to his psychological strain. He still lives his nightmare in and out of sleep. But were there for him. Zander and I, we visit him at the clinic whenever we get a chance to. Were spending more time together again as well, mending our friendship. 

I dont think you can live through what we did with someone and not feel tethered to them. 

Were strong for one another, all three of us. 

Baby steps, day by day, were fixing each other. 

The strangest thing is that despite everything that happened to us, the detail I remember the most, the one that will stay with me forever, is Margerys rose garden. Not the sound of cracking bones, not the sight of flesh being ripped apart, not Margery's eyes, the colourless depths of inhumanity. The roses. I hadnt noticed the first day I arrived. But I noticed as they carried me out on a stretcher. 

In my delirium, in that eddied world of pain and flashing lights and screams I remember the roses growing in a little patch along the walkway. 

Beautiful, well-kept. 

Much like the rose garden she once maintained a decade ago.

 A near four-dozen of them. 

It was only once the police spoke to us that everything clicked into place.

 Margery and Lionel Fitzwilly were suspected to have kidnapped and tortured forty-five young adults. 

I could hear Margerys voice in my head singing,  * . . . you seem a smart girl and you know what happened to the other girls and boys who just werent quite smart enough. You wont make their same mistakes, dearie. Those precious little flowers.*

 Forty-five roses for forty-five deaths. The other nannies. 

Forty-five roses and I would not be the forty-sixth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...No one with the name "Jeremy" deserves to be a bully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
