<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2433</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 21:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply

You mentioned lack of support from parents, and I think that may play a role in this

My parents didn't abuse me, and they did provide me with the essentials and more, such as Christmas presents or sometimes helping me pay for college, but they were always overtly strict and critical, and yelled a lot

I'm also afraid of coming to them for any advice because I'm afraid of them being critical of me, and for the many reasons I will mention below. My parents are also overly stubborn, and trying to reason with them is tough, and my mom always seems to think she is right

I'll admit, I try to avoid my parents as often as I can because they always seem to point out my faults or criticize me, even though they are trying to help. 

My mom also seems to criticize me all the time. She always points out how I'm overweight and should do something about it, and similar things like being on the computer too much, or spending too much money, or not being productive. Sure I may be bad with my money, but complaining to me all the time just makes it worse

They also get angry or upset easily. One example, a year ago I said I might be able to help out with the car insurance because I knew a guy who works at the insurance agency we get our insurance from. Instead of being thankful, my mom yells at me asking if I gave out are insurance information, and scolds me saying how I shouldn't give anyone our insurance information. Situations like this have happened more times than I can even remember.

Or my parents would get mad or overreact at very small things. One time, I left a few wrappers on the table and forgot to throw them away. Later that day, I get a bunch of angry texts from my mom, saying how I'm so immature and irresponsible, and how I shouldn't leave wrappers laying around. She then sends pictures of the wrappers to my therapist asking her to talk with me about why I did that.

And my mom yelling at me, even today that's one of the things I fear most. I lie a lot to them just to appease them, and because of fear of being yelled at or punished. I also want to know I'm right for once in my life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 20:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for writing that

While it may take a year, will there be any noticeable progress along the way? I'm asking because i'm gonna be a senior in college starting in the fall, and I want to be able to enjoy this year and make new friends and stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 06:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes thanks for this. I may have to read it a few more times, but hopefully it sticks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 05:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would work, and at the same time would not

Like you said, it would take a few years, but I don't have that kind of time. 

I don't know why, but I wanted to have this kind of confidence and stuff while I was in college so I could have a good experience there and find a bunch of friends and have a good time, but now I'm gonna be a senior this year so why bother, after college its just work

I guess the problem now is why bother, I guess its a step in the right direction though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 02:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I do have good friends, but they all are from college and live far away so I can't really hang out with them right now.

Also I'm too afraid to get out of my comfort zone, I don't know how to push myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 02:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is I think I am doing it excessively or doing it wrong, because I'm starting to annoy people. Like I want to hang out with friends, but they are always so busy, so I keep on trying to contact them to see when they are not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
