<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4921</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 20:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of our favorite and pretty underrated place for coffee is Ma Petite Shoe.  Delicious lattes.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always validate your primers by running a gel.  Just because you plugged it into some software which claims it is specific doesn't mean shit.   Also, you need to determine the efficiency of your primers if you want to do good science.  Doing these steps takes more time initially, but it saves you headaches in the long run and you'll do better science because of it.  I see too many people that just blast their primers and claim they're specific because they only got 1 hit back and that's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although this album is platinum, I still feel like it is one of THE most underrated albums of the 90s.  One of the best albums of that decade and I still listen to it in full from time to time.  

Tim Armstrong is also a hell of musician.  Back about 2 or 3 years ago he released a new song/cover song every day for an entire year straight.  You can listen to his entire project here:

http://timtimebomb.com/music/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We didn't elect Duterte, the Philippine people did.  He is their problem, not ours.  It isn't our place to proselytize the Philippine people.  This exactly what China understands and where the West fails, because Americans are still stuck in a mindset that the world can be changed to think like them.  It. does. not. work.    

It doesn't hold any water at all when Americans scream that he is killing people in the streets for using drugs while our own government performed syphilis experiments on poor people in Central America (hell even syphilis experiments on our own people), released crack in the inner cities of our own country, supported murderous regimes under the likes of Pinochet, and the list goes on.  Why aren't you just as outraged over US support for Teodoro Obiang Nguema Mbasogo, who is known for "unlawful killings by security forces; government-sanctioned kidnappings; systematic torture of prisoners and detainees by security forces; life threatening conditions in prisons and detention facilities; impunity; arbitrary arrest, detention, and incommunicado detention," and who is considered to be the absolutely worse piece of dictator filth in all of Africa?  Here's our president with him:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Teodoro_Obiang_Nguema_Mbasogo#/media/File:Teodoro_Obiang_Nguema_Mbasogo_with_Obamas.jpg

You can not demand people do one thing while you go about the rest of the world doing the complete opposite --which is exactly why the West fails at international diplomacy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 14:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duterte has a point, although he could be much less of a douchebag about it.  The problem with the West is that in order to do business with us, we will try to enforce our ways of life on you, whether you like it or not.  Believe it or not, there are billions of people in this world that think in mindsets completely alien to Americans and Europeans.  Sometimes in order to get what you want done you need to make deals with the devils of this world without proselytizing. China understands this.  American foreign policy strategy really hasn't changed since WW2, which is a colossal mistake since there are now more players on the block , unlike after WW2 where we were pretty much the only ones available to rule the world.   It is completely ingrained in Western mindsets that other people need to think and be like us--the west has been trying to colonize people and run their countries for oh what, the last 1000 years?  It doesn't work anymore when you have major powers in the East.  How well has trying to install a Western style democracy worked in Iraq?  Or any of the other countries in the mid East that we've been trying to democratize since the 1940s?  All it has done is lead to the Iranian revolution, extreme Islam, and ISIS.  We don't always have to impose our style of democracy where it probably won't work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC reported on the King's failing health. Should significant unrest be expected if/when he passes away? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 06:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 05:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women's Industrial Exchange in Mt. Vernon may suit your needs:

http://womansindustrialexchange.org/

Even as a guy I enjoy supporting that place.  Lots of cool and local craft work.  I'm not sure if you can always walk in and buy things though.  Just double check.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 03:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, all I was asking was whether or not the area of Bear was known for its racism. This is like claiming Rising Sun MD isn't known for being racist or Long Island, NY isn't well k known for its racism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Bear known for being particularly racist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the other day my sister in law, who is Thai, received a nasty letter in her door from someone in her neighborhood claiming that she and her husband are 'ruining the neighborhood' and that her 'dog was ugly' (she just got a new Rottweiler puppy).  The letter then goes on to call her a 'Chinese eggroll' and not to mess around in the neighborhood because the author apparently believes in practicing their 2nd amendment right. The letter also criticized her for marrying a 'old white guy' (who isn't even old). Btw she and her huaband are a lawyer and a manager of a restaurant and they probably easy pull in over $100k combined.  I fail to see how they're going to 'ruining a neighborhood'.  


Since when was Bear so racist that you feel intimidated toive in your own home due to hostile neighbors?  And FWIW, the sis in law didn't think the haters are white people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 23:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay, the 10000th time this has made it to the front page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 15:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, there's a plethora:

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2015/03/03/francis-colliins-nih-funding_n_6795900.html

http://www.sciencemag.org/careers/2013/09/funding-cuts-ravage-academic-laboratories

Replace those scientists in the second article w/ my PI except we can't even get the 'bridge funding' from our institution because too many other people in our institution are competing for it.  Institutions almost never pay to fund the lab because then then would no longer be multibillion dollar behemoths.  An institution couldn't afford it either - our place spent over $2bn per year in NIH money, which is nearly the nstitutions' entire endowment.  Yes, not every scientist's lab would need institutional funding if grant money were also thrown in, but institutions would run out of money in no time at the rate biomedical scientists spend it.  Our entire floor has recently had a lot of problems with funding, including scientists and engineers named to be some of the top young scientists in the country.  If our institution is having so many problems funding research, I can only imagine it is 10x worse at other smaller schools.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 06:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This won't be popular on this sub, but I'll tell you exactly why I now watch less football compared to what I used to watch 8-10 years ago:

1.) Too many games  relative to number of days.  There's TNF, Saturday games (sometimes) Sunday, and MNF.  I watched more when it was only 2 days.  If you're a college football junkie it is even worse.  What, are you gonna blow Thurs, Fri, Sat, Sun, and Mon all on football if you have a family?  And 9 AM games in England?  LOL, not happenin', I ain't getting up for that.  


2.) Fantasy has ruined football.  Yeah, people like to claim it gets them interested in games that they normally would want to watch. BS.  A ton of people no longer care about the game anymore, which is why bastardizations of the game like the NFL redzone exist.  People now have figured out you don't need to watch the game anymore and get live texts on their phones when their players score a TD.  Additionally, the fantasy novelty factor may be starting to wear off.  

3.) Too many commercials and the games take to long because of them.  A typical game will have over 100 commercials.  It is completely ironic that everyone claims a game like baseball is 'boring' because it is too slow.  The typical baseball game takes 2h 52min.  A typical football game takes 3h 12 min because of all the stoppages and advertisements. The NBA is even faster - 2h 15 min and average NHL game is 2h and 20 min.  The action in the latter sports constantly moves and because of it, it is hard to interject with commercials.  

4.) Too much criminal conduct wrt the players.  Drugs, insurance fraud, murder, drunk driving, gun shootings, you name it.  Why do NFL players get held to a different standard than the rest of us?  How many times have multiple players sexually assaulted women and are still in the NFL as stars?  How many have been arrested multiple times for DUI?  

5.)  Too hard to watch games.  I cut the cord a long time ago, and more people are doing the same.  You can't watch a game to stream because you need a cable service login or you need to subscribe to an expensive package. NFL game pass for $60 per mo to watch 100 ads per game? And to only watch 4 games that my team plays per mo?  No freakin way. 

6.) This is not my opinion, but there probably is a growing trend of people that are turned off by the whole brain injury issue.  Yes, players get paid millions of dollars to get on the field and take the risk, but at the same time some people would argue that you are enticing poor minorities off the streets with large amounts of cash to put their health on the line for our entertainment.  Again, not my opinion personally, but there are more people than you think that think like this.  

How to make it better:

1.) Go back to Sunday/Monday only.  

2.) Allow people to stream 1 free game per week by signing up with the NFL related website.  If they want more they can pay, or they can stream their ad riddled game for free.  

3.) Increase the speed of the game.  Figure out a way to cut a half an hour off.  An NHL or NBA game flies in comparison to NFL games.  Get rid of the direction changes on the field after every quarter, only do it after half time.  Get rid of the clock stoppages on incomplete passes.  Get rid of icing the kicker, it doesn't do anything and slows the game down.  Cut down on TV timeouts. Give 4 time outs total, for the entire game.  Increasing the pace can be done.  1970s games could be routinely done in under 3 hours.  



The biggest problem is due to complete oversaturation.  Watching football was more of an event when it was only on Sunday and once on Monday.  Now you have people talking about the NFL draft in March, sports analysts constantly talking about football during the Summer, and football everywhere everyday of the week except Tue/Wed.  Mark Cuban nailed it, and politics/the whole Kaepernick saga has nothing to do with my decline in watching.  You realize that my generation is really the last generation that grew up constantly with TV right?  We all did fantasy when it first started to become huge and were addicted to football because of it.  That has now warn off now that we all started to have families ourselves and have other commitments.  A TON of kids in high school and college now have grown up their entire lives in households that not only cut the cord, but grew up entirely cord free.  They have no allegiance to watching anything on TV at all.  Kids in college get pissed off if a GIF on the internet takes more than 8 seconds to get to the punchline, and you think they'll want to sit through an add laden game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funding.  Is Academia really a sustainable career option or do you expect mass layoffs coming very soon?  I'm currently in a lab that is on its last leg.  When I first started we had 9 people, and now it is just down to me, we have 0 new grants, and the one we currently have runs out in March 2017.  We've literally submitted over a dozen grants with no luck.  It's not like my boss is a bad scientist either; we have produced good papers before, although we can no longer publish a lot of papers because I simply can't continue to do an amount of work for 5 people.  Thus we're caught in a death spiral where you can no longer publish because you don't have the hands available, and you don't have the hands available because you don't have the funding.  It just seems like the whole game is rigged against you--the NIH will help you start a lab and routinely give new PIs or PIs who have never recieved an R01 a R01, but once you get into you're mid-career you're screwed unless you are a superstar lab with 30 people.  The NIH cuts your funding off just as you're reaching the prime of career and after your lab has been setup.  Kind of disheartening to pour your life into science only to have it destroy your soul in return.  My PI has probably aged 10 years in the span of 3 years; and I'm extremely stressed out having to grind out inordinate amounts of experiments for moonshot grants.  I just don't see how this ends; it seems like academia is a ponzi scheme waiting to implode as soon as things start to go sour or your lab hits a rough patch.  This is at a top 3 insitution BTW, not a small college with non-famous professors.  Multiple Nobel winners here.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Internet was $58 when I first moved to Bmore.  Then it was $68, then $78, then $92.  I never understand why it keeps going up for the same service.  That's with no phone or cable either.  Just to get on the freakin internet costs nearly $100 /mo. now.  And just wait until everyone starts cutting the cord even more.  Watch it get jacked to $200 /mo.  within the next 10 years without competition.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if there is bumper to bumper traffic, like what you often encounter in a major city during rush hr, and you can't see the light as you approach an intersection because a large truck is in front of you, you can get stuck blocking the box if you can't see the light starting to change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 17:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, because it can be difficult to see the light if you have a large truck in front of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good tips on how to get someone to work in Fed Hill on Sat. and avoid that whole area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My wife is foreign and has been living in the west for years, yet when she falls asleep and dreams she talks in a foreign language. Why does her brain default seem to be her foreign language then if she uses English everyday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 07:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea what your downstream application is, but have you looked into a bligh Dyer extraction ?it is used alllllllllll the time to obtain lipids, proteins, and polar metabolites for proteomics and metabolics.  The proteins will precipitate.  All it requires is chloroform, methanol, and water.  It is super easy too and you can resuspend proteins in a desired volume after.  Again, not sure of your downstream application and if this would be suitable for it.  It might also be more difficult on a small scale, but you can give it a shot for pennies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guessing Maori....basically kiwi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, that's English? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one was god awful.  This one will be different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 04:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about those aged 20-40?  I'm pretty sure I'm orders of magnitude over 261 mgs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 03:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I mean I go there too, but it is just so damn expensive.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 22:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, I go out of my way to drive 1 hour *away* from Baltimore/Towson/Whitemarsh area if I ever want to go to the movies.  And the movie better be pretty damn good for me to want to travel that far.  The reason I go out of my way is because I have no idea why people in this area are absolutely so obnoxious while at the theater, especially the kids around here.  Whitemarsh is a total crap show.  I've been there more than once and they pretty much almost had to call the riot police to breakup the mobs of teenagers causing trouble and getting into fights.  I mean I went to the mall and hung out at the movies when I was a kid too, but I don't ever remember causing the obscene amounts of violence that I almost always see around this area at the theaters on a Friday/Sat.  The real horror movie is in real life right outside of the theaters around here when you're trying to go to the show or get out.  I just don't understand why people around here can't refrain from the pervasive use of profanity and violence against each other.  I pretty much don't even go to the movies anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 16:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. They do it on purpose.  They don't want to wait.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 03:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell you in words how much eczema SUCKSSSSSS.  I've recently (for the last 3 years) been battling hand eczema and pompholyx with very little success.  When it it breaks out it can be quite painful because you literally have open sores all over your hand.  The fissures that develop are large and very deep--you could literally stick a dime in there and they'd stay.  
[Hand Eczema 1](http://www.pcds.org.uk/ee/images/made/ee/images/uploads/clinical/Hand_derm_800_526_70_http:www.pcds.org.ukeeassetsimgwatermark.gif_0_0_80_r_b_-5_-5_.jpg)

[Hand Eczema 2](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/_zAjq1kHJqys/SV9McGqKKcI/AAAAAAAAEVs/eMhY33j18rI/s320/Vittone1.jpg)

[Hand Eczma 3](https://usercontent2.hubstatic.com/12083061_f260.jpg)


And you simply can't stop using your hands in order to let your open wounds heal.  You have to do the dishes, wash your hands before eating, take a shower, etc. etc.  The constant washing of the hands makes things worse.  I mean I try to use gloves as much as possible, but my hands will go for weeks looking like beef jerky.  Heal for 2 weeks, and then it'll come back.  Rinse and repeat non-stop, no matter what season it is too.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of Times 1986.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 01:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  Finally they're enforcing traffic laws.  Should be a gold mine for this city that could plug a lot of budget holes with the insane driving habits residents have in this city.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 15:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So dumb.  Injuring other fellow citizens over sports.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 06:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the idea might have been to release thousands of them because they were cheap. If Japan ever got wind of success, who knows what would have happened if the US Office of Censorship failed.  They might have sent over 100,000 balloons loaded with biowarefare, which we knew Japan was working on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 06:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were even able to reach Nebraska.  Amazingly, US scientists were able to figure out that they were coming from Japan because of the types of sand being used in the balloons' sandbags. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that during WWII, the Japanese developed what are considered to be the first intercontinental weapon: balloon bombs that took advantage of the jet stream in order to reach the US and Canada. It worked but the US govt was able to keep a lid on it to prevent panic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 06:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 05:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, crusties.   Do. Not. Feed.  They're a scourge in Hampden now.  One of em even had a pet goat they were trying to use to get money from people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 03:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see what the problem is.  They post their rates on the windows.  Customers can choose whether or not they want to patronize the business.  Unless they're hiding fees or something, I don't see how this is 'swindling'.  People are free to choose which gas stations they go to, even if some cost 10-25 cents more per gallon, what's the difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 06:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if it doesn't exist at all? Isnt that worse?  When you die you become nothing but carbon atoms. A bad after life better than 0 after life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 05:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad.  They had some of the best pastries in the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 05:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are literally right next to Charm City Wings and Waffles. Amazing place if you like that kind of stuff.  They make waffles too without wings if you don't want it. 

http://www.charmcityww.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 20:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Privately owned land, do whatever you want with it.  Other people shouldn't be allowed to tell you what you can and can't do with the land.  Why stop there?  It so happens that I'm not a fan of you renovating your house like you are planning and don't like your new porch plans. I should be able to block you from doing it?  Rolland Park residents should just buy the land themselves with all the money they have if they don't want it turned into anything. Put their money where their mouths are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 20:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly why, if ghosts ever did truly exist, there would be nothing to fear because of the fact that their existence alone would prove there is an afterlife.  The worst thing  a ghost could possibly do would be to kill you, but then your existence wouldn't end.  Thus, nothing to fear about ghosts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 03:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WW2 is so overplayed. Like to see more Korean War, Vietnam, or Desert Storm films. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 16:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shop around for refinancing.  Consider any potential fees and calculate if there will be any savings once the interest is taken into account.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 16:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone knows what credit unions are, right?  There's a reason why the banking industry like WF et. al. have tried for decades to kill credit unions, and that's because of the fact that they're non-profit organizations that are consumer friendly.  Credit unions are literally your friend. 

It only takes a small amount of time if you really, really want to 'stick it to the system'.  Imagine if everyone got home and auto loans and banked with credit unions.  Trillions of dollars would be funneled away from for profit enterprises and back towards the consumer.  The convenience argument also hold very little water.  I've used credit unions for the past 20 years and it has never been a major issue.  Tons and tons of gas stations have free ATM withdraws.  I almost never carry cash anyways these days, because like most people, all  I mostly do do is swipe a card anyway for a payment.  Even if you need to deposit from far away, many credit unions form networks where you can make a deposit anywhere and they'll process it to your account for free.  A lot of credit unions will also let you take a picture of a check and put the money in there for you.  All you have to do is mail it in.  Really little excuse to not have a credit union account.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 16:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> absolutely.  just shop around and see which CU offers the best deal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my take on this and I know it might not be popular:

1.) a lot of people are turned off by the constant criminal behavior of the players who still get rewarded with big contracts.  From insurance fraud, murder, gun violence, and drugs to sexually assaulting women, players have done it all and are still on the field.

2.) health concerns.  Yes, a small but sizable amount of people do care about the detrimental effects of playing football for one's brain health.  Yes, the players get paid millions of dollars to put their health on the line, but many would argue that we're paying poor minorities to bust up their brains on the field for our entertainment.  Not my opinion personally, but there are a lot of people that think like this.

3.) The fantasy football wave of popularity is starting to die.  The NFL really was never as popular as it is today until fantasy football started taking over the sport.  Fantasy cheapened the sport to just constant bombardment of Red Zone plays every 2 minutes.  Who cares about the game, all everyone cares about is if their fantasy players are scoring TDs.  Well, the novelty is starting to wear off from fantasy, and I wouldn't be surprised if either participation in fantasy has plateaued due to saturation or a lot of casual fans just move on. Don't get me wrong, fantasy football is still huge, but its probably already peaked.  

4.) The insane amount of advertising.  Should I really have to sit and watch 100 commercials in order to watch the browns get their asses kicked by the patriots?  

The Kaep effect?  Meh, minimal, I don't care about it at all.  I'll tell you exactly why I watch less games and NFL: I simply have shit to do on the weekend and can't burn an entire day in front of the TV watching commercials.  I quit fantasy after playing for 15 years--the novelty has completely worn off. The only thing I care about now is just watching the Eagles' games and that's it.  Mon/Thurs. night football are meaningless to me now unless my team is playing.  It's like baseball or hockey, I don't care about watching other teams play until it is the playoffs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 04:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the worst feelings of all time is when you get owned by a trash talker that can back up the trash.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 14:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this going to get flooded out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 15:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that within the margin of error though, meaning it means nothing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 07:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So dumb.  If the right guy wins he could be killed with one punch.  Can't stand the guy though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wouldn't want to be the lowly paid lab serf making $19k a year that has to work with and grow  'deadly, drug resistant superbugs'  just to test this stuff out on.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, Santa Claus is fictional? :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 00:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why they're the Clowns:

http://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/many-of-the-browns-scouts-fired-before-the-draft-favored-carson-wentz/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 00:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think it is hilarious the Cleveland Browns fired all of their scouts that told them to draft Wentz.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More ridiculous Matthew McCononaughey Lincoln commericals.  God I hope Jim Carey does another SNL parody.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 23:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God the difference between this team vs. Chip's team is like night vs. day.  The D doesn't look anywhere near as gassed as they did almost every play under Chip.  Controlling the clock is a must in the NFL.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 69 people were shot in Chicago during memorial day
http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/local/breaking/ct-chicago-shootings-memorial-day-20160530-story.html


Chicago is also the same city where gang member executed a 9 year old, and was also planning to torture him first:
https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/morning-mix/wp/2016/03/08/suspected-triggerman-charged-in-execution-style-slaying-of-9-year-old-chicago-boy/


America is just a fucked up place.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 18:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem though, is that the reverse isn't always true: just because you have gene X expressed doesn't mean at all that it equates to protein level.  I can't tell you how many times I've experimentally come across the situation where my western blots have the reverse levels of protein that one would have predicted from gene data.  Does not correlate at all many times.  If you knock out the gene though, of course you'll effect protein levels. That's what makes it hard, the converse isn't always true. Worse yet, protein level can also not correlate with function at all.  Right now I have two types of cancer I'm working on and cell line X has the same or less of protein A as cell line Y.  What's peculiar however is the fact that protein A seems to be much more active in cell line X.  I can directly measure the amount of metabolite the protein produces, and in cell line X, it produced several fold more metabolite than cell line Y even though cell line Y has the same or even more of protein A.   Disease is still more complex than this, as there are still several more layers of organization that are completely outside what is encoded directly in the genome.  I mean I suppose you could target the gene expression w things like RNAi (though the tech isn't there yet), but targeting the protein products seems less clear, to me at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 17:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huuuuuge loss for the MLB and the marlins.  Pitchers like that don't grow on trees.  Top 5 pitcher in the league who would have dominated for the next 10 years is gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 06:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe it.  That movie was god awful.  The acting was horrible.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was an amazing show like Deadwood canceled? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 01:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean a show like Oz still spanned 6 seasons on HBO.  Deadwood was also pretty popular and received wide critical acclaim.  So why cancel it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dayman Cometh to Work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 01:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 00:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, maybe some good can come from this, science will just have to get more clever.  Maybe killing bacteria is the wrong strategy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 23:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caffeine doesn't make you beat your family, cause you to kill people while driving, or urge you to pimp your child out so that you can obtain more of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 17:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  Once got an entire carton of doubles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 05:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the freshman star is inelligible to play because of the way the NCAA cartel interprets when grade 9 starts, yet the NCAA allows an organized criminal enterprise like UNC to continue to operate for years while falsifying grades and setting up fake classes for their players?  I see how it works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it has a similar mechanism to ethanol, I imagine you still can get blackout drunk and/or die from drinking too much of this stuff just like with regular booze.  The only thing that's different is that it probably isn't metabolized into a toxic byproduct which causes hangovers, unlike ethanol.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 16:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, if only I had this when I was in college.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you secretly do besides whack it when your roommates are gone and you have the whole place to yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 08:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 07:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the parrallels between Fight Club and Mr. Robot keep on coming.  Just before Tyler Durden and Ed Norton blow up the banks, Ed Norton shoots himself to kill Tyler Durden.  E Corp is going to get blown up just like all of the banks at the end of Fight Club.  The ending is similar in almost every way possible to Fight Club.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 05:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Begins with a S.  I'll leave it at that.  Man, sometimes I question why I even do science.  Apparently you can make hundreds of millions of dollars selling a huge catalog of antibodies that are all specific towards BSA and/or milk.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 02:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost always Cell Signaling.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally took the same exact memebrane and blotted for the same exact protein using the vendors' protocols, which were identical.  Difference is night and day.  Don't cheap out on antibodies and have to waste time with this garbage.  This is exactly why I spend an extra $100 on antibodies from a good vendor, so I'm not redoing blots, reprobing, reblocking etc etc.  Huge waste of time. 


 /end rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good antibody vendors vs crappy ones. Why do I have to waste time with this bullshit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 23:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm usually pretty careful about my personal info--I try to never give out my cell phone number or other private info out online as best as I can.  I mean I'm not OCD or crazy about it, but I'd say I'm more careful about it than average.  Just recently though, my phone has been spammed beyond tolerable levels by scam artists claiming that they're from the IRS and that I owe back taxes (obvious scam).  I'm also getting all sorts of calls now from out of state and from other random numbers.  It is super annoying now.  How did they get my number though?  

I downloaded a few apps for my phone, but nothing anything that hasn't been downloaded less than 1 million times.  Spammers getting the info from apps?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is completely non-scientific, but something does seem different. I can go many weeks now, heck, even almost an e entire summer without ever seeing a single bumble bee now that I think about it. Growing up as a kid though, I remember seeing them everywhere almost everyday , even getting stung by them multiple times during a summer saying out in the yard so much.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 07:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chemistry is probably the worst of all the fields.  How many times do you ever see % yields reported with +/- errors? Virtually never. That's because we all know chemistry just either A.) tries a reaction once, and as long as they validate the structure it is OK so that means the reaction is good or B.) report only the results for a reaction attempt that provided the highest yield.  No one in synthetic organic chemistry is repeating reactions 3,4,5x and reporting the variance of the yields obtained.  It just isn't standard practice in a field like chemistry.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 07:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Improving statistics isn't always the answer to all of the problems either, because it can't always be done.  Ask yourself, should you even attempt to answer a biological question if you know you can't obtain a highly powered study?  What if it takes 10 months of work to grow a cell line, engineer it,  and then test it?  It is almost impossible to replicate that from square 1 5, 6, 7 times in order to obtain a more highly powered experiment.  There are inherent limitations to biology that simply can't be overcome, as of yet, for a lot of scientific problems.  Should that limit us to what we can ask? It is easy to obtain giant sample sizes if you do things like study populations in fields like ecology, epidemiology, or whatever, but it is literally inhumanly, and even economically, impossible to get say 30 independently tested samples for every single type of experiment that you try in a field like molecular biology.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 06:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't always THAT simple.  We once had someone from NIST come in to give our group a talk.  In one series of experiments, they gave out the same exact cell lines, same exact reagents, and same exact protocols to different labs across the country in order to test toxicity of compound X  on the cells.  The assay was very, very straight forward (like a MTT assay).  The results that the labs sent in to NIST were shocking.  The IC50 values calculated by different labs varied by as much as 1-2 orders of magnitude, IIRC.  Nobody was doing anything knowingly wrong or with any malfeasance in play; the huge degree of variance simply came down to scientist skill, lab location, type of pipettes, etc. etc.  In order to cut down on the variance, NIST eventually figured out an insane, absolutely not obvious,  zig-zagging pattern in order to add the reagents to the cells.  If something like a simple cell toxicity assay can't be repeated without 1-2 orders of magnitude of difference, how can we possibly expect a huge chunk of science to be replicated when many procedures and experiments require many dozens of steps, months or even years of work, proprietary/non-common items, different levels of skill, different locations, etc. etc.?  The gravitational field strength at your lab's location probably comes into play at this rate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, can I link back to my gilded comment?


https://www.reddit.com/r/TwoXChromosomes/comments/4fob41/harriet_tubman_to_replace_andrew_jackson_on_the/d2aqsaa?context=3
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good.  Poise.  Good decision making.  Still hasn't gone against a top D yet or has had to make a clutch comeback win yet though. Time will tell.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 05:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is amazing how much different the Eagles' D looks.  They don't look completely gassed every single time they're out on the field because the offense doesn't constantly go 3 and out and no longer tries to do gimmicky Chip Kelly plans to run as many plays as possible, which does nothing except cause a turn over of downs and kills your D.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really Fitz?  Horrible ad for a predatory school like Univ. of Phoenix.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very impressed by Wentz.  He's got composure.  Good decision making.  The Eagles are no longer constantly going 3 and out.  Good things to come.  Maybe it was good that Kelley got rejected when he tried to trade the farm for Mariota.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 22:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm...nope, but I'm wondering if one of my previous students did! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 06:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're going to get sick because it is cold outside.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dynasty keeper leagues mckinnon should be bought big time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 05:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really need to start pounding it consistently w/ McKinnon.  He's the future.  This is APs last year as a full fledged start, most likely.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 23:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude just never learned to protect himself.  It was cringe inducing watching him play, having to listen to those massive hits and watching his head constantly slamming on the ground.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 22:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys: use old school style safety razors.  The shave is comparable or even better than all of the disposable cartridge type razors like the mach3s etc.  It also saves you a HUGE amount of money, because a double edge razor blade only costs a few dollars for a 20 pack, unlike the $40-50 charge you get for only something like 8-10 heads for a mach 3.  Complete rip off.  If you want to save even more money, a straight edge razor is awesome, but takes a looooooooot of practice and takes a lot more maintenance.  The old school safety razors are awesome.  

Ladies, give your man an old school safety razor for a gift too.  Trust me, over the long run they'll love it.  Much better for the environment too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same-haven't owned a TV since about 2001.  You pay over $1000 a year for cable just to get commercials and a few additional sports channels and if you don't even care about sports, cable is even a bigger rip off.  You can buy shows individually from networks.  

Just hope more competition for ISPs opens up before the back of cable companies is permanently broken so that they don't start charging $300 per mo. for internet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Robert Morin had his quirks: a regular breakfast of Fritos and a Coke; a refusal to give up on the 1992 Plymouth that he drove to his job as a library cataloger; the 18-year span, from 1979 to 1997, during which he watched more than 22,000 movies  an average of about three a day. **Morin read in chronological order every book published in the United States between 1930 and 1938, excepting only textbooks, childrens books and cookbooks**."

Impressive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMDB: where people go to give a movie like Transfomers a 8+ rating when it came out.  IMDB ratings are virtually worthless, along with websites like Yelp.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> University to buy $1 million football scoreboard with thrifty librarians money, outraging critics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 06:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just hope this doesn't go the Lost route.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 05:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although, it should be noted that just as of April 2016, Johnson and Johnson dropped this controversial policy.  Other manufacturers, however, have continued the status quo and have fought bitterly in court  against the state of Utah's where they made this practice illegal (although Utah appears to have won for now).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that major manufacturers of contact lenses have implemented 'price floors' for the costs of contact lenses in order to block discount retailers from undercutting prices offered by eye doctors. As a result, some consumers pay nearly double the price they used to for some brands of contact lenses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 05:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 07:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, what the hell is EA Skate?  I must be so old.  I remember when getting 100k points in Tony Hawk was amazing because the manual hadn't been incorporated yet.  You have NO idea how revolutionary adding the manual was to skating games back in the day.  We went from being able to pull off maybe a 4-5 combo to comboing the whole time from start to finish during H2H matchup.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Within the last 3-4 years yes.  It is basically Hampden Jr.  Pretty soon there's going to be trendy stuff from 29th street all the way down to Clavel. R House, Clavel, WC Harlan,  Parts and Labor, and a big apartment complex on 28th opened in that time.  I'm sure more trendy restaurants and bars are going to keep on coming since there's basically no space left in Hampden.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 21:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot twist, the Snowden is a double spy who secretly gave the Russians garbage intel and collected useful data from the Russians after being allowed in.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thai noodle soups at Mayuree Thai Tavern.

They don't have the late night noodles anymore, but every once in a while they'll still have them.  Completely different than pho or ramen.  


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 17:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably costs 200x less than trying to develop a machine that'll do it.  They also already display a high degree of intelligence too and have been engineered by nature over millions of years to be good at swimming under water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 06:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And just wait until that have autonomous piloting in order to make the decisions quicker.  It'll be skynet.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 04:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, and results were pretty interesting:

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1900035/

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3203784/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 14:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, they're trying!  For example, people have been trying for years to make cancer vaccines against the Thomsen Freidenreich antigen which is a sugar.  They haven't been quite successful yet, but they're trying.  People have also been trying for years to develop things like antibodies against cancer specific glycan epitopes (these are called tumor associated carbohydrate antigens or TACAs for short in case you want to do more research).  Success has been fleeting, but I've seen some encouraging progress that has been presented at recent cancer conferences. 

Making vaccines and antibodies against glycans *is hard*, which is why people haven't been quite successful yet.  I suspect it also has to do with the same reasons why protein people are also often unsuccessful--they often ignore the carbohydrate covering of their proteins--and in a similar manner, carbohydrate people tend to think the sugar is more important.  What needs to probably be tried are more efforts aimed at developing antibodies and therapies that are able to recognize *both* the carbohydrate AND the protein parts of a molecule that can be used to target cancer.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 14:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question.  If O-GlcNAc is so important it should have feed back controls, right?  In fact this is definitely true.  An enzyme known as GFAT is known as the 'gateway' into the HBP; it is feedback inhibited by UDP-GlcNAc production, so yes, in theory there should be a cap on the amount of UDP-GlcNAc a cell produces so that it doesn't start become 'sick'.  In reality, a lot of stuff goes wrong.  For example, in cancer we known that total global levels of O-GlcNAc are consistently overabundant.  Why doesn't the feedback mechanism work anymore?  In other disaeses such as diabetes and Alzheimer's, patterns of O-GlcNAcylation are also different, which seems to suggest that the flux through the HBP is probably perturbed (why?). 

Has increased sugar consumption been shown to alter patterns of O-GlcNAcylation?  People are trying!  For example, here's a reference where they fed mice a 'western diet' and observed changes in O-GlcNAcylation in the rat heart:

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3372663/

Clearly more work needs to be done, but what seems to be emerging is that yes, in fact, diet can influence patterns of O-GlcNAcylation and this goes on to do things like affect epigenetics, gene expression, etc. etc. since all of the proteins involved are modified by O-GlcNAc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 14:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biochemistry is never that easy.  Imagine biochemical networks as a network of pipes, with each pipe having a different diameter.  What's regulating a large aspect of life would be akin to 'how fast' or 'how much' water would be flowing through the pipes.  Think of it like an electronic circuit.  What's important are the amounts of electrons flowing through it.  But it isn't as simple as fixing an amount for use.  A cell has to be able to adapt to stresses and the environment.  What a cell will do is start changing the diameters of the pipes in order to regulate 'the flow' going through the network.  A cell is a mindblowing and an extraordinarily engineered machine with all sorts of feedback control mechanisms to turn on and off pathways in order to regulate flux.  For example, why doesn't your AC constantly stay on as it cools down your house?  It has a feedback control mechanism to say 'enough is enough' when your house is cool enough.  Similarly, a cell has control mechanism to regulate and change the amount of O-GlcNAc it needs in order to respond to stress--more O-glcnac is generally 'protective' during times of accute stress, for example. 

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2782048/ (for the 2-5% claim) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 14:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good questions!  And they're all big reasons why sugar biology and O-GlcNAc are so tough to crack.

1.) you can IP using O-GlcNAc recognizing antibodies (and the the reverse IP as well) in order to see if your protein of interest is O-GlcNAcylated.  Beware, not easy and has given me many gray hairs over the years!  Other than that, there really aren't good ways to do it outside of extremely specialized mass spectrometry techniques that most labs  can't do.  

2.)  No, no known consensus motifs exist that can predict sites of O-GlcNAcylation.  All we know is that it occurs on SER/THR residues.  There are some hypotheses floating out there trying to explain why and where it will occur, but nothing solid yet (again why it's so hard to understand). 

3.) No, the O-GlcNAc modification is an intracellular sugar modification (like phosphorylation).  It is probably on most, if not all proteins at some point in their life (this includes all intracellular proteins).  Nearly all transcription factors are O-GlcNAcylated (e.g. big ones in cancer such as MYC has its half life regulated by O-GlcNAc and the entire core machinery that regulates stem cell differentiation is regulated by O-GlcNAc, for example).  

4.) Something they're working on, but nothing exists yet AFAIK.  The only way is look through the literature yourself.  I believe some websites for proteins might list 'predicited sites for O-GlcNacylation', but that's about it.  It tends to be a big deal if you prove a new protein is O-glcnacylated since the work is probably novel, so if it interests you go ahead and try!  There's a good chance you'll get a decent publication out of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 05:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lame answer: everything in moderation.  

I know, I know, not what you're looking for, but there's a big, big leap from understanding what happens at the molecular level to making macro level guidelines for people, but that's certainly an active area of research (albeit one I don't really keep dibs on).  But without question, we know a bad diet high in sugar can lead to things like diabetes and and pre-diabetes.  Diabetics are more at risk for developing heart disease.  What I can not say is how much sugar or what types of sugars a person can and can not consume.  I'm not a epidemiologist or anything, but how prevalent was heart disease an diabetes back when our grandparents were young?  How about before sugar became widely and cheaply available?  Did ancient civilizations avoid grain?  I tend to think not, as bread has been a staple for millennia for many civilizations.  Even to this day, countries with lower rates of diabetes and hear disease still consume huge quantities of staples like rice.  

We are increasing our understanding between cellular/tissue abnormal sugar consumption and the development of heart disease, but the other thing we don't understand well is what gets a cell or tissue to consume sugar abnormally in the first place?  Too much sugar in the diet? Probably, but not the only answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 05:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely.  Heh, and what's also true is that the 'yin-yang' hypothesis also isn't true, but people often like to describe it that way for lay people.  One case never discussed:  What if O-GlcNAc has its own very unique sites for addition?  In reality that's true.  Consider how many combinatorial possibilities there are now with a single protein in this hypothetical example--2 sites where O-GlcNAc/phosho cycle, another site where only phospho is added, and another 2 sites where only O-GlcNAc is added.  I'll let you do the math, but the number is astounding!  Certainly much more complex than a simple yin-yang description.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 05:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting idea--that humans do not contain hydroxylated sialic acids while most other mammals do.  When we consume things like red meat we break down mammalian tissue and release things like Neu5gc.  Neu5Gc is then uptaken by our cells and appears on the surfaces of our cells, and because it is unnatural for humans, it supposedly elicits an immune/inflammatory response.  Such is the reason why Varki has hypothesized a diet rich in animal products is linked to the development of chronic inflammation and/or things like colon cancer.  It's interesting for sure, but there's still a lot more work that needs to be done.  Just keep in mind sugars are rapidly turned over, so while we may incorporate Neu5Gc onto our cells, it isn't there permanently.  For now, just keep things to a moderation. 


BTW, the much more interesting thing wrt to Neu5gc, imo, is how might possibly explain the evolution of the human brain and the development of our intelligence.  On this topic Varki has some very, very interesting hypotheses.  The ends of synapses of neurons are heavily decorated with sialic acids (NeuNAc).  By remodeling the levels of sialic acids on synapses, neurons are able to 'rip apart' and reconnect in different ways--in otherwords sialic acids are heavily heavily involved in the molecular physiology of neuronal plasticity.  But what Varki discovered is that the gene that allows primates to synthesize Neu5gc (CMAH) mutated *right around the time we started evolving from apes into homo sapiens*; the mutation completely inactivated CMAH and no longer allowed us to produce Neu5Gc.  And because sialic acids are so heavily invovled in learning, memory, and the development of our brain (how does Neu5gc vs NeuNAc change this process?), Varki has hypothesized that the mutation of the CMAH gene helped us become what we are today.  Very interesting to readup on:

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK210017/

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4198446/

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/11786991 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 05:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say equally, if not more complex.  Basically no one knows how to decipher the 'O-GlcNAc code' (see here):

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3783028/


What are we really asking?  We know O-Glcnac regulates has the potential to regulate the entire physiology of genetic output and proteome activity.  Basically what's happening is that a cell is dynamically responding 'to the amount of sugar and metabolites being pushed through to make UDP-GlcNAc'.  That concept is flux.  Based on the flux of a sugar, can we not only predict WHAT proteins might change O-GlcNAcylation states, but exactly WHERE on the those proteins O-GlcNAcylation might change.  For example, during starvation protein X might have no O-GlcNAc while in a fed state protein X has 3 O-GlcNAcs which will help it turn 'off'.  However duringa starvation state protein Y might have 2 O-GlcNAcs.  During a fed state it might now have 3.  But more importantly, we need to know exactly where those O-GlcNAcs are being added and removed--maybe they're at a site that blocks another molecule from docking, maybe it is on a distant site of protein that changes the shape of the protein and the way it entirely behaves.  Maybe O-GlcNAc signals for the protein to be sent for desctruction.  The list goes on.  Understanding how metablic flux of sugar regulates proteome o-glcnacylation AND the physiological consequences is something that's vastly, vastly complex and something no one understands.  It is like solving a massive quantum mechanics puzzle.  I mean we know 'the amount of sugars going through biochemical pathways' regulates the patterns of O-GlcNAc we see, but there's no predictive formula that'll allow us to tell what will change and what will happen.  In short, cracking the O-GlcNAc code is a non-deterministic problem.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 05:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohhhhhhhhhhhh boy, huge topic.  You bet we do!  One of the first hallmarks every described with respect to cancer was the discovery that cancer cells and tissues have 'abnormal' types of sugar coatings on their surface.  What does 'abnormal' mean?  Well, if you were to molecularly analyze the surfaces of cancer cells for the sugar portions only, you'd find extremely strange patterns, such as sugar glycans that only are known to appear during a stage like early development.  Why do they all of the sudden appear then in cancer?  You'll also find sugar patterns that shouldn't normally be found in the type of tissue where the cancer is (e.g. a type of sugar pattern that is only found normally in the brain is now all of the sudden appearing in breast tissue that is cancerous).  Long story short, we can tell a cell is sick by looking at the patterns of sugars on its surface.  

And how might this assist cancer cell growth?  There's a lot of reasons why sugar coatings can help cancer cells grow, but I'll only focus on the topic of immune evasion since immuno oncology and immuno therapy is so hot right now.  A type of sugar known as 'sialic acid' (my screen name! ) is often found to be overabundant on cancer--again, one of the first things we ever discovered about cancer.  Many, many years later, a scientist at UCSD by the name of Ajit Varki made the discovery that there are special receptors on immune cells called sialic acid immunoglobulin type lectins (SIGLECs for short).  When SIGLECs on immune cells bind to sialic acid the immune cells are basically 'turned off'.  In this way, the overabundance of sialic acids on the surfaces of cancer are probably helping the tumor to grow and avoid immune detection because of the SIGLEC-sialic acid interaction.  There are tons of papers out there on this, search for Varki.  Start with the book chapter on Sialic Acids and Siglecs here as well as the references below:

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK1920/

http://www.nature.com/nri/journal/v14/n10/full/nri3737.html (if you have academic access)

http://journal.frontiersin.org/article/10.3389/fonc.2014.00028/full
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 04:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, here's an entire textbook for free!

http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK1908/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 04:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sugar biologist here.  The role of sugar and carbohydrates in disease has started to gain traction and there is a small, but loud community of us 'glycobiologists' that is increasingly growing in number as time goes by.  In fact, MIT once predicted that sugar biology will revolutionize medicine in the 21st century, because it may be a big piece of the puzzle towards our understanding of many complex diseases, the root causes of which we still haven't really understood well nearly 2 decades after we've cracked the genetic code.  

What do you think of when you think of the word 'sugar'? You're probably thinking of table sugar and high fructose corn syrup, both of which you consume in food.  You might also be thinking about glucose, the key energy carrying molecule every cell in your body burns for energy in order to maintain life.  For the longest time that's what most people in the scientific community thought when they thought about 'sugars'.  But there's a different  and an extremely important role sugars play in regulating life.  After a huge number of proteins are made that are encoded in your genome, they are modified further by a theoretically massive set of sugars.  This entire set of sugars in known as 'the glycome' (akin to the genome, proteome, metabolome, etc.).  Just how big is the glycome?  Well, many scientists have reported that it is theoretically 'many orders of magnitude more complex than the genome' and that it is 'one of the most complex entities known in nature'.  When you think about it, taking the genetic products and modifying them with sugars is almost like a quantum leap in complexity for life.  Genetics and DNA would be tantamount to our understanding of classical physics.  Just as classical physics can't explain all physical phenomena, we now know that a huge portion of the complexity of life exists outside what can be coded directly in DNA (for example the glycome).  The study of sugars, their modifications on proteins, and the functional role that this has could be considered like the quantum revolution that physicists needed to explain the nature of fundamental particles and small scale stuff.  


But there's one type of modification by sugar that's quite special.  Back many decades ago two scientists by the names of Krebs and Fischer discovered that proteins were modified by phosphorylation (phospho groups) to regulate their activity.  To simply put it (in reality it isn't this simple), when a protein is phosphorylated it is 'turned on', and when it is dephosphorylated it is 'turned off'.  Kinases are enzymes that add phospho groups and phosphatases are enzymes that remove phospho groups from proteins.  There are literally hundreds and hundreds, if not thousands, of different kinases and phosphatases that exist in order to regulate the phosphorylation states of all proteins in a cell.  For their work, Krebs and Fischer won the Nobel Prize in medicine (to illustrate the importance of protein physiology regulation).  However, nearly two decades later after Krebs and Fischer discovered protein phosphorylation, scientists soon discovered that hundreds and thousands of proteins inside of a cell were also modified by a single sugar known as N-acetylglucosamine (GlcNAc for short).  This observation was later dubbed 'the O-GlcNAc modificaiton' and 'O-GlcNAc'.   After a ton of grunt work, scientists were able to show that what really, really made O-GlcNAc interesting was that O-GlcNAc appeared to modify proteins often times *at the same exact sites* where proteins were phosphorylated (remember how important that was for Krebs and Fischer?).  And what really, really, really, really made the addition of O-GlcNAc super duper special was the discovery that only 2 enzymes regulate the addition and removal of O-GlcNAc to proteins--an enzyme known as OGT (which adds it) and OGA (which removes it).  That's it!  Contrast that to the hundreds and thousands of different kinases and phosphatases that are needed to regulate the phosphorylation states of the proteome.  O-GlcNAc is much more conserved.  The importance of O-GlcNAcylation can not be overstated.  Think of O-GlcNAc as a 'cap' on the sites of proteins where they are phosphorylated.  In order to phosphorylate and turn proteins 'on', you must first remove O-GlcNAc to clear the site for modification by phosphorylation.   In otherwords, O-GlcNAc is also a master regulator of the entire physiology of proteins inside of a cell.  It is like the yin-to-the-yang of phosphorylation.  This observation has now been called the 'Yin-Yang hypothesis'.  After 30 years of more work, we are increasingly understanding the importance of O-GlcNAc.  For example, nearly every type of protein involved in epigenetic modifications and regulation is now known to be modified by O-GlcNAc.  Nearly every type of transcription factor (proteins that help to turn on a gene) are modified by O-GlcNAc.  RNA polymerase II, the main protein that decodes your DNA, is heavily O-GlcNAcylated and doesn't work right unless it is coated with sugar.  Histones (the proteins that your DNA wraps around) are modified by O-GlcNAc, meaning O-GlcNAc is directly part of the histone code.   In fact, if you were to stain your chromatin (basically your DNA) for O-GlcNAc it would light up like a Christmas tree, meaning your DNA mass and all of the proteins on it are absolutely covered in sugar. O-GlcNAc also regulates cytoskeletal structure and dynamics, many proteins inside of the mitochondria, mitochondrial cellular mechanics, modifies the proteins that regulate circadian rhythm.....the list goes on.  

So what does this have to do with 'sugar consumption' and heart disease?  Well, what I didn't discuss yet is *where* exactly the GlcNAc that is used for the O-GlcNAc modification comes from.  When most people think of glucose metabolism, they think about using it for glycolysis and oxidative phoshorylation--i.e. using glucose as fuel for a cell.  However, what many scientists outside of glycobiology and biochemistry and the general lay public might not have ever heard of is the fact that roughly 2-5% of all glucose turn over is shunted away from glycolysis and energy production and down a biochemical pathway known as the hexosamine biosynthetic pathway (HBP).   The HBP does several transformations to glucose, but ultimately it produces a very special metabolite known as UDP-GlcNAc.  UDP-GlcNAc is THE substrate for OGT (remember that's the enzyme that adds O-GlcNAc to proteins).   While 2-5% of glucose shunting down the HBP doesn't seem like a lot, it really is because of the massive turn over rate of glucose that exists in a cell.  In fact, I've repeatedly been told that next to ATP, UDP-GlcNAc is the next most abundant molecule found in a cell (further illustrating its importance).   If you can finally see the big picture here, we are, for the first time linking carbohydrate metabolism, carbohydrate uptake, carbohydrate fluxes, and 'sugar consumption' directly to virtually every single aspect of physiology inside of a cell since the O-GlcNAc modification modifies so many things like what was discussed above.  The link is O-GlcNAc and the HBP with glucose.    More directly, how is this relevant to heart disease?   There are many, many things to discuss on this topic alone, but I will defer to the abstracts posted here to get you started:

**Cardiac O-GlcNAc signaling is increased in hypertrophy and heart failure.**  
http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22128088


**O-linked -N-acetylglucosamine transferase (OGT) is indispensable in the failing heart**:

http://www.pnas.org/content/107/41/17797.full

**Spliced X-box Binding Protein 1 Couples the Unfolded Protein Response to Hexosamine Biosynthetic Pathway**
http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3959665/


**Protein O-GlcNAcylation and Cardiovascular (Patho)physiology**

http://www.jbc.org/content/289/50/34449.full

The point is just to explain to you exactly how sugar might, and is probably involved in the development of heart disease.  
We've long observed that diabetic patients have higher risks for things like heart disease and cardiomyopathy.  What do diabetics have?  Of course they have dysregulated sugar metabolism which will probably go on to aversely affect normal O-GlcNAc cycling.  Maybe O-GlcNAc is the reason why diabetics are more prone to heart disease.  In fact, many major disease that affect millions of people every year such as cancer, diabetes, and even Alzheimer's are all associated with dysregulated sugar metabolism and abnormal patterns of O-GlcNAc.  Now you might have some inkling as to how sugar metabolism is, probably, in some way involved in the development and progression of many major diseases.  


TL; DR:  Scientists discovered that sugars play an important role in regulating how proteins work.  The sugar that does that comes from glucose and glucose consumption.  The links between abnormal 'sugar uptake' and conditions like heart disease are becoming increasingly clear.  The science on the molecular level is there! 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A little worried about the recent uptick in violent crime in CV. What can I do to reasonably protect my wife, who is 5'1" and 100 lbs, when she has to walk home by herself from work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Jan. to the end of July '16 there were 16 robberies and assaults with either a knife or gun in CV.  Within just the past month (Aug.) up to now, there have been approx. 7 assaults and robberies in CV committed with a gun and/or knife.  The level of crime which originally took 3 months  to reach from the rate of crime during Jan. - July of this year has been achieved in a little less than 1.5 months now from Aug-Sept., meaning the rate of crime in CV appears to be increasing.  Just this week a man was accosted by a group of individuals who had multiple guns and a knife at 29th and St. Paul.  He was stabbed.  Another guy was also robbed at 30th and St. Paul/Calvert by a suspect with a metal rod for a weapon.  The first incident took place at 5 freakin' o'clock in the afternoon, and the other took place at 140 PM--both occurred in broad daylight and not in areas anywhere where it would be considered 'unsafe' and against common sense to go.  It is starting to worry me that criminals are becoming more brazen in and around CV.  What can I do or give to protect my wife who I'm starting to worry about?  I can't be there when she walks home from work from the stop since I'm still at work.  Obviously guns, mace/pepper spray, knives are illegal.  What else should I or she do?  She has to walk all in the areas where violent crime has recently been reported.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck man, pets and their medical care.  My cats have literally been to vet 4-6 times *each* within their first 1.5 years of life. I literally haven't been to the doctor in almost 12 years and I have insurance.  I mean I know I have to go because I have some skin conditions, but fuck if I'm paying a doctor a couple hundred dollars to see me for 5 minutes and prescribe a cream.  But if my two little guys need it, somehow I never mind paying.  Kinda absurd if you think about it.  My pets literally get better medical care than I do.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got stung by a catepillar that looked sorta like that in New Orleans.  HOLY FUCK those bastards hurt like a mofo *for hours*.  Worst bugs ever created.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 14:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pruneface.  Still remember from the McDonald's game they had back in the day when that movie came out.  It was similar to the monopoly thing they had/have IIRC.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man, PG movies back in my day were a lot more violent than I remember now that I've re-watched Dick Tracy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 02:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I'm a bit dyslexic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 00:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna be a llllllllllllllooooooooooong season for Dez owners with a rookie QB at the helm.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, ivory is used in traditional 'medicines' too, just like rhino tusks:

http://www.nytimes.com/2013/03/02/world/asia/an-illicit-trail-of-african-ivory-to-china.html?_r=0

From the article: *Ivory is etched deeply into the Chinese identity. Popular lore tells of emperors who believed ivory chopsticks would change color upon contact with poisoned food. In Chinese medicine, ivory powder is said to purge toxins from the body and give a luminous complexion. As part of its public relations effort to legitimize the trade, the government in 2006 added ivory carving to its official Intangible Cultural Heritage register, along with traditional opera, kung fu and acupuncture.*


I'm just wondering if you can genetically engineer a tusk so that if consumed, it'll poison you.  It would even make artwork more hazardous, as ivory dust particles would also be toxic if breathed in while making art if someone was using a burr or something to shape an art piece.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of ivory is used in art and jewelry making.  But it is also used in medicines after being ground up.  That's especially true for Rhino horns (rhino horn is NOT ivory though).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if there's a way to genetically engineer elephants, rhinos, etc so that the tusks produce poison that make it virtually impossible to purify out.  Consume a tusk?  You die.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Autrian ethologist Karl von Frisch was nominated for the Noble Prize in 1927 for his work on deciphering the Waggle dance of honey bees. Using the Waggle dance, a bee communicates to other worker bees the direction and distance of the most productive flowers using the angle of the sun. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 17:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Gregorian Epact is the number of days between Jan. 1st and the previous new moon. It is used to figure out the date of Easter and uses the following formulas: GN = (year mod 19) +1, JE = (11*GN -1) mod 30, S = (3*century)/4, L = (8*century+5)/25. Gregorian Epact = JE - S + L + 8. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 07:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 04:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad YouTube exists. No way I'd spend 25 hours setting something like that up.  Ill let someone else do it and watch the 3 min video without having to cleanup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 02:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peyton Manning's net worth includes $228 million in salary and bonuses earned since the Indianapolis Colts signed him in 1998. The star quarterback has also earned an estimated $157 million for endorsement deals. Taxes subtract $172 million from the Peyton Manning net worth total.Feb 7, 2016



Wow, so basically Manning has been working for years for free doing advertisements so that the Federal government can take his money.  After all those ads, the government still gets to take another $15 million from his sports salary.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a horrible shit movie.  And it was my childhood.  We had horrible shit like this, 3 ninjas kick back, Beverly hills ninja, Side Kicks.....the list goes on,but we were obsessed with ninjas in the 90s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Baltimore's beloved 'Mr. Trash Wheel' has removed over 350 tons of trash, which equates to 200,000 bottles, 173,000 potato chip bags, and 6.7 million cigarette butts, from the Baltimore Inner Harbor in as little as 18 months. He is even a Redditor! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 20:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been following this guy's post for years:

http://www.protocol-online.org/forums/topic/6014-rt-pcr-primer-design-guide-how-to-check-gene-structure-and-design-the-primer/?hl=%2Bdesign+%2Bprimers

It's a little dated so some of the links might not still work, but just search for the tools that are similar.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 19:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BTW if Cutco is capable of making a perfectly decent knife like many claim on here, then why the fuck don't they just run a legitimate business and try to break into the mainstream market where their products can be sold normally like at Macy's, Bed Bath and Beyond, etc? Why ruin your image with such a shitty sales arm attached to your product? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know people that own restaurants.  They pay their wok chefs $36k per year.  To wok.  Why spend all of the time doing science and even going to college on student loan debt in order to get paid less than or equal to a wok chef?  Finance is easier than say, physics, and you can make $70k right out of the gate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50-60 for major alterations is pretty normal.  I hate to say it, but the easiest way to save money in the long run is to buy a suit that fits the way you want it to as close as possible in the first place. 

Dmitry did an amazing job for me.  

http://yourtailorforlife.com/


It was about $130 total for major work:  1.) pair of jeans hemmed 2.) suit jack sleeves shortened  3.) jacket body shorted  4.) suit pants hemmed 5.) crotch fixed  6.) leg slimmed and tapered.  

You get what you pay for, especially for something like tailoring.  Maybe the amount of alterations you'll need will be less than what I needed, but that gives you an idea of his prices.  Turn around time was 2 days IIRC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
