<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7081</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-31 17:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I please share this in my Gaming Mommies Play D D Facebook group? We have several people looking for a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 23:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I attend a UU church and we are forming a CUUPS (Covenant of Unitarian Universalist Pagans) group. I was missing the same things from "church" after 18 years as a mostly solitary Pagan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 01:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are a wordsmith, my friend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 23:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for sharing that album. Very lovely and inspiring artwork! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 01:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been considering this. I have actually started doing erotica "warm-up pages" before I work on my main project. Thanks for the info in this thread, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 05:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the suggestions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Kickstarter to fund editing of my book series is in progress! I am looking for tips on how and where to get Backers from those who have been successful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 23:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just over a week into my Kickstarter to fund professional editing for my existing books and the upcoming third. I have had some generous backers, but honestly thought I would $1-$5 my way into funding. That is not happening. I would be grateful for tips, trips, and ideas about drumming up interest. [HERE](http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1003911666/the-half-realm-book-iii-through-the-veil) is the link to the Kickstarter. Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 23:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is how I'm working with my editor. Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 21:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is genius! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 20:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have spent years picking Faery elements out of various Celtic Pagan traditions. It is time consuming, but it's the best way to find what speaks to you in my opinion. I got a lot of good info from [Faery Wicca by Kisma Stepanich](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/576122.Faery_Wicca_Book_1), that might be a good starting point for you. Brightest Blessings

*EDIT she has had issues with plagiarism, I have heard, but again I pick and choose what I find helpful, take with a grain of salt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got brave and sent out a press release about my books and my Kickstarter! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 17:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 15:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sierra Vista Herald put my story in the Tempo entertainment magazine today!
[YAY!](http://www.svherald.com/content/submitted/2014/01/15/365926) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 20:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't really read it without a subscription, but [HERE](http://elwoodpublishing.com/editionviewer/?Edition=36147b81-56da-4c2e-b317-d0067ca96f2c) is the link to the 1st article in my hometown paper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today Show NoPoo story. Big surprise, they all acted disgusted and gave no real facts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 18:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 16:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just added it. That was my feeling on it. I was incredibly intimidated about publicity and promotion, and my first year sales reflect that. I am slowly getting the confidence and tools to improve both my books and my promotional plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 02:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sent an email with my press release and attached some pics of myself and my book covers to the papers. They were forwarded to a reporter in one case(small paper), the entertainment editor in another (larger paper) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dear fellow /r/fantasywriters, do not be afraid to send out press releases to local papers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 22:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used a Press Release template I found on Google to write up a quick package to promote my books and my Kickstarter. I will be in both my hometown (Indiana) paper as well as my current city paper (Arizona) this week. This is something I had no idea how to do last week, maybe took me an hour of work, and will put my name and titles in front of potentially 40,000+ pairs of eyes this week. For an absolute beginner and self published author, this is a priceless resource I wanted to share.
*EDIT
As requested [HERE](http://www.selfpub.info/templates/book-press-release-templates-and-examples.html) is the press release template I used. [HERE](http://thetoridouglas.com/press/) is my own press release that I sent to the newspapers. I plan to send it out to the local TV stations as well, and will keep you all posted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 20:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woman returns to her childhood farm to discover her "imaginary" friends are real and the door to Faery is in a tree in her horse pasture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 16:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! I really thank you for the honesty and tips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 23:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am really struggling with motivation right now. Every day that I get something out of my brain and onto the page is a victory. Stick with it. Best of luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 21:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the honesty and will be revising the video. In your opinion is it enough to fix the typo situation, or should I scrap it and re-record. I am, obviously, not good at this end of things.Thank you 
*edit, expanded the question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 21:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shared this on my Twitter! I can't wait to see more of the photos, they are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 03:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best. Title. EVAR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-13 03:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you, Steel! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 22:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you do! I am just so excited and grateful that something is coming from getting brave enough to publish. I have no illusions about the Bestseller list, but if I could make this series something to really shine, I would be happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 22:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am right there with you...so tempted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 22:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can certainly understand your frustration. If there is nothing you can do to resolve it, I hope you can make the indiegogo work. I am just so shocked that Amazon screwed you like that! Best of luck to you, I hope this does not make you give up on your project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 22:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate any and all support! I have not done a complete total, but I have had a few thousand books go out over the last year. Much of it has been from promotions (free or reduced price). I never expected to get even that much attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 22:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can see why I need an editor!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 22:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh wow, thanks for the catch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 20:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is crazy! I cannot imagine why and why they would not at least tell you why! Is there some kind of appeal process? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 20:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reposted on the correct thread and included links to sample chapters. Thanks so much for your interest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 20:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took me about 2 minutes to find music to use free and legally for my book trailers, why would they risk it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I launched a Kickstarter to fund editing of my fantasy series Through the Veil. Links to the Kickstarter and to writing samples inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 20:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! My name is Tori Douglas and I have self published the first two books of my fantasy series. I am currently working on the third, and have the chance to have them all professionally edited. I launched a Kickstarter campaign to fund it. Here is the link to my [Kickstarter](http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1003911666/the-half-realm-book-iii-through-the-veil), as well as sample chapters from my published work [Hole in the Stone](http://thetoridouglas.com/2014/01/11/sample-chapter-hole-in-the-stone/) and [The Gossamer Crown](http://thetoridouglas.com/2014/01/11/sample-chapter-the-gossamer-crown/). I hope you enjoy it and welcome any comments or critiques! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 20:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so sorry! Thanks so much, I will post it there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 03:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one has turned them in for it yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 03:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many internet hugs to you. You are not a bad parent, and you are not alone. Good on you that you reached out for help and support, even just from Reddit. There is some great advice in this thread that I wish my 8-years-ago-self could have read. Take care of you, sweetie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 02:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to make 2 calls to Amazon before I got verified, but it only took a little over a week. Just call customer service until you get someone who will chase it down for you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have self-published two fantasy novels, and am working on my third. I just launched a Kickstarter to fund editing of the series! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 02:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 00:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 working on my 4th. One was non-fiction, the others are my series Through the Veil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 00:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a huge step, bravo and good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 00:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just launched a Kickstarter to get my self-published fantasy novels professionally edited! Give it a look, and give it a share! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 22:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kickstarter for a published Fantasy series to get the editing it deserves! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 22:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 16:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different writing methods for different writers. Some people do well with high output that can later be distilled down, others need to dwell over their every word choice. Each writer needs to find what method makes them, personally, a better writer. I need a goal. I try to have a weekly wordcount goal, and I build some slack into it so I don't feel pressure to just pump out whatever. I do, however, need a goal. Wordcount goals work for me but I don't think it's a blanket answer to all writers to follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 04:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been trying to plug my books at least 1 new place a week along with weekly pimping on Facebook, twitter, or Pinterest. I am slowly seeing more sales. I recently sent an email to my local paper and they jumped on it, really looking forward to that! Send out some emails to local newspapers/radio/TV and see what response you get. Best of luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 01:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At my last trip to the local Target the "Plus Size" section had exactly 1 rack that was not maternity...less than impressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 00:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 23:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That made me very happy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 04:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is glorious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 03:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bravo!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 21:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you for the whole thing!!! Beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-27 02:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that snail is adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 23:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am Tori Douglas on Good Reads. Send me an invite! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 19:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-25 00:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That might be a little harder to convey in a photo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 23:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My school pics look like I am slowly getting a perm lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 23:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might not be relevant for you, but I used my own photos for my book covers. One non fiction, two fiction/fantasy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE not have curly hair as a little kid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 23:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hair was straight and fine until around 8 or 9, then got curlier and coarser every year until it was full on 3A/3B in my early teens. Just wondering who else had this experience? I wonder if my kids will follow this hair pattern? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FREE PROMO] Fantasy novel on Amazon. The Gossamer Crown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 03:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 03:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work SO hard to make sure my kids are not brats. I cannot stand this kind of thing and am right there with you on fearing the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 16:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [FREE Kindle download](http://www.amazon.com/Gossamer-Crown-Through-Veil-ebook/dp/B00H56U6PG/ref=la_B00GQJ1BKM_1_3?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1386601282 sr=1-3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Kindle] The Gossamer Crown by Tori Douglas (FREE 12/9-12/10) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 16:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Trailer for The Gossamer Crown. Book II Through the Veil. Link for FREE Kindle download (12/9-12/10) in comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 15:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Kindle] Hole in the Stone by Tori Douglas (FREE until 12/9/13) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 23:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 23:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Corrected link](http://www.amazon.com/Hole-Stone-Through-Veil-Douglas-ebook/dp/B00H4A650S/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1386455356 sr=8-1 keywords=hole+in+the+stone)
Thanks /u/Chtorrr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 23:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oops, Thanks so much
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FREE Kindle download of my fantasy novel Hole in the Stone today and tomorrow on Amazon!Please give it a read and leave me a review! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 16:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before Book II comes out on Monday, I am offering Hole in the Stone: Book I Through the Veil FREE for Kindle download this weekend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 23:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 06:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually put in a submission for it. Even if I don't get picked, still super excited for the series! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 03:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Congrats!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 01:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 02:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 02:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are all right there with you! Stay strong and grind it out. I took the weekend off due to family birthdays and getting back on it today was hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 15:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to see my Dad, who is in the final stage if Alzheimers, today. It is heart wrenching for me to see the man who used to be my Dad, and I cry most of the drive back home. But sometimes I catch him in a lucid moment, and he is so happy to see me and my kids. It is few and far between, but worth it when his face lights up and I can see the joy and understanding in his eyes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 01:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Midwestern girl now living in Southern Arizona, I love finding things like this. I have been here almost 2 years and I find something beautiful and interesting nearly every day. Thanks for sharing this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  Calling All Volunteers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 15:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  LEGO City Undercover: The Chase Begins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming Mommies  A Gaming Mommys View on GTA V </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked in the animal care field for 14 years as a vet tech, groomer etc. I had a dog bite put me in the hospital for a week and I went right back to work. It was asshole, entitled, "how can you do this to my dog" when they can't pay owners were the reason I had to get out of the field. I love animals, but could no longer take abuse from their owners. A dog could chew my arm off and I would still do my best to help them. Owners screaming at me over $$ or them thinking they know better than a vet or other professional who has dedicated their career to animals loses any fuck I had to give as soon as the attitude starts
edit, clarity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 20:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's your personal BoS, only you can answer that
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 20:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
MAKEDA, QUEEN OF SHEBA - THE QUEEN OF HEAVEN-THE VIRGIN WARRIOR QUEEN 

"Ancient moon priestesses were called virgins. "Virgin" meant not married, not belonging to a man-a woman who was "one-in-herself." The very word dervies from a Latin root meaning strength, force, skill; and was later applied to men: virle. Ishtar, Diana, Astarte, Isis were all called virgin, which did not refer to sexual chasity, but sexual independence. And all great culture heroes of the past, mythic or historic, were said to be born of virigin mothers: Marduk, Gilgamesh, Buddha, Osiris, Dionysus, Genghis Khan, Jesus-they were all affirmed as sons of the Great Mother, of the Original Onem their worldly power deriving from her. When the Hebrews used the word, and in the original Aramaic, it meant "maiden" or "young woman," with no connotations of sexual chasity. But later Christian translators could not conceive of the "Virgin Mary" as a woman of independent sexuality, needless to say; they distorted the meaning into sexually pure, chaste, never touched. When Joan of Arc, with her witch coven associations, was called La Pucelle-"The Maiden," "the Virgin"- the word retained some of its original pagan sesne of a strong and independent woman."

The Great Cosmic Mother: Rediscovering the Religion of the Earth
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 20:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> other than it being cited on the web, no. All my books are in storage right now. I found the 3 references to it above in a google search for "pagan definition of virgin". If I come across anything else useful, I will post it here for you
EDIT...[HERE](http://pagancelibacy.wordpress.com/2010/08/03/not-like-a-virgin/) is a blog post on this issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 17:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it is better in a Christian dominated society to not allow women power over her own sexuality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 17:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my books packed up right now, but here are some articles that cite this
[*Blog*](http://tardislady.wordpress.com/2012/11/04/virginity-the-real-meaning-in-the-celtic-world-the-pagan-times/)
[*Book excerpt*](http://books.google.com/books?id=DYV7RdFnH_AC pg=PA80 lpg=PA80 dq=celtic+concept+of+virgin source=bl ots=lL-wJT4Omz sig=JChfvUsADos5txhHqeIOHEpCtfk hl=en sa=X ei=PIxNUpaoO-ahiQLOyYG4Ag ved=0CE4Q6AEwBQ#v=onepage q=celtic%20concept%20of%20virgin f=false)
[*Arianfhod*](http://feminismandreligion.com/2013/02/23/arianrhod-celtic-star-goddess-2/)
I came across this concept of virginity early in my Pagan journey (1999) and it has been an important distinction in the term "virgin" for me ever since. I hope this helps, and feel free to PM me if I can help in any way. We as women, especially ones dealing with the lifelong effects of abuse, need every spiritual tool we can find. Brightest Blessings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 23:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a thought, an ancient definition of "virgin" is a woman of her own worth, not belonging to a husband or father, and therefore "owned" by no man. This made her sexually free. The concept of a virgin woman being sexually pure became the primary definition with the rise of Christianity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 04:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband gets taken back to court regularly to have his support raised because Baby-Mama has not had a job in about 7 years and refuses to get one. A few years ago a judge actually told her in court while she was bitching about needing more $$ "It is not his job to pay for your life. It is his job to support his daughter. If your only income is his support that is your choice and maybe we should discuss custody instead" . This was just before she got busted for Welfare fraud... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 21:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sorcery is this! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 20:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a former foster, then owner of an abused Whippet mix who was literally afraid to eat for years and looked starved most of his life, that was delicious and made my day. Good on you for the work you do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 19:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked at an animal shelter years ago that had a crematorium that offered cremation for deceased pets as income for the shelter. We had to smash the bone fragments up with a hammer before putting them in the urn for the pet owner...good times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-11 18:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are in the midst of a major life change into permanent RV living for at least the next 1-2 years, followed by buying land cash and building some type of alternative house( i.e. Earthship, yurt, Tiny Houses etc). I am getting a lot of well meaning questioning and suggested alternatives to moving into the RV. Thank you for posting this. I have been sticking to the mantra "It's definitely not for everyone, but it's for us." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 07:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hence the need to crowd source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-10 06:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Steve Jobs is crowd sourcing ideas now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 05:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tombstone. They cleaned up Wyatt and Josephine quite a bit. Source: I live near Tombstone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 22:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband was raised in a racist family. It took years of being in the world, outside of our whitebread small town, to get enough life experience with people he was raised to see as inferior or wrong to counteract that. Even now, years later, he is hyper-sensitive that he is being unintentionally racist. It takes a long time to overcome those dyed in the wool, knee jerk reactions, but the fact that you are aware it is not a good way to be and want to correct it speaks volumes. Go easy on yourself.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 18:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 2 little girls who woke up one night to a spider the size of my 8 yr olds hand on the ceiling above their bed. (we live in Arizona, out in the desert) ALL spiders now have to die and their mangled corpses have to be shown as evidence of their death or they cannot sleep. I like sleep more than spiders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-04 18:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are beginning our transition to Tiny House also in Arizona. We are rebuilding an RV into a more Tiny House-ish design,  then plan to build a Tiny House from the trailer up starting in the next year. We plan to plumb both. 

We are going to live on my parents land and hook into their water and electric while building, then find a piece of land to park them on. We want a well on our land, or at least in an area one can be drilled. We live in an area with aquifer access. Look up a map of aquifers for the state/area your land is in. [HERE](http://web.mit.edu/12.000/www/m2012/finalwebsite/problem/groundwater.shtml) is a link to the MIT aquifer map of the US. I hope this helps you decide  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 18:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Dad's Shih Tzu used to attack the TV during animal documentaries, but only horses and lions. I guess the other animals were cool, but lions and horses had to die. You could hear the thunk when her little face hit the tube (this was years ago, no flat screens were injured in these proceedings) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
