<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7377</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 02:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second this. Been running it on my latest build and really happy with what it produces. Plus I don't have to share all my stats with Google anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 02:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't use the software. I imagine it will get fixed shortly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 01:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beats by Dre are god-awful if sound quality is important to you. Go pick up a set of [Klipsch S4As](http://www.androidcentral.com/review-klipsch-s4a-earbuds-and-companion-android-app). You will love them.

[Amazon has them for $70](http://www.amazon.com/Klipsch-Image-S4A-In-Ear-Headphones/dp/B008VHHYLW/ref=pd_sim_e_2?ie=UTF8 refRID=06M9RE2Q93TDX6HPE9JT). You may be able to find them cheaper elsewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 20:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently they give you [a smoother ride](http://www.cyclingnews.com/reviews/photos/review-pinarello-dogma-65-1-think-2%202%20think/241481). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summer bliss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 19:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 18:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Giving the estimated time 'til it hits your wallet is a great feature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 18:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how it gives you an estimate of how long each option will take. Nice job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 08:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's not my build so doesn't hurt my feelings ;-) This sub does seem to have a pretty percentage of douchey snobs tho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 07:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll mention that to my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 07:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  * Full Shimano Ultegra gruppo
 * Zipp Carbon handlebars

(will find out the rest of it)

Total weight 16lbs including pedals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 07:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wheels were also bought direct from China. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 00:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's what $2500 now gets you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 23:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 01:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get in touch. I can help you out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vancouver "immediately shows that its inhabitants only intention is to gain wealth as rapidly as possible. They set up their lives exclusively in accordance with this task, giving no thought to beauty or comfort." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 18:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 18:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a similar note I have an old [Zotac MAG](http://www.zotacusa.com/mag-hd-nd01.html) that I was considering doing this to. Can anyone point to me to a howto to set this up under Linux (Debian preferably)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 16:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add in [his views on Snowden](http://www.businessinsider.com/marc-andreessen-snowden-is-a-traitor-2014-6) and he is without a doubt one of the biggest douches alive today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pipeline prospects take a hit as Supreme Court grants land title to B.C. First Nation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 01:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pipeline prospects take a hit as Supreme Court grants land title to B.C. First Nation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 01:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 16:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what would that make Rob Ford? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 22:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understandinbg is that Bitpay already has all of their AML/KYC procedues in place so this doesn't affect them in the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 21:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And some of use believe there will be a phase III when fiat no longer matters and the whole conversion from digital currencies into fiat will be nothing but a distant memory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 21:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the first 4 years of bitcoin's existence they were created at the rate of 50XBT roughly every 10 minutes. That ended at the end of November last year when the 'reward' (rate of creation) was halved to 25XBT roughly every 10 minutes. The next halving with occur sometime in 2016 wherein the reward will drop to 12.5XBT approximately every 10 minutes.... and so on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 23:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been using this a lot lately - great tool. Good to learn that it's not yet complete for Mysql 5.5. Wonder how far off that is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 23:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summer of 2000 with Debian Potato. Same reason as /u/Linuxllc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 18:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Eligius reference is to the fact that they refuse to process SatoshiDice transactions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 04:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [There's a collection here - various stuff](http://www.diydharma.org/divine-meditations). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 16:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Larger trips (from downtown) include Steveston (60km return direct, 120km return the long way), Horseshoe Bay (60km return), Deep Cove (50-60km return), or a UBC circuit (40km). Or perhaps some hil climbing - SFU, Cypress or Seymour (in ascending level of difficulty).

And don't ignore [Strava's global heat map](http://labs.strava.com/heatmap/#10/-123.17760/49.31128/blue/bike) - it's good for showing where the more competitive riders prefer to ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 01:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of these studies are only for their effects on _humans_. Please point me to some studies that examine the potential ecosystem disruption and/or toxicity effects on non-human plants and animals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 00:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that some are radically changing things. Perhaps that's not the case with these bananas but they would be the exception rather than the rule with regards to GMO's thus far. 
Furthermore, can you please point me to a definitive, peer-reviewed study to show that expressing genes to produce more vitamin A won't also make it generate toxic byproducts for some other species? I pretty sure you can't for the simple reason that Vitamin A itself is almost certainly a toxic substance for some other living thing. Please note that I'm not against research into genetic engineering - that horse is well out of the barn. I'm merely opposed to a narrow, anthopocentric notion of "harmless". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 23:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what about all the other species that may end of up feeding on them or otherwise interacting with them - have they been tested for their interactions with all bacteria, insects, plants and animals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 19:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How exactly do they test the effect that mass release will have upon an ecosystem? I'm not being sarcastic - I'm genuinely interested. And I'm all down with utilitarian calculus. - I just need to be convinced that there are studies being conducted that consider the ecosystem as a whole, rather than just a few narrow studies focussing on a few variables. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 16:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A far bigger problem is that people seem to think that they can introduce new plants into ecosystems without unintended consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 02:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [http://www.diydharma.org/how-meditate](http://www.diydharma.org/how-meditate) is a great guide. Thousands of dharma talks, guided meditations, etc on the site too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 02:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just exploring the border ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 01:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are bike lanes not "...the making, modification, usage, and knowledge of tools, machines, techniques, crafts, systems, and methods of organization, in order to solve a problem, improve a pre-existing solution to a problem, achieve a goal, handle an applied input/output relation or perform a specific function?"

-/r/technology </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 22:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to get pissy about this but how are bike lanes not "...the making, modification, usage, and knowledge of tools, machines, techniques, crafts, systems, and methods of organization, in order to solve a problem, improve a pre-existing solution to a problem, achieve a goal, handle an applied input/output relation or perform a specific function?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 22:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would bike lanes not be considered technology? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 20:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also choose to be a partial exit node. I run most of my relays with a few exit ports such as 53 (DNS), 123 (NTP), 8222-8223 (bitcoin), 9999 (darkcoin) and sometimes add 443 (HTTPS). Never had an ISP complain yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 17:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Case in point. Last year this same flap was all about BTC Guild. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Integral Revolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 16:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Bike Ridership Surges With Protected Bike Lanes, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-14 16:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 02:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you give Tails a try? It's safer anyway and will set you on the path to software freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 21:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a little more at stake here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 20:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes there is one which you should be able to find via DDG. You can also make contact with them through [Free Geek Vancouver's](http://freegeekvancouver.org) open help night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 19:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be fantastic but I doubt it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 15:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for your kind words. We look forward to hosting you again soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crypto Block Party @ Car Free Day (Sunday) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 07:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Can Strengthen Anonymity, Privacy and Free Speech on the Internet by Running a Tor Relay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-12 06:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 20:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of anyway around this unless you can figure out how to bypass the wifi captive portal. 

I think your best plan might be to get on the internet through an incognito session of your regular browser and then do some "typical browsing" (ie. a few recipe blogs, etc.)  while you fire up your secure browser and do what you want to do, keeping aware of shoulder surfers and video cameras!

If you dig around you may discover how to bypass the captive portal by making manual changes to your network settings after you've probed your surroundings. [This video shows one way to approach that](http://www.securitytube.net/video/4999). DDG around and you'll find others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 16:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the others here have stated, yes they can. To add "plausible deniability" to your activities run a relay so that they are always seeing Tor activity - now they have no idea whether it's from you or someone else. It also helps the network for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 01:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just DDG "setting up sparkleshare on x" and you should be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 20:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sparkleshare](http://www.sparkleshare.net/) rides on git and is open. It's been working well for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 18:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the nature of your content? If it's something I'm interested in I can provide free hosting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collection of Buddhist video and audio files </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 00:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitcoin is just the beginning (Fully transparent organizations, autonomous corporations, decentralized voting, secure verifiable private identities, robots, etc.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-07 18:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 21:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. We'll run out a just few short years after the heat death of the universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 21:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This page](https://check.torproject.org) will tell you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For shame! There's not a single Tor server in the top 10 that's based in the Americas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 16:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For shame! There's not a single Tor server in the top 10 that's based in the Americas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 16:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For shame! There's not a single Tor server in the top 10 that's based in the Americas. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 16:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 15:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should probably follow the format they suggest as it's designed to make you reachable by humans yet slightly harder to be spammed. I wouldn't bother putting your real name unless you are running an exit node and thus plan to be contacted at some point to explain why certain activities appear to be originating from your IP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 00:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open up a terminal and enter:

    gksudo gedit /etc/tor/torrc

That should let you edit it.

After you've made and saved your edits try to start it by entering the following in the terminal:

    sudo service tor start

You will know right away if it has started successfully. If it doesn't edit it again until you've addressed whatever error it complained about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 07:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This article](http://www.techrepublic.com/blog/five-apps/five-top-apps-for-managing-inventory/) looks at some options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 18:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time todo some hard core googling 

~~googling~~ duckduckgoing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 18:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What we want is an end to the pathological expressions of the nation-state (eg. NSA spying, unjust wars, etc.) while keeping the healthy expressions (eg. international climate treaties). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 18:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. There was always too much of the "greedy banker" vibe going on with that bunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 04:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't still be running Ubuntu 5.10. Support for it ended a few years ago. You should upgrade to at _least_ 10.04, 12.04 if possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 17:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is GPS such a battery hog? I can't see any reason why it should if you are using pure GPS and not the extended location services with the wifi and cell triangulation turned on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 05:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too bad you're on indiegogo. You're a great fit for [dana.io](https://dana.io). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 04:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Bitpay already announced that they were transitioning to bits? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 17:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything is possible. We considered Doge and while we are impressed with the generosity of the Shibe tribe we have decided to test the business model with just these coins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New pay-it-forward platform for artists, activists and authors. Crowdfunding with PayPal, credit card, bitcoin, litecoin   darkcoin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 08:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New crowdfunding platform accepting DRK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 08:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 21:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Libreoffice. Also completely free and doesn't require a net connection or have the privacy issues of cloud offerings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-26 17:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only music that really works for me is ambient. Give SomaFM's [DeepSpaceOne](http://somafm.com/deepspaceone/) or [DroneZone](http://somafm.com/dronezone/) a try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 23:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you probably want to ask your bank what they recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 22:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LibreOffice will do that if you know how to use a spreadsheet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 17:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get stated with free software. Install Ubuntu and do some searching for packages that will provide the functionality you need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 17:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Do you have a source for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 16:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure it helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 23:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't. I used to but now people have to reach me another way. Someone has to make a stand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 20:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tox is looking promising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 17:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be that guy.

* [http://techcrunch.com/2014/05/13/nsa-docs-detail-efforts-to-collect-data-from-microsofts-skype-skydrive-and-outlook-com/](http://techcrunch.com/2014/05/13/nsa-docs-detail-efforts-to-collect-data-from-microsofts-skype-skydrive-and-outlook-com/)

* [http://arstechnica.com/security/2014/05/encrypted-or-not-skype-communications-prove-vital-to-nsa-surveillance/](http://arstechnica.com/security/2014/05/encrypted-or-not-skype-communications-prove-vital-to-nsa-surveillance/)

tl;dr Don't infect your Linux box with Skype. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 03:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually [the volatility has only declined, historically](http://blog.mycoinsolution.com/2014/04/04/congressional-hearing-and-volatility/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How anonymous transactions could save politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 17:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 17:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What /u/Vash2k6 says but more specifically:

* At the login screen hit CTRL-ALT-F1 to take you to a terminal.
* Login with the user account you are having trouble with.
* Enter _rm -r .*_ to remove all the hidden files and folders in your home folder.
* Enter _exit_ to logout of the terminal.
* Go back to your GUI to try logging in again with CTRL-ALT-F7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 18:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great time to pick up a copy of Wilber's _"Integral Psychology"_. That really helped me make sense of what was going on during a similar experience I had about a decade ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 02:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I travelled that route on Monday (albeit in a car) and it seemed great for cycling. There were lots of cyclists on the stretch between Whistler and Pemberton. There wasn't any construction, maintanence, etc. that I noticed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 20:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear that [botcha](http://Drupal.org/project/botcha) is the shit. Please let us know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 07:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [(related)](http://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/25lk14/glenn_greenwald_us_corporate_media_is_neutered/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 05:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use one of the [Logitech wireless media keyboards](http://www.amazon.com/Logitech-Wireless-Keyboard-Built-In-Multi-Touch/dp/B005DKZTMG/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1400124895 sr=8-1 keywords=logitech+media+keyboard). All the controls work well and they are pretty cheap. Only downside for me is just the half-width right Shift key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Payments: The end of a monopoly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 05:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Payments: The end of a monopoly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 05:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 02:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you don't need a gigabit VPN - just 300M. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 18:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'm in Vancouver and it would cost me over $100CAD/month for 300/15M service and that's with a 1TB cap so it doesn't look that bad to me.

The point I was really making is that instead of paying the ridiculous snoop charge (when you know they are snooping anyways) save yourself $20/month and run all your traffic through a VPN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 16:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd let them snoop and just add $10/month for a VPN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Future Of Innovation: Five Things We Can Learn From Bitcoin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 18:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 03:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winners has a decent selection at good prices. Not sure if you have one in your area though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 03:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would go with a top level domain like .ly or .io

Much better chance of getting what you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 02:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article states that miners that didn't get into it for business reasons get a different tax treatment but there's no detail on what that is. Does anyone know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 00:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 10%'"tipping point" figure undoubtedly comes from Malcolm Gladwell's eponymous book. Not sure where the 5% integral level figure comes from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 03:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 03:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use bluefish to edit and mount your remote file system through sftp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 07:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I don't think you let the installer finish all the way to the end. Go back and install again and make sure that you get all the way to the message telling you to reboot and remove the USB stick. Installing the grub bootloader is the last thing it does and is essential for having a bootable machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 23:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I agree](https://imgur.com/OeGrGv8). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 04:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not familiar with the "Put" function but I'm comfortably running a couple of alternative animations, wobbling windows, and centering new windows courtesy of compiz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 03:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Cheapair.com](http://cheapair.com) is my goto these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 02:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I attended an Indiegogo dog and pony show last November and used it to ask the head honcho point-blank when they would be accepting bitcoin and he stated _"when PayPal does"_ so I wouldn't hold my breath.

Fortunately [new crowdfunding platforms are springing up supporting crypto-currencies](http://cointelegraph.com/post/dana_io_aims_to_shake_up_the_crowdfunding_world) so it won't matter much longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Technology Destroys Capitalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 16:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rebooting Civilization: Survivors How-to Guide for Restoring Technology after the Apocalypse [Excerpt] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 05:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To ride or to drink? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 03:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 02:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop by The Gumboot in Robert's Creek for a snack and a coffee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-30 07:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a start-up that is 100% funded through bitcoin including the payroll for 7 employees and our office rent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Known Peer-Reviewed Medical Journal Officially Classifies Fluoride As A Neurotoxin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 04:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 03:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Steve Jobs said 7 inch tablets were "dead in the water" when the form factor was first introduced?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 22:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've (~~appears~~ always - _edit_) assumed this was the case as a matter of course. It's merely surprising to me that this has finally been tested and affirmed by the court.

Another nail in the coffin of big US cloud services and their plans to setup data centres overseas in the hopes of providing more privacy  for their users. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 19:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also worth noting that this was not part of the 14.04 final release but in one of the betas. Nothing really to see here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 18:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all quite doable in Drupal. You will find numerous approaches for the forums. I would stick with the Drupal core forums rather than integrating with a third party forum platform. Go with the votingapi module and those that use it for the voting part. For the wiki I would probably just use the markdown editor and turn on revision tracking for a custom content-type. Setting this up and configuring it should take only a day or so. Then you will want to start theming it. I would recommend starting with with Zen or Omega 4.

Good luck!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-26 02:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the tech side you can install a browser widget that will constantly reload the page (every x seconds). On the reservation hack side I hear the best approach is to book for days before the date you want and include the days you want and then cancel the days you don't want afterwards. I haven't actually tried that so can't personally vouch for it as a technique (and I don't really understand why it would work). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-24 00:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> River Road in Richmond has become a favourite. Will connect you to the Alex Fraser bridge (which sucks for cycling) but gives you full access to Steveston, Reiffel Bird Sanctuary, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 16:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should try Franco r46. I'm amazed at the difference it has made for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 05:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one of each running Linux. The only downside to the Asus, imho, is the 4G of RAM. The screen is nicer, the trackpad and battery life much better. The Lenovo is a lighter carry, the fingerprint reader works well, and it has 8G of RAM. You really can't go too wrong with either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dana.io Gears Up For Its Crowdfunding Donation Platform </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 16:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 17:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm... that's very strange because I've been running relays from home for years and have never experienced this (I'm running 2 relays on 2 different connections into my place right now). Could you give a few examples for me to try out and see if I get the same thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 19:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bitcoin's [volatility continues to decrease](http://blog.mycoinsolution.com/2014/04/04/congressional-hearing-and-volatility/). If it stabilises at 0 then no one will be using it. However if/when it stabilises at 1000, 10000 or 100000 there's no reason not to denominate in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 17:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least not yet. Once it stabilizes somewhat then there should be no problem with transacting purely in Bitcoin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 20:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Install the Xposed framework and some of its modules. Install F-Droid and then Ad-Away from the F-Droid repo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 03:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have used (and continue to use) bitcoin to buy computer hardware, headphones, dinners, coffee and snacks; make donations to causes (eg. wikipedia, Tor, EFF, OpenMedia, PeaceGeeks, etc.); pay employees and office rent; invest in companies and give to my friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 03:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can try [installing Google's Pepper Flash player](http://www.webupd8.org/2013/04/install-pepper-flash-player-for.html) for your other browsers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 18:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 18:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Holarchy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Holoarchy), FTW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How's that monetary policy working out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 18:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How's that monetary policy working out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 18:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 02:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome job. Great work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 17:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are going to do it. It was announced with great fanfare but it has sunk like a stone. The last piece I saw about it was it that it would only be for small transactions (like $20 or smaller). I think they finally realized how vulnerable it was and how much undesirable attention it would attract if it contained any real value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 17:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are all sorts of transactions that aren't conducive to credit cards - sending $20 to a friend on the other side of the planet, paying for something online where you'd prefer not to give any of your personal information, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 16:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not here to tell you to to stop using your credit card if you want. But not every transaction needs that "feature". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 16:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right - the more accurate description would be "self-serving interest". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 07:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I'm against monetary policy that's the whim of politicians and bankers. I favour a set monetary policy governed by a transparent alogrithm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 18:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exchanging into fiat is only a stop gap measure. Cryptocurrency is the endgame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 18:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because putting your faith in hardware doesn't ultimately work. Plus it's centrally controlled so misses most of the point of bitcoin and its ilk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 18:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people are for that and some aren't. Get over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 16:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  One of the key features of bitcoin is that transactions dont require a third party to sign off, like a bank or a credit card company. Every time a credit card gets swiped, the issuer charges a small fee  typically around 3%. It doesnt sound like much but it quickly adds up and consumers ultimately end up paying.

But since bitcoin transactions dont require a third party, theres effectively no fee  a huge benefit to the economy.

Its also not controlled by any government or central bank. Bitcoin is part of a peer-to-peer software system. The amount in circulation is strictly controlled by an algorithm. That means it cannot be incorporated into any countrys monetary policy and new bitcoins cant be created at the whim of central bankers.


This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 05:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think escrow with multi-sig will be a good first step.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 23:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really sure. The devs are quite open and accessible, or at least they used to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 20:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't tried it myself. Status.net has been around for a few years and is pretty mature and made for these kinds of use cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 18:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Status.Net probably comes closest to what you are looking for. Twister shows some promise.

http://status.net

http://twister.net.co/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 16:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fully agree. Every capital control crisis is another boost for bitcoin. This will be the year that government really tries to get a handle on crypto-currency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 03:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 02:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I know I'm a bit of an exception. I also have 7 employees and contractors who are getting paid in bitcoin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 02:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The total was 16.13mBTC which included a 15% tip. Vancouver, Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 23:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I had coffee and a cinammon bun this morning, paid for with bitcoin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bitcoin Is Pointless as a Currency, But It Could Change the World Anyway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 22:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 22:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Htop for showing what's going on and letting you manage processes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 03:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Plus after you replace the 'new' wallet.dat file with your backup you will need to run bitcoin with the "--rescan" flag. Your balance will return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 34% of Britons believe that bitcoin is the "currency of the future" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 18:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 18:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes all the VC money that has poured into POS, etc. over the past year has to be pausing for the moment. [Matonis has an interesting take on the ruling](https://twitter.com/jonmatonis/statuses/449830429752061953). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 16:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That also happened right after the 2011 correction. It was so horrible that I moved over here and have never really gone back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 07:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This will help get you started](http://www.diydharma.org/how-meditate). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Cassidy: Is Surging Inequality Endemic to Capitalism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-29 01:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 16:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is no doubt currently true. Do you think that will still be the case in 3 years? How about 5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 16:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So one transaction a month between two people who know each other, with the payee knowing exactly how to find (and make homeless) the payer, involves a cheque. I agree that costing yourself the 2% and the extra steps of involving Bitcoin in this transaction makes no sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 16:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what percentage of your transactions involve cheques? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 15:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm... you must live in a small town because most places won't take cheques anymore where I live. Also doesn't really work over the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 15:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case you expect to lose approximately 2% (1% for each conversion) which is better than the ~10% that Western Union charges or the ~4% that credit cards charge. Of course with credit cards consumers get some "protection" through the ability to issue a chargeback. Bitcoin transactions, like cash, are tipped somewhat in favour of the vendor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 15:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can sign messages with the private key(s) that correspond to that "account" ("address" is a better term here). This constitutes absolute proof that you control the bitcoins associated with that address. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 15:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You only have to deal with exchanges if you are converting to/from fiat. For me cryptocurrency is the endgame and that won't require any exchanges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 21:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes  I find the [COCOMO](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/COCOMO) very useful in explaining to clients how much value they are getting from open source software. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 20:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if you desire more anonymity than bitcoin provides (at present) consider [darkcoin](http://darkcoin.io). I already use bitcoin for almost half of my monthly transactions including meals, paying employees, online purchases, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 19:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as a transportation activist I say "great" - be sure to arrest every single one of them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 17:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a presentation 4 or 5 years ago that purported to answer this question for Drupal 6. The answer at that time was $6 million - based upon something called the "constructive cost model" - which purports to be a standard way of costing coding. It is just based upon the number of lines of code and how long it would take a competent coder to build, test and debug that codebase. I believe you can easily apply the same model to Drupal 8 - perhaps even as simply as multiplying by the differential in the codebase size and adjusting for inflation.

Interesting aside - the presenter also mentioned that the stable version of Debian would cost $4 billion at that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 03:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making online purchases without handing over a bunch of personal information is my main use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 03:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great looking service. Would you folks be okay with me running some Tor services on some of those (including exit nodes)? I've been taking with the Tor Server guys and they were expressing the need for more in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 03:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Download the file through Tor and then play it in VLC? Pretty hard to stream through Tor, flash or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 11:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I last used Windows in 2000. I had built a web hosting and development business in the 90s on Microsoft. When I sold it at the end of '99 part of the reason was that I was fed up with Microsoft's licensing regime. I switched to Apple for front end dev and Debian for hosting. It wasn't long afterwards that I dropped Apple altogether and have been fully open source ever since. I switched my workstations from Debian to Ubuntu on Breezy (5.04) and my servers over on 8.04 and have never looked back. On the home front I have three laptops, my wife's  workstation, a media server, and a development server in our condo all running Ubuntu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 14:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh... I didn't realize there was going to be different content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 02:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered going with the mobile module and simply have it serve up a different theme? Doesn't that approach address this very issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 14:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's is [my reply to /u/PirateBing](http://www.reddit.com/r/vancouvercycling/comments/20ip6g/purchasing_a_used_bicycle/cg4poer) most of which applies to you. EXCEPT for you I would be looking for something in the 56 range. I think you'll find a 58 a little too big. You might be able to go down to a 54 depending on the geometry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 14:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the view I would use](http://vancouver.en.craigslist.ca/search/bik?zoomToPosting= catAbb=bik query= minAsk= maxAsk=500 excats=). As you can see there are lots to choose from in your price range. I put in a max price of $500 because you might be able to make an offer on something slightly above your price range or stretch your budget a little further if you really think you've "found the one for you". 

Since you aren't going to be getting the latest, greatest with your budget I would look for one that:

1. fits and that you will ride. You probably want to be looking in the 54cm range.

2. seems well-maintained and ridden OR one of those "I'm cleaning out my garage and noticed this which I hadn't ridden in years" deals.

4. ignore fixies. You will see a lot of them and there's a reason that they are all for sale. 

Take a test ride and don't worry too much about how comfortable the saddle is, how smoothly it shifts or if the brakes squeal - you can deal with those on your own time. More important to make sure that the frame is solid and true and that nothing is badly rusted or bolts are stripped. 

Now is a really good time to be buying a road bike, imho - before the rain ends, spring arrives and more people think about digging their bikes out.
Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 16:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cruise Craigslist's bikes-for-sale-by-owner a lot and IMHO you can score some great deals if you know your way around. How tall are you and what's your budget because I was looking just yesterday and there seem to be an enormous amount of road bikes at the present time which should help you?

I wouldn't take too much stock from the prices listed on other forums. Much depends on the condition of the bike and what the local market is like. Often the forums are referring to places in the States that simply have a better market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
