<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2315</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think he'd ever hurt me. He's not that kind of man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is, yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to leave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 16:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only been Muslim for 1.5 years and have only been married for 6 months, but I am miserable. My husband is a wonderful man. He's sweet, gentle, and understanding. But he would never leave Islam. He's happy in it. It's been his way of life for 20 years, since he was just 15. For me, it is oppressive and constricting and bleak. It feels akin to nihilism and I absolutely cannot stand it. I do not know why I even took my shahada. Now, I'm in the KSA and trying to figure out how to leave without hurting my husband. I don't want to break his heart, but I am so unhappy. 

How did you all finally leave Islam? How do I make my husband understand without hurting him?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 15:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too adorable! 

Such a shame there are so many miserable racists and homophobes commenting, like fucking always.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 07:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cannot be racist towards whites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just probably aren't used to seeing such smooth, wrinkle-free skin beyond teenaged years in whatever white-centric enclave you reside in. It's very likely they're well into their 20s. Black doesn't crack, as it were.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really shocking and upsetting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 23:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A 'choo-choo' train!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 06:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cats are jerks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 00:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cute that his treats are veggies! I love him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 00:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really cool! A lot of these being posted today. One guy just got one for his cottage. Another dude had his stolen, poor fellow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 22:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me so much of scenes in Sound Of My Voice!!! 

Also, in episode 2 when Abel, Nancy, and OA are getting a family photo taken, a heavily medicated OA is looking down and the photog is saying stuff to Nancy and Abel and his words become muffled as the camera zooms to OA. And then we hear the photog clearly say "towards the sound of my voice, honey" 

Since Brit and Zal also made Sound of My Voice, they could have just thrown in these things as little Easter eggs for superfans (like myself) to find. But I'm wondering if there might be some actual connection between the two projects. I don't want to give any spoilers for those who haven't seen Sound of My Voice, but the story arc does mirror The OA in certain aspects!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 10:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this cat! So sweet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
