<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9825</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:32:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homophobic? Yeah, he was so homophobic that he [publicly opposed the Briggs Initiative in 1978 which would have banned homosexuals from working in public schools](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Briggs_Initiative) despite it hurting him politically. Racist? Yeah, he was so racist that he [made MLK Jr. Day a national holiday](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Martin_Luther_King_Jr._Day). Reagan was twice the President Obama was. But sure, continue to lie to people if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia didn't hack voting machines. Voters made informed choices on Election Day based on the information available. Should we look into what Russia did and punish them? Yes. But in no way was our democracy compromised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our country was fucking founded on overthrowing a government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 10:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a list of the programs the left is trying to undo.

the left is hell bent on cutting any health services that protect the people of this country.

Since you can't even remember the difference between the left and right I can't honestly expect you to understand any further arguments I could make. I encourage you to do more research on these topics so you'll realize how wrong you are. And also so you can learn the difference between the left and right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 10:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to destroy a government is like the most American thing possible lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 10:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planned Parenthood

There are many other reproductive health clinics besides PP. Withdrawing federal funds would not be a danger to any Americans. In 2014 10% of the money they received wasn't even used.

The ACA

Repealing the ACA would cause *less* danger to America. Forcing people to buy expensive insurance that they do not need is a danger to our liberty. Companies being forced to fire people or cut hours due to increased costs is a danger to people's ability to make money and provide for themselves and survive.

Social Security

Social Security will almost definitely fail by the time my generation reaches the age to actually benefit. That's assuming they don't raise the retirement age. And again, how is this "dangerous" if its gone? SS isn't intended as a retirement plan.

Medicare/Medicaid

Well nothing is happening to Medicaid so I'm going to assume you put it in there by mistake and you're not an idiot. As for Medicare, one could certainly argue that its existence is a danger to the many younger Americans who are forced to pay into it while receiving no benefits for decades. And the planned voucher system will keep coverage, but people will need to pay a bit more. Wow. So dangerous.

Minimum wage

Raising the minimum wage is dangerous because it will force many small companies out of business, which will cause many people to lose jobs.

Education

Do you think you are significantly smarter than your parents? Like, noticeably smarter? Because unless they're in their early 40s they received at least some of their education without a federal Department of Education. Generations of people were educated just fine without it. So again, you fail to say how this being taken away would be dangerous, let alone the greatest danger.

The EPA

I will give you this one. Environmental policy is becoming a major issue and the United States will need the EPA to ensure that climate change is left in check.

Net Neutrality

Come the fuck on. I'm not even going to address this one. You think ending net neutrality is THE GREATEST DANGER TO AMERICANS? Good think you put this one last or I would have just written you off as a 15-year old with no idea how the world works and not bothered replying.

So, out of those 9, only 1 could *potentially* cause danger to Americans (in the very far future). And you have failed to address how this would be THE GREATEST DANGER TO AMERICANS IN THE WORLD, ahead of terrorism or Russian interests attempting to influence elections. For someone named "TheSmartestMan" you really should do more research before attempting to argue.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 09:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. But nothing that the GOP (or Democrats) have done or plan to do are worse than what those can do to harm the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 09:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case you didn't notice, America did just fine without these for hundreds of years. I fail to see how their absence is a 'danger to the United States' let alone the *greatest* danger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia.

China. 

Terrorism. 

Iran. 

Lots of things. If you actually believe that the GOP defunding an abortion clinic makes it the "biggest threat to America in the world" then you must be ignoring much of what is going on in the world today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yeah sure buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they? They don't want to do anything. Obama does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 18:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did Obama ever even try? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's from Wisconsin... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan reelected Speaker in near-unanimous vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? You're not making sense. It literally wouldn't have changed a thing. Even if Michigan and Pennsylvania flipped with the recounts Clinton still would have lost. Do you know how this works? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wisconsin and Nevada were recounted and the result stayed the same. So Michigan and Pennsylvania wouldn't matter either way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The recounts wouldn't have changed the result...not sure what you're trying to say here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was bred for one reason, and one reason only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 23:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ITS AN OUTRAGE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Won by 77 electoral votes. 

Everyone knew the rules going in. Trump won fair and square. Whining about the popular vote distracts from the actual issues that his presidency will cause.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldnt even mad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 20:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I nearly got him. And I could have killed him

-Bill Clinton of bin Laden on **September 10, 2001**

Shit.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Supreme Court said gay marriage is legal."

"That's a fallacy of appealing to the authority of the Supreme Court." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 01:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That touchdown was just salt in the wound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 22:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My drunk roommate came home 3 nights ago and said i have really nice thighs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 06:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *SE-VEN...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 23:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother and I still quote the [GPS scene](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QF5x4oP9OT8) whenever we're driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 21:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here we go again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do they still let kids into the cockpit of airplanes or did that stop after 9/11? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when I went on vacation in 2000 i was able to go into the cockpit and I got a set of wings. The next few times I was on a plane I was way too old for that and I haven't been on a plane in several years. Do they still let kids go in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't hate bro I'm just in it for the karma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 22:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT YEAR IS IT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Challenger speech.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obamacare Didnt Fail Because Its Timid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 03:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather live under Hitler than Stalin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.fraserinstitute.org/article/pipelines-are-safest-way-transport-oil-and-gas

http://www.lfpress.com/2015/03/09/pipelines-are-safest-method-of-moving-oil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 01:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 years ago is pretty nostalgic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Democratic Primary based on states won and EC votes by state.](http://www.270towin.com/maps/PkKd3) Blue=Bernie. Red=Hillary.

[Republican Primary based on states won and EC votes by state.](http://www.270towin.com/maps/yVBLd) Blue=Trump. Red=Cruz. Gold=Kasich. Grey=Rubio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes we should. If those people are in the "wrong" parts of the country it doesn't really matter. What matters is winning elections.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOCK.....................BOX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 8 years as VP trumps all other experience, in my opinion. Gore was also in Congress for 16 years. He was way more experienced than Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sprite Remix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 03:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 00:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modern obstructionism really began with the tactics Gingrich introduced when he was Speaker, but it reached its current level after Obama and the Democrats passed Obamacare. It had 0 Republican support in either chamber and was forced through, so the GOP said "Fine. That's how it's gonna be then" and refused to cooperate with the rest of the administration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hugh Hefner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: Spielberg didn't hire Liam Neeson for his acting ability. He hired him because he was so good at making lists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would the doctor care for some brandy, before retiring?

Some warm milk?

Ovaltine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Werewolves!

THERE wolves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird UPS Truck in my Front Yard [Part 43] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 00:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's morally binding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Letter: Obama's pardons can become a problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get that racist shit out of here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 19:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanders wins basically every debate he's a part of

Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 00:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe Lilo has insane durability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 00:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So California should be allowed to do what it wants as a state without interference from the federal government?

Good to know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 278-Pasthole: Designed to be a living black hole that sucks you up and takes you to the past.

279-Futurehole: Designed to be a living black hole that sucks you up and takes you to the future.

594-Colm: Designed to make soda.

606-Holio: Designed to create a matter-sucking black hole when he opens his mouth.

 607-Launch: Designed to warp the fabric of time and space, causing the entire universe to collapse upon itself.

611-El Fin: Designed to make the universe implode when Jumba speaks the password.

620-Page: Designed to possess any other living being.

Honestly, if they were all working together you'd need to get to the upper-tier abstracts. There are **2** of them that can destroy the universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 19:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mean Bob holy shit that brings me back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 04:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If they had won or if the war had dragged on longer there is a very solid argument to make that things would have gotten much worse.

This is the main failure of your argument. There was never a chance they could have 'won or dragged on longer'. Their entire economy was based on conquest of other nations. They would *eventually* have run out of places to plunder. This is the main difference. The USSR had far more long-lasting horrendous impacts around the world that we see TO THIS DAY. Human rights abuses in China? Caused by the USSR. North Korea? USSR. Cuba? USSR. 

We can argue about a few million people killed by either Nazis or the Soviets but the point still stands that people killed by ALL OF COMMUNISM (which all can be traced back to the USSR) dwarfs those killed by the Nazis in WWII.

To circle back to the original argument, Reagan did not single handle bring down the Soviet Union anyway

Oh yes of course. If that's what you thought I was arguing I apologize. He certainly didn't do it all himself, but its undeniable that his actions significantly hastened the fall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrat Media Fail: Only 29% of Americans Convinced Russia Was Behind Election-Year DNC Hacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 03:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://humanevents.com/2011/02/06/top-10-reagan-achievements/

I have lists too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The civilian casualties due to the Germans exceeded the USSR by several million and over a shorter time span.

Who cares if it was a shorter time span? If the USSR killed more people over a longer time span, wouldn't they be the worse entity?

The Soviet civilian death estimates were widely overblown which was addressed both in my source and by modern historians.

My source proved this incorrect.

they were internal deaths of their own territories by and large.

Does that make it better? Over 100,000,000 people lived in the USSR. Just because they were "in their own territories" doesn't excuse what they did.

But you are still missing the bigger issue. The USSR has had the single worst impact of any state in modern history. It has led to many other communist movements, which by modern estimates, have caused the deaths of near [100,000,000 people](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Black_Book_of_Communism).

You're missing the forest for the trees. It's not *just* about what the USSR did within its borders. Its about the effects of their supporting and propping up other communist regimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. I see what you're saying. You're incorrect, but I see why you are.

 Total deaths as a result of WWII (which was caused by the Nazi's) are 60+ million

WWII was not the sole fault of the Nazis. [The Second Sino-Japanese war began a year before Germany even annexed Austria](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Second_Sino-Japanese_War), and is widely considered to be one of the driving forces behind the start of the war, and even a possible start of the war.

The USSR is estimated to have at least [56,000,000 deaths between 1928-1954](http://www.ibtimes.com/how-many-people-did-joseph-stalin-kill-1111789). Subtracting the ~20,000,000 caused by the German invasion, that is still millions more than the ~35,000,000 killed on both sides between the Western and Eastern Fronts in WWII as well as the Holocaust. And that is not even mentioning the many more millions dead in other wars caused or prolonged by the USSR, such as the Chinese Civil War or Vietnam War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In about face, Navy restores traditional job titles after objections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 23:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true. In both number of deaths caused directly and indirectly the USSR was far worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *California governor and union-president  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. That is what happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think someone did the math and it would take multiple atomic bombs worth of energy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aang can while in the Avatar State.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WACHA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Soviets were worse for the world than the Nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who mentioned Trump? And if that happens (it won't) I'll be the first to say I was wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Republican Congress worked behind Carter's back to broker the end of the hostage situation. *This was unconstitutional.*  

I stopped reading right there. That is a [conspiracy theory with no evidence whatsoever](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/October_Surprise_conspiracy_theory). If you believe hat I have a pizzagate story to tell you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In terms of worldwide impact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top 10 best without question. Just because he did things you don't like that doesn't make him a horrible president.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reagan's actions directly contributed to the fall of the Soviet Union. Whether or not you agree with his domestic policies, that is the single greatest thing any President has ever done and has had the greatest positive impact on the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 16:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop blaming gerrymandering for every failure of the Democratic Party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seasons change every few months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the new /r/politics masterplan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/KillThoseWhoDisagree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The McDonald's Gamecube Kiosk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They actually took it down last year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 06:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. I've had a bit of a bad week. Sorry for lashing out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 05:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's term limited. Do you know anything about government? No wonder you're a Democrat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 04:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The facts of life are conservative. 

-Margaret Thatcher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 21:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -Guru Laghima </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [?](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/b1/57/89/b15789629e249fa3730ce852a23af1c7.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I am become Jeb!](http://i0.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/original/001/189/106/726.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arthur's Perfect Christmas, one of the only holiday specials to feature Christmas, Chanukah, and Kwanzaa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daredevil [MCU] vs. Chirrut mwe [Rogue One] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **MINOR ROGUE ONE SPOILERS**

[Daredevil](http://vignette4.wikia.nocookie.net/marvelcinematicuniverse/images/6/6e/Full_Daredevil_Suit.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20150805234158)

[Chirrut mwe](http://vignette2.wikia.nocookie.net/starwars/images/7/76/Chirrut_Imwe.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/500?cb=20160809161338)

Daredevil has his billy club and Chirrut has his staff.

Round 1: Takes place on [Jedha](https://i0.wp.com/media2.slashfilm.com/slashfilm/wp/wp-content/images/ZZ4CD53BD6-700x293.jpg).

Round 2: Takes place in [Hell's Kitchen](http://static.srcdn.com/wp-content/uploads/Daredevil-motion-poster-without-the-motion.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of laugh to myself when progressives do not understand that they are conservatives.

If they weren't they'd believe in things like prohibition, or eugenics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 08:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You have to block it from going to ballot, that is the only way it can be stopped

That's just not true. Congress would need to allow it which would never happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 08:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure. But it's definitely in the whole-number percents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 07:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. 0.05% of the population of LA. That'll show him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 07:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That will never happen. Please stop pretending it'll ever come close to happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 05:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They turned out. For the other guy. Bush was that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Calexit is so self-destructive and wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. It's a horrible idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typical Bernie supporter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we can't allow Russia to influence the politics of our country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_longest_bridges

Yes you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's literally the opposite of what's happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Calexit leader lives in Russia. Still want California secession? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 02:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, Obama.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 01:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well seeing as how  over 45% of land is federally owned in CA I don't see "not paying taxes" going well at all. Not to mention the lack of water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an idiot. You're gonna look really stupid when none of this happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure y'all will hurt more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 06:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If businesses can't survive without hiring illegals then they'll go out of business. That's how the market works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 06:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Reluctant and restrained desegregation

So if you don't like how Ike did it, I'm assuming you would prefer his 2-time opponent, Adlai Stevenson's position on desegregation. "Adlai E. Stevenson, front-runner for the party's presidential nomination in 1956, urged the government to "proceed gradually" on school desegregation in deference to the South's long-held "traditions.""

Interstate System that's had massive and mostly negative impacts on our land use/environment/air quality/physical fitness

You can't honestly be saying that the IHS was a *bad* thing, can you? Physical fitness? Come on.

 space agency that put the second satellite up and the second man in orbit.

And put a goddamn man on the Moon.

Bro. Come on now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who will check Facebook's 'fact checkers?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 05:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 04:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember how Biden said to African-Americans Romney was ["going to put you back in chains"](http://abcnews.go.com/blogs/politics/2012/08/vp-biden-says-republicans-are-going-to-put-yall-back-in-chains/)? Or how Romney going out of his way to hire women was [called sexist](http://www.dailykos.com/story/2012/10/17/1145818/-A-Binder-Full-of-Gender-Discrimination)? Or how [McCain was called a racist for questioning Obama](http://www.alternet.org/story/102993/backlash%3A_six_challenges_to_mccain's_racist_fearmongering)? 

Neither Romney nor McCain are racists or sexists. They are decent, dignified men who wanted the best for their country. But the Left has been crying wolf for so long that when an *actual racist and sexist* comes along, nobody gives a shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 03:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I read comics too.](http://allenbwest.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/09/Cartoon-Reagan-Obama.jpg) Doesn't make what's in them accurate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 00:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler wasn't elected democratically. If you're going to argue something at least know what you're arguing. You sound like an idiot otherwise. Not saying you are just giving you advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they were celebrities when they were voted into office

Arnie and Trump, yeah, but Reagan was involved in politics for decades before he was president. He was the Governor of California for 8 years for God's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 23:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top 10 Presidents, easily. Just because he did things you don't like doesn't mean he wasn't a good president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  reagan, arnold, and trump

Well they're all politicians, so...yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has any Republican *ever* said they want to live in Russia? Please show me because I'd love to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Not very.](http://ijr.com/2015/01/230371-2-map-shows-red-states-rely-federal-aid-looks-can-deceiving/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Obama to Putin.](https://media.giphy.com/media/Sy5TpQXJlJeQE/giphy.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Obama to Putin.](https://media.giphy.com/media/Sy5TpQXJlJeQE/giphy.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOD BLESS AMERICA, BABY! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama seeks to tone down hacking fight with Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buzzfeed and Vox reach the top here multiple times a week. I don't see how this is much different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a "policy", its more guidelines. Comey feared that the details would be leaked either way to the press so he tried to get ahead of it by informing Congress, and that's when all hell broke loose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congress holds "meetings" so that they're never technically in recess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's this? Some new, advanced form of shitpost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. Honestly, what was he supposed to do? He received information that was relevant. He could either sit on it until after the election and Hillary is likely elected, and he gets crucified by people saying he didn't do his job and aided Hillary. Or he could done what he did and released it TO CONGRESS when he got it, and get accused of people saying he aided Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every presidential election is 51 (counting DC) individual elections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that Walter Mondale is the only major-party candidate to lose an election in all 50 states, losing in all but Minnesota in the 1984 presidential election, and losing a Senate election in Minnesota in 2002. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the first one was really successful. People will see the poster and ask "They made another one?" And the answer is right there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The correct answer is vote for whoever the hell you want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Clinton says Putin holds grudge against her at donor party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh how the turn tables... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Says No Serious Person Could Rig An Election Even After Several Govt Hacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People vote, not cities and not states.

That's false. States do vote. That's what the EC *is*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 04:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In general the US has pushed more towards than away from the direct Democracy, this change would be counter to this trend and make the Senate less accountable to voters.

Well just because it goes "counter to a trend" doesn't mean it's a bad idea. Prohibition was with the "progressive trend" and that was a horrible idea. In regards to your second point, does the Senate *need* to be accountable to voters? We already have the House for that. The Senate was designed to represent the interests of the States.

Your second point I admit could be a legitimate issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 03:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop! I can only get so erect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 03:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No parody. No parody. You're the parody.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 03:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JOHTO MOTHERFUCKERS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could he find a way to trap Buu in Minusland?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And HRC and the Senate Dems won the popular vote. 

If Dems wanna keep trying for the popular vote they can have it. It'll leave more seats for the GOP to actually win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.ontheissues.org/AskMe/plurality.htm

In elections, a majority happens when more than half of the electorate votes for one candidate. For example, if a candidate gets 50.1% of the vote, she gets a majority. A plurality happens when less than half vote for a candidate that wins because the vote is split among more than two candidates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they didn't this year so I'm doubtful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats have controlled the House 4 out of the last 22 years, and the GOP has one of the largest margins in history. It's not in the cards for them in 2 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -H.A. Goodman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Libertarians outnumbered Greens in *every* state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's *President-Elect* Herr Dipshit. 

I hate the guy but have some respect for the office.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romney  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pipe dream.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop. You're embarrassing yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only because she cheated. Obama's name wasn't even on the ballot in a few states.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 16:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad the people don't pick the president.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 15:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The facts of life are conservative.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
