<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6464</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Ideas of an Adult-themed Niyandar Kamen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 03:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fall of the 45th President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 02:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Republicans Repeal Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Safari Not Fulfulling Anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Revival of Old Shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 01:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summer Vacations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I immigrate to the US in 2000, the first summer vacation I have taken was in 2003 when I went back to China. I stayed for a month. Every morning, I was with my grandpa eating cheong fun rolled noodle rolls. That's when I go swimming daily.

In 2005, we went to Canada for a 3-day trip. I met my father's friend's family. While in Toronto, I saw the Toronto light rail passing by. That's when I want to ride the Hudson-Burgen Light Rail in New Jersey.

In 2006, we went to Boston. We stopped at Yale University and the No Name restaurant at the harbor.

In 2007, we went to Washington, DC. We stopped at important places that were the foundation of US, the White House, and the Sedonnah Caves.

In 2011 late Spring before I start the 5-day suspension in High School, I went to the Longwood gardens in Pennsylvania with my mom. We saw beautiful flowers around the gardens. In the summer, I went back to China the second time. Everything has changed. We rode on the high-speed railway, saw plants growing on the highway, and went to Beijing.

I haven't gone to summer vacations much. I don't seem to be interested in going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sea World Ending Killer Whale Shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently, according to The Ring of Fire, an alternative news network, reported that Sea World Ending their Kiler Whale Shows. PETA can clam claim victory for now.

PETA have videos of the abuse behind the scenes of Sea World. Orcas and whales are kept in captivity, being forced to reproduce. This is the good thing as Sea World is being criticized for the ethical and moral behavior. These social sea animals needed to be together to support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes and thanks for reminding me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ringling Bros. Closing After 146 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After 146 years in operation, the Rigling Bros. Circus announced that they are closing due to declining attendance and high operating costs. This is good news for PETA.

The company has been criticized by PETA for animal abuse. I saw videos of abuse behind the scenes. Elephants were beaten with whips. They are seen being chained and kept in compartments with very little moving space. Monkeys are seen tortured during rehearsals.

Now that Ringling Bros. are closing, PETA claims victory. This is good news for the elephants kept in captivity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using Two Web Browsers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a MacBook Air. The default web browser it Safari. After finding out that some of the websites that I use are inaccessible, I downloaded Firefox. Firefox is better than Safari as the websites I use are accessible.

Before using Safari, I used Internet Explorer, which was full of flaws. I knew that I need to update or get a new computer. I chose to get a new computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warbears Back Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 17:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Mishaps in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 06:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Spring Semester, I applied for five class. I wasn't doing well in Accounting and Microeconomics. The professors weren't that good. I ended up having to drop the classes to save my GPA. If I have went to tutoring and not go to the Japan Club all the time, I would not have dropped.

During the Summer, my father's friends's company closed down and moved to Chicago. I was applying to several jobs. I was able to get a job at Greenpeace, but did not get accepted because I couldn't get three people to sign up.

In August 10, I dislocated my shoulder from diving. It took me 2 weeks to heal. I couldn't swim.

In the Fall semester, I took physics. I never taken physics in high school, so I struggled in the class. However, the professors are laid-back. Ended up getting a D+ in lab and a D in physics. If I went to tutoring, I would have did better.

I regretted of not registering to vote. If I have vote, I could have voted for Jill Stein if I knew Hillary was like Trump. The electoral college voted for Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 20:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What game is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let Hillary Run For Mayor of NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> States Becoming Self-Sufficient </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that Trump and GOP clams the White House and the congress, we will likely see states becoming self-sufficient, using tax money for local programs.

The rich states send money to poorer states to help them. Trump and the GOP will gut social and environmental programs, which will hurt the poorer states. The three biggest states are New York, California, and Texas. California and Texas have succession movements. California will have a referendum for succession by the next election.

There will be less taxes going to the federal government. What will likely happen is that with the states becoming self-sufficient, Trump and the GOP will be useless, other than enriching themselves. The poorer states would have to become self-sufficient. They will suffer.

By 2020, if the Democrats or moderate Republicans win the White House, states will share taxes and stop the continental congress policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 17:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bald Eagles and 2016 Elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 04:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bald eagle is the national animal of America, which is a symbol of courage, strength, and freedom. 2016 turns out to be the one of the worst years in US history. Lately, the bald eagle is unhappy of the future of America.

Two days of the election, two bald eagles are caught fighting in mid-air, eventually falling into the storm drain hole. The male is protecting the female from falling, but gives up and the female ends up falling into the drain. A few days after, the female dies. Many Hillary supporters made this metaphor of the election.

When an another bald eagle named Uncle Sam visits Trump, it attracts Trump. When Trump tries to approach the bald eagle, it attacks back. This is a metaphor that America hates Trump and want him to fail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Opinion of Adam Ruins Everything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 03:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adam Ruins Everything, and informational show hosted by Adam Conover aired on truTV. This show informs viewers the Truth about everything topics.

Before the show premiered on truTV, he worked with CollegeHumor with the skit. I have seen several of the YouTube videos online. One that I saw was about the Trumps that have existed in US history.

The show, however, barely makes 1 million views per episode. The show was renewed for a second season. GradeAUnderA is a possible rival of Adam Conover, how also criticizes about anything he wants.

Here are some future thing I hope Adam ruins: porn, presidency, governments, such as monarchy, autocracy, socialism, communism, feudalism or democracy, public schools, colleges, wars, railways, air travel, ninjas, samurais, water travel, public transportation, credit cards, TVs, debt, superstitions, news, racism, bulling, banking, cellphone, and corruption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Will Likely Happen in the Next 4 Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that Trump becomes president in Jan. 20, here are the likely situations that will likely happen in the next four years.

America will be incompetent and ungovernable. It has become very polarized, where both political parties are at opposite extremes. The Capitol will be full of infighting, disagreements, and no good solutions coming out. Trump is unpredictable. He flip-flops often, causing policies to flip back and off often. The GOP can't get things done. If they do, people will feel unhappy and blame them for the incompetence, where they will scapegoat Democrats and their supporters.

Due to the incompetence, state and local governments will do the congress' job. They will help the people while the congress will be full of infighting. People like Sanders and Ellison are reaching out to people about what the GOP is doing and what they can do to help America. Lately, governor Andrew Cuomo proposed to give free college to the middle and the working class. This will help them climb the social ladder.

Rich people will feel that the congress and the White House will help them, not the poor. After seeing the middle and the working class feeling the effects of incompetence, they will help the state and local governments to help the needy, thus fulfilling Sander's policies of socialism.

With the state and local government helping the locals, 2018 can help Democrats control the congress. With this in mind, Trump and the GOP would be scared that the Democrats will expose them for their incompetence and corruption. Trump will see his approval rating drop and would lose 2020. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Will Happen To America in the Next Four Years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Thoughts on School Years During Pre-College Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I started college, a school year is usually between early September to late June. During the school year, I would expect short breaks during holidays, with two months of summer break.

The Fall semester is usually between early September to late January. The Spring semester is usually between early February to late June. We have pre-planned curriculum, half-days, and parent-teacher conferences.

During my elementary school years, we have recess and lunch. The classes are much more slow and I often go to after-school. Each day, the classes are different. There are field trips often.

During my intermediate school years, we stopped having recess. The classes are much faster. The field trips are not as much. Each day, we do have different classes each day. In the 8th grade, I have math class that consists of two separate periods, instead of consecutive periods. I got suspended once for sexual harassment.

During my high school year, the classes are much faster. I only have one field trip. In science class, it happen to include lab class. I got suspended once for racism. After this situation, I became more liberal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Presidency Will Be Similar to Amy's Baking Company </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 06:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2013, Chef Gordon Ramsey visited Amy's Baking Company. However, he was unable to make changes due to Amy being not open to criticisms.

We seen many breakdowns on Facebook and Twitter. Eventually, the restaurant closed last year.

Amy herself divorced in 2003 before committing identify theft. She later married Samy before opening the restaurant in 2007.

This fiasco has manifested into the 2016 election. We will see how Trump's presidency will likely parallel Amy's Baking Company.

Trump has divorced several times and caught up in several lawsuits, I.e. Trump University.

His policies are likely to be final and are likely to be inelastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Presidency is Parallel to Amy's Baking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 05:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who I Would Have Voted For If I Have Voted in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 01:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't vote because I thought it wasn't that important. I skipped on the primary elections. If I have voted in the primaries, I would have voted for Hillary. Back then, I didn't have any thought about Sanders even though college students are supporting Sanders.

I heard about same day registration for election day. I still didn't think about registering for election day. I told my parents to vote for Hillary, while my grandpa didn't went to vote. My aunt supported for Trump, but I know that move is a regrettable choice.

If I have known about Hillary isn't that trustable like Trump, I would have vote for a third party. If I have known about Johnson and Stein, I would make a protest vote to Stein because she is also liberal and the Green Party supported conservation, which is important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free College </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 03:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 05:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Summer of 2011, I went to China for vacation. We took the high-speed railway from Guangzhou to Shaoguan. The trip takes between 30 and 45 minutes. When we returned, the train was able to reach speeds of up to 315km/h. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keith Ellison As DNC Chairman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 04:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even though Democrats lost 2016, there is some light in this darkness. By March, the Democratic Party is electing the next DNC chairman.

Sanders endorsed Ellison. I started to believe in Sanders after the special forum 2 weeks ago in Kenosha. I started to appreciate Sanders. Elison is a representative from Minnesota. He is Muslim and a progressive.

I appreciate progressives. They are the kind of people who can give everyone liberties. We seen good things that Obama has done in the last 8 years. Now that Trump and the GOP takes control of the government, they are trying to make things worst.

With Ellison as the DNC chairman, they are able to win back 2018. By then, the GOP are the majority and they will rant about the Democrats all the time. Trump will likely to be exposed and the people who voted him will they they were tricked by voting him.

The Young Turks say they Bernie Sanders, Tulsi Gabbard, and Nina Turner as good potential candidates as DNC chairman or chairwoman. They are populists and progressives. However, I checked mainstream media saying that Alan Dershowitz would resign if Keith Ellison runs or he will help republicans. The mainstream media are trying to discredit him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the psychic, Trump will be a president in name by 2019 as he will be residing in a nearby hotel. There will be no wall, but programs for illegal immigrants. Trump's won't keep promises, but rather selling his supporters out. His cabinet will follow the agenda of dismantling FDR-era social programs. Any readings of such? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I Became a Fan of Trains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 20:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I immigrated to the US, my grandpa and I walk on the streets regularly. Whenever I walk on the streets, we look at the cars on the roads. I became a car person.

As I became older, my grandpa started to decline. We started to walk less. I become less interested in cars. I didn't want to get a driver's license. A few days ago, I get my first non-driver ID.

As I became interested in Japanese culture, that's when I became interested in railways. Railway traveling is very heavy in urban and suburban areas while sparse in rural and regional areas. A few days ago, I realize that JR Hokkaido plans to transfer several sections to 3rd sectors or to close them down and replace with bus systems. Honshu has the highest railway passengers.

I find railways very eco-friendly and efficient. Having cars on the streets pollutes the environment. Railways help connect from one city to another.

As the Shinkansen has expanded into Hokuriku and Hokkaido, sleeper cars are phasing out. Before, sleepers cars were common, now the last blue train Cassiopeia was also phased out. In current terms, to travel from one city to another, people can use airplanes or with the Shinkansen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 04:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will 2018 be certain the GOP get ahold of the Senate in 2018? If yes, will they have a supermajority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
