<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1156</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Senate Democrat says unlikely Trump court pick can clear procedural hurdle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 25 Extraordinary goals of the month [March, 2017] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn: new evidence spy chiefs had concerns about Russian ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Flynn indicates he would testify in Trump-Russia inquiry in exchange for immunity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 21:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Carolina lawmakers vote to end state's so-called 'bathroom bill' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theresa May wants 'deep and special' partnership with EU as UK triggers article 50 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scottish lawmakers back call for independence vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll shows Macron win in French election in shadow of 'Penelopegate' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RBS raises offer to settle 2008 cash call lawsuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FBI Director James Comey told Congress last Monday he had seen no evidence to support the claim.

Trump's mention of wiretapping drew attention away from U.S. intelligence agencies having said that Russia tried to help Trump in the election against Democrat Hillary Clinton by hacking leading Democrats and spreading disinformation.

Moscow denies any such activities. Trump has also dismissed them.

Nunes told reporters on Wednesday that he had briefed Trump "on the concerns I had about incidental collection and how it relates to President-elect Trump and his transition team and the concerns that I have." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intelligence panel chair reviewed sensitive file on White House grounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mosul: 112 civilian bodies pulled from site of coalition airstrike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Messi Vs Ronaldo  Crazy Skills, Assists   Goals Show  2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great video dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kremlin critic detained in tense anti-corruption protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Along with former Trump campaign manager Paul Manafort, who has also offered to testify, Stone was among the Trump associates whose communications and financial transactions were being examined by the FBI and others as part of a larger investigation into possible links with Russian officials, according to a Jan. 20 report in the New York Times.

Without citing any names, FBI Director James Comey confirmed at the committee's public hearing last week that the FBI was investigating possible Russian ties to Trump's campaign as Moscow sought to influence the 2016 election. Stone said he was anxious to testify in public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump ally Stone offers to testify in Russian meddling probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hong Kong: Carrie Lam selected to be city's next leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 11:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a modern romcom featuring a television star and a politician -- complete with a social media twist.
What started out as a diss on Hulu series "The Mindy Project" may lead to a dinner date between the show's actress Mindy Kaling and New Jersey Sen. Cory Booker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GOP health care bill would eliminate many of the taxes and eradicate the individual mandate imposed by Obamacare, officially known as the Affordable Care Act. Instead of the Obamacare subsidies that are tied to income and premiums, the GOP plan provides Americans with refundable tax credits based mainly on age to purchase health insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asked if Republican leaders might pull the bill if they do not get enough votes for passage, Davis said: "That's not something that we're discussing right now. We fully intend to have that vote today and we fully intend to make sure that vote passes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still short on healthcare votes: Republican whip team member </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House of Representatives debates the pros and cons of a Republican bill to roll back Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IS THAT ACTUALLY EMMA WATSON SINGING IN 'BEAUTY AND THE BEAST'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Senate Democrat promises fight to block Trump high court pick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One hundred years ago, people had a very different idea of what it means to be heterosexual. Understanding that shift in thinking can tell us a lot about fluid sexual identities today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 08:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London attack: Police investigating associates of lone attacker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A self-described political moderate, Fukumoto was the first Republican in 26 years to represent the largely middle-class central Oahu district outside Honolulu, capital of the predominantly Democratic state.
She said she originally joined the Republicans out of a sense that Democrats were the status quo party, but she grew gradually disillusioned with the Republicans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> many more are coming soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fukumoto, 33, the youngest Hawaii legislator to serve as House minority leader, said divisive campaign rhetoric during the 2016 elections convinced her the Republican Party no longer reflected her political values or the interests of her state's diverse population.
"This election, I saw members of my party marginalizing and condemning minorities, ethnic or otherwise, and making demeaning comments towards women," she said in an open letter of resignation to the Republican Party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaii lawmaker resigns from Republican Party to join Democrats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The aftermath of the apparent knife attack, which seemingly saw the attacker shot by police, could be seen in Old Palace Yard, the courtyard directly outside parliament.

At least one person could be seen prone on the ground, tended do by ambulance staff. An air ambulance landed on the grass of Parliament Square, and medical crews rushed in. However, they soon stepped back, and there was no sign of anyone being taken away.

While police looked clam, dozens of armed officers could be seen in the area. At one point, a group of about a dozen officers armed with guns arrived, some also carrying shields. They marched into parliament. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration hosting first meeting of anti-ISIS coalition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sky have spoken to an eye-witness who said he saw a 4x4 vehicle crash into a person and a railing near Parliament, before the driver fled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sky have spoken to an eye-witness who said he saw a 4x4 vehicle crash into a person and a railing near Parliament, before the driver fled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minutes after the incident, an emergency services helicopter landed in Parliament Square, as sirens were heard outside.

Air ambulance medics came from the helicopter to assist the casualties.

Two people lay on the ground in the yard. One of them appeared to have had clothes removed as emergency workers attempted to resuscitate the pair.

Parliament Square was closed to traffic.

An ambulance entered the gates to New Palace Yard.

Witness Don Brind told the Press Association he heard shots being fired and saw two people apparently injured on the ground.

Brind, a researcher for MPs, said: I heard some shouting and saw some running out of the corner of my eye and then a short time after that there was a shot. I looked and I saw a civilian on the ground, with somebody standing over him with what I assumed to be a gun.

Then I looked and about 10 yards away, there was a yellow jacketed person on the ground, who appeared to be alive and talking.

He said he assumed the person in the high-visibility jacket was a police officer.

Pictures emerged of a car having crashed into the railings of Parliament at the end of Westminster Bridge

Press Association reporter Laura Harding, who was in Westminster at the time of the incident, said: Everyone has been evacuated into Central Lobby, including a group of schoolchildren and kitchen staff.

Around 15 schoolchildren aged around 10, with armed police coming through the lobby now.

The children are really calm, the teachers are comforting them.

Everyone is standing around on their phones.

There are also a bunch of young people from the Hammersmith Boxing Club in their tracksuits and the British Lionhearts boxing group.

Dennis Burns, who was just entering Parliament for a meeting when the security alert happened, told the Press Association: As I was coming through the doors at Portcullis House, a policeman grabbed someone who was coming in and threw him out.

As we were coming though the glass doors I was told by one security guard to get out while another one told me to get in.

As I walked in I heard a security guard get a radio message saying a policeman has been stabbed.

Then I walked in as police officers and security start rushing out of the front doors on to the street.

When I got inside I was wondering what the hell was going on and I saw dozens of panicked people running down the street. The first stream was around 30 people and the second stream was 70 people.
It looked like they were running for their lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parliament attack: man shot after police officer stabbed at House of Commons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Said Sam Barodi was fired after he refused to cooperate with customs agents who he believed were targeting him because of his ethnicity and religion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The French interior minister has been forced to resign in a row over employing his teenage daughters as parliamentary assistants during the school holidays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its the average numbers of peoples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its version number </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BERLIN Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan has crossed a line by comparing Berlin's government to the Nazis and is no longer welcome in Germany, a senior ally of Chancellor Angela Merkel said on Tuesday.
German media have reported that Erdogan plans to visit Germany this month to rally the estimated 1.4 eligible Turkish voters living here to support a package of new presidential powers in an April 16 referendum.
Erdogan repeated his criticism of Germany and other European countries on Tuesday, saying today's "Fascist and cruel" Europe resembled the pre-World War Two era. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rebuke from Volker Bouffier, vice chairman of Merkel's Christian Democratic Union (CDU) party, reflects growing exasperation over Erdogan's assertions that Germany and other European powers were using Nazi tactics by banning Turkish political rallies in their territories.
"Enough is enough," said Bouffier, who is also premier of Hesse state where the financial capital Frankfurt is located. "Mr. Erdogan and his government are not welcome in our country, and that must be now be understood," he told DLF radio.
German media have reported that Erdogan plans to visit Germany this month to rally the estimated 1.4 eligible Turkish voters living here to support a package of new presidential powers in an April 16 referendum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish President Tayyip Erdogan has crossed a line by comparing Berlin's government to the Nazis and is no longer welcome in Germany, a senior ally of Chancellor Angela Merkel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 11:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he is a Jerk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knows very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lee De Paauw, 18, had met Sophie Paterson while drinking at with a group of friends into the early hours of Sunday morning at a backpackers' hostel in Innisfail in northern Queensland.
According to local media, De Paauw told Paterson that backpackers were more likely to get eaten by crocodiles than Australians, and was ready to back up his words.
Accepting a dare to jump from the wharf into the crocodile-infested Johnstone River, he was grabbed almost immediately by a crocodile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Australian teenager who was bitten by a crocodile when he jumped into a river in northern Queensland on a dare is now recovering in hospital and looking forward to a date with the British backpacker he was trying to impress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Restoration work completed on site of Jesus's tomb in Jerusalem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah big thug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump on Putin: One tough cookie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House tax reform may begin in late spring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 10:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens if New York gets nuked? Scientists simulate 20 MILLION people in massive computer system to see how state would respond to a nuclear attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 08:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump administration appeals partial block of travel ban by Maryland judge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 12:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House jumper on grounds for 15 minutes before caught, Secret Service source says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vanessa Veasley and other users speculated that Trump supporters could launch a boycott of the chain, as they threatened to do after Starbucks Corp (SBUX.O) Chief Executive Howard Schultz vowed to hire 10,000 refugees after Trump's first executive order temporarily banning refugees from certain countries.
"McDonald's already deleted the tweet? lol Well at least Trump supporters can finally boycott something they can actually afford, Veasley (@VanessaVeasley) wrote.
Other users praised the fast-food chain, which has been fighting to reverse two straight years of customer traffic declines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> poor Trump even McDonald's din't own him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump did not respond to McDonald's on Twitter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonald's deletes Trump tweet, says Twitter account compromised </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Franois Fillon's scandal-hit campaign to become France's next president took another blow Tuesday when he was placed under formal investigation on multiple counts, including embezzlement of public funds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Francois Fillon charged over fake jobs scandal as election nears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Merkel is due to meet Trump for more than two hours on Tuesday, followed by a working lunch, her spokesman said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before Trump meeting, Merkel says trade vital for U.S. and Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islamic State frees Mosul prisoners as grip on last major city slips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 11:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> India has returned to Pakistan two boys who strayed across the de facto border in disputed Kashmir and were then accused of links to a militant attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC, ITV launch BritBox video streaming service in U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of Argentine teachers strike in test for Macri's government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle of skills and agility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No,he is good in EFL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finnish foreign minister Timo Soini would step down as leader of the nationalist and eurosceptic Finns party in June, a move which could challenge the future of the country's three-party government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you are right.In football fancy tricks doesn't matter as much as control, skills and  efficiency.We need that from him. We need performance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK scientists estimate that air pollution cuts British people's lives by an average of six months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caterpillar shares rise as import practices scrutinized </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah /u/Bigmatti because they are legends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a letter dated Wednesday, seven Democrats on the Senate Finance Committee urged the panel's Republican chairman, Orrin Hatch, to request the documents from the U.S. Treasury so that lawmakers can review them in a closed session and determine whether the returns can be released to the public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Democrats seek Trump tax returns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gina Miller warns Theresa May of new court battle if Parliament not guaranteed vote on leaving EU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Swedish mother's successful stand against sugar has turned her into a social media sensation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Interior Dept. pick wins Senate confirmation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The White House issued a guest list for the president and first lady, Melania Trump, which included three relatives who lost loved ones at the hands of an individual found to have entered the country illegally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it is kind of Hitlery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. judge dismisses case against Wal-Mart over Mexico bribery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Press Secretary Sean Spicer to hold daily White House briefing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Einstein of football world! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puppy in search of food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tens of thousands of children at more than 800 schools, nurseries and colleges in London are being exposed to illegal levels of air pollution that risk causing lifelong health problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One dead after man drives into crowd in Germany, no sign of terrorism: authorities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In just a few years, the world's second biggest economy has undergone rapid change - leaving an eerie legacy across the landscape.The cities where nobody lives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the king of scorpion goals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zaza beat-down Cristiano </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And also a good human being </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HMB While I do a couple flips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Trump is doing their job very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration in its first month has largely benched the State Department from its long-standing role as the preeminent voice of U.S. foreign policy, curtailing public engagement and official travel and relegating Secretary of State Rex Tillerson to a mostly offstage role. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National Security In first month of Trump presidency, State Department has been sidelined </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i agree that messi is incomparable but on the other hand he is also an awesome player.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No,he has valid alien passport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah whatever and wherever he is from, i am sure he is not from this planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i think that too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Man from Another Planet. A Legend! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 08:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father vs son </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Many houses in Bhutan carry painted phalluses on their walls.Decorating houses with phallic symbols came from a monk who lived in the 15-16th century and adopted blasphemous and unorthodox ways of teaching Buddhism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed /u/tfm_ephemeris </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl with cerebral palsy wins Supreme Court case after her school banned service dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers have detected a record seven Earth-sized planets orbiting a single star </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game of skills between two legends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
