<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9437</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudi Mufti (Islamic scholar) says chess is haram in Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 20:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 23:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Than who?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way you write - Butthurt because I disapproved of Cumberbitch's new role as Dr Strange. You probably sat too hard on your chair in your anger so the action figure got thrust further inwards into your butt - so now you are butthurt and writing back in an overemotional manner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never got pissy you stupid fuck. I just expressed my disapproval. We all have our opinions. What about you, huh? A sheepish motherfucker who will watch every one of his roles just because he is starring in them. I like the show itself. I don't pretty much care about the actor or what other movies he will star in. I will simply not follow every one of his roles. Fuck you and this benedict cumberbatch idol of yours. You probably have a cumberbatch action figure stuck up your ass now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, i did not mean it in a technical sense, you stupid idiot. Back to the Cumberbatch fandom with you, you dumbass fanboy sheep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 22:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you buddy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 21:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, I don't find that any of his other roles would be enjoyable to me. So, why watch something that I would not enjoy? I am not a fanboy so I could watch every single thing that has Cumberbatch in its cast. I am not saying he shoudl be forced to do the BBC shows - of course not. He has his choice to star in Hollywood movies. And, I have my choice not to watch them. But, it is just my opinion that he would suck as any other role than Sherlock. I told you, to each his own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 21:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he can choose whatever he wants to do but I just don't like Hollywood. And, you know, to each his own. I will continue to watch his BBC dramas - just not those other movies he is choosing to do that are impacting Sherlock greatly (we have to wait till 2017 for the next series just because of this Dr Strange shit). After all, Sherlock is the show that shot him to international fame. The BBC is the reason why he is famous. So, I find his leaving aside the BBC and going to Hollywood a little bit disingenuous (again, just an opinion).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 21:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> terrible  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslim shiekh: "This is what will happen to you in your grave. Repent and do good deeds before it is too late!" Acts it out in a video. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 20:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a video I found on a Muslim facebook page: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BkxkfZ2twP4 I uploaded it to YouTube since I cannot post Facebook videos here. I do not know who the original owner of the video is but it was not even the facebook page itself. The video is being wildly circulated across Muslim pages. 

But, this is truly laughable and ridiculous. The guy starts off saying this is how you will be in your grave. Then he says you will plead with God so you can get back to life so you can do good deeds but then it will be too late and that will be it. He also says you will wish for just a single good deed that you have done in your life so you escape punishment. Afterwards, he advises all Muslims to do good deeds and work hard to reap the rewards when the time finally comes.

Then the most ridiculous part comes. He asks God to turn the graves of people who share this video into a heavenly place of eternal rewards and not to make it a "pit" of Hell (probably explains why the video has about 150,000 shares lol). He also asks God to prevail upon people who share this video to do good deeds so they do not face a grim ending when they die. Then he says, with God all things are possible and finally, asks Allah to send his blessings upon the "Prophet" Muhammad. 

I'm absolutely stunned by the immense absurdity. Seriously what the heck was that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 22:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. It is one of the worst cities I have ever visited, pollution wise and everything wise. Traffic is terrible. You will simply never get anywhere. And the city smells awful! I'll never visit there again. Fuck that place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 22:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude..Have you even read the title? I said "it is alleged" - does not mean it's true. Yes - it was alleged to have been so by Ayto but not me. I am simply reporting on this matter. Take a little bit of breath, man.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 08:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if you had actually completed reading the article, it goes on: "In 1990, John Ayto brought Le Fucker to wider public attention when he claimed in his Dictionary of Word Origins that the surname was the earliest recorded instance of the English swear word fuck" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 08:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is why I said "alleged"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the first written example of the F-word is alleged to have appeared as a personal name of 13th century Englishman, John le Fucker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 08:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
