<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6816</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of another suburban region with a transit system as extensive as the LIRR. For many people such as myself, I can take a 15 minute walk to my nearest station, take it to Jamaica, hop on the AirTrain, and board my flight at JFK without ever stepping foot in a car or dealing with traffic. Same goes for heading into the city. 

If the station's not walking distance, the vast majority of LI-ers can drive to their station in 5-10min and park. As much as I love to hate on LIRRs many annoyances, it's def a game changer to have that option. It would be very missed if I were to ever move somewhere else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internal documents show Ubers autonomous cars travel an average of close to 0.8 miles before the safety driver has to take over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dealt with this problem a lot with counterfeit MacBook chargers that were labeled as official Apple but actually fake. As others have said, [Fakespot](http://fakespot.com/) all the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Map of Arizona's water supply </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up Public Private Partnerships. It's actually a pretty clever way to get infrastructure built quickly and on budget when done right. The gist of how it works is that the "Private Investor", who is essentially a development company, foots the bill for the project themselves. They make their money back plus some profit by taking a certain % of tax revenue from that infrastructure until they've made the money. 

The benefits are that unlike gov, they don't need to go through the length process of getting the budget/tax hike approval to fund it, the cost is spread out. Also, because they don't start making the money back until that piece of infrastructure is actually being used, they have an incentive to finish it quickly. PPP is becoming more and more widely used because of those advantages. I pray Trump's administration doesn't find a way to screw it up, because it can result in a massive amount of modernized infrastructure, and fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once I had the idea to make it look like the Apple logo had wings, I HAD to put GS in the middle lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
