<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you work at the business layer? I guess there is lot more coding work there because of frequent change in business logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. This is the first time I am hearing about someone using proprietary coding language at work. Mind sharing some details? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 08:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's difficult to work in an environment where even your immediate seniors don't have confidence in what you are building. The sooner you switch, the better your career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 08:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I shouldn't be asking this, but still: do you enjoy your work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 07:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reportees also respect a manager more when they know she can go into the trenches if need be. It is also difficult to fool such a manager, which can be frustrating at times! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 07:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  write code 80%+ of the time. The rest is testing the code

Whoa, testing is *outside* the 80% of coding time? I'd be wary of what you build then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 07:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta protect your internship days, man. I wouldn't care much about this agile fluff during my internship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 07:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've taken a separate side job doing consulting work

I don't think that is strictly legal! I, on the other hand, keep myself engaged by answering questions on Stack Overflow.

How did you land this consulting work, if you don't mind sharing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, it must becoming tiring if you are expected to keep getting promoted *by your company*.  It should be an individual's choice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure the woman at the end, with huge muscles and everything, did the trick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To each his own! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 05:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't do any calorie calculations, because not worrying about that was precisely the reason I started IF.

But I see your point. I am now thinking of moving to 18:6 or 20:4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our discussions too, at times, go beyond the 15 min reserved for standup. But we make the team optional.

If the entire team gets sucked into post-standup discussions, that would be a waste of time for everyone, in an *agile* way or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you planning to move back to an Individual Contributor role then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I am in the same boat as your current situation. *Just* writing code seems to be a menial job IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 04:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  employee #1

You would also be rewarded well if the startup becomes a hit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
