<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 23:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My appetite has been terrible ever since I was a kid.
I can't do it,  it makes me sick to eat sometimes, but my family makes me. It just can't go down or else I feel ill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 21:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, you can be both. In the few rare months I wasn't with my problems, I was still classed as different. 
I'd say when it's negatively affecting their life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 21:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No chance of that for me. UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else like this? You get to the very edge of doing but at the very last minute something stops you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 20:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got this a few times. The only time which I very nearly did it was when I got drunk,  but someone fucking stopped me.
I'm so frustrated that I can only do it when drunk! I might just have to bite the bullet because it's so frustrating! 
I did not want to be saved, but of course you fucking had to. That's just made me so mad and what the fuck about how I'm going to do this!  
I have no idea why I'm like this, I've been toying with this idea for a long time, nearly do it and then I get stopped!
I hate this, fuck...sorry turned into a rant but oh well. I think I'm just gonna have to do it even with the fear of the unknown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully within the next few days, possibly even hours.
I attempted a few days ago and got stopped. I've been looking at other places today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't get to read the full thing, but there are snippets of it.
This is our choice, and this is our subreddit to express our choice. 
This post will not change anyone's minds, and this is certainly not the place to say it.
We have already made up our minds, where some of us is getting up the courage, planning, or just biding our time, it's our choice and you can't change this. Respect it and be gone from here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep!
I've said about attempts,  I even posted a picture of the bridge I was planning of jumping off while at the bridge.
So I'd say it's safe, you just have to be very careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! 
Might be joining you soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 19:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm OK with talking to strangers these days but pretty much everyone thinks I'm weird. It's so harmful but schools don't take it seriously.
I know I'm not going that far with life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 13:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean. While its not that major, I have Dyspraxia,  which in turn, singled me out to be different. 
That caused bullying,  which cause some of my mental health issues.
2 of them can go away.
PTSD can't.  It's hell. 
My eating has been fucked since I was a kid. 
I'm basically fucked for life.
I know there's help, got if before but it only works for a short time. I can't deal with this bullshit anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 10:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried a few days ago, and got stopped.  
People care too much about total strangers, or they do it for bragging rights. Tell the rest of the world to let us die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 10:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gun would be the quickest. But I live in the UK.  
My method is either jumping or train.  
5 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 10:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! My family wants me to redo my room. 
It's bizzare talking about it when I have no idea how much longer I'll be here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 10:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know exactly what you mean. There is nothing left for us here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 17:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite band actually encourges people to engage in self-destructive behavior, suicide included. 
Their name is Shining, and they are DSBM, which is a sub-genre of black metal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 13:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be a lot more easier then dragging out and trying to prevent the inevitable.  
But as they class it as a loss of a person they know, why shouldn't we stop them trying to die?  
But, with some cases, you've technically lost the person, or they have lost themselves, so what's the point in prolonging the hell they live in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 13:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know my family will be devastated, but I've got nothing going on for me. I've been living like this for 8 years, nearly 9 as it is my 21st Birthday in nearly a month.  
But I've been living like this since I was 12, and it never seems to end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 12:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah possibly, I think that was it.  
I am too because I'd be fucked, my parents have no idea how I am, everyone thinks I'm going relativly ok apart from my eating.  
I think we are getting brigaded/trolled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 12:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't live in the area, I live a couple hours away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 20:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that was my mistake.  Enjoying the view. Might have to bite the bullet next time. And FYI - I really don't care that you called me a lad, just thought you should know I'm a girl :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got stopped! That's fucking annoying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 12:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK,  so I got to the bridge, drank a bottle of cider. Took a couple tablets. 
Decided to enjoy the view from the bridge.
Walked over to where I was going to climb.
Someone noticed me and came over and grabbed my fucking arm and wouldn't let go! Was going to call the Police but I ran off. 
Started feeling sick so I was going to take the bus back to the station. Threw up on the bus. Went to nearby Boots to get water and wet wipes to clear up, fainted so they called the fucking EMTS. 
Lied and said I had too much to drink, they wanted to call my next-of-kin.
Said my friend would pick me up, gave them my real name but fake address (oops!) 
Then walked to the station, got on the train. Got to the station I needed to change, got off went to a waiting room.
Fell asleep. Threw up again.
Then was asleep for the whole journey back.
No-one knows this has happened.
FUCK ME AND FUCK THIS WORLD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen if a non diabetic overdosed on insulin? How much would they have to take to die and how long would it take? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 16:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 16:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Climb and I hate drinking and I just feel a bit tipsy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the insulin?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morphine? 
We got a lot of medication, no morphine though.
Got codine,  seroquel, insulin and a few others I can't rerember  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know,  but I'm in the UK and still live with family.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 14:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of people here as it's a landmark, but the left side is closed to the public anyway 
I wished it wouldn't fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 14:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't know how much it's gonna hurt when I hut the ground but I do know it's around a 5 second fall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 14:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it's me making that call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 00:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see suicide as a bad thing, it's just working up the courage to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 18:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pratice  restraint?
If I can't any Xanax I'm gonna combine alcohol and Seroquel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 17:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it works, If not I'll come back within the next few days but have a few drinks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be a gun, falling from 250 foot takes around 4 seconds, internal bleeding out takes around 30 seconds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same haha I've just been walking around here
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was planning on getting drunk.
Or taking Seroquel or Xanax but I'm not sure how the Seroquel would work, I've got it with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why am I such a coward :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 14:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 14:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How fatal is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would happen if you used a heart defibrillator on a consious person with a healthy heart when they didn't need it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 13:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long would it take someone to fall 250 ft? And how long would it take to die when they hit the bottom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 08:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 23:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can finally get answers to question I couldn't think of anywhere else to ask! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So hitting the ground after that fall and then dying would take less then 30 seconds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that how you die from falling? 
I thought internal bleeding took hours 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would your body react falling 250ft and how quickly would you die? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 19:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 14:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Why's that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 10:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm I see, thanks for the help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 10:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a black sheep. I stick out like a sore thumb, not accepted anywhere. All people have done is hurt me, or want to change me in some way, be it eating more or wanting me to decorate my room when I said I don't want to. The response? Calling me stupid.  
My real Dad's side of the family exclude me, so I know they wouldn't care. 
Also my problems aren't temporary. I've had them since I was 12. Always flucating in intensity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 10:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure how much of us are, but I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 10:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, all he did was ask you a question, stop being stuck-up.  
And for me, I know how it will affect my family, but it's painful and I'm never ever going to get completly better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 09:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, I see your point.  
What if the method was jumping? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 09:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, I see your point.  
What if the method was jumping? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 09:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, I see your point.  
What if the method was jumping? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If someone suicidal but was scared of surviving took a whole load of alcohol before attempting, would it help them not to be so scared? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 13:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 12:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually had a gun pointed at my head.   
I said "Haha I know you won't actually do it!"   
And then I stuck up my middle finger  
But then again it was my abusive ex and we were in the street at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicidal here.  
Not gonna lie, it's seeing no way out and being hopeless. 
 And being complety overrun with problems.
With me, I have mental health issues, and no matter what I do, even if they get better, they get worse again, and I can't handle it anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your in the UK you can kill me if you want :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DBSM is a good genre. I suggest the bands Shining and Forgotten Life, there's another band called Coldlife but they aren't as depressing.  
2 death metal bands called Cattle Decapitation and Necrophagist are good too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 tablespoons? 
So what happens if it's like around 6? 
Ground up I'm guessing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 19:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep correct, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 19:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah that's fine, wasn't expecting it to stay up :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 17:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bristol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those who have tried and failed, how did you build up the courage in the first place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried it too, I want to do it again but because I failed I'm scared of failing 
I've already chose the method, I'm researching how to climb over the barriers,  and was just wondering what your experiences were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any idea on how to get over this? PM :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Look at this I can't use because it's too hot but I really wanna do it again  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 17:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 11:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh haha I'm a dumbass xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 10:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does MOS mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 09:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha trying not to cut after months so I've stopped eating, lost 6/8 lbs in a month yay xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 11:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People always think I'm weird.  
My best mate said that he think's I'm the weirdest person he's ever met, but he absolutey loves me for it.  
You shouldn't have to change, just learn how to embrace it and people will follow your lead. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 10:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are kids better then adults?  
They're tighter :P

Another one! With a bit of background, I had to be fostered back when I was 3 and the guy they put me with was a sexually abusive pedophile.  
But anyway, I wonder if he was a dentist due to how many fillings he gave me.  
Would explain why I hate Dentists xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 12:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of a worse joke haha but its dark af. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 04:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was really bad, all the time.
But I had a sorta casual thought about it earlier today, involving a train.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 11:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi :)  
First off all disclamier. It will get better, but it will not go away complety, you just learn how to cope with it and the symptoms then fade, but then it can come back with a vengance, but you will learn.  
I tend to listen to music and go for walks.  
But there's something called grounding techniques.  
This can be like getting an ice cube from a freezer and holding it in your hands, getting something to fiddle with, or trying to stop 5 things of differnt colours. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 10:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much did that burn? 
How's your stomach? :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 13:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that PTSD can get better, but it can never go away. You just learn how to cope with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 10:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 10:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I've been subscribed to it and they've now banned it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 20:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the main one is my mental health is shocking and it pisses me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My psychiatrist has told me he's almost certain that I have C-PTSD and BPD. I don't know how to process this as my Mum has been diagnosed with BPD and is getting intensive outpatient treatment for it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 04:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's referring me to get an assessment.  
I know I definitely have PTSD, classic symptoms: Nightmares, flashbacks, hypervilagance ect.  
But I'm not so sure with the BPD. I hardly ever get angry, I can get clingy. I'd really hate to be abandoned. I get very extreme moodswings, I'm very impulsive and I've always had trouble making and keeping friends. I'm also very suicidal and I used to self-harm. My Mum has always said she sees a lot of herself in me. I know it's not been diagnosed yet, but I never thought this could be a possibly for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 14:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's going to hurt like he'll, but getting absolutely plastered will take the edge of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 10:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to me in the past </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 09:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thoes are my 3 favorite Billy Talent songs. I absouly love every song on that list, Slayer being my favorite band ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 09:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, I'm thinking quite a few songs, I'll list them/  
Papa Roach - Thrown Away  
Billy Talent - Devil On My Shoulder  
Project Deadman - Trapped   
Yung Simmie - Fancy  
Slipknot - Metabolic  
Korn - Daddy  
Machine Head - Five  
Slipknot - Gently  
Dark Lotus - My Head Is Haunted  
Billy Talent - Nothing To Lose  
Metallica - No Leaf Clover  
Shining - Claws Of Perdition  
Billy Talent - Pins And Needles  
Slayer - Seasons In The Abyss   
Slayer - Eyes Of The Insane  
The songs I'm more gearing towards is SLAYER \m/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only thing that gives me comfort is imagining my suicide. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 08:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suffer from mental health problems that are getting worse. Psychosis, Depresssion and PTSD. It's the PTSD which is really making life hell, espeilly the nightmares. I wake up terrified most nights and I find it really hard to get to sleep, which is making me tired and it's just making things worse.  
I'm already on Medication and I'm starting up therapy again.  
There are other things wrong. My Mum has BPD and she's starting to bottle up her emotions which is making me worried.  
My sister is going through a stressful time with her job.  
My Dad's physical health is getting worse.  
I'm worried about everyone in my family, and they are worried about me. I might get one of my friends who doesn't know how bad I'm doing to buy me a bottle of vodka if I give him the money so I can finally get the courage to jump. I just can't handle it anymore. Sorry for the long read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 01:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's flashbacks and nightmares which affect me the most.  
I do get terribly anxious and have panic attacks, hypervilagence, intrusive memories as well, but by far the worse is the nightmares and flashbacks.  
Flashbacks can be caused by some expected things, some unexpected. Unfamillar bathrooms, old men, walking past my abusive ex's house, people grabbing me ect   
These can send me into being really scared, being suicidal or crying.  
Nightmare are worse for me. Flashbacks I can handle because I know more or less when they could happen, but waking up crying and shouting and being terrified is hell. I've been sleeping with a bat by me since I was 6. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 01:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I used to self-harm, don't anymore. But I'm really struggling a lot with being suicidal at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 [F4R] I want to die. Please be a distraction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 21:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 [F4R ] I want to die. Help, I'm really sorry :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 19:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 13:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you you too. See you there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life just isn't for me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 07:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought that. I have a myriad of mental health problems, I'm not normal and will never be. Just have to get enough courage to CTB then the pain will end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How quickly can I lose a stone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 22:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have to go to the Dentist tomorrow which always triggers flashbacks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 21:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have ti go to the Dentist as part of my tooth broke. Problem is, going to the dentist always triggers me to have flashbacks. How to deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 02:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but I always shake afterwards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My nightmares are getting so much worse, and I don't know how to cope </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 17:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the past week my nightmares have gotten so much worse. I've only been sleeping for 3-4 hours a night which isn't normal for me. I had to go away on Residential for 4 nights, which triggered this. But since I've came home my nightmares have been the same, stopping me from going to sleep because I've been too scared to, so I've been staying up at like 3-4 in the morning to completey exhaust me, but I always wake up around 7-8 to get ready for my course which starts at 9:30 and carries on till 4. The lack of sleep is really catching up on me. It's making me all shivery with headaches and I'm constantly tired and snappy. I don't know how much longer I can handle this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've heard from someone that one of the guys that sexually assaulted me is getting over-friendly with a girl on his bus. I'm scared for her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 23:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex let me know this. He said that he warned the girl about what happened to me with him, and she said that she will keep an eye out for him. But I'm still really scared. It's been a couple of hours since he told me but I've had 2 panic attacks already and getting intense moodswings. I can't help it, I don't want anyone else to go what I've gone through. It's hell. But the only way I can keep anyone else safe is to go to the Police, but they didn't help before so I'm very reluctant to. But it'll be all my fault if it happens to anyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 23:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone I know has suggested EMDR to me, and I don't know what to think about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going on a residential trip for 3 nights with a group of new people. There is going to be triggers for my PTSD and I'm not sure how to handle them, any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 01:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm going to be going on a residential trip for 3 nights. I have to sleep in a room with some other girls, luckily the boys are in a different room. But whenever I have a shower or go to the toilet in a new place it's very likely I'll have a flashback. Even at home I have to listen to music in the shower. I also know my sleeping is going to be really bad. Another thing is when I have nightmare I sometimes shout in my sleep and I don't know if I should mention that or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 20:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah could do. I've got some comfort items I could bring.
I'll have to think about it as I wouldn't want to wake anyone up with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 19:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it's something we have to do, and I can't really avoid these triggers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going on a residential trip for 3 nights with a group of new people. There is going to be triggers and I'm not sure how to handle them, any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 19:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm going to be going on a residential trip for 3 nights. I have to sleep in a room with some other girls, luckily the boys are in a different room. But whenever I have a shower or go to the toilet in a new place it's very likely I'll have a flashback. Even at home I have to listen to music in the shower.  I also know my sleeping is going to be really bad. Another thing is when I have nightmare I sometimes shout in my sleep and I don't know if I should mention that or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The more time I spend with people the more I realize I'm not normal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 10:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not normal. It's so painfully obvious.  I can't socialise properly. I only have 1 friend, and my ex who is staying my friend to be polite. I'm a worthless burden who should kill myself. I'm just not fucking normal and that makes me feel so bad about myself :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 11:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mental health problems which is always changing between good and bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 11:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got so closed but was stopped by a train station staff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 15:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went down to the slope, train was in 5 minutes,  got spotted and pulled back by him. He wanted to call the Police but I ran off before he could. I'm so frustrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I will be scared, but I have to remember something. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 11:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That the unbearable physical pain will end the unbearable mental pain. I'm terrified of surviving,  and what comes after death. But I'll finally be at peace.  Hopefully with this in mind I shall be able to do it soon. Wish me luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 [F4R] Devon, UK - Lonely and suicidal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 07:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Netflix, some games, Reddit and listening to music. I'm trying to find some more Metal to listen to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 07:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I have no social skills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 07:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching Netflix or on Reddit listening to music </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 07:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Monsters Universty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 01:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My day went alright, went out for a family meal and watched a film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 [F4R] Devon, UK - Giving up on life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 01:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me your experiances, or we can chat about Netflix.  
I'm also trying to find some more Metal to listen to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 01:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know exactly how you feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 23:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever things get better and bearable they suddenly go downhill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 22:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems very hopeless. I can't tell my family what I'm planning because they'll get worried  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 21:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the same boat. I sometimes skip my meds but my family catches on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to cut again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 14:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm over a year clean but I've been getting worse and it's so tempting. I deserve it. I've been looking at my self harm pics and I've relised how much I miss it. Help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of a pro suicide forum where we can discuss methods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 08:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 07:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mental health problems that started when I was 12. I ended up in Hospital when I was 16 for 7 months because of them. I'm now 20, and it keeps on changing between good and bad. I'm sick of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 07:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overdosing or drowning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 11:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Depression, Psychosis and PTSD so I know what it's like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 22:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been on meds for a few months and no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 20:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I can  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 19:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I'm gonna need it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm getting closer and closer to killing myself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 09:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last time I was at the cliffs I sat with my feet over the edge.  
I think I'm getting more courageous. Next time on Friday I'm gonna try hanging myself over the edge using my arms.  
I'm nearly not a coward anymore, so my voices are happy with me for putting myself in danger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 09:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mental health problems keeps on changing between good and really bad.  
There's always seem to be something wrong with this planet, the human race is a parasite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 23:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going back to the cliff on Friday.  
I'm already in therapy and meds, what else can I do?  
It's just my mental health keeps getting worse and then getting better, then worse again. It's just gone downhill in the past few days and I'm just so sick of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 20:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been admitted to hospital before, it went alright but I really don't want it to happen again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 20:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try and tell her tommorow but I'm still scared of her reaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
