<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7891</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 16:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 14:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm... Aliens, not Alien. But awesome nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 13:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I was brilliant and it was a bloody good laugh!"

Plunkett   Macleane is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 01:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One in ten seems quite low to me. Numbers in the UK for regular (always/usually/often) TV viewing with second-screen activity are right around 30%* and I would have thought that viewing the debates would have generated more social media interaction than the majority if TV viewing.

* Source is a consumer research exercise for my employer which I conducted earlier this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 15:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hail Eris! All hail Discordia!

If you haven't read "Illuminatus!" By Robert Shea and Robert Anton Wilson, you should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some if the ones I've met do. But it wasn't meant to be an equation; hence "tendency". There are lots of SGI people who don't come across like that at all. But there are also lots who do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 11:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear every word of that and share very similar experiences. It put me right off "joining" SGI. However, not being one to ignore the evidence of my senses, I have to say that daimoku (chanting nam-myoho-renge-kyo) actually works for me, although I was similarly freaked out by the chanting "to" the gohonzon scroll. BTW, I use both daimoku and insight meditation

I see a lot of benefit in the practice of Nichiren Buddhism and I see a lot of good intent in the SGI organisation, but I wonder if there's a natural tendency for humans to gravitate towards "creepy cultishness" (for want of a better phrase) in any spiritual organisation that promotes egalitarian values. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 10:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, sorry. Tokyo Marui. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 01:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There used to be an airsoft kit that went on a TM M1A1. Ibelieve they're well out of production, but I have one on my shelf and I can tell you they're awesome. :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 01:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pffft! It's not a proper Halloween costume if you don't have to spend all night explaining it.

I would have recognised it, and I would have told you you had the best costume at the party.

"One, two, three, *branch*, goddamnit!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 14:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The photography is also incredible - those landscapes in the final reel are jaw-droppingly beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 21:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find the reference now but there was an analyst/pundit's comment early in the campaign to the effect that Romney is exactly the kind of person who wouldn't even think to thank you for letting him merge in front of you in traffic because he would honestly believe that he had spotted an opportunity himself and just took advantage of it. That pretty much nailed it for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 17:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me neither, and I'm a proper film buff too. Everyone I tell is incredulous, but here's the thing - I really, really hate gangster movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 02:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, all that's good and it does explain that scene a little more. However, it doesn't explain why a xenobiologist who gets excited about alien worms would pass up the chance to examine primary evidence (ie. the corpse) of an alien HUMANOID. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 05:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thelma and Louise? American Gangster? Black Hawk Down? The Duellists?

That's assuming that his being the auteur behind Alien and Blade Runner - two of absolutely the most influential science fiction films of all time - is not enough for ya! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 05:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe Scott actively resisted putting the deleted scenes back into an "extended version" on the Blu-Ray/DVD and has said "there will be no Director's Cut - the theatrical release *is* the Director's Cut."

For my part, I literally cannot understand why they would cut those scenes. Not only can you see where the pure deletes have been crudely hacked away in the final version, but also every one of the deleted scenes that was replaced with something else was much better than what we saw in the cinema - especially when Mutant Fifield comes back, and the extended axe fight/chase between Shaw and the Engineer through the lifeboat, both of which feel much closer to the Alien films than what we're left with in the theatrical release. 

And many of those scenes explain some of the character oddities. For example, the angry make-up sex scene between Holloway and Shaw explains why he's so depressed and turns to drink ("We came to *talk* to them!"), and the extended scene with Vickers and Weyland contextualises that stentorian "...father!" that stands out so badly in the final edit.

Still no explanation of why an exobiologist would be afraid to examine an alien corpse, but would try to tickle an obviously aggressive alien snake-thing. Or why "I'm here for the money, not to make friends" Fifield is suddenly smoking weed in his helmet. Maybe that's why he got lost, even though he's the mapping expert...

The most telling change IMHO is the final sequence of Shaw recovering David's head and body. In the final release she actually apologises for zipping his head up in a bag ("I'm sorry," she says. "It's quite alright," he assures her). This is the [artificial] person directly responsible for the horrific death of her partner, her alien pregnancy, the death of the entire crew, and for putting the whole Earth at risk, and she apologises tenderly for bruising his dignity?! On at least a couple of occasions, he's gone out of his way to cruelly and personally torture her about her father's death, for god's sake! In the deleted scene, she picks him up by the hair, calls him a "fucking robot" and shoves him, protesting into the sack. Much more believable.

"Deleted Scenes Shaw" is way ballsier than the one we see in the theatrical release, almost a worthy successor to Ripley. Almost.

Can't wait for the inevitable fan edit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 14:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It originally came from the expense of making film reels for cinema exhibition. The distributor would print so many copies of the film and use them for the US theatrical release, then pack them up and ship them to Europe. After the European run, the reels would be distributed to the Far East and South America. This is where we get the Region 1/2/3 thing on DVDs and it has screwed up the gifts management side of things no end as we move towards 100% digital distribution.

Today, it is a way to optimise marketing spend. Global campaigns are very expensive and a staggered release means the distributor can manage spend on a territory-by-territory basis based on the performance of the film in previous territories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 14:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
but as long as the world bends over backwards to help us do whatever we want

Oh bless you, that's hilarious! Thanks for brightening my day. Your innocence and navet is refreshing.

Over half the world's population is explicitly invested in opposing the US agenda. You forgot about China, North Korea, the entire Muslim world, sub-Saharan Africa, most of South America...? Damnit, even Russia is making rumblings again! Or by "world" did you mean Europe and the British Commonwealth? Because let's see how much support the US gets when it launches a war of conquest in Iran. Isolationism has its downsides too.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 04:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Dancers_at_the_End_of_Time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 03:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, winning what, exactly?

http://rankingamerica.wordpress.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 02:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Global politics should not be about "winning". And that's the most worrying thing about America's foreign policy for the last few decades - the assumption that the world is a zero-sum game. Please stop fucking it up for the rest of us who already grew out of that phase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 01:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm totally getting this line engraved on my new MacBook :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 01:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THANK YOU for saying this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 14:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you're certainly not alone in that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 14:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even so, reporting it will help stop him reregistering with a different account and therefore help make eBay safer for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 13:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes no sense at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 12:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fincher distanced himself from Alien3 because he felt that the studio screwed him in the final edit. That's why there is no director's commentary available. There is, however, a Director's Cut which is a much, much better film. Apart from a few script changes and deleted scenes, the majority of the difference is in the pacing and it's incredible how much difference it makes.

Having said that, it is still a problematic addition to the franchise. But it's not bad, and it does bring a new dimension to the saga. Without spoilering, I think the final scenes would have been a fitting conclusion to the Alien story and you would be missing out if you ignored it.

TL;DR: Alien, Aliens, Alien3, Prometheus and [Prometheus' untitled sequel]. That's the Alien canon as far as I'm concerned. Ignore anything with a Predator in it and Alien Resurrection is an abortion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 12:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, you buy software from a seller in China and it's eBay's fault that you get stiffed?! If you file a Significantly Not As Described (SNAD) dispute, you will not only get your money back, but you will get the seller banned for selling counterfeit goods  - and you owe that to the community.  

Also, in future, if you pay with PayPal even off eBay you get buyer protection which means that even if the seller runs off with your money, PayPal will refund you at their own expense as long as the seller has lied to you (ie said it was legit but sent you a counterfeit/pirated item).

Try that with Amazon... ;-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help finding quality fake goatee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 04:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, /r/cosplayers, I'm planning a Walter White (Breaking Bad) cosplay for a Halloween party, but due to my work I can't grow a beard. All of the fake stick-on beards I can find look  more like Tribbles than facial hair. Any suggestions on where to look or what to search for? I'm in the UK, so UK or EU sources would be preferred. Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 17:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a fictional exploration, granted, but "Babel 17" by Alfred Bester is an exploration of the cognitive effects of operating in a language with no way to construct the concept "I". http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Babel-17 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 01:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the case of the Alien, my pet theory is that the lack of eyes forces you to "look it in the teeth." And of course eyes are the windows to the soul, so no eyes no soul right? Worst thing they did in the whole canon was give the Newborn eyes in Alien Resurrection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
