<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2952</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bungie - Please make the Kings Fall raid drop gear at max light level for the relevant difficulty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 15:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 10:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This applies to other aspects of the Grimoire, for example you also have the fact that Major/Ultras don't count toward grimoire kills for that specific enemy. Daft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 17:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God this does NOT bode well for me. Last time there were gauntlet engrams I bought 5 - 2x sunbreakers, 2x no backup plans and another random one (Can't remember) I didnt need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please make Ward of Dawn what it should always have been - impenetrable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 11:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grimoire card for WoD states:

"Open a pocket in the universe, an impregnable fortress for you and your allies. The mighty Ward allows Guardians to hold key points and gather their strength in the face of overwhelming opposition."

I cannot count the amount of times I have used it in Crucible to be instantly broken by a Nova bomb or Golden Gun which then leads to a few of us being slaughtered. 

Then there is being killed by the blade dancers Psion-like arc wave through it. Not to mention the Psion's themselves! (Prison of Elders in particular)

Bungie can we please make WoD what it should always have been? Impregnable.

It wouldn't be OP IMO as we still cannot shoot out of it and it ultimately restricts the players inside it to the location it is placed meaning the opposition can wait for it to run out or run into it shotguns blazing still. 

Yes it would give those players a chance to cap an objective with very little chance of you taking it back straight away but this leaves you open to go and take another.

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 14:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha dont worry, it happens to us all at some point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
