<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject670</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 00:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If one act of anger makes a terrorist we would all be terrorists.

Depends on what you mean by "one act of anger." I'm pretty sure one act of anger IS all it takes, depending on the act. Just like one act of murder is all it takes to be a murder, one act of sedition to be a seditionist. [Seditionist](http://www.thesaurus.com/browse/seditionist?s=t) being synonymous with terrorist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 17:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was angry at the money changers charging usury or what we call interest. 

That's not in the Bible. Where are you getting this information?

He flipped their tables and scattered the coins.

You forgot his whip: *"So he made a whip out of cords, and drove all from the temple courts, both sheep and cattle; he scattered the coins of the money changers and overturned their tables."* John 2:15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 23:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might not have said it, but the Bible is pretty clear [Pontius Pilate](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pontius_Pilate) was the guy in change of the crucifixion. And, that the recorded crime was "king of the jews." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 20:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first book of the New Testament was writing about 30 years after he died, and the last was written over a hundred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 16:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, [Poe's Law](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Poe%27s_law) and all that. I mean, look at the comment below yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 16:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jews are from Israel. Do you know where Israel is on a map? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 15:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Romans didn't handle Jewish religious crimes, only civil ones. Thus, the Romans couldn't crucify him for 'blasphemy.' His *official* crime was claiming that he was King of the Jews instead of Caesar, also known as sedition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 14:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In the temple courts he found people selling cattle, sheep and doves, and others sitting at tables exchanging money. So he made a whip out of cords, and drove all from the temple courts, both sheep and cattle; he scattered the coins of the money changers and overturned their tables." John 2:14-15

And "Australia."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They like ignoring this about him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 14:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 14:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many countries today classify acts of sedition as terrorism. Jesus was crucified for sedition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 14:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many countries today classify acts of sedition as terrorism. Jesus was crucified for sedition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 05:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So he made a whip out of cords, and drove **all** from the temple courts, both sheep and cattle; he scattered the coins of the money changers and overturned their tables." John 2:15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 00:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Torah is not the Bible in the same way Jews aren't Christians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 00:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Historical_Jesus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 21:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was executed by the Romans under the charge of sedition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 15:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the ways to spot a psychopath is their lack of shame and social anxiety, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 02:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negative energy isn't a real thing? You sure? Cuz the [Casimir effect](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Casimir_effect) has been observed experimentally.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Negative_energy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pop the balloon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 19:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 15:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I just assumed they wanted me to watch all their videos over and over until I got it, which would be never.

So they'd get more ad revenue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 15:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the drink is named after the bombing from [the Troubles](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Troubles), which is why its not a good idea to try and order one in Ireland. You can get them just about anywhere else. I'm Irish American and I like drinking them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 05:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Terror Attack](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dublin_and_Monaghan_bombings)

Or

[The Drink](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Irish_Car_Bomb) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 04:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's EXPLICIT that racism involves treating another race differently BECAUSE you think your race is superior. 

I recommend you actually read the full definition. The first definition in most dictionaries say something about 'superior,' but the second definition normally just says "racial prejudice or discrimination." An example of which would be not letting someone drink at a water fountain because of their race, or not letting them into an awards ceremony for the same reason.

That's why people in non-power positions in society, can't be racist because there is no mechanism in place for them to exact that perceived superiority over another race. 

You don't need a "mechanism in place for them to exact that perceived superiority over another race" to be racist. If that was the case, Hitler wasn't racist when he wrote *Mein Kampf,* since he was in jail at the time and lacked agency to follow through on his views. Yet, I'm not sure how anyone could read that book and think it wasn't written by a racist. I mean, go look how people describe that book. 'Racist' is used a lot. Anyway, even under your definition, the awards ceremony would certainly be considered a "mechanism in place for them to exact that perceived superiority over another race." Proving superiority is pretty much the point of most awards ceremonies.

They can be prejudiced and bigoted, but by definition can't be racist.

Sigh... "bigoted" is a *synonym* of "racist." Again, if you have an issue with this semantic fact, I recommend you take it up with Merriam-Webster (or whatever your preferred dictionary is) and ask them to remove the secondary definition of the word.

Don't cheapen the definition of the word because you feel like throwing it around. It seems that you need to take it up with the dictionary.

This is ironic because I am the one that started this conversation by quoting the *actual* definition of the word. But, as is indicative of dramatic irony, I guess I can't expect you to see the humor in it.

Anyway, I am done with this **literal** semantic argument. I am well beyond caring if you will accept the given definition of the term or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 18:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was never tried because separate is never equal. It was never tried because 'separate but equal' is an impossibility.

But, look, regardless of anything else, if you hold that members of different races *should be* treated differently (for good reasons or bad), then I'm going to call you racist, because that's what the word 'racist' means.  

If you have a problem with that, take it up with the dictionary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 23:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sacrosanctity of your mother isn't in question. I am sure she is a lovely woman.

I'm more asking why it matters if their is a real (and -again- I am sure very nice) woman his meaningless words are in the vacuity of.  But, as I type these words I feel like they -too- are meaningless. So, I think this will be my last post on this topic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 22:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, obviously what that guy said was stupid and horrible (as well as incentive, rude... etc.)

But, do you think it will affect your mom -in any real way- that he typed those words? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether or not you realize it, your logic is essentially the same people that advocated for 'separate but equal' used. That as long as the organizations enacting such social norms *think* the races are equal, they should be allowed to segregate them.

Now, I'm not saying **people** have to have diversity in their friend choices. People -certainly- are free to choose who they hangout with. If the only reason you don't want to hang out with me is the color of my skin, I'm not going to picket the white house.

But, I am saying -historically- when **organizations** make discriminatory choices or rules based *solely* on race, it hasn't been a good thing.

An eye for an eye leaves the whole world blind - Gandhi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 16:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think **if** your goal is to minimize something, **then** it's *probably* a bad idea to do it.

But, since I don't really know what the goal of BET is (or -really- anything about it other than that one commercial I saw a few years back and what I've read on this thread) I can't accurately comment on it being 'good' or 'bad' in pursuit of that unknown -to me- goal.

For example, if instead of attempting to minimizing racism, their real goal is to make money filling a niche entertainment market, then I would *guess* (again, with next to no information) that they're likely doing a **good** job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 16:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant: "If people still are [delineating based on race], then people still are [delineating based on race]."  As in, you can't stop the practice of something by practicing it.

I meant it as a logical tautology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 16:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, then you'll take into consideration that I've never written anything bad about BET. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 15:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comment of yours I was responding to was you responding to a post that contains **only** a quote of the dictionary definition of racism. There is nothing about anything else in the post you responded to but that dictionary definition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 15:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, 'think' is the problem. Just as an example, plenty of people *genuinely* thought that segregation in the South was justified, not because one race was necessarily better than another, but because black and white people were different. Thus, we got the term 'separate but equal,' which the supreme court ruled against in *Brown v. Board of Education.*

Whether or not you realize it, you are essentially arguing that there is nothing wrong with 'separate but equal.' That as long as people enforcing such rules *think* the races are equal, then they should be allowed to *physically* segregate them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 15:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop pretending to be upset about [the definition of racism], and if you're actually upset about it you need to re-evaluate your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 15:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you treat one race differently than another -for noble or ignoble reasons- then you are being racist.

In saying that, I would like to say I am not against Night of Black Stars or scholarships that have a racial requirement. They should keep doing what they're doing if that's what they want to do. I am just pointing out that when you delineate based on race -for good reasons or bad- you are being 'racist,' by definition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 14:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Where people downvote dictionary definitions that don't support their argument...](https://www.reddit.com/r/AdviceAnimals/comments/429tsu/ill_just_put_this_here_and_disappear_for_a_while/cz8w8vp) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 14:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *"Racism is prejudice, discrimination, or antagonism directed against someone of a different race based on the belief that one's own race is superior...*
**It may also hold that members of different races should be treated differently.** " [[1]](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Racism) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 14:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't fight racism with racism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 16:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll ban all people from a place because of the actions of a few? So, if [green-eyed people] did it, you'd have no problem with them banning ALL [green-eyed people]? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 14:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Now the rest](http://orig11.deviantart.net/062c/f/2014/138/5/4/the_king_in_yellow_by_grivetart-d7iuaog.jpg):

https://librivox.org/king-in-yellow-by-robert-w-chambers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The King in Yellow," a 1895 story that helped inspire Lovecraft's Cthulhu Mythos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 14:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 04:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Now the rest](http://orig11.deviantart.net/062c/f/2014/138/5/4/the_king_in_yellow_by_grivetart-d7iuaog.jpg):

https://librivox.org/king-in-yellow-by-robert-w-chambers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The UK parliament will debate banning Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The UK parliament will debate banning Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 22:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 14:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as they get tried for *sedition,* I could care less what you call them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How amazing would Deckard Cain be in HOTS? What are the chances? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 12:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Talk about a total One-Eighty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 07:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 01:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, it only works with Mercury-196 (you need the right # of stuff in the neuclous, so not any-old eleent will do), which is rarer than the base isotope of gold. So, how do you make the Mercury?

The best way to "make gold" is in a supernova, but it's one of the rarer metals to be created in those explosions. While we might get more gold as we get better at mining (on and off of the planet), it will ALWAYS be one of the rarer metals, because it is rare in the universe.  So, we might eventually get to the point were we have an overabundance of *EVERYTHING* we need, but -even then- we will have a smaller overabundance of gold. Simply because less of it **exists** than other substances. (Not that there aren't even rarer metals) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 05:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you have schadenfreude, goodbye.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you manufacture an element?

http://money.howstuffworks.com/question213.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 04:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does? And how is it relevant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 01:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 16:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Advanced Idea Mechanics [(A.I.M.)](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Advanced_Idea_Mechanics), a fictional terrorist organization in the Marvel Comics universe
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 15:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *But let none of you suffer as a murderer, or as a thief, or as an evildoer, or as a busybody in other men's matters.*

1 Peter 4:15

*And that ye study to be quiet, and to do your own business, and to work with your own hands, as we commanded you;*

1 Thessalonians 4:11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wars were literally fought over salt and pepper, which now comes free with plastic silverware. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 15:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 01:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 03:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's way too much text.

Not as much as [[Ice Cauldron]]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colorless is the Sixth Color </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 13:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 14:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would work if he bounced up and down really fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 00:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not the one who made the cards. I just want to see a deck list. Gez... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 22:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you show me the list for your EDH storm deck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has been Magic's most popular sets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 16:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you like them to do with Experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 02:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Happened to Garruk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 01:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Rakdos Augermage]] ?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should the reprinted Magic Invitational cards still depict the winner/creator in the art? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 16:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planeswalker Fair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 12:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle for Zendikar: Tentacles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 16:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 13:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Tivadar's Crusade]] Even [the picture](http://img.aegen.nl/MAS/Tivadar's%20Crusade.jpg) is brutal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does your casual playgroup have any special mulligan rules? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 12:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder what that would have done... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 00:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 22:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://blog.orbsccg.com/post/54941262210/should-a-ccg-have-dedicated-resource-cards-like

The article has been taken down, but I remember reading it.

(http://www.vtesinla.org/articleGarfield.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 19:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 19:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, alright, if you want to talk about points:

I feel everything within the comic is valid. You are correct about different aspects of the arguments, but those arguments aren't presented in the comic. 

I also understand the concept of the slippy slope fallacy, but the *logic* behind many of the arguments for homosexuality can be used for incest between consenting adults. Are they the same? No. Does the comic claim they are the same? No. In fact, the punchline RELAYS on the fact they're different. To claim the comic is saying they're the same is to strawman what is being said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 19:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you're in favor of incest as long as they use protection?

By the way, that was meant as a joke, as is the comic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 02:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the people that buy the products will *literally* die if they boycott. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 20:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they counter your sorcery and not your dudes, then you kill them with dudes.

Now, if you're saying that if they kill your guys AND counter your sorcery, then you'll lose, sure. But, any deck that stops EVERYTHING the other guy does will win regardless of what we're talking about. The fact that there are answers for the card or strategy doesn't make it bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 19:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you'll just need to have one in play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 19:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Counterspells normally send guys to the 'yard, and if they swing with fliers they can't block.

 We can make up hypotheticals all day. You say Allies will not run this card, I say they will. I guess we'll just have to wait and see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 19:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homelands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 19:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're not filling your graveyard, you're going to win anyway. They need to kill your guys to not lose, and if they don't you'll win regardless of having a 5 mana sorcery in your hand. March from the Tomb is backup if the "swing 'till they're dead" strategy doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 19:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Chasm Guide]] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 19:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find your blanket criticism of apologism against blanket criticism (along with the *ad hominem* ending) to be a delicious from of dramatic irony. Well done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 16:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that ________ is on par with the suck of Homelands and/or Prophecy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> _____________ is the worst set ever! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 15:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some First World Mythic Card Problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 01:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 21:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if they're from the first print run. Have to have "0A" on the serial number or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just don't pull a Smoldering Marsh promo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 04:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We've all played against this guy, admit it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 12:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I self identify as a male, which is a sex not a gender. So, I am denying the gender associated with my sex (masculine) for the transgender of 'male.' Thus, I am transgender. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 19:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zendikar III will be all about the Noms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 13:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IGNITE YOUR SPARK! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 23:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If life evolved in the Sun, it would likely never be able to get out of the Sun's gravity well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 20:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abiogenesis occurred on ancient Earth when it was in a volatile state. Reactions occurring all over its surface finally gave rise to ones that were self-propagating. From there, evolution took over and 4 billion years later, here we are.

The Sun is much larger and more volatile than the Earth ever was, so why didn't abiogenesis occur there? It wouldn't be self-replicating amino acids, but maybe something like self-replicating plasma structures. 

Remember that the Sun -in galactic terms- isn't much older than Earth, 4.57 billion years to 4.54 billion years. Then think about how long it took Earth life to evolve intelligence and climb out of the Earth's gravity well. Think about how much different Earth's environment is to space, and the precautions we need to take to survive there.

Now, think about how much GREATER the Sun's gravity well is. How RIDICULOUSLY different the Sun's environment is to space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 23:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'd still have to change the rules if you want to cast the spell. As of now, my understanding is that you can only generate mana of the CI of your general. Which is why I ran [[Celestial Dawn]] in my [[Zedruu the Greathearted]] deck.

Even if you could put it in, how would you cast it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 20:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the girl with the cinnamon thinking?(second to last) I would like to see the source for that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 06:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.amazon.com/Living-Dolls-Minis-Squeak-removable/dp/B00SMT4PXY/ref=sr_1_269?s=toys-and-games ie=UTF8 qid=1439525531 sr=1-269 keywords=Living+Dead+Dolls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 15:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Poe's Law](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Poe%27s_law) at work. Unless you say its sarcasm, people think you're serious.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the Venn diagram would be a very small circle inside a very big one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the difference?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This will always be one of my favorite videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 01:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 20:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, it shows you want to get Nefarian even more, since you might win just for showing up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 16:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should be the other way around. The bottom half of the cup can hold less than the top half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but you have to pay money, so probably not so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you measure/prove "no malicious intention?" Psychics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 15:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  hell compared to most countries Americans pay a ton of taxes.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_countries_by_tax_rates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we laugh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 22:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's *technically* true, since we say that stuff all the time, before or after sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we laugh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 15:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I expected to be down voted to hell for this, but...

It's not "mean words on the *internet*." It's "mean words on a *privately owned site*." If someone walked up to my lawn a posted a sign on it I didn't agree with, no one would say I was against free speech if I took it down. That's what's happening now. The owner of this house is choosing what kinds of signs can get posted *on their property.*

Now, I'm all for people boycotting something if they don't like it, and if people want to do that they should. But, people seem to forget this site is *owned,* and making spam posts just to make them is akin to spray painting a wall you don't own. (it's just easier to make and remove than real spray paint) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 17:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Client: "YOU CAN'T DO THAT!! I WON'T MAKE ANY MONEY WITHOUT MY WEBSITE!!"

It's not "your" website until you pay for it; it's mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I shouldn't watch it than. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Indescribable" is never the right adjective to use. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 22:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm always offended. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 19:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 22:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best Part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ITS JUST A PRANK BRO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 20:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 20:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I post this next time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I googled "Thug Nasty Soap," not sure what to think... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 18:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 17:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.etymonline.com/index.php?allowed_in_frame=0 search=sloth searchmode=none </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 02:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they never saw him again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 01:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ask /r/thebutton: Why is yellow the rarest flair? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 18:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's getting harder and harder to be a GreyMan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 03:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That's the Joke.](http://www.quickmeme.com/img/00/00ddce11eb42d72fd22ab4b7d9875eea4419fd39916dbe8dd946dfe8558ec180.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 02:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now you have! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 19:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the 50th person to say this! [Congratulations!](http://img.pandawhale.com/93002-reddit-silver-medal-meme-funny-B9d2.jpeg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 16:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [RIP my inbox](http://i.imgur.com/IUeYEqv.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone with a popular post says: "RIP My Inbox" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 05:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Following reports that interpreted this to mean she was human, a Sanrio PR representative said that the organization had "never said she was a human", explaining anthropomorphization by comparing the character to Mickey Mouse: "No one would mistake the Disney character for a humanbut at the same time he's not quite a mouse. Just like Hello Kitty isn't a human, she's not quite a cat either."* [[1]](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hello_Kitty) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the link, the gap is there so that the doors still operate as the frame loses its initial alignment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 00:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should have said "stall **floor** gap." It explains why stall walls don't go all the way down to the floor in most cases.

The gap is there so that the doors still operate as the frame loses its initial alignment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That American toilet stall doors have a gap "To prevent unnecessary queuing, anyone entering the restroom should be able to easily determine the state of occupancy of stalls." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 19:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Equal Rights Amendment (which would make men and women equal under the law) was 3 states away from being a Constitutional Amendment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 17:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 00:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Branded](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1368440/) was right? Like the movie, how awful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legislatures essentially get to say "not" at the end of every bill they don't like. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 17:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Gaining or losing weight can be easier or harder depending on genetics though.

And gaining and losing height is impossible, regardless of genetics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 21:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why its better not to make a big deal when you do something wrong.

As a high school teacher I can tell you it's a lesson people really don't learn early enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
