<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4860</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The company says that although the phones key selling point is photography, its not aiming to compete with the likes of the iPhone 7 or Google Pixel on picture quality.

If youre not competing on picture quality then photography is not your phones unique selling point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple sues Qualcomm for withholding $1 billion as retaliation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hugo Barra is leaving Xiaomi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 10:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consumer Reports now says the new MacBook Pro's battery life is awesome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 12:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 12:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella is urging for companies to take a considerate approach. "

The job of companies is to make a profit. As long as that is tied to consumer service. I have no problem.
Chances are I'm not going to support and buy a lousy product just because the CEO wants to be nice to people.

ALL technology has replaced jobs (old technology) for others with a long term gain in jobs being a historical fact. The idea companies have to go around dedicating themseleves to keeping jobs that exist to implement technology is self-defeating and is not providing consumers who want that technology with their needs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's now much harder to see if someone edited a Facebook post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 11:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Practices for Calibrating Your Flow Meters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 07:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 11:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very sad...that's why for a tough job you need a tough person! Marissa was a complete disaster for the company!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $4.8 billion? Wow. The name "Altaba" sounds like a medication, Yahoo is a great name than this.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple plans to build computers in the US, but they won't be for consumers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 10:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
