<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2699</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Charged in Disturbance at Bourbonnais Target Was Protesting Policy on Transgender Bathrooms: Police </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 20:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ex-cons literally work to stay out of prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 19:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When people told me about it I thought it was a big thing, but when I looked at it like you cant really tell, it's kinda hard to see," said Zach Anthony.

Zach Anthony is savage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transgender flag raised at Boston City Hall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 20:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eyewitnesses say police shot Demarcus Semer in the back while his hands were raised </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 19:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Standoff video shows police shooting hostage without warning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Are Deleting Smartphone Videos At Crime Scenes Even Though Its Illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maine legislature overturns Paul LePage's veto on Narcan bill to allow pharmacists to provide drug to addicts families and friends without a doctors prescription </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 22:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oklahoma governor signs law to allow recovery of attorney fees by those who have unjustly had their assets seized through the civil asset forfeiture process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 18:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we should also drastically increase funding for education, prevention and treatment, so that people won't need naloxone, and that those who have to use it will have the resources to ensure that they don't need it again. Naloxone is still important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More people died of prescription opioid overdose than heroin overdose in 2014.

http://www.cdc.gov/drugoverdose/data/overdose.html
https://www.drugabuse.gov/related-topics/trends-statistics/overdose-death-rates </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically come in a 2 pack -- 2 applicators, 2 spray doses administered nasally. In these cases though, "you" will not be taking too much. You will be unconscious and likely not breathing. Someone else will administer it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 16:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So let them die instead? Also, this cure is not "sweet" and almost dying is never fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CVS Offering Overdose Reversal Drug Without a Prescription in N.H. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 15:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 23:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will probably end up depending on the Param 2 value of their armor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of Iowa felons will have an easier time applying to win back their voting rights after changes to the application form </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 15:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spokane police allowed to review body camera footage before interviews in officer-involved shootings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 16:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State awards $18 million tax break to Noahs Ark theme park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 22:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dramatic dashcam video shows Chattanooga officer pulling woman from brink of death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baton Rouge police sergeant placed on paid leave in Earth Day incident; video shows apparent beating of teen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing you're white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore police investigating home arrest after video lands online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 17:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virginia Man Exonerated After 30 Years Behind Bars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 16:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Murfreesboro parents outraged after kids arrested at elementary school </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 23:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 911 caller won't be charged in Ohio Walmart police shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 22:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police: Man stinks up downtown Athens bar with fart spray </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 21:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 21:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not weighing in on the merits of this particular case or broader issues of manufacturer liability, but finding parallels is difficult. Louisville Slugger does not aggressively market its bats as good head-bashing tools, and Dodge doesn't stake its reputation on how effectively you can mow down pedestrians without doing damage to your truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congressman Turner objects to removal of Bible from Wright-Patt POW display, calling it an effort to "restrict religious freedom" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 20:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fed's New Heroin Initiatives Aimed At Tracing Drug, Finding Dealers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 16:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feds indict Brooklyn Park man in heroin-related death, first-ever federal indictment of its kind in Minnesota </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 23:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of Migrant Teens Are Being Held Indefinitely in Locked Detention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Annie Dookhan, ex-drug lab chemist who faked test results, out of prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 14:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Central Indiana pain doctor accused of exchanging pills for sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 23:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia Capitol police put out alert on gun-toting, anti-Islam rally; organizer has promised to shred a Koran as part of the event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 22:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois police department discontinues body camera use, chief says workload for staff increased too much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atheist Group Renews Fight To Eliminate $700 Million Tax Benefit For Ministers Of The Gospel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 17:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 100 medical groups urge Congress to fund CDC research on gun violence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in '94, the world watched as fragments of a comet slammed into Jupiter, with one impact estimated to have released energy equivalent to 600 times the entire world's nuclear arsenal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NC man charged with hit-and-run and reckless driving after running over Trump sign and posting video online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 18:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bible Study in Public Schools Sought In New State Laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 15:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 20:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she's speaking to the motivation to force the motto upon people. That motivation harkens back to the Cold War and fear of communism. But yes, as a question of semantics, you are correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 20:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest institutional push [came at the height of the Red Scare](https://www.treasury.gov/about/education/Pages/in-god-we-trust.aspx):

A law passed by the 84th Congress (P.L. 84-140) and approved by the President on July 30, 1956, the President approved a Joint Resolution of the 84th Congress, declaring IN GOD WE TRUST the national motto of the United States. IN GOD WE TRUST was first used on paper money in 1957, when it appeared on the one-dollar silver certificate. The first paper currency bearing the motto entered circulation on October 1, 1957. The Bureau of Engraving and Printing (BEP) was converting to the dry intaglio printing process. During this conversion, it gradually included IN GOD WE TRUST in the back design of all classes and denominations of currency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NC city commissioners vote unanimously to deny request to add In God We Trust on city hall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 17:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge accused of sexting while sitting on judicial conduct board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 23:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal prosecutors declined to pursue civil rights allegations against law enforcement officers 96 percent of the time since 1995, a Tribune-Review investigation found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 13:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 19:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU SHALL NOT PASS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civil Forfeiture Changes Pass Florida Senate Unanimously </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 16:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A non-profit is raising $400,000 for a kilo of MDMA by hosting psychedelic dinner parties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 00:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inventor creates weaponized wig for Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 21:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 20:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump's face is now literally being used as a racist insult or attack. That should tell you something about his candidacy and how it's making people feel at ease displaying their bigotry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After veto, Wyoming governor signs civil asset forfeiture reform bill into law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 17:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 21:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare people be discontented with police! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 20:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a man who has no idea what evolution is would refer to women bearing their breasts as "evolving societal behavior." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patients Legally Take Ecstasy While Receiving Therapy In Marin County </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 19:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vermont childs story about growing special plants ends in major pot bust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 18:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pastafarians now allowed to perform marriage ceremonies in New Zealand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 16:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tennessee names the Barrett .50 caliber as the state's official rifle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 17:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virginia House panel kills bill that would keep police names secret </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 02:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man shot dead by Sanger cops wasnt a lethal threat, sheriffs sergeant testifies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 17:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sheriff answers questions about Beyonce comments on radio show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Township drops charges against zombie nativity scene </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People in the ancient world did not always believe in the gods, a new study suggests  casting doubt on the idea that religious belief is a "default setting" for humans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 17:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atheist lawmaker can't give official prayer that starts off every session because it won't mention God </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 23:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former police officer sentenced to probation for posing as DEA agent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
