<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8398</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say Reddit is moderate as opposed to liberal, bashes feminism too much to be liberal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 4 finished YA manuscripts lol, each over 50,000 words long ;_; the people in my writers club all say my writing is really good and I have even published a novella with an indie publisher, but still no agents who deal with the big publishers want to represent me. Only made it as far as a couple partial/full requests but no bite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting a novel traditionally published. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 23:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want a pop duet, you can do "Need You Now" by Lady Antebellum if the guy part isn't too high for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TK from Digimon, and I'm 13 again, and this time we fall in love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a system admin for a couple different software programs, technically I'm IT department but I'm not the person you contact when your computer is slow.

It's usually not with a fellow IT person though. It's usually someone in Sales/Tech Support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my mom's (male) employees told me never to become successful, because men don't like successful women and that his own son ended his engagement when he found out the girl had a higher salary.

They were mainland Chinese, btw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I get in an argument with a coworker and this insult bubbles up to the surface and I hold back. I spend the rest of the night thinking I should have said it, I sleep on it, and the next day I am glad I didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Immigrant parents, I'm the only American in my family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A caretaker for old people, there will always be old people (in fact there will be more of them than ever) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Browsing reddit for entertainment instead of going out and spending my money, hence why I have money in the bank. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 22:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enrique Iglesias's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweeney Todd! "A Little Priest"

Or if you two are older, "Let's Walk" from Light in the Piazza would be wonderful.

Seconding "City of Stars" from La La Land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eddie Redmayne </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because God is a Democrat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rest of my relatives speculate my dad (I was raised by a single mom) is a narcissist, he has all sorts of crazy ideas. For one, he once complained that that his greatest regret in life is that my mom never gave him a son, and I pointed out even if he had a son he wouldn't have taken care of it. My dad replied it didn't matter, what mattered is that he passed on his legacy.

That's right, my dad has a kid he doesn't raise and meanwhile thinks his greatest regret is not having a son to pass on his legacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 28, 70k, I am saving up to buy a house but they're so expensive where I live that anything half-decent is worth half a million dollars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rapidash, don't wanna get burned and forked at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He talked me into auditioning for a mock beauty pageant at the California Latin convention. I won first place, but not him :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the craziest story you have of someone getting fired? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn I don't even have those moves NOW, slowly calcifying from my full time desk job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a coworker whose wife worked for a non-profit organization that paired former convicts with jobs. Perhaps you could find an organization like that to help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is better, a half-hour lesson once a week or a full hour lesson every 2 weeks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have no TV and a crappy laptop, how much would it cost me to get virtual reality gaming set up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really, really want it and I was thinking of blowing some saved up cash. Won't bother if it totals over $2000. If I can get everything under $1000 then huge yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you flirted with him, I would report a guy like that. Maybe he does this to every attractive female rider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go on walks and sing as I walk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew a girl named Brady, and then there is Alex, Sam, Robin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> being jittery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha they're pretty different from the movie though:

-Dorothy is younger than 15, I'd say around 10. And she has short blonde hair.

-Oz was real, she doesn't wake up

-Glinda was the good witch of the South, not the North. The good witch of the North wasn't in the movie, she was a cheery woman who gave Dorothy a kiss on the forehead for protection. That's why the movie had a major plothole with Glinda knowing the answer the whole time - in the book Glinda is the most powerful of the 4 witches and so Dorothy seeks her out after the wizard leaves.

-The Tin Woodman used to be a human, but he fell in love with a girl and her mom was an evil witch (different evil witch) who cursed  him to make his ax slip. The first time he cut off his arm, got a magical arm, then the other arm, etc. until he was completely made of tin.

-Witch wasn't green, slippers weren't red

Not all the Oz books feature Dorothy though, she is in maybe 4 of them? There's a pretty big cast of characters.

But yeah Frank L. Baum is the author. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah in this version she and the prince are friends who have known each other for years, but she is afraid of loving him because she knows someone with her curse can't become queen. I read this book when I was 11 and so many little girls loved it.

Oh yeah and her name is Eleanor, therefore Ella and then Cinderella :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a huge bookworm as a kid, so I've got this.

-Enchanted Forest Chronicles by Patricia C Wrede. Basically it's a wacky comedy fairy tale world except the characters are all a little weird.

-the Oz books that The Wizard of Oz comes from, The Wizard of Oz was just the first book of a series by the author. The Scarecrow becomes the emperor of the North, Dorothy is best friends with the new ruler Princess Ozma, and Auntie Em and Uncle Henry end up living in Oz after they lose their house.

-Princess Nevermore - about a 15 year old princess from a fairy tale world who accidentally gets whisked off to the modern world. She meets an old man and his grandkids, and enrolls in the local high school. It becomes a high school drama, eventually she returns to her own world.

I already mentioned Ella Enchanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 05:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ella Enchanted would me amazing for her. It's nothing like the movie, way darker. It's the story of Cinderella, but Cinderella was cursed by an incompetent fairy to be obedient and her mom and fairy godmother try to keep everyone from learning her secret so she won't be taken advantage of. Eventually the stepsister finds out, and you know the story from there.

Won a Newberry Honor Award, I read it when I was a kid and loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what books you like, if I like YA I like YA leave me alone I read more than you! ::runs off crying:: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voice types in singing. When I see youtube videos of singers there will always be people who know nothing about singing but are quick to say so-and-so is this voice type based on what high notes they hit, when in fact voice type has more to do with where your natural voice is set and not what notes you can reach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops sorry for spam, phone glitched on me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I thought I couldn't do "I Could Have Danced All Night" since it is musical theater. Last time I went to an audition soneone was singing an aria so I thought I had to go super classical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 02:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my singing isn't that good :( I get told I have a nice voice and that I am good at opening the back of my throat for high notes, but otherwise I have no strong points </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 00:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was asking me what I wanted to do lol hence my post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good audition song for a choir audition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, what is a good audition song for a more traditional choir I can add to my voice lesson practices? I sing Soprano II in my current choir, voice teacher says my type is technically soprano but I've only had a few months of lessons. Confident vocal range is from maybe A3 to Bb5, but I can go down as E3 if I "dig" for it. 

A comfortable, easy song for me to sing is something like I Could Have Danced All Night from My Fair Lady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he can exhibit self-control instead of getting into fights easily. He can keep his cool if something upsets him, and rather than to react emotionally he will actually think things through. He is also the type of person who will read a bedtime story to his nephew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rather than a comeback, I would just play victim and get them in trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Masseuse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start foodie blog like in Julie   Julia, get followers, get own channel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Digimon, it kept having new sets of characters for each season and they don't even take place in the same universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lived in China for 3 years. Cookies-and-cream milk tea - a lop of thick sweet cream on the bottom and crumbly Oreo bits. I don't miss much else, but I will miss that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most you've pigged out on in a single day that made you ashamed of yourself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> End it. My dad is like that, it's not good for your own psychological health to be around people like that. They will make a terrible spouse and a terrible parent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angemon from Digimon. I used to get all confused about it too, because he was a digimon and when he devolved back into Patamon I felt uncomfortable. To be 13... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think he will throw you out for rubbing one out lol. I think it was a good idea, but you might as well have done it for real instead of putting all that work into faking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creative writing major, I now work as a salesforce/tableau admin for a tech company. Most of my tech skills I learned on the job, got hired originally as a manual proofreader and got promoted from within the company.

Did spend 3 years after college doing just part-time jobs though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Compliment" from my dad, "You are starting to look like me." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend and I were college students at the time, both virgins. He was really cheesy and sheltered (his mom was Thai and apparently very strict) and right when we were about to have sex I asked if he had condoms. He said he did and jumped up to get some. I remember him walking off, looking kind of girly in how skinny and girlish his frame was.

Anyway, I watch him put on the condom, and immediately after he put it on he got soft. He pulled it off, rubbed himself, and when he got hard again he tried to put it on and went soft again. He gave an embarrassed laugh and tried to enter me soft with the condom dangling, that did NOT work.

He then said "it wasn't meant to be" and we just ate ice cream in silence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I put glitter nail polish on and admire it when I am bored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in my first full-time job after college, which I didn't get until I was 25 (2010 was a bad year to graduate as a creative writing major). I have been at the company for 3 tears now, and my company got bought by another company and so now my job/company names have changed but I still work at the same place.

I am the salesforce/tableau administrator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lingerie, pronounced it lin-jer-ree. In all fairness my Chinese mom pronounced it that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good your mom backed off once you talked to her, I talked to my mom and she only said "If I don't tell you who is going to tell you" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar concept, Join.Me is better one-time use because it is easier to ser up, but my mom was exceptionally nooby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being Asian is awesome I love it 95% of the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's because they're dumb, I wouldn't consider that trivial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they have an annoying speaking voice. I have a thing for nice speaking voices so it is an automatic no. But then again I am still single so I am a bit too picky, but I can't help it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hawaii for weather </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleting my browser history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me, too high a chance of getting caught (but if I am guaranteed to not get caught I would) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought them from a local Asian grocery store, they have the 12 packs for $4 in green tea and strawberry. I remember wasabi being the best though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American Revolution. Stamp tax to full-fledged war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Japanese Kit Kats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pavarotti. This would sound so badass from a tank: https://m.youtube.com/watch?v=xCFEk6Y8TmM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do your parents fail at computers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know it would take her that long to find the button, I kept thinking she would see it "any second now" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a popular TV show on the CW on it, except they got rid of all the Asians and Hispanics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has happened before, she got fired about a month after I started. You can't throw someone under the bus when your work has been consistently bad and theirs consistently good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of Mean Girls quotes and The Producers quotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe basketball courts are more readily available in poorer neighborhoods and more socially encouraged. I am not saying black kids won't be better at basketball, I am saying that the reason they are better may have nothing to do with biological makeup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or that when you grow up in a black neighborhood, being good at basketball is your ticket out of there and so black kids may strive harder for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> East Asians aren't smarter as a whole, the reason they seem smarter to you is because the cultures put more emphasis on education. Not only that, but the families who immigrate here tend to be from upper middle class backgrounds with advanced degrees and highly-sought professions. Go to the rural parts of an east Asian country and you will meet the same type of hillbillies you will meet in any rural area.

Dogs are bred through eugenics. You take the two smartest dogs you know, mate them even if they are related, mate their babies together, and do that generation after generation. Humans are not controlled the same way.

I am guessing you assume whites are smarter than blacks. Possibly due to advancements in European technology. Well, humans have been around for what, a million years? Guess how long all that modern technology has been around. Most technical advancements only came during only came during the Industrial Revolution, less than 200 years ago.

Think of how so many things happened during the Renaissance. Does that mean no one was smart before then, and all the smart people popped up at the same time. Of course not, a civilization can't flourish unless there is economic and political stability along with the right resources. If Stephen Hawking had been born in Africa he would have been fucked. You can't assume one race is dumber than another based on what inventions have come out or what grades the kids are getting in school because there are so many other underlying factors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.psychologytoday.com/blog/busting-myths-about-human-nature/201204/race-is-real-not-in-the-way-many-people-think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny enough I do work in IT as well, but I am not the one who fixes your computer. Instead I work on the data side, and I used to get this:

"The dashboard isn't working! It says I have no sales this quarter!"

"It's the first day of the quarter. The quarter has just started."

"Oh."

3 months later, same people...

"It says I have no sales this quarter!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was it readjusting to life back in the US? I heard a couple guys tell me it freaked them out how everything stayed the same after all the high-alert stuff they were used to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo. I have had guy friends like this. Then when they get a girlfriend and the two of them walk by you, they pretend they have never met you before. The next week their girlfriend isn't there and they go back to their flirty form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I have had friends like that, they only flirt with the more attractive ones. Casting a wide net. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those of you who fought in Iraq in non-combat positions, what was the average day like for you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 22:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Submitted a story to my writers' group. I am the youngest member by far.

Mentioned that a kid is playing video games and Yoshi dies on the screen. None of them knew who Yoshi was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mama! Mama! Mama! Mommy! Mommy! Mommy! Ma! Ma! Ma! Ma!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knew a kid named Thomas growing up. Thomas only played with me because I was in his age group.

One day, another boy showed up. Thomas would rather play with another boy than with me (a girl) and then Thomas was a total dick to me after that. Damn Thomas.

He became a Democrat. Damn Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Affect is a verb, effect is a noun.

He was affected by the effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are trying to understand and you can explain it well, then it can be understood regardless. If they don't want understand then that's another thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't hate it, I just feel lonely because I'm the only one in my department, my manager works at the company headquarters in Utah, and every day I go to a silent office, away from the tech support guys, and sadly type away in loneliness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's about how long it took my mom to find the bright orange button in the middle of the page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women's studies. I took a class (I am a woman myself) and I remember there was a lot of scrutinizing of magazine covers to talk about how sexist certain poses are and blaming men for them. I dropped the class a few weeks in because it was so ridiculous, I can't imagine someone majoring in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Science. I always hated science. Too memorization-based for a spaz like me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dumbest thing I've ever heard from a friend...

Friend: My dad said he will pay for me to study at an art school in the US. I'm going to DeVry.

Me: DeVry? Why DeVry?

Friend: Because it's the best.

Me: Why is it the best?

Friend: Because it says it's the best.

Me: Wait. Did you go on Google and type in "best art schools in the US" and get a link for DeVry?

Friend: Yeah.

Me: THAT'S AN AD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cousin's husband is authentically Chinese - that side of the family never immigrated to the US. Only my parents immigrated, which I think may be why I feel so isolated sometimes. I am the only American in my family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my mom has called me from 300 miles away to have me fix some computer issue of hers. I end up having to remotely access her computer with join.me and it's a pain.


"Click on the orange button"

"I don't see it"

"It is right in the middle of the homepage"

"It says About. Should I click on that?"

"No."

"We provide a variety of services that..."

"No, go back. Go back."

"And have offices in 15 countries including..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have skills that take years of lessons to get to, like ballet or singing opera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty normal scenario for me. Coworkers talking smack about a manager you find cool, stuff like that. I just bring up what they may see from their perspective, but otherwise I don't say anything. Won't tell the recipient people are talking smack about them, that just spreads drama and hurts their feelings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Telling a friend who is trying to make it as a singer/actor that they're not that good at it. Maybe a harsh truth is necessary to prevent them from ruining their future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvoting because of annoying use of shift key </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a relief, I still get hit on more by men old enough to be my father than men in my age group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are we weaker than our fobby counterparts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My aunt was belittling my depression and telling me stories about so-and-so who had also been beaten by their parents and turned out fine.

"Your cousin's husband's mom stabbed him through the back of the hand with a pencil over his grades, the lead broke off in his hand and left a permanent mark, but you should see how caring he is towards her!"

"I hit your cousin regularly when she wouldn't play the piano properly, then your grandmother would start yelling at me because she babied your cousin, it was so annoying, that is why your cousin never learned how to play the piano. You know what she told me the other day? She said that she wished she had kept at it because she doesn't have any special talents to show off during her company party. Look how much your mother cared about you, she did it for your sake!"

She keeps saying my depression caused me to fixate on my childhood problems, as opposed to my childhood problems causing my depression. She only acknowledges that my parents' divorce had an impact on me.

Sometimes I do feel weak, since I do know people in Mainland China have crazy parents who do what mine do only they don't suffer depression years after the fact. I don't know if it's because I grew up in a country where it wasn't seen as normal so I felt more wronged or what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah and after I got the highest grade in the class in my non-advanced program, "So what? You're in the stupid class." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least they said it was nice you got an A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I never got that, my parents were shitty in other ways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Las Vegas gambling thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing where you can count cards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For us there were 2 programs, one was IQ-based and the other was based on academics. I got in the first program but not the second, which got me in a lot of trouble because my parents were convinced I wasn't trying hard enough. Meanwhile I was convinced the school made a mistake and switched up IQ tests on me.

I later found out I got diagnosed with ADHD at a very young age and my mom didn't see it as a legit thing so she kept trying to beat it out of me. That is why I am 28 and still bitter lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom complained loudly about me to her sister over Skype, she would go on and on and everything she said about me was negative whereas my aunt would try to defend me. Anyway, I would sometimes get so mad I would go unplug the router for a split second and then plug it back in. My mom is a monologuer so she would talk for another good 5 minutes or so before she realized her sister stopped responding and restart the call. If I did it 3 times during a call she would give up and say the internet was choppy that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I didn't get placed in the advanced program at school, my mom went to the school and demanded I get placed in there anyway, then when they said no she came home and beat me for humiliating her publically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When something bad and uncontrollable happens to someone else, God is punishing them. When something bad and uncontrollable happens to you, God has chosen you for testing and you are blessed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you wasting your time and energy on them in the first place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who will play all the white people in historical fiction movies a few thousand years from now? Are we just supposed to use this imagination thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Number two. Lesbians can wear lingerie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In high school I was in the Latin club and every year we had the state Latin convention. One year I was watching the mock beauty competition and only 1 girl tried out. They said they couldn't just hand the award out, so they would take people from the audience. I had a crush on a boy in my class and he turned to me and told me to try out. I said no but he talked me into it because I had a crush on him for 3 years (I was ugly and wore glasses). I went on stage, sang the Star Spangled Banner a capella, and was voted the winner of the beauty pageant despite being a frumpy kid in jeans and a sweater.

The girl who actually tried out and got all dressed up was pretty mad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a creative writing major, i would advise them against it, because I know that if they are anything like me they would have done it in spite of everyone telling them not to do it anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but I thought it would at least talk about her singing or audition processes, or things that went on backstage when she was a child actor on Broadway. It had none of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
