<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's The trump Administration .... you think they were going to political and international scholars? shit son this is fucking amature hour 24/7 now in the white house </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes we know their Brokeback Mountain romance is too dangerous /r/The_Donald knows all too well ....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 05:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yuge Ass? That's Adult Diapers I hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Red state Blues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a joke about republicans, because I feel it's a joke about republicans ....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "if you aint fighting, you aint living" is a saying that comes to mind to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm your mama, I'm your daddy

I'm that nigga in the alley

I'm your doctor, when in need

Want some coke, have some weed

You know me, I'm your friend

Your main boy, thick and thin

I'm your pusherman

[I'm your pusherman](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hCDAfa-NI-M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or translation, written by native Russian speaker ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://healthypets.mercola.com/sites/healthypets/archive/2016/11/10/10-healthiest-dog-breeds.aspx

If you want a small dog Chihuahua actually are pretty darn healthy  too. They were bread to be watch dogs, living house alarms. Just make sure you get one with a longer snout as breeding them to look squashed face is starting to become popular. I don't know why the squashed face is so popular but it just is for dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pence is so ingrained into the deals of the trump administration if Trump goes down he will go down with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It truly is the darkest time line </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fatwa, if you are going to call it anything call it a Fatwa from a bloated corrupt asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you get the idea they support equal rights for women and minorities? Traditional values from the religious christian right who make up 60+% want women staying at home and to have no control over their own bodies though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO you are saying you still can't afford to have kids yet had them anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conservative American Journalism comes from a very nationalistic slant. It says only our country is great and anyone who questions it is wrong. Liberals use shame in debates because as a form of Ethos it is one of the things Conservatives typically have in spades since they usually say their morals from a strong protestant christian upbringing typically. Conservatives will always use the fear of the other for their ethos in debates, people who are not christian, people who are not white, women who do not listen to the bible and be subservient to men are all trying to take something away from you. They want to take your property or ability to get more property gun rights is entirely a property based debate or the right to shoot things debate. But they are the first to try to outlaw dissenting opinions in historical records. They try to take away the right for people to vote. American Left / Progressive have always fought for everyone being able to vote and for the idea that you help the least fortunate you help the entire country. Since the 30s and the rise of Ayn Rand Libretarianism you have a sect of conservatives who want power by means of economic dominance. That Might means right by the way of a gun or checkbook (either buying or paying a lawyer to sue something out of existence)

Breitbart != Buzzfeed 

Intellectual Poison != Intellectual Junkfood

Washington Examiner vs Washington Post

Conservatives use religion as a tool to instill fear in people that outsiders hoards from beyond the city gate are trying to take your religion away. If you are poor you deserve it, if you are sick you deserve it, Social Darwinism RAR RAR RAR

Liberals are like hey just let people live life and make sure that you make up for fucking over people in the past and help lift people out of the gutter because those people cause crimes out of desperation or untreated medical issues, mental health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you don't know you are aware of it though. It's typically entirely subconscious. If people didn't care about a transgender girl protagonist why did the rabid puppy movement try to game and manipulate the Saturn awards for Sci Fi books to get right wing authoritarian books to win?

Think about what people said when they cast a black woman as Hermione granger in the harry potter and the Cursed child play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compare "Liberal satire" to conservative "satire"

there is a level of animosity that comes out of conservative media that wishes to crush their enemies and put them down. There is a level of vitriol you don't see in liberal media. Liberals are depressed and angry but hopeful to all get along. Conservatives come from a we must crush and break our enemies and put them in their place mentality.

Conservatives dehumanize and uses a lot of logical fallacy as arguments and just plane talk based on faith something they do will work. Liberals tend to use facts and figures that comes from multiple sources. 

Liberal media for how ever sided it is still tries to come down in compromise and appeasement. Conservative media is like no fuck you our way our we destroy the world with us, IE government shutdowns.

Alex Jones, Sean Hannity, Glen Beck use hyperbole and fear mongers and not facts to support their agenda ideas for a perfect conservative utopia for a select few chosen people. Liberals go we have no idea how to make it better for everyone but we have studies and facts that show these programs help make it better for everyone.

liberals are bleeding hearts while conservatives will cut off the legs to make a point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its a literary joke. Goggle the quote text and look up "Snow Crash" Also representation in media changes how people see the world. Most black kids never thought they could be president until Barack Obama took office. When you are only shown images of performers and sports stars and business men who look like you you don't think about becoming a scientist or programmer, or engineer.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that is a serious false equivalency though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is a terribly setup site and running on Tumblr .... yeesh. I would love to go to a meetup.com organized event if possible since this looks like it hasn't had a meeting since 2014 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No U </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we need more black "Hiro Protagonists" for black kids to get behind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DSM V update?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gallup polling has his approval rating only at 37%  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is One with the force, the force is with him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I think Amy Schumer reacts to all the people calling her whale and fat and stuff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with Adult ADHD .... yeah no. ADD means you get distracted but its slow and drawn out and the stimuli makes you looks track. ADHD means you are getting shit from all directions with stimuli and you also have massive excess energy so you can't sit still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in order to run surveillance in the united states you need something first. It's called a FISA Warrant. A FISA warrant is a requirement under the The Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act of 1978 ("FISA" Pub.L. 95511, 92 Stat. 1783, 50 U.S.C. ch. 36). That United States federal law prescribes procedures for the physical and electronic surveillance and collection of "foreign intelligence information" between "foreign powers" and "agents of foreign powers".

Please take the time to do a little research and understand this. Also the NSA / CIA are intelligence agencies and do hacking and monitoring of foreign groups all the time. That is how intelligence is gathered. It is what allows us to make informed decisions as a nation under the leadership of sane and rational president to make the political, military, and diplomatic actions we take as a nation. 

The NSA / CIA are now withholding some of that information from President Trump for fear he will leak it to foreign masters.

There has been no record of a FISA warrant issued on Donald J Trump a united states citizen who would have only had it allowed if a FISA COURT run by a judge agreed with the State's evidence that showed a strong credible evidence that Donald J Trump was an "agent of foreign powers". If there was Donald J trump as now the president of the united states could have released it and unclassified it, but he hasn't and he won't because there is no fisa warrant. Just the rantings of an old 70+ year old man who is a bullshit con artist. 

Hacking happens, security holes sold to government happens, the wikileaks story was a nonstory to anyone in the network security world who goes to hacker cons like Defcon, Shmoo, and such. It is a known thing that government uses exploits to gain intell. Its like i'm shocked shocked I say gambling goes on in this establishment while at the same time collecting your winnings before you shut down the bar.

Donald J Trump is a snowball artist and even says as much in his own books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up TAD!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI's Comey Says He Has No Info to Support Trump Tweets [Bloomberg] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US Patent means USA East Coast time, Washington DC Federal USTPO hours

AC-3 is required by many companies from Netflix, Amazon, and video game consoles and dvd / bluray players because it was the format that took over for surround sound, even in video games. There are other formats as well but the fact is the patent doesn't just cover the codec it self it covers how the codec worked and that can block third parties, particularly open standard / open source codecs from being legally released as enhanced superior formats that might take far less space, have far higher fidelity, and take less processing power to process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well .... [they got the mustard out!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VCO0J1N661U) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a [shitpost] none to be taken too seriously. Unless Patrick Stewart was in Beauty   The Beast. THEN YOU KNOW THAT SHIT WAS REAL!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny way of saying "god damn" We will also take gob dom and gag dem and gaz darg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 10:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of us, one of us. Gooba-gobble, gooba-gobble </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 10:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perfect. I respond to a lot of trumpets with this video clip. https://youtu.be/uuL6cJPz3Nk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The last Dolby Digital AC-3 surround sound audio Patent has expired, 25 years of dominance because of a bloody patent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Its over, it's done!](http://i.imgur.com/EbHlfop.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps approval rating falls to record low, finds Gallup poll | 37%, the lowest of any USA president in their first 100 days in office ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://gifsound.com/?gif=i.imgur.com/fPufeTM.gif v=3ZKq2ptu7qw s=86 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy fuck this show is awful. I couldn't even get past episode 4 before I noped the fuck out. The martial arts choreography looks like it was done by Rex Kwon Do or some cringe lord kid. Seriously the fight all look like they are dancing and not at all trying to actually punch anyone. Fuck Gymkata the movie looked like it had better marital arts. MIGHTY MORPHIN POWER RANGERS had better martial arts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of a Meetup for motion graphics / Video editing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use to do video editing for journalism stuff covering Tech and consumer electronics. I was never great with motion graphics but  I wanted to start learning how to do rotoscoping in after effects and start doing more special effects in videos for fun and giggles, mostly for meme shitposting or for /r/HighqualityGifs. Anyone know if there is any meetup groups for that in Portland?


Meme I'm working on right now. https://youtu.be/fxaRb53UX90

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my diet consists of 4 string cheeses a day for snacks, two eggs in the morning, a 1/3 lb of ground beef with a tablespoon of raw peanut butter and classic pickles for lunch and 3 cups of stevia sweteened coffee with either half half or unsweetened almond milk a day, dinner will be cheap 4oz stake which cost 2 dollars each in a pack of 5 with mushrooms cooked in coconut oil and seasoned with a side of spinach and feta or carne asada soaked in lime juice then night before with a cucumber / tomato chopped up salad.

This is my diet for currently for three months everyday now. Its about 1600 calories a day with no more than 5g of carbohydrates and I just maintain my weight. Why? because damn meds that keep me bloated and fuck up my metabolism because they treat my bipolar type 2 disorder and panic attack disorder. I drink about 5 litters of water a day too with my 1 litter flask I have clipped on my messenger bag.

Its a sisyphean existence because shit fucking sucks and I'm tired of eating the same damn thing over and over. It would be nice to eat pizza or Indian food or some god damn rice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sup people fat person here. Just wanted to say something. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 09:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a fat person. When people treat me like shit, you know what i do? I want to eat more fucking ice cream and cry my eyes out. Food is the heroine of choice for most obese people. I know I'm fat. I know it's unhealthy but there comes a point where you are like hey I ride a bike 45 minutes a day for an 8 mile ride and shit and swim laps. But hey I guess that look of disgust I get when I'm at the gym or that random person throwing something at me and laughing while I'm riding my bike to work or class is so well deserved. It really motivates me to want to commit suicide and make sure my fat ass ruins someones day having to clean it up in the best possible way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last episode of Seinfeld is the only one I really liked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purple pilled? seriously? fucking cringe sheeesh. Unless your name is means ""the cool breeze" in Hawaiian there is no need for you to talk about pills kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then someone will be equal to me and i can't have that, then my shit isn't worth as much like my white privilege!!! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May day bitches! This country needs help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which is going under due to competition blocking them with ALEC and other lobbyist groups putting out legislation and suing to block them from Public Utility poles and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah the fucked up fact is to screw over the consumer is part of capitalism in america. The fact is if you do something and don't say it was to make money you can be sued by stock holders. Its a really fucked up thing. Ask Henry Ford about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sometimes people just don't want to be treated like shit for what they look like 24/7 man thats the point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reminder ...[ this is the skull of a pug vs other dogs and a wolf.](http://i.imgur.com/0eSgsFb.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lord Of The Shooting Stars Rings: Return of the Bag Riders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was his voice that threw me off. His american accent in Legion is so stilted and staccato and wispy and he sounded like he was trying to mimic Robby Benson so hard in this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gag dag magneto! Trying to control David!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the same "delicious cherry pie" i want to make a text gif for this once my motion graphics in after effects get better.

like this.

https://www.reddit.com/r/HighQualityGifs/comments/5zkx4o/mrw_i_watched_the_latest_hqg_studios_video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edited up a new video meme, how much do you think I can sell it for? Still a work in progress as my After Effects skills are lacking still. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Shitpost] David is just having weirder and weirder dreams in this show man. I just saw an all musical episode is next. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 08:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox news tried to make a comedy news show as well. You need to watch the pilot. It was just plain mean. They just viscously made fun of poor people and and working class people calling them lazy. It was a level of out of touch crinsge that you swear it must have been written by an android trying to learn to be funny and thinking slapstick meant hitting someone over and over with a hammer until their was brain damage was "funny"

It was a wannabe daily show and only lasted 2 episodes episodes i think before it was pulled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> third season felt lack luster i  agree. But I feel it had good thoughts and ideas with the campaign trail cover story and what happens when sources screw a news agency to discredit them on purpose, which has happened in the past with news papers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand why it ended. It must be so hard to come up with shows around news that just came out. The longer the show got the more the show got closer to the current time. I think it might be intresting if they revisted the show sometime down the road. But killing off charlie was kind of a strong point to the whole thing that news as we know it is sadly dead. The news of today is so alien to just 10 years ago. I mean fuck sake fox news is coming to the defense of CNN now when Trump attacks them and calls them fake news. A racist conspiracy rag like the Gateway Pundit and Breitbart have White House Press creds now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok ... but i converted and posted this one to vid.me because all the other version of I saw of it lacked the full context of the scene with the full opening. I know it has been posted before but I thought having a whole clip would be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not really guy did the crime and other people also did the time too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Budd Dwyer

During the early 1980s, public employees of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania overpaid millions of dollars in Federal Insurance Contributions Act (FICA) taxes. As a result, the state solicited bids from accounting firms to determine refunds for its employees. The contract was eventually awarded to Computer Technology Associates (CTA), a California-based firm, owned by John Torquato, Jr, a native of Harrisburg, Pennsylvania. Later Pennsylvania Governor Dick Thornburgh received an anonymous memo detailing allegations of bribery that took place during the bidding process for the $4.6 million contract.

An investigation was undertaken by federal prosecutors. Dwyer was charged with agreeing to receive kickbacks worth $300,000 in return for using his office to steer the contract toward CTA. The US Attorney also indicted Torquato, Torquato's attorney William T. Smith, Smith's wife, and Bob Asher, the former Republican Party Chairman for the State of Pennsylvania. In return for lighter sentences, Torquato and the Smiths pleaded guilty and testified on behalf of the Federal government against Dwyer and Asher.

Dwyer denied any wrongdoing. Federal prosecutors offered him a single charge of bribe receiving (which would have meant up to a maximum of five years' imprisonment), resignation from his office as Treasurer of Pennsylvania and full cooperation with the government's investigation but he refused. Instead Dwyer went to full trial. However his defense was curtailed by the prosecution because the case was limited to only those who had been charged. The names of the unindicted co-conspirators who were linked in the bribery scandal but were not on trial were withheld. These unnamed individuals were believed to have been staff members of the Dauphin County Republican Party.

On December 18, 1986, Dwyer was found guilty on 11 counts of conspiracy, mail fraud, perjury and interstate transportation in aid of racketeering, and consequently faced a sentence of up to 55 years' imprisonment and a $300,000 fine. His sentencing was scheduled for January 23, 1987, to be performed by U.S. District Court Judge Malcolm Muir.

Bob Asher, Dwyer's co-defendant, was sentenced to one year in jail. He later returned to politics and served as a Republican national committeeman for Pennsylvania </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HBO's The Newsroom - "America Is not the greatest country in the world anymore" - This series opening scene still gives me chills when I watch it today. It needs to be watched by more people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like the fisherman's wharf parking garage in San Francisco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget his "purple heart" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SOUTHERN STRATEGY!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conservatives humor, so a dumb nigg$  or eliteist liberal or butch bull dyke gets beaten up  by the police


Liberal humor, so i got so drunk last night because of blinding depression i forgot that my right to decide what goes in my body is being taken away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude Buissness is far from "dry" most business people i know are the most crass and drunken assholes i know. So many gonto strip clubs for fun and think spending money makes up for the lack of empathy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that. Punch up or across. That sums up good comedy perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dennis miller use to be liberal and somehow 9/11 traumatized him so much he went Anakin skywalker and killed a temple full of younglings  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daft punk, rabbit in the moon, paul van dyke, digweed, amon tobin, aphex twin, lcd soundsystem, deep dish (obviously), theivery corporation ( obviously), BT, evil nine, diesel boy .... and those were just buzz night. Alchemy night was just as good with lords of acid, kmfdm, Marilyn manson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They typically has asbergers or some sort of personality disorder then. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 23:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The place to go was eastcoasthappy.com for me one of my old dj friends ran it and it was organized by genre of event. Buzzlife use to link to it even. /pour a 40 for nations at the capitol ballroom/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 22:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear leads to anger, anger leads to hate, hate leads to suffering

Most rednecks dont know anybetter that is why that black guybwho befriended klans men was able to have over 50 i think lifelong klansmen quit the klan because none of them actually personally socialized with or knew black people.

Do not take for maliace which is just plain honest ignorance. I feel many people who are bigots are only so because they know no better and look for things to justify their world view  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes absolutely. If you look at "redneck" comedy or humor its always very biting or mocking of people "smarter" than them and relishes in reinforcing stereotypes. While every other major comedian pokes fun of their own community theybare from but mostly focuses on bullies or even focuses on self deprecating humor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump sends 'hate group' to a UN conference on women's rights: The US delegation includes groups that believe the UN's advocacy on gender equality and LGBTQI rights is a threat to society </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump sends 'hate group' to a UN conference on women's rights: The US delegation includes groups that believe the UN's advocacy on gender equality and LGBTQI rights is a threat to society </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved dennis miller too as a kid. He was logical and educated and witty and snarky. He was pro civil rights and understood history. Its not like anyone he knew died on 9/11 from what i know but he fucking just snapped and became mean and just cruel and so bloody bigoted. He use to put bigots in their place.

Dennis millars fall to the dark side was a real sad loss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [MRW i have to come to terms with the stupidity of my fellow white people](http://gph.is/XIJRA1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a reminder Conservatives do not understand Satire or Sarcasm and frequently lack a sense of humor. It is proven through MULTIPLE psychological studies and polls.

- https://www.psychologytoday.com/blog/rationally-speaking/200905/conservatives-lack-sense-humor-study-finds
- http://washingtonmonthly.com/magazine/septoct-2012/why-arent-conservatives-funny/
- http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2009/04/27/colbert-study-conservativ_n_191899.html
-https://www.theatlantic.com/entertainment/archive/2015/02/why-theres-no-conservative-jon-stewart/385480/
- http://www.salon.com/2015/11/23/republicans_just_dont_get_colbert_why_the_fox_news_watching_climate_change_denying_crowd_cant_understand_complex_satire/
- http://www.mediaite.com/online/when-conservatives-dont-understand-satire/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 18:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anywhere near portland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man you worked in NYC at a dotcom like when Pseudo.com was still a thing. That must have been crazy up there during that time. I just imagine all the Faux "Hackers" vibe all over the place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going through the list of /r/WritingPrompts to write for and saw this gem of stupidity on the second page and just got triggered, i'm terrible that way my moronic friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Humanity has mastered the technology of going into people's minds. The once chaotic mess of people with untreated rapid switching Bi-polar disorder, schizophrenia, and dissociative disorders has made them sought after and commercialized into modern entertainment for 3rd parties to experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 16:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Madness is now a thrill ride you can enjoy and those who are it's conductors are paid handsomely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if you are the bottom my sweet sweet sugar tits. I got the pegs if you got the board if you catch my drift /*wink*/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get put down you rabid puppy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes .... right, because you used SJW i know you're an asshat too. get fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit .... potter came! I said to myself as i stared wide eyed. Years of this came to this night. It was like my coronation and Potter's corpse would finally be the drape over my throne. To think born of muggle blood I got to become this lord of darkness. It's funny you don't think something like this would ever happen but hey you roll with it. So many wizards in the past fought for power like I had achieved. I sometime wonder why I do this? It seems like a lot of work just for so many damn sycophants. Oh well hmm potter looks ready to die. I wonder, why is it this damn kid caused me so much problems? No matter really, I'm about the Abra kedavra the fuck out of this four-eyed poindexter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 15:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world was always in a state of flux. As the winds carved their way across the landscape the mountains had been sandblasted down and made smooth lumps of earth. No hard edges existed at all across the landscape anymore as the winds of change always had my world smooth and bare. Rolling hills of sand and dust. The stories of trees and vegetation on the surface were relegated to the thing of legends. 

This is what I was taught in school each day. I was left to dream and wonder about the surface world like all children. But finally my birthday had come. I would take the right of passage and get my own wingsuit. It was time for me to rise from the under-caves we had made our homes. My father had told me the best of us would ride the winds to other lands in search of people to trade with. Very few though ever came back, those who did were never the same. They had a passion of flight, they ran to the surface to be one of the air riders. 

I dreamed for my chance. To ride the winds like a specter of the lands of wind, ready to explore. I raced home after class got out. My mom had made my favorite, lichen and mushrooms, their pale glow in the darkness of the cave always made me lighten up. But now I was about to have more. I would ride those winds tonight. I was ready to be able to see the surface. Once my father came home we would go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, Its the penumbrae of the Albino Rabbit!

They have formed over the last untold millennium to form a warren of pure anarchy. They are the harbingers of chaos against the lords of order. Fear their dark desires as they combine their insidious powers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just for your knowledge this is basically what gave us the Wizard of Oz series of books by  author L. Frank Baum. He didn't like reading the same basic stories to his kids so he just started making up stories for them and created OZ and Dorthy and everything. Just so you know you might be able to parlay this into something similar. 

Just something to chew on for you to think about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bassnectar's remix of Nina Simone's "Feeling Good" as featured in the FX Network's Marvel mutant adaptation Legion - Featuring Aubrey Plaza dancing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They USE to do good things. Then they went fully nazi when the armies of StormFront invaded. Now we need the avatar to master all four meme elements to bring back balance to the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude i bought this record in yoshitoshi records when I was teenager when it first came out. I realized how old I was when Matrix was 15 years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God this is such a classic track. I remember going to Yoshitoshi record shop in Gerogetown Washington D.C. and picking up the vinyl record when I was teenager.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bassnectar's remix of Nina Simone's "Feeling Good" as featured in the FX Network's Marvel mutant adaptation Legion - Featuring Aubrey Plaza dancing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 13:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Daft Punk is one of those EDM artist duos that have transcended the genre. But It wasn't until they release Interstellar 5555, their anime visual album did people even give a damn. They became popular because the Iron was hot on the popular acceptance of anime in american culture thanks to Cartoon Network's Toonami Midnight run broadcasting block. Their Album was broadcasted on the Toonami music special night that featured Anime Music Videos produced around Toonami anime shows they broadcasted as well as music from Daft Punk and the Gorillaz first album. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CRYSTAL GEMS!!! COME OUT AND PLAY!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meal prep Meals On Wheels ..... you are doing good work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked all of the animatrix, which ones did you not like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just let it happen. All it takes is one bad day /;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kanye is a very derivative artist. Nina Simone was a true artist and amazing performer. You need to listen to her music and the covers she performed more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> off the back of a truck near a raging torrent of a river ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should read about the plot they did for the The Matrix MMO It was pretty cool ideas. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry i said it wrong. I mean it would be haram </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think agent smith was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a line i thought would work perfectly but its a paraphrase from something I saw when I was like 9 years old on TNT, the sci-fi space soap opera Babylon 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He actually laughed and apologized he offended the man so much he would throw his shoe at him, which is one of the biggest insults in all the Arab world, showing the bottom of your shoes. You are trained by the state department to always keep your feet flat on the floor and never cross your legs in a chair when talking to Arab country dignitaries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 03:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zathras knew, Zathras oldest care taker, there was belief around three. Three castes -- worker, warrior, religious. Three languages. Light, Dark, and Grey. The Nine of the Grey Council -- three times three. All is three... As you are three. As you are one... As you are the One. You are the One Who Was. She is the One Who Is. And He is the One Who Will Be. You are the beginning of the story, and the middle of the story, and the end of the story that creates the next great story. In your heart, you know what Zathras says is true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don not want to see that at all. Man those war scenes and organic experimentation are all sorts of disturbing. The one scene where the guy gets ripped out of the battle armor screaming still haunts me when I think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They released two volumes of short story comics for the matrix which were a combination of the comics from the old ass website they ran for the community and some newer ones as well. They really were great stories and amazing art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keanu is immortal and they can always jump the story a few years of peace and then there is a group against the peace. It would be interesting to see them living in the real world on the surface with the Machine's help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even imagine how this would be sold in most arab countries. Lebanon I can totally see it, Jordan too, Palestine, UAE maybe? In Saudi Arabia it would totally be haram  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See they know what they were doing was illegal then. They were trying to cover their ass but the fact is this is the kind of stuff that shows illegal hiring practices. Hiring models for example and only i'm assuming white models when people with a degree in hospitality shows serious issues. The entire thing has a stench of corruption. These kind of practices can have serious class action lawsuits from staff for the issues of making it a hostel working environment and illegal hiring practices. The only way these kind of lawsuits happen is when fellow coworkers are willing to stand up and say, "no, this is not right" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's your civic responsibility to inform the public to the polices of the racist who conned his way into the white house. Did you sign an NDA when you worked for them? If so you can contact the ACLU or Southern Poverty Law center about this if they try to take action against you. Please, be brave on this and go public about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wolverine and Logan actually do relate to each other and the Adamantium bullet is a ref back to Wolverine Origins  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are saying there were manager / establishment level rules that said no Black or Hispanic looking person could work the front door? Did this apply to the front desk and concierge staff as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "their" super cars, and by clean look do you mean you are hella white looking for south Florida standards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do an AMA then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QMn4KkABuac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry Detroit and Flint beat you to that by a nearly 30 years. Baltimore a close 3rd. But Baltimore is still alive because it has Johns Hopkins, Social Security Administration, Maryland University Hospital and a few other major anchors to keep it standing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aubrey Plaza strutting her stuff in the Marvel FX show Legion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aubrey Plaza Strutting her stuff in the Marvel FX show Legion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> posted a higher quality version of the video without the FX Logo to vid.me so incase of youtubs getting DMCA'ed

Lenny's Sexy Fungus Strut Dance 

https://vid.me/oPVM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electronic dance music in the united states that becomes pop culture popular sadly is really base level i feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are doing YED's work my good boy, YED's work ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] Lenny's Sexy Fungus Strut Dance - 1080p w/o corner logos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case the other video get DMCA'ed and for people who want to see it without the FX logo in the corner.

https://vid.me/oPVM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 01:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you ask him if he will do an AMA on here to talk about the process it takes to get in that makeup and what the part has been like so far up till the last broadcasted episode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 00:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need an AMA!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeh im fine with people mocking someone its when the lump all feminism as some cause of injustice i take issue with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there is so much porn on tumblr! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My liberal dream is a star trek next generation future i dont know what the heck you are talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you .... not go mens rights red piller reeeeeeeeee reeeeeeeeee all over this good carpeted floor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Now the real game begins!](https://vid.me/dI5X) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I pass college Calculus I and I can now take calculus based Newtonian Physics I </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP most USA based open non-profit  post doc research  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [More like Lenny Smash, Am i right? HEY OHHHHH](http://i.imgur.com/NCPdgLw.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lafayette, Baton Rouge, Shreveport, and New Orleans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/0yyIbCc.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And taking away meals on wheels, public energy research, public health research, and school meal programs for the poor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rupert Murdoch really fucked them hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Los Angeles, Louisiana, or Laos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gph.is/1TQ1HfJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does it really matter? She would totally smash! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
