<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2851</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 03:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like it's crushed bricks, which I think is a voodoo thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 06:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mortify
mrdf/
verb
past tense: mortified; past participle: mortified
1.
cause (someone) to feel embarrassed, ashamed, or humiliated.
"she was mortified to see her wrinkles in the mirror"
synonyms:	embarrass, humiliate, chagrin, discomfit, shame, abash, horrify, appall
"I'd be mortified if my friends found out"
2.
subdue (the body or its needs and desires) by self-denial or discipline.
"return to heaven by mortifying the flesh"
synonyms:	subdue, suppress, subjugate, control; More
discipline, chasten, punish
"mortifying the flesh"
3.
archaic
(of flesh) be affected by gangrene or necrosis.
"the cut in Henry's arm had mortified"

Know what word means horrified?  Horrified  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why were you so embarrassed about knocking over a stuffed bear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 06:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awww yeah, for once my insomnia is working FOR me, I've been waiting for this XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 08:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of something by Junji I to,   that is quite possibly the highest praise I can give </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 05:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my God, I love your writing style; the description of your love of driving made me long to go somewhere, anywhere, as long as it's by car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fetus in fetu? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favourite is to take a screenshot of the desktop, save it as the desktop background, then delete all the icons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My   my hubby's initials are S M
much fun is had </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 22:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when you delete an e-mail, does it delete the e-mail from the other person's inbox as well?
it makes no sense to delete e-mail from someone's inbox who hasn't pressed the delete button </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 04:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your friend is an idiot.  I draw everything on regular paper, then 'trace' it onto cardstock before inking   colouring (I call it transferring, but tomato tomato) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, Canadian  :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 21:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear their first thought when they think of 'dumpster food' is a half eaten hamburger pulled out from the bottom, soaking with dumpster juice  :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
