<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5053</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine personally where: Dye Fantasy: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6QFwo57WKwg Backwater Gospel: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vVkDrIacHJM and the deadtime stories: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lIF8VdoWKCk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine personally were Dye Fantasy: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6QFwo57WKwg Backwater Gospel: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vVkDrIacHJM and the fucking creepy little girl from dead time stories: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vVkDrIacHJM witch I all watched at age 8 (Edit) I watched pretty much all the creepy animations on youtube and even if they are crappy today I didnt notice at that age </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most disturbing video you ever saw as a child and still somehow gives you chills when you watch it now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 20:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definetly our last day. We had a huge show, where the students off our school could show off their project to the teachers, wich we had done for the last half year. After the top 10 projects got announced (including mine :), we all got a check for 50 bucks and could go on stage and show off our Project to about 250 Parents. After that most off us (the students only) went to a little cottage that someone rented for the afterparty. Loud Music, Alcohol and snacks for everyone. Some had never drank alcohol before, without saying it was pretty funny. Some shy students got completly out off hand on the dance floor and did some stupid shit. It was a pretty great night and everyone got into drunk little conversations and maybe even found a new friend. I got home save with my friend at around 2:30.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intelectual NiBBas like turtles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like 50.- for 4.5g of really good quality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
