<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2522</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so please enlighten me on the greatness of Trump. What are his policy stances? Not his empty platitudes, but actual policy plans on how to achieve his platform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None, I'm just a neoliberal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you she wished she had near as much power and influence as you think she has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, imagine the shitstorm people would kick up if Hillary did an AMA on /r/hillaryclinton and a bunch of difficult questions were removed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a direct attack on our democracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is a **horrible** idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreeing to reform something is not the same as sharing policy positions. By that logic the Democrats and Republicans are the exact same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with you. I like Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, they don't tolerate any disagreement with Trump, his policies, or his supporters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well when your expectation that anything going wrong is planned, it is rather self-serving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure if you want someone with policies that will destroy the US than be my guest and vote for Trump. Who doesn't want a President supported by the leaders of "illiberal democracy?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 22:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia started frozen conflicts it long before Georgia in Transnistria in the early 1990s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 22:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No such scientific studies exist. I seriously hope from the bottom of my heart you are a troll. No one can seriously hold your views and consider themselves a logical and reasonable person. Next thing your going to do is say that vaccines cause autism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are saying we should have acquiesced to all the Russian demands and allowed the former Warsaw pact countries to remain under the boot of imperialist Russia? I don't buy that shit. We are past trading spheres of influence. If a nation wants to join us it is up to that nation. Russia can kick and scream all it wants but if it didn't treat others like absolute shit they wouldn't be treated the way they are. The Russians have earned everything that has happened to them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 18:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It hasn't fucking changed man. Put down the hyperbole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 17:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russians make up a pretty disproportionate cross-section of a lot of our assets, Trumps son, Donald Jr., told a real estate conference in 2008


Page did not respond to questions from The Post. In an interview this year with Bloomberg News, he hinted that Trumps election could be a boost for some of his Russian associates who have been hurt by U.S. sanctions imposed after Russias intervention in Ukraine. Theres a lot of excitement in terms of the possibilities for creating a better situation, Page told the news service.


Hmmm...I would disagree with you.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 17:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've really fallen for the Russian propaganda...damn son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 17:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russia fucked itself over. Don't give me that Russian propagandist BS. Russian oligarchs robbed the country blind during its mass privatizations in the 1990s. This led to the economy tanking, the military rapidly contracting, and the loss of prestige on the world stage. Eastern Europeans were tired of being under the foot of Russia. What makes Russia's interests any more important than Poland's, Latvia's, Estonia's, and Lithuania's interests? These are countries that successfully democratized and privatized. To say this is NATO's fault is being willfully ignorant of the domestic situations that led to Russia's decline. Russia no longer has a leg to stand on when citing international agreements since they shredded the Budapest Memorandum. So please stop being a Western apologist and just accept Russia has gone down a path where our interests will not significantly match up without significant political change within Russia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 17:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/inside-trumps-financial-ties-to-russia-and-his-unusual-flattery-of-vladimir-putin/2016/06/17/dbdcaac8-31a6-11e6-8ff7-7b6c1998b7a0_story.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 17:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump cares too. He has a bunch of money tied up in Russia. 

https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/inside-trumps-financial-ties-to-russia-and-his-unusual-flattery-of-vladimir-putin/2016/06/17/dbdcaac8-31a6-11e6-8ff7-7b6c1998b7a0_story.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 17:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if there is something it is no where near as bad as Trump's campaign manager, Paul Manafort, running Viktor Yanukovych's campaigns. Trump literally has direct connections to the Kremlin and its puppets yet people think he will be best suited to run our foreign policy. I can't believe I am living in this joke... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 17:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're perspective is so warped it's remarkable. Black people don't have lower IQs. Generations of oppression and institutionalized racism has led to widespread black poverty in the US. The black population has consistently had worse nutrition, worse early childhood education, and diminished opportunities solely becuase of people like you. I'm being generous when I call you a person more like a pile of human filth. Your views are what led to the genocide of the Native Americans. You're views are what led to the Civil War, produced segregation and Jim Crow. Your views are what led to the genocide of Jews, homosexuals, gypsies, and the mentally challenged. Don't try to hide behind pseudoscientific bullshit. What you are espousing is no different than phrenology was back at the time of the last century. Go ahead and blame all your ills on minorities. I will take great comfort in your failures. I take great comfort in our black president. In my many minority colleagues. Freedom of speech doesn't fucking apply to social interactions dipshit. Freedom of speech is a protection against the government. Social mores can tell you to shut the fuck up and stop being a racist bag of shit. For your sake and everyone like you I am glad you're lazy ass is getting left behind. America is better of without you and your kin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 00:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a way too idealistic view of people.

That view is the same reason communism always fails. It is the same reason pure capitalism fails. It is the reason pure libertarianism fails. I know it is shitty, but not everyone is equally capable.  We may start out with generally similar capacities, but that is not true by adulthood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 23:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're trying to tell me the US isn't a democracy?  Please, do explain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elections are all PR, dealing with Congress and other world leaders is all politics. He can get elected running a PR campaign, but I don't think those skills translate to getting things done in the beltway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean they are creating significant instability in one of the strongest democracies in the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being able to play a publicity game is not the same thing as playing the political game. They are two very different beasts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 21:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump and Christie are talking about civil servants. [\[1\]](http://www.vox.com/2016/7/20/12233454/christie-trump-purge-federal-employees)[\[2\]](http://uk.reuters.com/article/us-usa-election-trump-purge-exclusive-idUKKCN10003A)[\[3\]](http://www.slate.com/blogs/the_slatest/2016/07/19/christie_says_trump_aims_to_purge_federal_civil_service_of_obama_hires.html)[\[4\]](http://thehill.com/blogs/ballot-box/presidential-races/288462-trump-would-try-to-make-it-easier-to-fire-government)[\[5\]](http://fortune.com/2016/07/20/donald-trump-fire-obama-appointees/)[\[6\]](http://www.cbsnews.com/news/donald-trump-could-ask-congress-for-law-to-oust-obama-appointees/)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 20:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because it is hard doesn't mean it shouldn't be done. That type of attitude is just pure laziness and kinda makes me pity you if you truly think that way....
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 20:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's patently false. Civil servants are not and should not be thrown at the whim of politics, that creates a corrupt, useless government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please if you think moderation equals censorship I would gladly like to see your explanation. Not one liners, not non-sequitors, a real, thought out explanation of what you mean. 

You need to get your head out of your ass. Supporting moderation is not the same thing as censorship. One liners like that show your obvious disdain for what quality moderation means. A little quip that attempts to derail a discussion and build it into an issue it is not. That is the type of shallow pseudo-intelligence that is driving the Trump campaign. Truth be damned. 

Quality moderation would provide a balance of well-sourced opinions instead of partisan drivel. It would prevent 20 links of essentially the same thing rising to the front page. But hey, if you like the hive mind. Keep in it brother. Who really wants to go through the trouble of free *independent* thought anyway?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 19:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Trump....he's against the 1st, 5th, and 14th amendments, wants to purge executive branch employees, and consolidate power in the hands of the president.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, NAFTA fucked over Mexico waaaaay harder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know what the real world is? Have you ever had to go out in the professional world and get slammed by the shit of the real world? Pragmatism is the only way to survive. Idealism gets you reckt. I lost count of the number of times I have seen it happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you know vote for the one that doesn't want to destroy our constitution, our secular values, and our liberal democracy. But hey, if you want an authoritarian...be my guest. I have enough guns and ammo to protect myself during the Trump state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please point me to this "direct hand" you speak of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or an atheist, or really anything that isn't a white male christian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the worst decision and never works. That's like saying a bunch of drug addicts should be in charge of drug policy and risk management of said policy. I can tell you from experience it doesn't work. Vested interests only care about those interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 18:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it is moderated like shit, you get shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really think an implosion of our political system is a good thing? Do you really think it will make you better off? Do you think the economy would walk away scott free? Do you think our global adversaries would sit still while we implode? What benefit do you see in the short- and medium-term from a Trump presidency?

As a corollary, what makes you hate Clinton so much? I find most character arguments against her are much lighter than what can be said against Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are saying because I am a neoliberal I am intellectually dishonest? It is dishonest to support free trade? It is dishonest to support stability through rules based institutions and backing them up with American military might? It is dishonest to support the equal rights of humanity? It is dishonest to support global economic prosperity? It is dishonest to be opposed to tribalism and nationalism? Well, then I would rather be the most dishonest person in the world than fit into your definition of honesty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok please do me a favor and outline why you support Trump and the specific policies of Trump that you support. Do it without slander, without name calling and I will respect your choice of Trump as a candidate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are saying people that support Clinton are not intellectual honest? Can you please elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really because they know they can easily jerk him around with how shallowly emotional he is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 20:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, it seems many people forget that the Citizens United decision came about because of political campaigning against Clinton. The left will always have an advantage with limiting individual campaign contributions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only speak on this in terms of Saudi Arabia. The system Nixon started was a way to prevent the oil crisis caused by OPEC in the 1970s, essentially he wanted to remove the political threat of oil and by extension OPEC. Thus was born our close friendship with the Saudis. We promised them military aid in exchange for them investing their money back into US treasuries. Essentially, Saudi petrodollars (from my understanding is more a word describing the income from oil) would fund US spending, thereby creating a stable alliance between the US and the leader of OPEC. [\[1\]](http://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2016-05-30/the-untold-story-behind-saudi-arabia-s-41-year-u-s-debt-secret) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 23:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Economist had a great special report on the US dollar and its implications in the global order. I'd really suggest checking it out if you can. 

http://www.economist.com/printedition/2015-10-03

[Specifically this one.](http://www.economist.com/econ2015) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 19:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.cnn.com/2016/07/13/politics/newt-gingrich-sean-hannity-fox-news-donald-trump/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Hillary Clinton is President: The First 100 Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 19:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Hillary Clinton is President: The First 100 Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Donald Trump was President: The World v The Donald </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parties exist to help the voters identify which groups they support and identify the general policy positions of the candidates across the ballot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then right into a Great Depression when he tries to end the Fed then can't get any economic bills through Congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, rise of anti-science parties! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 14:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lies

http://www.politifact.com/personalities/donald-trump/

Russia

https://www.foreignaffairs.com/articles/russia-fsu/2016-04-18/putins-foreign-policy

Disunity

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/gop-mayor-leaves-party-donald-trump_us_5766d092e4b0853f8bf13387

https://www.bostonglobe.com/news/nation/2016/07/13/these-top-republicans-are-skipping-convention/CmcCTMkSOu0kOIThlmymhN/story.html

http://www.politico.com/story/2016/07/national-security-clinton-trump-225137

http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2016/07/where-republicans-stand-on-donald-trump-a-cheat-sheet/481449/

http://foreignpolicy.com/2016/06/15/can-paul-ryan-save-the-republican-party-from-donald-trump/

http://www.msnbc.com/msnbc/meet-the-republicans-speaking-out-against-trump


You need to reevaluate your views on race and racism apparently. What you just said makes absolutely no sense.

Edit: forgot a link

The bankruptcies and destruction of small businesses

http://bigstory.ap.org/article/10bbe40a86774bac9ad1fbd3a936c808/little-guy-contractors-still-angry-trump-taj-bankruptcy
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 06:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you really going to call Hillary a liar and not Trump. He lies far more often and to just as much if not greater detriment. 

Putin sees Trump as someone he can manipulate to create rifts in NATO and other Western alliances. Russia is not our friend, not so long as it is under Putin. The best we can hope for is that it doesn't get worse. Obama tried reconciliation, he kept the missile shield out of Poland, which happened AFTER Russia invaded Georgia. Where did that get us? Crimea annexed by Russia and Eastern Ukraine in a frozen conflict. 

I said the conservative foreign policy community, not the political GOP establishment. They are two different things and even then the establishment isn't really united behind him. 

Trump wants to enforce a religious test on people and blames our ills on Mexicans and Muslims. He has said a judge cannot perform his duties because of his race. This is straight up institutionalized racism he is espousing. Can you frame it any other way?

Oh so he has creates jobs? How about all the small businesses he bankrupted by refusing to pay them?




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pfft...I'm not a D and I'd be an R if it weren't for the religious right. Neoliberalism is the way to go. It's not a problem of the policies but of the way the policies are packaged and conveyed to the public.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 23:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm...what invasion of Syria?

Oh yes the coup, big whoop. It wouldn't be a US administration without fucking over at least one Latin American country. As much as I would love to discuss what ifs with you, it won't matter. Do you really think Honduras would have reinstalled him with both the Supreme Court and military against him? Do you really think that would have solved the problem or do you think this was a way at keeping the new Honduran government in our pocket? Realpolitik.

Uh, yeah. The post-war liberal world order is the most prosperous period in human existence. The wealth gap in the US and around the world is not a result of the repeal of the Glass-Steagall act, though it did help precipitate the Great Recession. The disparity is a result of globalization and automation (which accelerated as a result of the recession) leading to a permanent restructuring of our economic system. Our economy is rapidly moving away from labor and towards service. Our economy is moving out of the real world and in to the digital world. To think closing our borders to prevent the free movement of goods and services will help bring back jobs is just wrong. Instead it will drive further automation and wreak havoc on our economy and diminish our influence on the world stage.

I agree with you on the need to reform the way we pay for higher education, but that is not through free college. It starts with better high school career counseling, then we need better apprenticeship programs for the trades. Then to drive students into degree areas of greatest need, offer some sort of debt forgiveness or other financial assistance, but only to the best students. If you don't work hard and get the grades, then the cost is all your problem. Drop outs are the major source of the inflating student loan debt. 

Oh the big scary banks, they are strangling us all. /s A vibrant banking sector is a sign of a prosperous economy. The banks can support whoever they want just like you can. If you consider yourself part of any organized group with a political agenda then you are by definition a special interest. Liberal markets are what makes our economy strong.

Health care reform is necessary, but an all at once process is unwise. Dismantling the current system and installing a new one would be a disaster mired in legal challenges for years. It should start at the margins and work its way in. Improve  Medicare, expand Medicaid, and start offering government catastrophic support. Our health care costs are as much a result of our culture as it is industry influenced policy. We need to move away from treatment focused healthcare to preventive and wellness healthcare. There is some regulation needed to better govern the relationship between hospitals and insurance companies. Many procedures and medication are not accurately priced so as to give the illusion of a great insurance discount, but most of it is in the form of an adjustment by the hospital, not because of a payment by the insurance company. 

You can be angry, but allowing your passions to drive your reasoning is setting yourself up for failure. Have you ever made a wise decision when *you* were angry? 

What platform does Trump stand on? Isolationism. Protectionism. Scapegoating. People keep eating up his sound bites, but when you try to look deeper for some substance, there is nothing there. His business record is a joke. His **extreme** selfishness is dangerous. Can you name any redeeming policy or trait of Trump's that would persuade anyone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 21:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong side of history? Globalization is the wrong side of history? Unprecedented economic prosperity is the wrong side of history? Unprecedented peace is the wrong side of history? Isolationism is the right side of history? Trade wars are the right side of history? No, no to all of these. The center has just lost its focus on the message and needs to refine it and tell it in a more compelling way. There is not a single policy point of Trump's that would work. He has no concept of macroeconomic policy. He has less consistency of character than Hillary. Putin and Kim Jong Il both support his candidacy. That alone should be compelling enough.  Trump has no real allies in the beltway. The entire conservative foreign policy community refuses to work with him. His constantly espouse racism. There is no civility to his tone. He represents the absolute worst in us. How people can honestly say they trust him more than Clinton is beyond me. What has he EVER done that has given him the credibility of trust? Name one single thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 20:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the speaker and not president of the Senate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Clinton's are experts at fighting back against exactly the type of political filth Trump spews. I think it will go a lot better than you think. Add the fact Trump has absolutely no grasp on **actual** policy and it should be a solid Hillary show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 00:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "End the Fed; they've devalued the dollar by printing money. (May 2011)"

Do you want deflation? Because that is how you get deflation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 19:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean you can make one pretty quickly. Just get some rope and tie knots at intervals equal to the length of your fore arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 14:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the issue, there is no definition or policy clarifying that clause and no precedent to support a definition either. You can't really build a case on just a "maybe this definition will be interpreted this way."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 14:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would her lawyers accidentally deleting emails fall under (1) such that they were destroyed or is the fact they were recoverable negate that?

I think having a whole case built around defining proper place of custody is too risky for any prosecution. The Clintons' lawyers are too good and they know the laws and policies of the executive branch too well to go down over a definition argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 23:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I fully agree with you. Legal analysis is extremely nuanced. I was only speaking of broader terms which I understand. If you would be willing to explain the factor vs element aspects of this specific statute I would very much appreciate. Even if you could point me towards another source I could look at for this specific context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 22:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I'll agree you know more and my opinion is armchair nonsense.  

Also, just as a little jab to you, it is jargon. Jargon is any set of words or specialized definitions used in a given field which are more difficult for outsiders to understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 22:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I would disagree with you now on what is and is not a factor. The factor primary to this case for her to be found negligent is evidence of unauthorized access. Having the private server wasn't negligent. She did what she thought was appropriate for her duties as Secretary of State. It is easily within her authority to decide the proper holding place of her information. Whether that was wise or not is another matter. On to (2) we see that there must be evidence of hacking or unauthorized access leading to the loss of sensitive material. Without evidence of such an event, what negligence is there? What harm is there? I can look up jargon definitions quite quickly. But hey good for you calling me out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 15:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Whoever, being entrusted with or having lawful possession or control of any document, writing, code book, signal book, sketch, photograph, photographic negative, blueprint, plan, map, model, instrument, appliance, note, or information, relating to the national defense, (1) through gross negligence permits the same to be removed from its proper place of custody or delivered to anyone in violation of his trust, or to be lost, stolen, abstracted, or destroyed, or (2) having knowledge that the same has been illegally removed from its proper place of custody or delivered to anyone in violation of its trust, or lost, or stolen, abstracted, or destroyed, and fails to make prompt report of such loss, theft, abstraction, or destruction to his superior officer

Is the head of a department not capable of determining the proper place of custody? The server was in her possession the entire time and no one gained unauthorized access. Insomuch as there is no evidence of unauthorized access. It can not definitively be said one way or another. There is far too much doubt in the evidence of the case. Any experienced prosecutor or law enforcement officer would never send to trial a case they know they cannot win. Sending a losing case to trial would be nothing but a political farce. It would serve no interests other than political brinksmanship. Do you say her not going to trial under the evidence is political corruption? Well, I say bringing her to trial would be a bigger sign of political corruption. 

But hey, if you want to destroy the independence of government agencies be my guest. But when some authoritarian starts concentrating power, good luck when they start coming for us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 13:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, please elaborate on the difference between an element and factor. Second, go read the law. There is no crime without someone hacking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The gross negligence only becomes a factor if something was found to indicate hacking. By saying "extreme carelessness", he effectively is equating her actions to gross negligence without using the strictly legal term. Since they do not have evidence of unauthorized access, they cannot recommend an indictment. Any trial would be quickly dismissed without evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 14:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true in the US but not so much in the rest of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 01:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to the poor farmer who has been working his land like his father before him and his father before that and so on.  It seems simple to us because we have the educational background. Most of the world does not and even less of the rural population has that level of education and knowledge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 01:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/_FoaomccQJY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey look, Hillary won't be charged with any crimes! Guess you were wrong after all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 03:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pronunciation of aqueous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone keeps saying know to your invitations it makes it seem like they don't want to hang out with you. So why bother when the person isn't interested. If they feel left out they need to make some effort too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 19:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My vote is for Oklahoma, that place is awful. Just give the rest of it to the Native Americans and we can be done with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 18:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the Republican Party is fighting to tear down our religious liberties. Both sides are fighting unconstitutional political battles. Then it just becomes an argument of moral alignment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 20:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Health is a fundamental human right, indispensable for the exercise of many other rights in particular the right to development, and necessary for living a life in dignity. The realization of the right to health is also a fundamental goal of States policies and programmes, regardless of their economic, social, cultural, religious or political background.

http://www.ohchr.org/EN/Issues/Development/Pages/AccessToMedicines.aspx

This right is established under Articles 12 and 15 of the International Covenant on Economic, Social and Cultural Rights.

Religion is never an excuse to deny access to medical care for those who cannot make decisions for themselves.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 21:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a city in a deep valley surrounded by rivers...driving sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 21:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Southeastern Ohio does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's one of the what if questions you could mull over forever. I would expect it to have ended up more like Syria given Saddam's history of killing his own people. Couple that with his hatred of Iran and who knows, maybe there would have been more problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say neoliberal like it's a bad thing.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, hindsight is always 2020. But who knows what would have happened to Iraq and the Middle East had Saddam still been in power for the Arab spring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 01:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know that Russia wanted to financially destroy the US with a massive sell off of Freddie Mae and Fannie Mac, but the Chinese didn't want to play ball? National Insecurity, David Rothkopf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian interests are served by the destabilization of the West. What greater way than electing a president of the US that is outspoken about his disdain for NATO and other Western alliances? If Russia is interfering with our elections that only means  bad things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 22:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when has Russia kindly done anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 22:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the plan is to play into Russia's hand and elect Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 22:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, every single person on my local Republican primary ballot was a religious zealot....unfortunately the party no longer represents me :( Libertarians are a little too fast and loose for me.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 17:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you agree no Breitbart either? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 17:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charities with a 501(c) designation can't participate in politics. Giving to a political campaign is participating in politics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 04:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard science and engineering research pays well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 17:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know that. Thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 17:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, the way the speak sounds a lot like 4chan to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 17:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could but I already got banned for disagreeing with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 12:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever heard of a Mossberg 500 or a Remington 870? AR-15s have no business being used to hunt. You don't need an AR to take down a deer, you should be able to do it with a single shot. Anyone that argues otherwise is a shitty hunter. I have friends that go deer and elk hunting with handguns because of the extra challenge. To think you need that many rounds is plain dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 05:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's not arbitrary insomuch as it is the most common configuration for semi-automatic long guns without a magazine. At least understand the topic before you start getting all hyperbolic about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 05:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever gone hunting or been sport shooting? Three rounds is about all you have time to shoot if you miss your query. 

And on skeet shooting:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Skeet_shooting?wprov=sfla1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 00:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, I just wanted to point out that no religion can be singled out. They all carry the same burden of hate in their scriptures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 00:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bible preaches that too.

http://www.patheos.com/blogs/dispatches/2015/01/22/yes-the-bible-does-say-to-kill-infidels/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 00:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about limiting the number of rounds a semi-automatic weapon can hold? Say we limit long guns to three rounds. What are the arguments against that? If you are skeet or trap shooting that is more than enough. If you are hunting and miss with the first three odds are you weren't going to hit it with another 15. That's just a sign of being a poor huntsman. I just don't see the need for high capacity magazines beyond being more efficient at killing people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 19:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure I understand your logic. The make up and values of the groups I mentioned are not important. But to point out an error in your statement, communists certainly hate and despise Western values. The struggle between communist East and capitalist West defined the last half of the 20th century during the Cold War. Your other points seem to miss the narrative of deeply conservative Christian societies in the former Warsaw Pact countries, like Poland. Catholicism is anathema to Western secular liberalism, which is an outgrowth of Protestantism. Why does Ireland ban abortion, why are gays hated in Poland and other Eastern European nations like the former Yugoslavia? It is Christianity that drives these viewpoints.

Muslims don't hate Christians, they view them as misguided brothers. I won't argue with you on the Islam being against Judaism since it is literally written on the first page of the Quran. Religion in general is the problem not Islam specifically. Both religions are capable of spewing hate and both are capable of extolling virtue and peace. It depends on who is manipulating the masses and for what purpose. Islam is just a younger religion than Christianity and is going through many of the growing pains that Europe endured 400 years ago. Considering Islam is 700 years younger it is not that surprising. 

Rather than spout blind hatred for an entire group of people, why not extend an olive branch? Try to understand them so they can understand you. This us versus them narrative will only lead to more violence and hatred. Hatred breads hatred. Violence breads violence. Our values and strength mean we should be more tolerant to the abuse others give because we are better and we must lead the world by example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 23:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bad tweet regardless. This type of language is thinly veiled extremism. It is essentially a threat to anyone that 'mocks god', which is everyone who doesn't believe in his version of god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
