<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject185</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, he absolutely cares about the people he represents. He represents the CEO and Board of ADM, the CEO and Board of Cargill, the CEO and... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And at least Bush grew up in a family that had political power so he was raised in it (insert obligatory Bane reference.) Trump has no inkling of how diplomacy works thus we have China scolding him for being a diplomatic rookie. 

It's gonna be a long four years - pass the Scotch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems we misunderestimated the gullibility of the average voter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/subredditnamesthatgoonforwaytoogaddamnedlong
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #WITCHCRAFT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of stupid, here's OP's line to which I was referring: 
 Not that other guy who has been strangling **GDP** [*emphasis added*] for nearly a decade.

Show me in OP's post where he mentioned national debt. You can't because he didn't fucking mention the fucking national debt. Reading comprehension FTW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shouldn't "Phonetic" be spelled F-O-N-E-T-I-K? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the annual change in GDP for the last decade - http://www.tradingeconomics.com/united-states/gdp-growth

That downward trajectory on the left side of the graph? Thanks, Bush. Then Obama and Summers took over with stimulus packages and things started to stabilize. 

And the raw GDP numbers: http://www.tradingeconomics.com/united-states/gdp


tl;dr You don't know what you're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ...I doubt they'd last long without the infrastructure and resources that the more populous coastal regions provide.

Or all the Federal tax dollars they suck away from the blue states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 22:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking more Hieronymus Bosch or maybe [Bruegel the Elder](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Triumph_of_Death#/media/File:Thetriumphofdeath.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 21:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or frequently drive into the Hinterlands that your carrier has never heard of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 21:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old timer here (50+). Even back when I had to wait until my parents were asleep and tune in with the volume all the way down, SNL was hit and miss and that was the original Not Quite Ready for Primetime troupe. I'm sure it's always been a case of they write 20 minutes of solid material, 10 minutes of stuff they think might work and whatever padding they need to make the full hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danke schoen, mi amigo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  plants like me

Wait, if you're a plant, how did you type that post? You're really a dog, aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rinsing carrots. To do it quickly, hold it under running water, wrap your fist around it, and stroke vigorously. Just don't let anyone else see you. Well, unless you're both into that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gurl, I would negotiate a trade pact with you SO HARD!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the world of international politics: https://www.wikiwand.com/en/Realpolitik

Political kabuki is standard in diplomatic circles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We live in a post truth world - what used to be obvious sarcasm could well be your firm belief, **especially** if it flies in the face of all objective reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 17:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, what has Pakistan ever done bad? OK, forget their ignoring reports that their [nuclear scientist was peddling secrets on nuclear weapons](https://www.wikiwand.com/en/Abdul_Qadeer_Khan#/Proliferation_of_URENCO_technology) - including to North Korea - and harboring Bin Laden. And the few terrorist attacks on India. And the human rights violations; what country doesn't have a few of those on their CV, amirite? Oh, and the [Benazir Bhutto incident](http://www.biography.com/people/benazir-bhutto-9211744) was a bit messy, sure.

Still, their good guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that the photo of them on the Wiki page shows them fighting. Classic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To quote The Onion from the transition from Clinton to Bush, Jr:
 Our Nation's Long Nightmare of Peace and Prosperity is Finally Over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We're all mad here!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 00:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... read ...

Well there's your problem. Anything longer than 140 characters, Trump loses interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 15:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But still, the "ya'll" in the title is just plain wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've a suggestion to keep you all occupied </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WA, but I went to VT for a wedding this summer and we could really be cousins. I guess we're just West Vermont. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Pink Floyd's *Sheep*:

The Lord is my shepherd, I shall not want

He makes me down to lie

Through pastures green he leadeth me 

The silent waters by

With bright knives he releaseth my soul

He maketh me to hang on hooks in high places

He converteth me to lamb cutlets

For lo he hath great power and great hunger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I **knew** God was gay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was always bothered about how God and Satan were real worked up over this one guy but his 19 kids? God couldn't give a fuck about them. So there's people in this world that are important and others that God would just let Satan do whatever he wants. How do you know which you are? Of course, Christians would claim they are The Important Ones. 

Just one of those little seeds of doubt that grew and blossomed, I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Socrates was right.

Which is why he had to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Skagit 

Which is pronounced with a soft "g". We love confusing visitors in the PNW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some White House intern will say that. This will never get anywhere near the Oval Office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if you eat a lot of carrots, like I do, you could see the missing apostrophe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> y'all == y~~ou~~ all

Y'all dropped the 2nd person plural pronoun so we Southerners fixed that for youse guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is Alabama, Alex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who Needs Sunshine When You Have a Subaru? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Kim Kardashian is active in Armenian genocide

WHAT WHAT WHAT? Google-fu powers, activate!... [OMG!](https://www.kimkardashianwest.com/behind-the-scenes/918-kim-kardashian-armenian-genocide/)

I... I have a shred of respect for Kim Kardashian. This year just keeps getting crazier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the one when Obama bowed to the emperor of Japan? And he wasn't even Muslim (Akihito, that is; Obama, as we all know, is in fact Muslim.) ^^/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the puppet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, he just picks them up from InfoWars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In that case, instead of blundering, he just got infuriated.

Having dealt with a parent and grandparent as they slipped into dementia, I've seen this exact same thing repeatedly. I've been thinking the whole "Donald Trump has Alzheimer's" idea was just an answer to HRC and Parkinson's but now I'm not so sure. And even more scared for the next 4 years than I was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "See, Wilber, Ol' Donny Boy is just like us! Now get off mama - it's my turn." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The good news is the rest of his job is ~~pretty easy~~ being done by Pence.

FTFY

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it's [trickle down](https://youtu.be/x1DLLAqLiAM?t=87) all right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What he meant was he'd slap their ass hard and then tickle it with a feather. It's corporate foreplay and the taxpayers get screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the pols who gave Remington those tax breaks don't care because they are already retired or will be soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Are said researchers genuine...

I found a picture of the [lead researcher](http://www.history.co.uk/sites/default/files/ancient-aliens-1.png). Seems legit.

Seriously, Daily Mail? Why not just link Weekly World News or NY Post?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/zeroneraven posted this above:
https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/5fuzto/military_experts_warn_of_epic_humanitarian_crisis/danjfah/

Check out the rise of 5 deg. video for the world where the methane clathrates have been belched out and all the carbon locked up in permafrost has been released. After that, Earth has become Hell - an atmosphere with heavy concentrations of Hydrogen Sulfide and Sulfur Dioxide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're incredible!

You won't get any argument from me :-)

And you're welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 07:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HINT: The "e" is silent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 07:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the recipe I use for the meltaways:
http://www.seriouseats.com/recipes/2011/04/mint-meltaways-recipe.html

And if you want to know the science behind why blending coconut oil and chocolate is a great idea:
http://sweets.seriouseats.com/2011/04/eutectics-chocolate-meltaways-science.html

TL;DR: Combining 2 fats lowers the melting point of both.

But, where to get the infused coconut oil? In order of easiness:

1) Live in a legal state? Check the menus in Leafly or Weedmaps for your local rec shops to see if any of them carry it. It will be weaker than homemade so you'll have to eat more chocolate to get the effect (the horror!)

2) Buy a Magical Butter Machine. Decarb an ounce of weed, throw it in with a jar of coconut oil and wait 2 hours. This is the route I go because I'm lazy. Sometimes stereotypes are true.

3) Follow this woman's process: http://www.wakeandbakecookbook.com/cannabis-infused-coconut-oil/  Takes longer than the MBM and won't extract as much THC into the oil but it will still beat what you can buy in a shop.

My favorite part of chocolate meltaways? No smell and they keep pretty much forever. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 07:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The correct question is how do you pronounce "Sequim".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another WA resident here and, yeah, that's been my theory. Parents get high, kids see how goofy they act and decide that they'd rather just play video games or shoot heroin or anything other than cannabis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 08:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmpfh glarm yurble glargh. Be, tnath narhb mjilou; 7 so num a x go liwq{ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 08:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be one with the s'ghettis.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 08:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, that's How you **think** you look at a [10] vs how you really look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 08:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, whoever looks the most like Ivanka is in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 08:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relax, Pence is only in charge of domestic and foreign policy. Trump handles everything else which is (exhaustive list to follow):

1)

2)


3)

4)

.

.

.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 08:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now have a mental image of DJT buck ass naked except for the one stitch of clothing he has on - Vladimir Putin's used banana hammock strapped backwards over his nose while he "polishes the Trumpet."

Thank you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rinse and repeat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We keep ~~fighting~~ fucking each other all the time since the ~~begining~~  beginning of ~~humantity~~ humanity, ~~yet somehow~~ so we're all still here.

FTFY

EDIT: I'll "humantity" could be acceptable too.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sexlexia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR Apes get bigger brains, discover fire, burn their home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad was from the "Smoke and pace in the waiting room" era. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 07:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "...the chocolate has hit..."

I take it you too have discovered the joy of making chocolate meltaways with infused coconut oil and a bag of chocolate chips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 04:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     soprano
        Yes, why do you ask?
    /soprano
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only polite to acknowledge them - they made eye contact 1st! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lesson One for men attending the birth - keep your testicles out of reach of the delivering mother at ALL TIMES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 02:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, be fair - he does admit to being a n00b. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 01:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big words? You mean talk all faggy? P-SHUH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why, what was it your mother said? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 23:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like [Len Bias](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Len_Bias)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This kind of rifting behavior provides another mechanism for rapid retreat of these glaciers, adding to the probability that we may see significant collapse of West Antarctica in our lifetimes.

8,000 years from the birth of agriculture to rendering large parts of dry land uninhabitable or not arable. Oh well, *homo sapiens* had a good run, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've probably run across it since this happened 13 years ago but Michael Shermer and Bill Nye had a little fun with cold reading:
https://www.quackwatch.org/01QuackeryRelatedTopics/psychic2.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's what powers all of our passive aggression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 09:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a "silver-lining" kind o' guy, aren't yah?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he's in south Pakistan? Imagine the reaction there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of Sammy Davis Jr and interracial kissing, SD Jr. did a guest spot on *All in the Family* which ended with him giving Archie Bunker a big ol' sloppy kiss. Carol O'Conner's look of stunned disbelief was priceless!

Interracial and homo. Norman Lear loved pushing the boundaries too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And my favorite bit with her was when Riker was trying to teach Wesley how not to be such a little git with the ladies so he shows how he'd chat up Guinan. Wesley interrupts for some clarification and Guinan's having none of it. "Tell me more about...my eyes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Robert Reich](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Reich) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 03:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is how much of a nonissue who you are drawn too is here in Seattle. Large parts of the ~~country~~ world, that would be part of referring to a mayor, His Gay Honor Murray. Here, yeah, that's "Ed".

But I do hate all the goddamn Subarus everywhere. s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TRADITION! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Lot was the one good man in the entire town. Just like Noah was the only good man in all creation and the first thing he does when he gets off the boat is get drunk, thus starting a tradition for sailors everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad someone picked up on that :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 18:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they do have super long prehensile tongues - BJ's would be AMAZING! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To sleep, per chance to dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, because according to that story, God made all the animals male and female but he only made Adam. Then he realized Adam was going to need "a help mate" so he had every species of animal in the world parade in front of Adam (The math on how long that takes is left as an exercise for the reader.) Adam named them all but, being neither Welsh, a Kiwi, nor a member of Daesh, he didn't think any of them looked doable. Shame, the rest of the planet would have been much better off if one species had to be the sacrificial lamb or goat or whatever popped Adam's cork. Then humans would have never populated the Earth and Adam could have lived forever in a goat fucker's paradise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Don't get my hopes up like that. I'm still trying to recover from when I thought Bernie had a shot because the DNC would remain neutral and allow the will of the people to determine the candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That picture should be in the dictionary next to the word *smolder*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Risky click of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From now on, [whenever I masturbate, I'm going to think of your mom.](/spoiler)

I had to pause the movie until I stopped laughing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 00:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that was what I was thinking while reading today's big announcement about another 20B barrels of oil in the Permian Basin - we have more than enough oil, natural gas and coal to well and truly cook this planet. And as long as there's a buck to be made doing it, we will do just that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 22:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tired of same old goat's blood @SatanicRitual. Any thoughts on new libations to Lucifer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 05:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing Disney's lawyers are SO understanding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I can see why he never wanted to do anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 19:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you have a daughter to sacrifice to the Lord of Light? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 06:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please clap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is accurate, George W. Bush holds the record at 19%:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_presidential_approval_rating#Historical_comparison

But, yes, then Truman in '52 at 22%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or it's like he saw a bunch of guys hanging out inside a dumpster fire who then invited him to join them and declined politely but firmly. Brings the motivations of those who are on board into question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ouch, yeah. Now I know we're through The Looking Glass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I think you [misunderestimate](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bushism) Trump's gaffe ability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 00:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Let's do it. 

Let's mas-tur-bate!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want playlists not to disappear. I'm about to switch to Spotify because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
