<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7666</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 20:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, absolutely. Mostly I want to not put down "Dark Age peasants" when even with Google to help I doubt I could keep my family alive with my own two hands and a field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When there are not definable rules for time travel that the book has to stick to. Same goes for superhero stories, fantasy stories with magic, etc. You can have the fantastic, even break the laws of physics if you want. But your system has to be consistent with itself or your story will never be convincing and you can't build up suspense if you can handwave away anything that doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ITAP of a friend on an abandoned motorcycle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much of it was usable, relevant information to your daily existence, though?

I'd be willing to bet a dark age farmer got more information about how his next year was going to go in his first 30 minutes of being awake than you do in a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off: I am not a lawyer. This is my opinion, based on current law.

You have the right to shoot anything you can see in or from a public place, or any privately-owned places where you have permission to shoot. 

Exception: You can't shoot through windows into private dwellings or public bathrooms. Illinois has the [Illinois Right of Publicity Act](http://www.ilga.gov/legislation/ilcs/ilcs3.asp?ActID=2241 ChapterID=62) that prohibits, among other things, shooting people where they have an expectation of privacy. 

However, a lot of places that seem public really aren't. Shopping malls, airplanes, theaters, amusement parks, schools, etc, all have property owners who may have restrictions on what can be shot there. There may also be restrictions at government facilities such as military bases, courthouses, museums, etc. If the owner or their designated representative (like a guard) asks you to stop or leave, you have to. Often public places with photography restrictions will have signs stating them, and you can always ask. Shooting at crime scenes is iffy and police can ask you to move away from the scene. 

On the street, you can take pics of anyone and anything, including kids, without model releases. I like shooting random scenes, little unscripted moments, myself. But don't do upskirt or creeper pics and don't get in people's faces for reaction shots: 1, it's annoying AF, and 2, you may get punched, and you'll deserve it. If I do shoot kids and their faces are visible, I always approach their parents or guardians after to see if they mind those pics being seen online. Some do, some don't. Some have bought prints. 

Keep in mind that if an identifiable person is the main element of your photo and you sell it commercially, that person may seek damages or a settlement for use of their likeness, especially if they are presented as an endorsement of a product or an advocate of a cause. The Illinois Right to Privacy calls this the "right of publicity."

Don't block walkways or streets, you can be charged for that. Some places, notably tourist attractions or rooftop restaurants in picturesque cities, prohibit tripods or any gear that uses a stand. 

Common sense is your guide, really. You can take amazing pics without breaking the law or pissing people off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 22:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coffee maker. No one in the house ever picked up the habit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 22:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it was intended to bring healthcare costs down but wasn't given any real ways to make that happen. Since insurance and medical companies had no intention of lowering their profit margins without being forced to, rates went up and services went away.

Because there was such a concentrated effort to slam Obamacare over and over that people who got their information solely from low-information, high-anger websites and news channels believed it to be a disaster, even though many of those same people favored every individual element of it when they were told about them and the word "Obamacare" wasn't mentioned. 

For some, because it required companies to provide access to birth control and other women's services and they didn't want to.

For some, because being forced to pay for anything, no matter how good for society as a whole, is wrong. These are also the people who forgot what health care was like even 5 years ago, when the emergency room was still the health care of last resort for many and taxplayers had to cover that as well.

Because it is seen as a liberal initiative even though it was based on a Republican program, and the GOP flatly refused to have any input it on whatsoever. Efforts to make it more appealing to the GOP weakened the law, to no avail. (Goodbye, single payer.)

Because some people see any social program as someone taking money away from them to give it to someone who doesn't deserve it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of OP's points was that Trump is not returning criticism with criticism. He's returning criticism with personal attacks. Several GOP leaders gave thoughtful responses to Lewis' inauguration boycott, for example. Trump did not.

And Trump seems unwilling or incapable of differentiating between anti-Trump rhetoric and actual, substantive criticism of Trump's words and actions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, it took how many years to get an iOS app after it was announced? :) But it's good to know something is in the works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've said in their forums as recently as late last year that there is an Android version in development but they're not announcing a fixed date yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes things so much easier for me and anything I write longer than a grocery list I write in Scrivener, especially now that there's an app.

That said, there are people who have tried it and moved on, so I'd say give it a shot but don't expect it to necessarily change your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like with any other story that relies on an "impossible" element (time travel, superheroes, magic, etc) you can have whatever rules you want BUT they must be established up early on, you must stick to those rules, and you can't introduce new rules or exceptions at the end. Readers will put up with anything as long as they don't feel you're cheating or lazy.

Example: "Back to the Future." One of the most acclaimed time travel stories of all (sorry) time, and deservedly so, and it asks you to believe that making a change in the past s-l-o-w-l-y affects the future which can somehow be tracked with a fading photograph. But shouldn't any change be immediate? And if you do accept that the photograph reflects changes, why would his siblings fade? Shouldn't they either be there or not? Makes no sense.

But by establishing it up front and be scrupulously honest to the rules the story set up, with no last-minute cheating, the movie is fun and easy to understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been a favorite book of mine for many years, and I literally just finished listening to the audio version this morning (discovered you can listen to it in the Channels section of a popular audiobook website I apparently can't even mention by name without a bot asking me not to use sales links). 

It depends on your own interests and knowledge. He gets technical when he's talking about computers and ballistics, but the book is narrated by a man with a simple way of talking so that may not be a problem and you can always skim the techy bits.

However, Luna in the book is populated by people cast off from many countries of Earth and some of the language from many places has become part of Luna's language. Manny Garcia O'Kelly-Davis, the narrator, is part of an old Irish family but he speaks English with Russian phrasing and terms mixed in. Where the book has unusual words for an English-speaking reader, it's because they're words from a different language. Will this help or hinder you? No idea.

But I'd suggest trying it. Entertaining, informative and always seems relevant in different ways through the years. Also a weird combination of feminism and sexism, as Heinlein had a healthy appreciation for women's abilities and worth for his day but still tended to think in terms of woman=eager homemaker, no matter what other world-class skills she had.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 16:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most traditional news sources turned to ad revenue because circulation and subscriptions were not enough to fill in for losses from people not buying classifieds or the physical paper as much. Good newspapers would much rather be paid for their work, not for their clicks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 16:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so much more. Every GOP wishlist ever is  on the table, and the insane extreme ones will help make the merely dangerous ones sound like a compromise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 23:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Gut the ACA without replacing it. (Already started.)
- Push through another Scalia right away, with more to come.
- Defund or eliminate any and all ethics oversight organizations that might point out what they're doing and how much it will cost. (Happening already; the very first move was to defang their main ethics committee and Gingrich is making noise about removing the non-partisan CBO)
- Pass federal laws about voter IDs, voting restrictions. redistricting, whatever allows them to remain in power.
- Refuse to investigate Russian connections with Trump, his staff or his cabinet.
- Get rid of the Iran deal.
- Ban abortions past 20 weeks (or entirely, if they think they can swing it) and defund Planned Parenthood. 
- Pass "religious freedom" laws that permit discrimination against homosexuals for any vague reason you can kinda sorta say is religious. (Several bills like this ready to go, most famous one also protects discrimination against unmarried straight people)
- Tax reform, i.e. if the rich keep more of their money everyone benefits, despite the fact that this has rarely, if ever, been seen to work in real life.
- Big push for charter schools and vouchers and more dumping on public schools.
- Strike down every regulation they can in the guise of encouraging the growth of business. Also deregulate banks and weaken the EPA, SEC.
- Change immigrations laws to be draconian, impossible to satisfy, and even lengthier. Strike down latest changes that allow children of immigrants to stay.
- Kill any transgender protections.
- Remove any and all references to or initiatives concerning climate change.
- Open up more oil and gas drilling, build the Keystone pipeline.
- Privatize everything. Particularly Medicare.
- Double down on the war on drugs and increase the use of privately-run prisons.
- Kill Net Neutrality.
- Haven't seen any recent calls for this, but bringing back abstinence-only sex ed and the bible to schools is always a perennial favorite.

An incomplete list, off the top of my head. And to many people, these are all good things. I don't understand these people, I probably never will. But every one has clear, observable, measurable harm, and I expect to see movement on every one of them the first year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 20:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dos Ve-DAN-ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 19:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LO-SER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As many have pointed out, you'll run into problems designating who gets this training.

I suggest instead that we work harder to remove the stigma of vocational training for everyone. It should not have the can't-hack-a-real-job reputation it has now. We NEED trained people to do essential tasks and how dare anyone look down on anyone in a blue-collar job. 

School counselors should be recommending it to anyone who may have an aptitude for it.  Bring back wood shop as an elective to let more students gets exposed to working with their hands and see who takes to it. Start apprenticeship programs with schools. Make carpentry and plumbing and electrical work and construction and even just damn digging respectable again.

When students (and, just as importantly, parents) don't feel they're being pushed into being second-class citizens with nothing else to offer, more will choose to do jobs appropriate to their abilities and their interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video of dog tethered to trailer on I-95 in Flagler causes stir online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hanging up on people on my iPhone would be way more satisfying if there was an option to end a call with an old-fashioned phone-slamming noise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 18:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  However he seems able to change his mind like he promised with Obamacare. He cares A LOT about what his voters think of him and has less allegiances than usual politicians.

Trump treats every engagement, whether it's an argument or discussion or business meeting or press conference or political rally or flirtation, as a confrontation. And he will do whatever he thinks he has to do, say whatever he thinks he has to say, to win that confrontation at all costs. Doesn't matter what he said before. Doesn't matter what consequences there might be in what he says. Won't make much of a difference in what he says tomorrow. He has no core beliefs, other than "Donald Trump is better than everyone else in the world." All that matters is that he wins, and he's *seen* winning, at every turn, and anything that undermines that is either viciously attacked or completely dismissed as fake.

That doesn't make him fair-minded or open to change. It does make him open to parroting the beliefs of people who flatter or benefit him, and it encourages him to spout jingoistic nonsense because that makes crowds love him and cheer. It makes him dangerous and unpredictable. It means that in his mind he is not capable of doing anything wrong, because if he wants it by definition it's OK. 

I can't think of a more dangerous person to be in charge of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an introvert, I internally cheer whenever I manage to get an extrovert to move on and leave me alone, happy with our interaction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 15:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever had to gear your villain back when they got too much more interesting/fun/compelling than the hero?

If you're adapting an existing work (book, comic, etc), do you want to talk to the work's creators about the story and characters or do you prefer to make your own interpretations without their input?

With the near-certain repeal of at least parts of the ACA, what advice do you have for writers without insurance for an employer?

C. A. Bridges

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 01:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breq's gender is mentioned once, I think, and the person doing so may have been mocking it so I wouldn't take it as definitive.

But a big point of the book is that in that society the default pronoun is female -- just as logical a choice -- and that just can't be allowed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Winning is easy; governing's harder" in Vox article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 22:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a book that was not from the viewpoint of a white male protagonist, and it didn't use genders. The content of it was irrelevant, that's enough to damn it forever in the Puppies' eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say he succeeded. And yeah, I got a little choked up there, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carl Edwards walks away with 'no regrets' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is my post inaccurate?

You're not wrong. All I'm hoping to get across is that when you call 911, what you think is the most important parts aren't necessarily what they need to know first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 22:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep a few in my camera bag and swap 'em out as I accumulate new ones. Very handy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 22:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear it. But I wasn't writing for 911 operators, I was writing for people who may have to call in, who may not be as good at it as you were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 22:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give landmarks. If you can, walk away from where you are to the closest place you can get a location like a street sign. If someone's around, ask.

Worst case, like, say, alone on an empty road at night, tell them what road, the last thing you passed, and how long you've been driving since.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A common thread I've noticed, in the operators that seemed the best at it, was that they all seemed eager to help. They were calm, they were patient, but most of all they sounded like they had absolutely nothing to do at that moment besides help this particular caller get though this. That's why I noticed your wording there, which was friendly and in just a few words gives the message "I'm on your side." The ones that (maybe) made things worse were brusque, or cold, or impatient, or (in a few cases) dismissive. And when an operator fails to say, right up front, that help is on the way, I already know how badly the rest of the call is going to go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "Stay on the phone for me, okay? I'm sending them your way now just give me one second."

That's perfect. I've heard operators handle callers with efficiency and care and I've heard operators who may have made matters worse (I've heard more good than bad). I think it's a valuable talent for a 911 operator to have, to be able to talk to a terrified or injured or excited person and get them through what may be the worst day of their life.

Also? Whatever you were paid, it wasn't enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's addressed to people calling in. For example, from the calls I've heard, it seems clear that many people calling in are not expecting to have to give an address. I guess they assume it shows on the computer when they call in? But no, much of the time the 911 operator needs to know, before anyone can be dispatched, where the hell to dispatch them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, I understand what stress can do. A lot of the calls I hear are from bystanders calling in something they saw and many of them are remarkably unhelpful.

And it can't hurt to tell people how to call 911 before they get into a situation that requires it, in case some of it sticks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "They" meaning 911, or the people calling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [LPT] If you call 911, tell them the problem in one or two words (fire, shooting, etc) and the address or nearest cross street before anything else. That lets them get emergency personnel on the way immediately and then they can get more details from you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 20:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea if this is the same guy but I clicked on that one and wow. That's a lot of self-loathing in a condensed space. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had it very long for over a decade in my 20s and varying degrees of length since. I'm middle-aged now and already balding, long looks sillier on me than totally bald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe I should have waited til AFTER the cold weather to shave it all off... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, it's been a week, I like the way it looks now and it's not that big a jump from what I had left.

But *man*, I had no idea the loss of even the little 1/4" hair I had left on the sides and back of my head could make that much difference when it gets cold. I was scrambling for hats over the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because FOX, and the GOP, simply don't consider him a real president. Never have. They don't believe he is a legitimate president and do not wish to offer him the respect he is due.

Contrast this with, say, the New York Times, which refers to everyone on first reference with an honorific.

(In years past I might have softened that with "the extreme factions of the GOP" but it's been awhile since any moderates dared raise their head. If there are any left.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people voted for Trump because they were tired of being told they should treat people like people, and they get a little testy when people keep calling them on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Liberal" has been used as an insult by detractors for many decades, but it wasn't until the Reagan years in the 80s when politicians began paying more attention to their television appearances and there seemed to be more of a concentrated effort to make "liberal" seem like a horrible thing to be, rather than just a different point of view.

In the 90s, Newt Gingrich (and one of his staff, Frank Luntz) [wrote a memo](http://www.informationclearinghouse.info/article4443.htm) advising Republicans how to word their statements to get the most impact. "The words and phrases are powerful. Read them. Memorize as many as possible. And remember that like any tool, these words will not help if they are not used."

Positive words on the list included building, change, children, citizen, common sense, courage, family, hard work, opportunity, pro- (issue): flag, children, environment, prosperity, strength, we/us, etc.

Words to be used when talking about Democrats and their issues included abuse of power, anti- (issue): flag, family, child, jobs, "compassion" is not enough, corrupt, criminal rights, disgrace, failure, greed, hypocrisy, intolerant, permissive attitude, sensationalists, steal, taxes, they/them, traitors, welfare, and, of course, liberal.

The rise of talk radio in the 90s and cable news in the 00s helped speed the process up considerably. Rush Limbaugh spent years denouncing liberals as the source of everything evil in the world, and FOX picked it up and ran with it. Yell anything long enough and people will start to believe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 21:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never!

However, I have felt remorseful, sorry, stricken, contrite, delinquent, depraved, felonious, hangdog, in error, in the wrong, incriminated, iniquitous, licentious, offending, out of line, regretful, reprehensible, rueful, and sheepish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said "evidence *against* our next president being a racist and collaborating with Putin" and I was coming in to see what the defenders said. I misunderstood, but I think it's a better question.

For what it's worth, I don't think Trump operates with the conscious motivation of racism. I think he believes *everyone* is a lesser human than himself, and maybe his family, and he does everything with that in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 06:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two notable ones, one of each:

I worked at the service desk of a building materials store. Late one night, maybe 15 minutes before closing, two guys and a woman were strolling through. One man was walking next to the woman, talking to her, and the other was walking behind. He was also holding up her skirt so that her nude rear end was exposed as she walked. She appeared unaware of this. 

After they passed, my buddy and I discussed the likelihood of whether she knew about it and what might happen when she found out. A few minutes later they came back around. The men looked extremely ashamed and she was walking behind both of them, furious. I suspect there may have been hitting.

Other was my friend at a medieval re-enactment campsite around a crowded fire late one night. Lots of people there and nearby. My very drunk friend was wearing a kilt, and someone asked if he was wearing anything under it. He promptly pulled it up to his chest, checked, and then said "No!" I'm calling it accidental because he was far too gone to realize he'd just casually and slowly flashed about 60 people and had to be told about it the next day. By about 60 people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 05:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does, and I like that one as well. Also the short story in the same setting in her collection "Trio of Sorcery." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of Harry Turtledove's books get too into the weeds about military matters for me, but I reread "Guns of the South" every couple years. Love that book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for more western fantasy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished reading the short stories "Jackalope Wives," "The Tomato Thief" and "Razorback" by T. Kingfisher. I love western fantasy stories! Other personal favorites include Alan Dean Fosters' "Mad Amos" stories, Orson Scott Card's Tales of Alvin Maker series (although the last couple weren't as good, to me), and Mark Sumner's "Devil's Tower" books.

I prefer a sense of humor in even the grimmest of tales -- usually makes the dark parts darker -- and I look for ornery antiheroes. Where should I look next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they could refuse to prescribe hormones, but they shouldn't be able to deny basic healthcare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understood. Damn frustrating, but understood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 21:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My moral position that everyone should be treated has immediate, measurable results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "First, do no harm."

Medical personnel have a much older responsibility. And while in many places this can be tolerated since there are other sources of medical aid, in some areas of the US there are not other sources in manageable distances. Is it right that a trans person could show up at an ER and get turned away? What about women who use birth control prescribed for other reasons besides birth control? I can maybe see allowing refusal for general practitioners or for optional services, but not for medically necessary services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milo is not a gullible fool. He knows full well what he is doing, which is building up his own brand by becoming the alt-right darling. He's using them every bit as much as they're using him and benefiting nicely from it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anti-discrimination laws can be crafted so that individual retailers can refuse service but government agencies and medical services cannot, I'd agree with you. I don't really have a problem if a baker doesn't want to make a wedding cake with two brides but I have a big problem if pharmacists, county clerks or hospitals decide they don't want to do their jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty good. I taught myself web design for fun back when the web was still getting started, and left a job at a building materials store to become the webmaster for a newspaper. That was almost 19 years ago. Still having fun at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We call it out, everywhere we see it, but I'm afraid it's going to come so thick and fast that we can't build up any real resistance. Like fighting a mudslide.

We contact our Congresspeople. Emails, phone calls, letters. Let them know their base aren't the only voters.

We vote. We get more people to vote. We get these people out of office before they can screw things up too badly or too permanently.

We run for office ourselves. One reason for the recent resurgence in the GOP is that they've been campaigning hard for local offices, city commissions, county councils, school boards, etc. Grass roots starts there, and that's where political leaders come from. The current president-elect excepted, of course.

And no, it's not a new sort of government. We've seen this before, we just never expected to see it in this country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a total shutdown of ethics. I'm sure the Independent Ethics Office will promptly be given permission to report widely on any breach of ethics by a Democrat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter. This election proved it. As long as you say the right things so your base elects you and keeps you in office -- or you've gerrymanded yourself into a lifetime job -- you can do anything at all you want.

Expect more like this, every day, from now on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sexuality is a spectrum. A lot of 'em, really, but lets we're talk about two: sexual preference and sex drive. 

Most people are in the heterosexual part of the preference spectrum, but a significant percentage is gay and quite a few are somewhere along the line in between. 

Sex drive is all over the map -- google "how much sex a week is normal" to find thousands of people concerned they're not doing it right -- with some on an extreme end where sex is all they think about, and some are asexual with no interest in it at all. 

This is not abnormal. People are not either-or anything, and when you have a curve you have outliers. Simple as that. 

Not to say it's not causing you problems, but I'd suggest accepting it and going into relationships honestly. Trying to build a relationship where you'd be faking it the rest of your life is a recipe for misery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 02:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revving your engine. Every time you do, I mentally subtract one inch from your estimated penis length. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 02:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand listening to Wil Wheaton read an audiobook. I love his work and his own writing, and the books he's chosen to read are often favorites. But his reading voice is just too flat and nasal for me.

It is entirely possible his reading voice reminds me of how my own voice sounds to me when I hear it, which is hardly his fault, but still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pulled the trigger this weekend.](http://imgur.com/a/Mq3cn)

So far I'm liking it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 21:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [And there goes the rest.](http://imgur.com/a/Mq3cn) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that NASA won't be studying climate change they can figure out how Elton John works on Mars and still comes home for weekends, oh no, no, no </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 14:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I posted over there last week -- one of the replies urging me to go bald helped galvanize me again. 

I'll say again, this subreddit and /r/beards are both incredibly supportive to people making potentially scary changes to their appearance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither son, or their significant others, seems interested in procreating any time soon. But I did get some sidelong glances from kids in restaurants and the mall this year, which was cool. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I think I'd have a ways to go before I could compete. I'm getting bulk, but control is a matter of my beard's whim and my mustache, even after 40+ years, is just a place where I don't shave. 

My brother-in-law has an awesome mountain-man beard that I envy, halfway down his chest with a flowing mustache to match. Lately he's taken to wearing Captain-Jack-style beads and ornaments in it. Someday... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 20:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At various times in my life I've had hair halfway down my back, hair to my shoulders, hair cut short and hair buzzed to a quarter of an inch (my style for the last five years or so), but this is the first time I've buzzed it all off. The process was simple.

1. Decide one day to let my neatly-trimmed beard grow out for the hell of it, to see what it would look like.

2. Enjoy the bushier beard, resolve to go full-Santa and let it go until I am forcibly stopped or it becomes an impediment to driving.

3. Begin to wonder if I shouldn't just put all my attention on the beard, where hair still works, and give up entirely on my head. To be fair, the hair on my head gave up on me first.

4. Google head-shaving, tips on shaving your head, products to use when shaving your head. Read this subreddit for a few days, note that virtually everyone's before-and-after pictures look better after. 

5. Ask wife what she thinks. She's fine with whatever I want to do with it, although she does point out that I started clipping my hair short and stopped shaving to give myself less to do in the morning, and this would increase my grooming time. A fair and accurate point, which I shall completely ignore.

6. Keep thinking about, but not doing it, for several weeks. 

7. Finally decide to do it for New Year's, both as a symbolic new start to the year and because I have a three-day weekend and that gives me time for any weird blotches or cuts to fade.

8. Having said that, skip the first day off.

9. While shopping at Walgreens the next morning, find myself hovering around the shaving products aisle. Pick up some Nivea cooling post-shave balm, no reason, la dee da.

10. Stare at myself in mirror. Take "before" pictures. Stare again. Wonder if I'd get better light for "before" pictures in a different room. Wonder if I slapped myself for stalling, would it open pores or close them?

11. Get out clipper. Wonder if I shouldn't wait till spring.

12. Quickly buzz line from crown down the back of my head, to stop self from stalling. Congratulate myself on taking plunge, but resolve to buzz the rest a bit more slowly because ow.

13. Buzz rest of head, check in mirror, snip and trim bits I missed. Shower.

14. "After" pictures. Note that I don't look especially different, at least from the front, as I was already trimming it short. Feel cooler. Smoother. Lighter. More aerodynamic.

15. Show wife, who says it looks good. Wife is almost a foot shorter than I am so there may not be a whole lot of difference from her angle, either, but I'll take it.

I'll try shaving it bald tomorrow, I want to give my head a day to recover. It really was more of a psychological hump to get over since I was just one setting away from cutting it that way anyway, but it does make a difference in how I see myself. Also, wispy bits of hair on the top of your head are not worth keeping.

Thanks to everyone here for your unknowing support as I lurked and read your stories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I finally took it all off, in 15 easy steps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 20:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 19:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possible my definition of "fringe" doesn't meet yours, as I'm not prepared to accept that as truth on your say-so (no offense intended), I'd need examples.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would pay premium prices to see Ronda Rousey fight, one after the other, the guys on Twitter saying she sucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This year I discovered [unpretty](http://archiveofourown.org/users/Unpretty/works) and fell in love with her version of the DCU.  Honestly, I don't think I've seen anyone write Bruce Wayne or his family better, and her Lois is awesome.

It's a tough call, but I'd pick [Third Wheel](http://archiveofourown.org/works/6918955/chapters/15784000) for my favorite series of hers (definitely some NSFW bits in there) where Clark and Lois come to interview Bruce Wayne for the first time. Favorite shorter story: [Unrealistic](http://archiveofourown.org/works/8082022/chapters/18519460), wherein we find out what the world's greatest heroes think about when they masturbate (NSFW as hell, but not what you'd expect). But really you can start at one end of her work and just work your way through. Love it all, even the fandoms I'm blind in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doesn't matter what the picture is about -- architectural, artistic, nude, selfie -- if there is a visible bookshelf in it I judge it solely on the book collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 04:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 04:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weird Al's polkas. Get that shit over in three minutes and go get on with your day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best: Giggly and fun and something to play with everywhere.

Worst: Figuring out where to put your knees. Deciding on pizza toppings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of sad that people's happiness was so reliant on sexual discrimination. I do note that you're conjoining the study you posted and some other one about women's happiness with the clear idea that one correlates with the other, with no evidence for that connection.

Also, no mention of any other events of the past 50 years that might impinge on people's happiness, such as numerous wars, changes in the economy that make supporting a family, advancement and retirement much more difficult than for earlier generations, increasing dissatisfaction with government, the increased awareness of problems and misery all around the world thanks to cable news and the Internet...

 Why should women waste time collecting resources instead of creating a new generation?

Because they want to? Because they are more suited to that? Because it challenges them? Because they have something to offer? Because they have no interest in producing or raising children? Because they cannot afford to live on one income, and if you're working you should be treated fairly? If a woman -- or a man -- wishes to stay home and raise kids, or volunteer, or be a teacher, they should be able to. But by their own choice, not because they are genetically required to.

It's not about making women subservient, it's about creating a culture that encourages people to do what fits them best genetically.

How about just creating a culture that encourages people to do what fits them best? 

If a woman has no maternal feelings, no desire to be a mother, no skill at it, would you force her to raise a baby anyway? Or would you encourage her to find what she is suited for, and do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Marxism label is also getting used a lot to fight against beliefs that are, according to the conspiracy theorists, intended to destroy traditional Christian roles and values and overthrow free enterprise. Ideas like feminism, multiculturalism, gay rights, atheism, etc. Generally this is being pushed by angry white dudes, and I apologize for unknowingly lumping you in with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, sorry, not interested in debating the current use of cultural Marxism to blame everything that nervous white dudes don't like. I suspect your theories owe more to William Lind than to Engels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See my comment re: humanists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I've worked with feminist activists and instructors since the 80s. You still don't get to decide what they are, largely because even within feminism there are a lot of variances. But the one thing common to all of them is the desire for women to have equal rights and opportunities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who dislike feminism have decided that feminism is an extreme ideology. Doesn't make it so, although apparently if enough people say it you get the same result. 

From Wikipedia: "Feminism is a range of political movements, ideologies, and social movements that share a common goal: to define, establish, and achieve political, economic, personal, and social rights for women. This includes seeking to establish equal opportunities for women in education and employment."

Wow. I can see why you wouldn't want that to catch on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Often people will say one thing and act another way. It's not exclusive to feminists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that is certainly a general assumption. I don't agree with it, and I don't see how you can justify or prove it, but it is certainly an assumption. It's actually a lot of assumptions. Apparently all feminists are exactly the same, and all men are exactly the same, and all women are exactly the same, and you know what they all think. I'm impressed.

(For what it's worth, I did the same thing when I mentioned MRAs. Some MRAs are not anti-woman, they're actively working against legitimately anti-man things like bias in custody settlements. But like feminism, the term MRA is rapidly becoming synonymous with its most outrageous, idiotic members.)

For a lot of people, things *are* better than they were. Sexual assault is taken more seriously. More women are in positions of power and responsibility. Sexism and condescension in the workplace is becoming less acceptable. Relative payscales are being looked at, if not actually getting changed much yet. 

Most (not all) of the people who seem to complain the most about feminism are people who want women to shut up and stay where they belong. If anything threatens that, I can see why they'd think "it's never been worse." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why do you get to decide what fulfills them the most? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most anti-feminist men, in my opinion, either want women kept in a subservient position (not many, I don't think, but they tend to be the loudest and most obnoxious) or are defining "feminism" by the stupidest, most extreme things anyone who called themselves a feminist has ever said. Those are the people who think feminism is anti-man, and if they really believe that then there's no wonder they're scornful. 

The bulk of feminists believe that woman should get the same opportunities as men, and should not be discriminated against because they're female. That's kind of it. I'd like to think an anti-feminist might change his or her opinion if they talked to a feminist, but I'm not sure a lone voice can be heard against the wail of the MRAs.

I have more sympathy to people who prefer to consider themselves humanists, wanting equality for all, but I think that while that's also a feminist goal, disdaining feminism in favor of that ignores the context that made feminism necessary in the first place. Like telling people to stop trying to raise awareness of cancer because we should be fighting against all disease. Accurate, but too vague to be useful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Netflix, YouTube, Vimeo, all the streaming channels that will suddenly get pushed into a higher tier and cost more.

Any political advocacy sites, women's health sites, sex ed sites, any sites that someone might pressure an ISP to block. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's part of the natural order for right-wing whackos; either books or FOX news commentator. He'll go on to do the Anne Coulter thing of popping out books every year and then saying something outrageously offensive JUST before the book tour.

(Before you ask: Left-wing whackos tend to go the documentary route. But they don't tend to be as dangerous.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.

Even aside from wishing death on someone makes your soul all sticky, his death would accomplish two things:

1. Mike Pence would be president, an arguably worse outcome.

2. Trump would become a martyr to his followers.

Then we'd never be rid of him. They'd make friggin' shrines to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 22:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad they're getting auctioned, but I'd love to see these released as prints. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 22:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to skim some and come back to them later. It was a bit much to read them all, one after another, in one big rush.

I thought they did an excellent job of balancing the lighter pieces with the heavy ones to help the reader rollercoaster their way through, but I still had to stop and recharge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 21:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mentioned in another comment that you'd already bought it so you don't need more convincing, but I will say this: while it works perfectly well as a standalone series in its own right, the more you know about Golden and Silver age comics and pulp novels, the more blown away you'll be by this. It's Ellis and Cassidy poking fun (and honoring) the huge, overblown ideas of comics creators in the last century and every issue is a tribute of some sort.

Also make absolutely sure you get the Planetary/Batman crossover one-shot "Night on Earth." Easily one of my top five Batman stories and just talking about it makes me want to read it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News] Comics creators, heroes unite for 'Love is Love' Pulse benefit book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 21:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe the reason people are more upset about celebrity deaths in 2016 is that so many of the dead were people who taught us that being different was OK </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 21:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife scoffed at those but picked up some on a whim a few weeks ago when we were going through the house, throwing out stuff, scrubbing and moving things around, and she was legit amazed at how well they worked. They also disintegrate fairly quickly so they're not very reusable, which is a problem with her, but they took off stains she didn't expect to go so easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 21:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is also assuming they traveled straight from one to the other, without taking any side trips to throw off pursuers or refuel or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stable" doesn't mean "getting better," though. Figured this was coming since all they would say is that she was stable but nothing about consciousness or damage or responsiveness. 

Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 14:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Let's say we're playing poker. You know that half the deck is red cards, so if you get 10 black cards for every one red card, you're going to think something is fishy. No matter how much I shuffle and cut the deck, if you keep getting 10 black cards for every one red, you're going to say the game is rigged - and you'd be right.
 Quotas seem like a shitty solution, and they are - if you insist on 2 red cards for every 3 black cards, you're not solving the root of the problem, and you're going to be tossing out a lot of fair hands. (Also, you can't get a flush, but that's kind of overextending the metaphor.)
 However, the whole point of a quota is that if the game isn't rigged, then you won't need to work to fill your quota. If a quota is a burden, then somewhere in your hiring process you're stacking the deck, and the solution should be to fix that rather than complain about the quota.

Just want to point out this is one of the best explanations of quotas I've ever heard. They're not fair, no, but the need for them points out an unfair situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My uniquely generated Bigger Blacker Box card may be surprisingly useful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 04:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much as I love audiobooks, I think that would drive me crazy. I read much faster than the average audiobook reader. It would be like reading over a slower reader's shoulder :)  I can see how it would help you retain what you're reading, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What triggered this question was me getting and listening to "The Time Traveler's Wife," a book I've read before. The book alternates between viewpoints, and while I greatly enjoyed reading it, it was entirely different hearing it from male and female voices. It's like, in my head it's all one story, but this way it felt more like possibly what the author was hearing when she wrote it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 14:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a huge OSC fan... up till about 2004, 2005, when he started becoming more obviously didactic and, for me, almost unreadable. But his early works remain personal favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stores that stick price tags solidly on the fronts of picture frames: I hate you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 19:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you buy an audiobook, do you look for a new one or a book you've read before? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seem to run about half and half. I like finding new stuff -- this year "The Night Circus" was a wonderful surprise -- but sometimes I don't want to take a chance on wasting hours before I decide I don't like the book. Sometimes I want something familiar, sometimes it's because a good audiobook is a whole new way of experiencing the same book (here I'm thinking "The Martian," which was excellently read, or anything by Neil Gaiman because I love how he reads his work). You? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't checked the numbers so I don't know if 45% is accurate. But I do know it's misleading, since all we know is the number for murderers who have been caught or at least positively identified. We do not know an actual percentage of murderers by race.

That said, I'd be willing to bet the recent upticks in murders in Chicago, Baltimore and DC have brought those numbers up. Elsewhere in the whole country, violent crime is way down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 04:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of impressed. I can see one outright lie in the title and one wild, unbacked claim. I'm afraid to click on the article to see how many are packed in there.

Blacks are not responsible for 90% of all murders. The FBI numbers for 2014 have them responsible for 90% of all *black* murders. Also, whites are responsible for 82% of all white murders, cuz, you know, you're more likely to kill people in the same neighborhood as you. 

As for police letting it continue... The police I know fight to solve every murder they can. That's kind of insulting, assuming that all police are so racist and uncaring, isn't it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Carry a small stack of Amazon gift cards the next couple of days. You can be the hero who saves Christmas after people open and power their gifts from other people and get disappointed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 20:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * They may have little or no interest in sex.
* They may have religious reasons to abstain for a period of time (before marriage, during Lent, during Ramadan, etc), or for life.
* They may be in an emotional state (just came off a bad relationship, recently widowed, etc) that doesn't permit or encourage intimacy.
* They may be in a physical state that renders intimacy painful or otherwise undesirable.
* They may suffer from depression.
* They may not suffer from any emotional or physical restrictions on sex but are in love with someone who does.
* They may be unwilling to settle for less than a specific person or goal and prefer to wait.
* They may be loyal to a mate but not geographically convenient to meet with them.
* They may wish to avoid pregnancy and do not, for whatever reason, wish to use birth control or non-procreative methods of intimacy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the embrace of science, reason and logic as the best ways to discover and delight in my universe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Constant insults to undermine your confidence. "You're wearing that?"

Inability to praise you for your accomplishments.

Too-close or no boundaries, at least in your direction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because your car can't run at flat-out max speeds all the time, so cars are designed to run at optimal speeds around average speed limits. But that means the engines are capable of higher speeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I've got to say, reading over this subreddit, this may be the most overall supportive place I've seen here :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 22:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse, it allows people to discriminate against anyone unmarried who might be having sex, even if they're straight. Don't want to rent to an unmarried couple, don't have to. Don't want fornicators in your clinic, throw 'em out. Don't want to provide birth control pills, morning-after pills, etc, don't. Your vague religious beliefs are now way more important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, good point. This is still a comparatively limited religious freedom bill. But if it passes, it will set a precedent for more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
