<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3700</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bayrock is the one George Osbourne works for, right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are the wealthy Russians investing in Trump luxury buildings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Toddler Trump become normalized?  

Is that how Trump must be handled, [lest he explode](http://i.imgur.com/TklzW3Y.jpg)?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need standards of some sort.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bravo, totally support this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck bigots, I don't care if they are blood.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best thing I ever did was stop talking to my dad after Obama was elected.  Been going on 9 years now, and I don't miss him for a minute.  Every phone call with him he used the n-word like 20-30x.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump won't ever win another General election.  Remember he lost the popular vote, if the Democrats run literally anyone besides Hillary Clinton, they win.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so let's have 50 Oregons.  We need 100 Senators.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to go all-in for open primaries and mail-in-voting.  

That will reliably increase Democratic voter turnout long term in general elections.  Independents will vote for Democrats more if they had skin in the game during the primaries.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fair public trial.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't consider Trump supporters as Americans at all.  Why should I?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Perez still hasn't given us his 50-state strategy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20% of Americans read below a 5th grade reading level.  That is his base.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 17:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perez inherited the lowest percentage of registered Democrats in modern history, let's see how he does.  Two special elections in the next 30 days.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rivers.  

https://www.arcgis.com/home/webmap/viewer.html?webmap=92662da07d224ff29f54947b21934ef9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lack of proper flooding infrastructure.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem isn't democracy, the problem is that rural states have more power than they should.  The way the US is structured won't last.  Lines need to be redrawn.  North and South Dakota can just become Dakota.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 15:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss winning general presidential elections.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go away Clintons! Begone!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suck it up old man, FFS, you just goaded North Korea to escalate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Meanwhile Japan is holding missile drills for the first time.](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-northkorea-missiles-japan-drill-idUSKBN16O0TG)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Obama was scared of populism, he shouldn't've been. 

Obama could've used his popularity like a cudgel to smash the Tea Party.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First three months are traditionally a media blitz for any political chair in the US.  He is the guy whose face donors have to know when he schmoozes with them this summer during the congressional recess.  

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For one, because Dean a month in was on TV for ~2-3 hours a day back then.  Perez isn't even on for 2-3 hours a week. 

The Chair has to rally the party in absence of popular leadership.  Dean did that.  Perez isn't.  There is still massive disunity in the Democratic party.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democrats, losing and blaming the Greens since 2000.  

Lol, look in the mirror.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why Obama should have done nationwide tours while he still had over 50% popularity, he didn't.  

Also where was Kaine?  Oh, he was sending money to safe seats and not even running candidates in all 50 states?  How did that work out?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except American car manufacturers are going to ignore Trump and listen to California on standards.  They always do. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howard Dean lost less seats than DWS.  DWS was more competent than Perez.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in Oregon, are you seriously whining about my voting Green?  

We ran up against the wall of centrist Democrats 20 years ago and toppled them here, that is why we have Wyden and Blumenthal, but even they aren't progressive enough for me.  

Neither one believes in single payer.  I do.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your analysis is laughably hyperbolic, aren't you the guy that accused me of being a republican because I vote Green?  Are you even American?  It does not sound like you understand even basic facts of American politics.  

Keep thinking the Republicans are stronger than they are, Democrats are expert at losing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations, you are the reason Trump won.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and he disappeared for three weeks of that. Great, great, leader!  Just like Hillary Clinton.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so Ellison gets 3% of the choices for who to hire, and Perez get 97%?  That is fair?  

Fuck the DNC and the deluded democrats who support them.  They are the sole reason Trump won.  Shame on them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I joined the Greens.  The DNC is just a shit show.  Perez is such an ineffectual leader, he has no gravitas when he speaks.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the GOP wasn't expecting the racist backlash against Obama to work at first, but when it did they fed it all day and all night.  Coming up with all sorts of new dog whistles like using his full name.  

In 2009 the GOP was getting ready to submit to anything that Obama wanted, and then Obama needlessly capitulated inch after inch.  Obama was naive.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people seriously think that Senators like Tom Cotton, who may very well have 30 years to go in the Senate, wants to go down the road where he is known as one of the GOP ghouls who destroyed Medicare/Medicaid for Trump?  No fucking way.    

What may very well save American healthcare is the selfishness of GOP Senators wanting to keep their seats for the rest of their unnatural lives.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IEWWRbn4zG0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obamacare only barely works because of the individual mandate/fine, yank that out and it will collapse in a few years.  Health insurance does not work without healthy people being the vast majority of enrollees.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 02:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The House GOP will change the plan to exclude it from affecting people 50+ and pass it.  

Millennials will just have to learn to die with dignity from lack of healthcare, and their children can starve in Trump's America.  I mean, *No Moochers* is our motto, right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This also does not save money.  

All this does is force seniors to sell their homes and move into nursing homes which medicare pays for.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Draw more, you got parts of some techniques down.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outside of major metros, yep.  

This is why state-level and national programs help rural folks the most.  It is insane that the Republicans have rural voters voting against their own interests.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippine lawmaker calls for Duterte's impeachment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 06:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Sikhs are middle class, try being an urban kid with a mom on welfare during the Clinton years when he helped pass the [Personal Responsibility/Work act](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Personal_Responsibility_and_Work_Opportunity_Act)  -- a cornerstone of the GOP's Contract with America -- when TANF replaced the AFDC program and cut welfare to families living in areas that had no work options for single mothers, families were thrown out on the streets in droves.  Bill Clinton dramatically increased child homelessness, and the breaking up of extremely poor families.  I have nothing but contempt for him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 05:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were white, maybe.  Sucked to be a brown kid during Clinton's Get Tough on Crime years. 

Check your privilege.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow the links therein.  

The Ivanka Trump foundation is pimping a GRU app.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louise Mensch on Twitter: "Not just any Russian tracking app. @IvankaTrump verified @IvankaTeam is pushing a GRU app literally named for Russian military intelligence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HHS Secretary Tom Price says it should be up to states to regulate whether immunizations are required </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, fuck the Clintons, they have done enough damage already.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dixie Chili is awesome, please expand.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way she had 90% approval among Democrats, source?  

Half of the people who I knew who voted for Clinton did so while holding their nose.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So obviously the best idea ever is to run Chelsea so she can lose too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Green, I left in the 1990's when Bill Clinton signed the Defense of Marriage Act.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 02:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton is a horrible person and politician.  I don't support her in any way.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally don't care about you and your problems.  I care about civil rights, I care about economic inequality.    

Why don't you just go vote for tax breaks like a Republican does.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 10:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the only reason you vote is for yourself, go join the Republicans or Libertarians.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They broke the story.  I don't support them.  I am a Green.  

Do you want to have a safe space or political breaking stories?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audio Emerges of When Paul Ryan Abandoned Donald Trump: I Am Not Going to Defend Donald TrumpNot Now, Not in the Future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I hate /r/politics, terrible moderation.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't support Breitbart, they have an exclusive.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exclusive  Audio Emerges of When Paul Ryan Abandoned Donald Trump: I Am Not Going to Defend Donald TrumpNot Now, Not in the Future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks Like Wikileaks Outed Some CIA Agents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 04:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conway went on to say that the monitoring could be done with microwaves that turn into cameras, adding: We know this is a fact of modern life.

I think Trump might be working with the Decepticons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if the Democrats don't have competent likeable national leaders. 

Pelosi and Schumer are more divisive than Clinton, and where the fuck is Tom Perez?  Tom Perez has disappeared.  

The DNC haven't learned, the Democrat establishment is fucking it all up again.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her child care plan would only help those who make more than 60k a year or so.  Those making 250k or more would be able to write off their nannies, which is insane.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 17:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen FP go after a sitting president like this.  

This is crazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is not 6'4".   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man sets fire at store; thought owner was Muslim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 21:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is true though, what other generation watches 10 hours of Fox News a day?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump pal Roger Stone admits he spoke privately with DNC hackers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 15:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 05:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop paying federal taxes.  Civil disobedience.  

They can throw me in jail, I'm not paying taxes to the federal government anymore, as it appears to be compromised by a foreign power.  What guarantee do I have that giving money to Trump will not be funneled to Putin?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond a reasonable doubt? Study reveals how eyewitness testimonies go wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 04:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this rate the FBI is going to be frogmarching Trump out of the White House in his golden pajamas by next month.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like Trump is used to being a rich guy who can hide from his problems.  He has pretty much spent half of his life jet setting around the world on vacations, and now he has a stricter schedule than a private in the armed forces.   

He must be absolutely miserable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, plenty of people associated with Nixon, including ones who went to prison had no problems with their careers really.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Dog herpes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your father was abducted by a Y2k Doomsday prepper cult.  He is scratching underneath you right now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love my representative Earl.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People bond easier over emotions than intellect.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is being blackmailed by Russia and used as a patsy by the House GOP.  He is doing worse with Congress than Carter.  Carter had energy bills already passed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should we be cruel to them?  We should be better than them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 10:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are alleging a conspiracy of 17 US intelligence agencies comprised of 100's of thousands of Americans who saw the raw data.  Proof?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Political pluralism is important, and I would love to see Oregon have more than two parties represented.  We really need Ranked-Choice voting statewide.  I think the reason so many folks are polarized is because there are only two parties.  

http://www.rcvoregon.org/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allegations of corruption surface around the Trump Tower in Baku, Azerbaijan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we need a new amendment that explicitly grants privacy for individuals as a civil right.  

Privacy for corporations should be strictly limited.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost 70% here in Oregon.  We are shooting for 70% again in midterms. 

Voting by mail works.  Soon it will be free to mail here too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 00:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to redraw the maps.  The Senate represents rural states but the nation lives in urban states, and that will never change without redrawing the maps.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raug is horrible.  Their leaders yell and kick people randomly, and when their leaders don't do their jobs like dropping bacons, they ragequit when told.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is zero evidence to support this claim.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russians just get more bang for the buck because they are trying to sow chaos, chaos is easy, it just takes gasoline and a match.  

Americans are trying to maintain economic and political hegemony around the world by going from place to place spinning plates, and it only takes a moment of inattention for a plate to crash.    

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on how much the CIA has that we aren't seeing.  

A hacked Samsung TV could be in the Kremlin with years of surreptitious audio and video access right now.  

Russians have no native TV manufacture, and S. Korean and American intelligence go way the fuck back.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [List of assassinated American politicians.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_assassinated_American_politicians)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy stock in child-sized body bag companies now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let the Republicans ever distance themselves from Trump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manafort denied knowing him as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overweight Lonely Manchildren. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the NYT and WaPo have something in their pipeline like the Trump Dossier that is taking up a lot of their time right now.  

There are massive leaks going on right now.  Everything will become clear soon.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Jong Un Lights Fires Across Asia, Raising Dilemma for Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who benefit from this plan are wealthy people and health insurance executives.  Everyone else gets the shaft. 

Older people can be charged 5x the rate of young people on this plan.  Young working families would go back to being uninsured.    

This is not a serious plan, no fucking chance to get through the Senate.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Catholic church is still around.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't link to Facebook on here but if you check the comments on Dan Rather's posts he seems to be getting through to more and more of the baby boomers every time he posts  -- check people's age on the comments.  

When Dan Rather started ragging on Trump most of the top comments were against him, but the tide turned at some point this month.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dan Rather: Trump administration in freefall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri is the only state not tracking prescription drug use. Here's why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 13:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it is just spoiled loserish manchildren, they have always been part of the GOP base.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best interview by Hayden so far, really impressed by this Yahoo anchor.  When did Yahoo get news anchors?  

Am I in an alternative reality?  I'll do anything to get back to the Kasich-led reality.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, the plan is to allow non-rich Americans to go bankrupt and lose their houses again.  Fuuuuuuuck that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No More Talking Heads at a Pennsylvania Gym </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 04:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NY state can afford to pay its own way with NYC.  If NYC leaves they are fucked.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely will drive the price of children's coffins down.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which they used to do, and will absolutely do again.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congress does not represent the will of the American people, they must be resisted like Trump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
