<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4091</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming all the basic needs are provided. Books, a sketch notebook, colour pencil and watercolour sets, extra batteries for phone(mainly for music), camera and a bunch of films, sun block, snorkling gear, fishing gear, torch, sunglasses, and most importantly, chili. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Have you ever seen the true face of god, exile?"

"Die in awe!"

"Why.. are you so in love with death?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same look looking at that rollei 35s she's holding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 10:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now we just need the roadkill version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 10:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then, here's your article http://hypervocal.com/culture/2012/blanche-dumas-juan-baptista-dos-santos-two-penises-vaginas/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 10:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a kanye fan but this is funny. I sometimes wear an old shirt with holes at home and just nod and say "yeezy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 10:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a married couple both of them having 2 genitals. Though i doubt youd like to see a porn of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 07:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not sure whether i should call it a cult or a coven. I joined a "meditation/buddhism class" so i can research for my scriptwriting class. Turns out they're more than that. We did circle magick and shit. I got in deep but not deep enough. Prior to my supposed initiation(to lead the circle), i had sex with the priest's sisters. Turns out it was just one of the girl's ploy to get rid of me. The priest would still keep me but it was too much shit for me, drama, being harrassed by the girl. So i left </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 09:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vork vork vork drink fight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 08:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/stigsd hey man, can i get details about this cheapo laser cutter? I do leatherworking as a hobby and this will greatly help in making camera cases fir my vintage cameras! Thank you so much in advance. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I sometimes wish that i stayed inside my mother, never to come out." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 07:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not fucking justin beiber, you motherfuckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the third world and even i have this. Wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prepare my art materials.

Then continue to do something else entirely; internet, game, terrorise my friends in snapchat, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do drawing/paintinf and fashion related commissions. Buy and sell stuff on the side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 05:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh baby. Hopefully very fucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Queue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless the timeline is promised to stay relatively close to the current one, most of the knowledge i have would soon be worthless.

That said, i would exploit technology, stock markets, and fuck around adults with my ahead-of-time thinking, write papers about things that are yet to be discovered. Id be the genius who peaked at 24yo but by then i'll be rich af.

If you consider the time concept of [about time](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/About_Time_(2013_film)) it could means that people yet to be born at the time might seize to exist cause its very unlikely for the same sperm to seed the egg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around 60hours. It was a hell week at school; had to finish major projects while also prepping for exams. Slept 22h after </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Public properties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad Obsession Motorsports

Mighty Car Mods

B is for Build </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rip cds and share among friends

Lan parties

Classic Need for speed underground 2


Internet came to my city really late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cubes? Cubes!?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timed it. It was 20secs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An uncle of mine was inquiring for granite prices to use for their multimillion dollar house. My dad and his brothers always dressed modestly. Some basic shirt, jeans and sometimes just flip flops. Often times, except for really important and official occasions, the driver and bodyguards are better dressed than them. So he was asking the store lady about the price of their mid-tier granite products as he is planning to buy loads of slabs for his house. The lady laughs at him thinking it was some sort of a prank and was waiting for the better dressed guy(driver) to ask them personally. Driver approaches and tells the lady that she was talking to his boss, and that he'd like to talk to her manager.

Uncle talking to the manager tells how much granite he wants, and instead of the mid-tier products he'd like to go for the best kind of granite they can offer.

The saleslady apologised several times before she was sent to some office.

He literally ordered trucks of them. So much that by the time they arrived to the construction site 400km away, the bed of the semis were slightly bent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 08:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a somewhat similar situation. I was the brilliant kid in high school, and now it's just nothing.

Last year was the highlight of my life, but also the lowest of the low.

I finally got accepted to the best uni for the course I wanted. Put in everything. I was doing pretty well with an online trading business but I poured it all in, my capital, every profit I've earned, savings and all, but it wasn't enough. I needed the support of my family but it wasn't the degree they wanted for me. That degree? I dropped out of.

This got me really frustrated which lead to break up, and losing most of my friends. Frustration turning into depression. I chose alcohol and smoking as a coping mechanism. That went on for a while but now it's just smoking. The only time I feel really happy is when I'm doing collabs and commissions. I hate to admit it to anyone but really I'm stuck on a dead end, barricaded by the pile of ambitions I have that's seemingly impossible to vault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doughnuts and cakes! But put a bowl of water in there to make sure it's moist and moulds well.

To add a bit of "bait" factor put in pieces of metal too so they can hear some "clank" in case they try to shake it.

Oh oh oh I got another.

A dvd of whatever video your family likes to watch or a personal message so as to keep them engaged. Edit the vid so that the sound get lower and lower gradually to the point that it gets almost inaudible. This will prompt them to raise the volume. At the last parts of the video edit in some porn sounds. Full blast! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is the one that made me cry! I laughed so hard my cheeks hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed! I miss the old Kanye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 05:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy - Kanye West

Man on the Moon - Kid Cudi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the drug deals were done behind the scenes. ;) ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War...


War never changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would refer to my hair as big(puffy) rather than long. I'm working freelance doing fashion illustration, (student level)portfolio development, and fashion graphics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philippines :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
