<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1459</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try therapy first =! Drugs are bad.

Also, this:

At the same time, Im a realist, and I understand that social anxiety is often influenced by our biology and genes. For some people, medication may be the best option they have.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wasn't an anti-"big pharma" article. It explicitly says that medication can still be effective for many people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It in no way turns over the many, many larger studies showing the efficacy of combination CBT/pharmacotherapy.

Can you share some of these studies with me? I've seen a lot about CBT/medicine combo being effective for depression and other disorders, but not much about social anxiety specifically.

EDIT: I'm not trying to be obtuse, I'm genuinely curious of other studies about social anxiety and medication. I did a quick search right now for "social anxiety medication study" and came up with a [meta-analysis](http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpsy/article/PIIS2215-03661470329-3/abstract) from 2014 that seems to support the study mentioned in the article:

Individual CBT (which other studies have shown to have a lower risk of side-effects than pharmacotherapy) is associated with large effect sizes. Thus, it should be regarded as the best intervention for the initial treatment of social anxiety disorder. For individuals who decline psychological intervention, SSRIs show the most consistent evidence of benefit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women already know that if their reaction to becoming angry is tears (yes, that's a thing), they will get shit on at work.

Hm? A woman can definitely get away with crying at work more than a man can. Hell, she might even use it to her advantage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Men: this study suggests its a really bad idea to cry in front of your colleagues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A daily cold shower seems to have some psychological benefits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Medication Should Be a Last Resort for Social Anxiety - "A new study shows taking medication for social anxiety might be a bad idea for long-term progress." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 16:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stefan Molyneux's Five Hour Christmas Spectacular (w/ Paul Joseph Watson, Vox Day, Duke Pesta, Scott Adams, Charles C. Johnson, Lauren Southern, Bill Whittle, Ben Garrison, Dave Rubin, Alex Jones, Bill Mitchell, Mike Cernovich, Gavin McInnes) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 05:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Changing Conspiracy Beliefs through Rationality and Ridiculing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 04:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rational arguments and ridicule can both reduce belief in conspiracy theories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 04:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rational arguments and ridicule can both reduce belief in conspiracy theories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 04:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rational arguments and ridicule can both reduce belief in conspiracy theories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 03:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 Life Skills to Start Working on Today - "The new year is upon us, and along with the celebrations comes a time for looking inward and focusing on what is truly important in life and how you want to improve in the new year." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Experience Junkies: The Futility of Searching for Every New Thrill and Sensation - "Ive never been the type of person who thought I needed to travel the world to find true happiness. Ive always thought I could find happiness in my own backyard." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Falsification ruled 20th-century science. Does it need revision in the 21st? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Falsification ruled 20th-century science. Does it need revision in the 21st? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Recent Anti-Trump Hate Crime Hoaxes that the Media Spread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A history of global living conditions in 5 charts - "Most people think the world is getting worse. They're wrong. The history of progress in 5 charts. Our World In Data" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 15:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016: The Year of Asian-Americans Fighting Back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smart Women Are Only More Sexy To Men Sometimes - Here's When </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 01:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Medication Should Be a Last Resort for Social Anxiety - "A new study shows taking medication for social anxiety might be a bad idea for long-term progress." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Big Brains Are Rare - "Studies of electric fish support the idea that really big brains can evolve only if constraints on energy intake are lifted." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make a Quick, Early Appearance at a Party If You're Just Not Feeling It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Define Maturity When the Brain Never Stops Changing - "Neuroscientists dont know when your brain is a legal adult. While the law has to draw a line between adolescence and maturity, ranging globally from 10 to the early 20s" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Define Maturity When the Brain Never Stops Changing - "Neuroscientists dont know when your brain is a legal adult. While the law has to draw a line between adolescence and maturity, ranging globally from 10 to the early 20s" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Testosterone Affects What Men Find Attractive - "Research shows that a dose of male hormone changes how men see women's faces." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our minds are imperfect. We cant account for all the factors that contribute to the outcomes in life. So sometimes its necessary for us to go through the pain of "trial-and-error" before we know the right path to take in life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No more drama: The game theory guide to a happy family holiday - "From who will host to the last piece of cake, tis the season to bicker like wild animals. Have yourself a merrier little Christmas with some strategic thinking" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 04:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My opinion of course, but I have to disagree.

I think Aesop is a lot easier to listen to than most other rappers who are getting acclaim this year. He has a clear flow, he enunciates all of his words and is easy to understand, and his beats are fire. His lyrics can get weird and quirky, sure, but I think people can enjoy his lyricism just as much as any other rapper (if not more). He's intelligent and maybe artsy/pretentious-sounding for your average listener, but his name recognition is enough for me to think a lot of critics would eat this release up. 

**I'm just surprised he's not on a *single* list so far according to [Metacritic](http://www.metacritic.com/feature/critics-pick-top-10-best-albums-of-2016).**

Counter-example: Danny Brown. I love him and I think his album is top 10, but he comes off way more inaccessible to me (and, I think, has less name recognition). His voice can be borderline irritating at times (for most people), the album was all over the place stylistically (I don't mind personally), and extremely weird. Yet, he's received a lot more attention from critics top 10 list.

I think the more likely reason Aesop is being over-looked this year is because his release was much earlier in the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but I would say most /r/hiphopheads and /r/indieheads would know him and love him - and this was a super solid release by him. Hell, Pitchfork gave this an 8.2 and it's nowhere to be found on their top 50. And not a single mention on any critics list according to [Metacritic](http://www.metacritic.com/feature/critics-pick-top-10-best-albums-of-2016)? He's not *that* underground or niche. This is being looked over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aesop Rock - Dorks (Is it just me or is this album getting seriously snubbed this year?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BrooklynVegans Top Albums of 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just came to upvote and say I agree, because The Impossible Kid is easily in my top 3 albums of the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aesop Rock - Dorks (Is it just me or is this album getting seriously snubbed this year?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps victory another example of how Electoral College wins are bigger than popular vote ones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 21:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our minds are imperfect. We cant account for all the factors that contribute to the outcomes in life. So sometimes its necessary for us to go through the pain of "trial-and-error" before we know the right path to take in life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 19:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Asian American Men Seek Therapy: The Invisible Struggle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noise Sensitivity Traced to Changes in Brain Function - "Some people experience strong discomfort of sounds around them and complain that they suffer from noise." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source](http://www.prri.org/research/poll-post-election-holiday-war-christmas/) (along with some other interesting findings) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic Women Most Likely to Block "Friends" Because of Political Views </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eye Contact can be Overwhelming - "Research shows that maintaining eye contact can make it harder to think" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 16:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic Women Most Likely to Block "Friends" Because of Political Views </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source](http://www.prri.org/research/poll-post-election-holiday-war-christmas/) (along with some other interesting findings) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic Women Most Likely to Block "Friends" Because of Political Views </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source](http://www.prri.org/research/poll-post-election-holiday-war-christmas/) (along with some other interesting findings) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic Women Most Likely to Block "Friends" Because of Political Views </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 20:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The education gap between Hindus in India and the West </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my intuition too. I wonder if there are any studies that show the opposite of OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why its hard to talk and make eye contact at the same time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Kindness Mindset Helps You Overcome Social Anxiety - "When we approach people with the intention to do a favor, it can often disarm our sense of inferiority because it takes the focus off of ourselves and puts it on the other person." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Men Really Get Over Breakups Faster Than Women? - "When graded on a scale, men, on average, did feel less pain than women after a breakupboth emotional and physical. It's not necessarily because the men were less into their partner. We may have evolution to thank instead. " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The compassionate sexist? How benevolent sexism promotes and undermines gender equality in the workplace. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traumatic Head Injuries Should Be Treated By Cooling The Patients </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaders are more powerful when theyre humble, new research shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Serial,' 'Lore,' 'Still Processing,' and More: The Atlantic's 50 Best Podcasts of 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The surprising self-interest in being kind to strangers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's A New Way To Avoid Dementia - "Frequent saunas are linked to a reduction of 66% in developing dementia, new research finds." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Problem With Using Fascist as a Political Insult - "Fascism is in the running to be Merriam-Websters Word of the Year. But its not the right word for the current moment." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's A New Way To Avoid Dementia - "Frequent saunas are linked to a reduction of 66% in developing dementia, new research finds." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 01:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reaping the Rewards from Relationship Advice - "Facing relationship challenges on your own could be daunting." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King Gizzard   The Lizard Wizard - "Evil Death Roll" (2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 04:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Unexpected Adaptability of Chimps to the Human World - "As conservationists scramble to protect decimated ape populations, chimps are adjusting to new surroundings in surprising ways." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Potential: Jordan Peterson at TEDxUofT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Power of Choosing Joy: Lasting Happiness in a Changing World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Self-Compassion Make You Selfish? - "A new study suggests that self-compassion makes you hold yourself to a higher standard of morality." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 00:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a second window of opportunity for learning in late adolescence and early adulthood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teaching philosophy at school isnt just good pedagogy  it helps to safeguard society </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Empathy is an overrated skill when dispensing medical care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many Americans Believe Fake News Is Sowing Confusion - "23% say they have shared a made-up news story  either knowingly or not" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 20:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans Name the 10 Most Significant Historic Events of Their Lifetimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americans Name the 10 Most Significant Historic Events of Their Lifetimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Power of Choosing Joy: Lasting Happiness in a Changing World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Power of Choosing Joy: Lasting Happiness in a Changing World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 03:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Runners Brains May Be More Connected - "MRI scans show that running may affect the structure and function of the brain in ways similar to complex tasks like playing a musical instrument" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infants Show Apparent Awareness of Ethnic Differences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infants Show Apparent Awareness of Ethnic Differences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teens Benefit From Later High School Start Times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Hearing Twist My Arm Engages the Brain - "Body part metaphors activate the extrastriate body area." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Hearing Twist My Arm Engages the Brain - "Body part metaphors activate the extrastriate body area." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Hearing Twist My Arm Engages the Brain - "Body part metaphors activate the extrastriate body area." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Religion Help Our Brains Evolve? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Religion Help Our Brains Evolve? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simply studying populism is no longer enough - "Sociologist Matthijs Rooduijn explains why the darkening political mood must force academics to step up and choose sides." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I miss baseball. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Orcas are first non-humans whose evolution is driven by culture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 02:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Mental Health Boosters to Combat Winter Sadness - "Winter sadness is when we feel more depressed and unmotivated during winter months of the year. Here are 5 mental health boosters to combat it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Civilizations Rise and Fall | Michael Woodley of Menie and Stefan Molyneux (lengthy talk on IQ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 23:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Impressions Count Even More Than You Thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live Reyes and Thor interview at CITI field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real recognize real.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly never heard of The Rebel until now - I shared the video because I thought it had some good information. 

When did The Rebel step on other's freedom of speech? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just heard of Jordan Peterson through this video so I'll have to check that out. It seems like a lot of his work is an extension of Jonathan Haidt (who is fantastic).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Do SJWs Come From? - "Dr. Jordan B. Peterson and PhD student Christine Brophy have been researching political affiliation, personality and political correctness." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 15:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Do SJWs Come From? - "Dr. Jordan B. Peterson and PhD student Christine Brophy have been researching political affiliation, personality and political correctness." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Do SJWs Come From? - "Dr. Jordan B. Peterson and PhD student Christine Brophy have been researching political affiliation, personality and political correctness." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Mental Health Boosters to Combat Winter Sadness - "Winter sadness is when we feel more depressed and unmotivated during winter months of the year. Here are 5 mental health boosters to combat it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Do SJWs Come From? - "Dr. Jordan B. Peterson and PhD student Christine Brophy have been researching political affiliation, personality and political correctness." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Do SJWs Come From? - "Dr. Jordan B. Peterson and PhD student Christine Brophy have been researching political affiliation, personality and political correctness." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1905 - You're Wrong (2004) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 00:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Journalists and Trump voters live in separate online bubbles, MIT analysis shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 19:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 3 Second Rule: Anxiety is a Call to Action - "The more time that passes  the more time you have to over-think  the higher your anxiety levels." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 16:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Times Trump Cover Is a Subversive Work of Political Art </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 00:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Bloom on why VR empathy projects wont save the world - "Empathy is all too easy to exploit" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Reid: Trump 'Not as Bad as I Thought He Would Be' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 06:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harry Reid: Trump Not as Bad as I Thought He Would Be </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 06:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 04:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anywhere blacks are in the world, they end up having increased crime rates compared to the general population (for example, see [race and crime in UK](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Race_and_crime_in_the_United_Kingdom#Race_and_crime_in_London) - which has less of a history with oppressing blacks than the US). 

Don't get me wrong, poverty can certainly play a causal role (it certainly doesn't help), but it's not the *only* factor (and it could also be a symptom of other factors). IQ (and the heritability of IQ, which is established to be between 50-80%) also matters. Culture (especially one parent households, which is another correlative factor to poverty and crime) also matters.

There's actually a huge web of factors (likely both nature and nurture) that cause blacks to generally be more crime-ridden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Honest Conversation About Race | Jared Taylor and Stefan Molyneux </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see some lists of general publications and authors, but I'm looking for specific information about "genetic astrology" and the shortcomings of ancestry sites besides the public statement you linked to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, am I missing something? The page reads like a press release or introduction, but I'd like to know more. Are there studies about this or more in-depth articles about the shortcomings of genetic ancestry sites like Ancestry.com or 23andMe.com? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anywhere I can read more about this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King Tut Was Eastern European, According to the DNA Results </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 3 Second Rule: Anxiety is a Call to Action - "The more time that passes  the more time you have to over-think  the higher your anxiety levels." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gary Johnson has Been High 'Pretty Much Constantly' Since the Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the Alt-Right Really Means </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 17:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump to Boeing: Cancel order for new $4B Air Force One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sizing up: women prefer slightly larger penises, new study reveals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Frankfurt School Knew Trump Was Coming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 00:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not supposed to build "social skills" exactly, it's supposed to give you a healthy dose of "not giving a f---."

Maybe doing purposely embarrassing stuff won't help you, but these tactics have definitely helped me a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical Implosion: Why You Should Embarrass Yourself On Purpose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, all of Dvila's writings are in this aphoristic style. Make sure you check out his other quotes on the sidebar ("God   Religion," "Democracy   Equality," "Progress   Progressives.") I go to this site once a month because it's just filled with insight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Wisdom consists in being moderate not out of horror of excess, but out of love for the limit." - Nicols Gmez Dvila </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 05:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The tissues of society become cancerous when the duties of some are transformed into the rights of others." - Nicols Gmez Dvila </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 05:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Swimming against the current is not idiotic if the waters are racing toward a waterfall." - Nicols Gmez Dvila </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Political science is the art of quantifying the amount of freedom man can handle and the amount of servitude he needs." - Nicols Gmez Dvila </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 04:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Truth About Social Anxiety and Introversion - "No, social anxiety and introversion aren't the same thing, but the relationship is a bit more complicated than that." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 03:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical Implosion: Why You Should Embarrass Yourself On Purpose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 17:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical Implosion: Why You Should Embarrass Yourself On Purpose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Stable Are Democracies? Warning Signs Are Flashing Red </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical Implosion: Why You Should Embarrass Yourself On Purpose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reductio ad Hitlerum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 06:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tanya Tagaq - Sulfur [2016] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radical Implosion: Why You Should Embarrass Yourself On Purpose </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad memories stick around if you sleep on them - "Dont go to bed angry. Now theres evidence for this proverb: its harder to suppress bad memories if you sleep on them." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad memories stick around if you sleep on them - "Dont go to bed angry. Now theres evidence for this proverb: its harder to suppress bad memories if you sleep on them." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 17:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Free Salamander Exhibit - "Undestroyed" (new song by former members of Sleepytime Gorilla Museum/Idiot Flesh) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fighting Depression by Staying Awake - "Insomnia is a common symptom of major depression, and yet sleep deprivation can be part of the solution for a patient seeking quick relief" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 19:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The media when Trump tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Kindness Mindset Helps You Overcome Social Anxiety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 16:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle Of Wits With Beetlejuice and Gary The Retard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 05:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Gates - Fuck It </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the result of increased stress levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Santa Claus Really Coming to Town - "A new study suggests maintaining a myth may be damaging to a child." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Santa Claus Really Coming to Town? - "A new study suggests maintaining a myth may be damaging to a child." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nazis are Fake News, Independent Analysis Proves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upward mobility boosts immunity in monkeys - "Changes in social status affect the way genes turn on and off within immune cells" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Kindness Mindset Helps You Overcome Social Anxiety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upward mobility boosts immunity in monkeys - "Changes in social status affect the way genes turn on and off within immune cells" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upward mobility boosts immunity in monkeys - "Changes in social status affect the way genes turn on and off within immune cells" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 19:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mates of State - Fluke [OFFICIAL MUSIC VIDEO] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 04:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Kindness Mindset Helps You Overcome Social Anxiety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 22:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Kindness Mindset Helps You Overcome Social Anxiety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 23:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely - or even 10 days! I just like doing the thought experiment with "10 years" because it shows a more drastic difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 17:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the hell are you getting downvoted? It's literally in the first sentence of the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment needs to be a lot higher because the rest of this thread is depressing the fuck out of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In truth, political polarity has been increasing since the Bush years and continued under Obama. Here's one [graph](https://static01.nyt.com/images/2012/09/17/opinion/17campstops-chart2/17campstops-chart2-blog480-v4.jpg) that shows "warmth toward other party" decreasing for awhile now. It's from Jonathan Haidt's recent keynote at APA called [What Is Happening To Our Country?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vAE-gxKs6gM), which I highly highly recommend if you're serious about understanding the divisions in this country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just rewatched it, I didn't notice any audio problems? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This also applies to dating apps like OkCupid or Tinder. Don't get caught in the "online world." Bring the relationship into meatspace and make it feel more real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 17:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly. The video isn't exactly about long distance relationships per se, but "falling in love" with people from a distance in the sense of never working up the courage to talk to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 20:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm here for. Recently moved from NY to vote down here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 06:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't wearing this shirt also protected by the First Amendment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 19:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.socialtransformation.us/social-confidence-course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 04:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No comments? This shit is bright, beautiful, minimalist, and precise as fuck.

[It is a tonal, and yet also a serial composition. It is "the first major Western composition to be based entirely on the production of vocal harmonics."](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stimmung) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 02:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greet/acknowledge anyone that comes within 10 feet of you (like passing someone on the street). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is about being published in scientific journals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who used to have a lot of approach anxiety, I've done this before: think of one opening line, then try it out as many times as I can in one night. 

I really didn't care about going anywhere else with the interaction, I just wanted to overcome my fear of people. For that purpose, it worked - though I did get some weird stares and reactions when people realized what I was doing.

We are all at different points in our path of self improvement. Sometimes you just have to power through that awkwardness to overcome a hurdle. 

For me, doing this was more about building inner game than outer game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually it's just a way to better communicate, build rapport, and gain trust. But obviously it has to be done in a safe way and you have to read the other person's body language in case they aren't welcome to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 16:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good one. I've written about this before in my article: [Find the loner in the room (then talk to them!)](http://www.socialtransformation.us/social-anxiety/talk-loner-room/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think intentions necessarily matter *too much* if you haven't made these things habits already. Just doing them for the sake of doing them can be good practice. A child can learn basic manners just to "please his/her parents," but later on they appreciate having learned those habits even if, at the time, they didn't really do them for the right reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 00:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of it has to do with context*, but despite some cultural quirks (as pointed out below), I think most of these are good habits and relatively harmless suggestions. 

*For example, my dad used to way over do the "holding doors" thing for people. He would practically run in front of someone from 15 feet away to hold the door for a completely random stranger, and it definitely came off a bit pathetic sometimes. 

But if someone is right behind me? I hold the door every time. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 23:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very likely. I always try to keep that in mind when discussing any type of mental disorder (depression, social anxiety, etc.) If not different sub-types, they can manifest themselves very differently from person to person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. There are theories that narcissism isn't based on just inflated self-worth but a very fragile sense of self-worth.

However, like you say, they often overvalue their opinions and are therefore more freely spoken in that regard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not always. But I think they can be when it comes to their opinions, which they overvalue compared to others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a [new thread without the distinction](https://www.reddit.com/r/socialskills/comments/57yui8/basic_signs_of_a_classy_or_respectable_person/) so we can move on to what the post is clearly about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 20:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't intend to group "high class" or "low class" based on economics or anything. I'm merely talking about "classiness" as a personality trait. 

[Here's a new thread without the distinction](https://www.reddit.com/r/socialskills/comments/57yui8/basic_signs_of_a_classy_or_respectable_person/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> General classiness and respectability. Just not being "low class" or rude.

A lot of these are basic etiquette, though I don't mind more advanced suggestions too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe narcissists are just more honest admitting they value physical attractiveness - which can be kind of taboo to say for more "polite" or "sensitive" people.

There's some evidence narcissists are fairly honest about what they think. For example, in one [study](https://www.psychologytoday.com/blog/socially-relevant/201601/how-profile-narcissist-one-simple-question), it was found that simply asking people "Are you a narcissist?" is a reliable way of determining if someone is a narcissist or not. 

Narcissists can be very transparent (especially about their opinions). They don't feel the need to hide themselves because they think they are the shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 19:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't really answer your question, but the TV version of Hannibal is a great interplay between an empath and a sociopath. It might be worth checking out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 03:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I thought this was a version with Bjork singing then realized what "FFO" means. 

Would've been my two favorite bands/artists collaborating.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 03:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to add:

- Irony Is a Dead Scene (w/ Mike Patton): When Good Dogs Do Bad Things, Come to Daddy (or the whole EP, it's only 4 songs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 03:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First time and last time. You're going to be pissed it took you this long to catch a gig. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 17:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mindfulness in Plain English" is a great start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 17:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I've read all of these. My recommendation would be to start with whichever sounds most interesting to you. Anything in particular you want to work on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. The fantasies will often be better than the reality. That's one thing we need to look out for as well: [magical thinking](http://www.socialtransformation.us/social-anxiety/avoid-magical-thinking-relationships/) (which often increases the more distanced we are from someone). 

I know I've personally idealized a bunch of people inside my head, who then turn out to be nothing like I thought they would be in person.

Is it healthy to choose these "fantasies" over "real relationships" though? I'm not so sure about that. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally just finished the first episode. Really great show! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 01:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this...*context*?!

Too bad most people who are outraged by this will likely never take any time to watch something like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 16:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are probably referring to "Pretty Hate Machine," which has some synth-pop elements and catchy choruses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 22:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a breakdown from the show notes (the checks are for points Trump should get with libertarians):

SHOW NOTES:

- 0:00 - Intro / Post-Debate Polls

- 3:00 - "Recovering Libertarians"

- 3:50 - Ayn Rand (and her shitlord tendencies)

- 6:40 - Libertarians that don't vote / "Voting is violence"

- 8:30 - Many libertarians think we just need more education

- 12:00 - Gary Johnson, appealing to liberals

- 13:00 -  Trump is pro-guns, pro-2nd amendment

- 13:50 - Libertarians and legalizing weed

- 16:20 - Libertarians like to pretend they are "above it all"

- 17:30 -  Trump is the closest libertarians will ever get to shaking up the establishment/special interests/lobbying

- 18:50 - Johnson is stealing more votes from Hillary than Trump

- 20:50 -  Trump wants to peel back regulatory state

- 24:30 -  Trump wants to decentralize education

- 28:00 - Libertarians and borders / National sovereignty

- 31:00 - Open borders + Democracy = Socialism

(Hispanics Favor Bigger Role for Government: www.pewresearch.org/daily-number/hifor-government/)

(Do Immigrants Import Their Economic Destiny: www.evonomics.com/do-immigrants-imy-garrett-jones/)

- 37:40 - Nations with Low IQ tend to be against rule of law, property rights, and classical liberal institutions (like free markets)

- 39:20 - Anarchocapitalist Argument for Pro-Borders?

- 43:10 - Libertarians haven't changed anything

- 44:00 - The libertarian "think tank" establishment

- 46:00 - Academic libertarianism as a job

- 48:00 - Walter Block, libertarians who endorsed Trump

- 51:00 - Peter Thiel

- 53:00 - Trump and "creative destruction"

- 56:40 -  Trump is against nation-building and "policing the world" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of my articles don't mention the course, here are some of my newest ones:

- [The Logic of Social Anxiety](http://www.socialtransformation.us/social-anxiety/logic-behind-social-anxiety/)

- [The Good Thing About Being a Sensitive Person](http://www.socialtransformation.us/social-anxiety/the-good-thing-about-being-a-sensitive-person/)

- [The Fear of Being Forgotten](http://www.socialtransformation.us/social-anxiety/the-fear-of-being-forgotten/)

- [The Truth About Social Anxiety and Introversion](http://www.socialtransformation.us/social-anxiety/the-truth-about-social-anxiety-and-introversion/)

- [How Your 'Imaginary Audience' Feeds Into Social Anxiety](http://www.socialtransformation.us/social-anxiety/imaginary-audience-feeds-social-anxiety/)

Cheers. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loving-kindness meditation*

If you want, PM me and I'll send you a link to that lesson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 18:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, just figured I'd mention that at the end since it was relevant. I have plenty of articles just like this that don't mention it at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 03:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm a great believer in all forms of energy." - Donald J. Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 17:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you be more specific? What's the strange conclusion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 15:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone has VIP access to the "pity party"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
