<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject723</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't expect Christ followers to not use the words of Christ.  Well, you can, but you'll be disappointed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can pray scripture, you can pray your heart, you can pray in expectant stillness, you can pray out loud, pray with others,, pray alone-you don't have to conform to any one practice.  The Apostle Paul prayed in tongues.  I never have.  
The guy who posted the Lords Prayer is right on too, but if you look through the rest of the NT there are a number of prayers that don't directly conform to that template, so we know not every prayer we pray has to be that one.  
God want to talk to you, he want you to talk to Him.  He wants to listen to you, and He wants you to listen to Him.  
Definitely don't pray to Mary-she can't hear your prayers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I would say is grow up.  Why would anyone expect to make people they are arguing with conform to their preferred argument style then bitch about them not agreeing to do so in a super-long rambling post?  I think the problem is with you not being realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about the epidemic of child-rape by priests and the Bishops that cover for them.  Ever seen Spotlight?  Ever heard of Cardinal Law?  Read of the only two abuse survivors on the Popes panel on Priest child-rape resigning recently because Pope Francis is granting leniency to the abusers and the Curia is blocking any real reform at every turn?
Your Church reeks of the shame inflicted on these kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first you've heard of it, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah-it's ridiculous.  My extended family (aunts and uncles) are Pentecostal, Church if God, and it hocus locus.  Learned behavior.  It is exemplified and emulated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tolerance of buggery bothers me about the RC Church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my go to as well.  I read the ESV and listen to it in my car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come to me, all who labor and are heavy laden, and I will give you rest. Take my yoke upon you, and learn from me, for I am gentle and lowly in heart, and you will find rest for your souls. For my yoke is easy, and my burden is light.
Matthew 11:28-30 ESV
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, WIKIPEDIA's article on the Fruits of the Spirit reads like a bible study.  It's great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christianity is not self-improvement.  It is self-death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Because God said it was-right here.

"You have heard that it was said, You shall not commit adultery. But I say to you that everyone who looks at a woman with lustful intent has already committed adultery with her in his heart. If your right eye causes you to sin, tear it out and throw it away. For it is better that you lose one of your members than that your whole body be thrown into hell.
Matthew 5:27-29  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a SUP-not impressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are saying he's not a liar?  You can go back into any speech, literally ANY speech, from the campaign and pull out at least a dozen downright lies.  
You need to go back and ask yourself if the truth is important on its own independent of whether it's your party that says it or not.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary certainly.  I can't recall any "alternative facts" pedaled by the other two off the top of my head.  
Are you implying Trump is NOT a liar or are you implying that I am being unfair in not pointing out all the other liars?  The article is about Trump after all, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lame </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glass floor?  What pervert designed that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever that means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to trick me into reading a book by posting a picture of a page on social media? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a liar.  His administration is a huge joke and will only get worse cause he can't shut his fat yankee mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you put up settling Trump University fraud charge with massive payout face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you put up a grabbing pussy face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, a person can't logically be two conflicting things.  That's why Allah is not Jehovah.  They have different attributes and characteristics.  One has a Son, one does not!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesus will balance perfect justice and perfect mercy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Behold my servant, whom I uphold, my chosen, in whom my soul delights; I have put my Spirit upon him; he will bring forth justice to the nations. He will not cry aloud or lift up his voice, or make it heard in the street; a bruised reed he will not break, and a faintly burning wick he will not quench; he will faithfully bring forth justice.
Isaiah 42:1-3 ESV
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a damn liar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  If it could be distilled to strong, clear principle in line with scripture I think it would be hard to justify not signing on.  Wise leadership is sometimes quiet, though, so maybe there are currents pulling that we don't hear about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd bewale should I fale to entale; by the jale and the rale in Old Irondail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting.  It may come to that.  Let's see what comes out of the convention AND the special prosecutor, I guess.

It would take someone of stature to spearhead it.  Who do you think it would be?  Moore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should take a bath then.  Other people can probably smell your penal too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the hale! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hale in Irondale!  C'mon James Spann! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a sick joke.  Power-hungry old men are going to investigate Moore for opposing Trump as a candidate?  He was a terrible candidate!  He admitted to sexually assaulting women, committing adultery, and settled a massive Trump University fraud allegation(which he'd have lost at trial).  You would be a terrible Christian leader if you DIDN'T oppose this clown!
Aren't they talking about setting up a special prosecutor just weeks into his administration to determine whether he colluded with Russia during the campaign?  Is this crazy land!?!
Makes me ashamed to be a Southern Baptist...again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  I pass that all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B-u-g-g-e-r-y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheapest Mulch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, it's essentially a waste-product that I'm just going to throw on the ground and leave there!  Who's got it cheap? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly-a-l-t-a-r.  Better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look.  You aren't really processing what I'm saying.  I included the Hosea text as quoted by Jesus in my post.  I INSIST that blood is required for the remission of sins (because the Bible says it), just not animal blood-GOD blood.
Please go back and read my previous response.  If you are just arguing for arguments sake find someone else to do it with and grow up (Eph 4:15). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a strange argument you are making.  I think what you are saying is that in the OT/OC and NT/NC repentance was always the way to forgiveness-and if that's your point then I agree.  My point is that that without the shedding of blood there is NO forgives of sin (Indeed, under the law almost everything is purified with blood, and without the shedding of blood there is no forgiveness of sins.
Hebrews 9:22 ESV) and that we can rejoice that Jesus shed His for our sins.

I have no wish to argue, and of course there were all manner of sacrifices proscribed in the OT/OC (propitiation, dedication, expiation), but I firmly disagree that "sacrifices were never necessary", as you say.  They were very necessary to tutor our stubborn hearts to the seriousness of sin, and to enlighten us as to God's plan for redemption.


And you shall offer one male goat for a sin offering, and two male lambs a year old as a sacrifice of peace offerings.
Leviticus 23:19 ESV

Go and learn what this means, I desire mercy, and not sacrifice. For I came not to call the righteous, but sinners.
Matthew 9:13 ESV

For every high priest chosen from among men is appointed to act on behalf of men in relation to God, to offer gifts and sacrifices for sins. He can deal gently with the ignorant and wayward, since he himself is beset with weakness. Because of this he is obligated to offer sacrifice for his own sins just as he does for those of the people.
Hebrews 5:1-3 ESV


And every priest stands daily at his service, offering repeatedly the same sacrifices, which can never take away sins. But when Christ had offered for all time a single sacrifice for sins, he sat down at the right hand of God,
Hebrews 10:11-12 ESV
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mangina maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there some punishment for worshiping on Saturday rather than Sunday?  No.  Would it be great if we could meet and praise and commune EVERY day?  Yes.  Is the Church above the Word?  No!  Jesus said " I am the Word"-the RC church says and does many things that are against Christ (just ask any group of alter boys).  Don't mistake them for the One True Church, regardless of their shiny outfits and gaudy churches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look in the OT and tally up all the sins that justify the death penalty-you'll be amazed!  The Old Covenant covers over sin with the blood of an animal-hence the sacrifices constantly being made at the Tabernacle, then the Temple.  There are literally millennia of rivers of blood in the OT pointing to the seriousness of sin.  
When Jesus came, all of those pictures of blood covering sin were fulfilled in the blood of God paying the debt and guilt accrued by sin.  His sacrifice actually cancelled the debt-the Lamb paid it-it wasn't covered over until the next time-He took the punishment for it!

Praise God!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Millennials </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he's dead. Gene pool filtered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rochester's finest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a retard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kids love  Masha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't make you sikh, will it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never divorce.  Trust God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a conservative you bigot.  I love how all you alt-righters whine and moan like a bunch of liberals.  
You just assume that if someone can't stand Trump they are a lefty.  You've got a very short memory.  Like 90% of the Republicans on Capital Hill can't stand Trump if you remember back when it looked like he'd lose the election.  They still can't.  Except for a select few, they are just sucking up-faking it to make it.
Trump is a terrible human being and that will ultimately be what he's remembered for.  Lack of character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They voted Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 03:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great post OP.  We know who the liar is-hint: he's orange with small hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are hoods required? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one cares. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 04:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an alt-fact, let's not call it a lie... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you're on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 01:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it ironic that he talks about "passing the torch of truth"-he wouldn't know the torch of truth if it lit his bouffant afire! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watch out for that thing under your bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fine.  I restate: most everyone who was paying attention knew that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many of you are millennials? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks..  I'm not at work, so I'll take a look! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  I'd read the these thrive on neglect, so I don't want to over-baby it.  I guess if I kill it I'll just get another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone else, then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok-I'll give you a brief sketch.  Central Americans were fleeing governments torn up by revolution.  They would get to the Southwest and seek asylum in local Churches.  They would go through legal channels to be granted asylum status, as they would likely be killed by the military or corrupt police forces back home, but be denied asylum because our government was allied with their corrupt government to limit the Cold War influence of the USSR.  So, they would be sent back and killed or "disappeared".  The Church on the border defied the government and provided safety, resources, and legal counsel.
That could never happen today, right?
Our pastor made a point about hospitality last week, not directly in regards to immigrants-"truth is added to welcome".  I think it does apply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to use a brain that's been blown out of your skull by government death squads or cartel violence... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoken like a true Trumpnut-coarse, vulgar, and thin-skinned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you think of the Sanctuary movement in the 80s in the American Southwest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone knew that already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad ( as I type in my cell phone-wait, you just posted this article on your cell phone, you hypocrite!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, please stop now.  I can't stand how everyone talks like Tarantino regardless of who they are-it's like watching a 3 hour Gilmore Girls episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't I just get kidnapped and beheaded here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone even listen to radio anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planting an American Smoketree today as a native alternative to Japanese Maple in my front yard.  What natives have you planted that you are proud of?  What exotic invasives shave been your everlasting shame? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lush! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat my edit, bot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry-should have mentioned I'm zone 7 in the USA-should have had our last cold morning today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice on tree planting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just got a little American Smoke Tree-about 18 inches tall.  It's going into my front yard in a little wild patch, kind of an understory setting but still gets good light, on a north-facing downslope.
My question is-when I plant it, what can I do to assure it roots well and is successful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Church Universal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't find any NT injunction for a"tithe", but we give.  The principle is to rely on God, so we give enough so that it hurts a little.  We do Compassion International and I have a friend who is a missionary in norther India, and we help support him and his multiple ministries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great question, OP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why don't you want immigrants here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just until the impeachment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donorcycle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Natural selection delayed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ghey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chemicals are bad... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a direct correlation.  They could eat from any number of plants.  They could only have sex with one another.  There is no indication in the narrative that the tree is a symbol for anything unless you think the entire story is symbolic-which I do not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yours isn't an information problem, but a transformation problem.  Knowing Christ personally puts these questions in perspective and allows you to trust an answer you may not fully understand, simply because it is given by someone who loves you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 21:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  If you look through his postings over the last week, his purpose is not edification or education, but to be titillating, divisive, and provocative.  If he put half the energy into ACTUALLY looking into the issues he'd have a very solid grasp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your leadership structure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to say it, but I think you are typical of your RC church and part of the entire enabling culture.  " It's not a problem anymore, it's not happening here, la la la".  To some degree you share their millstone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not.  Read the Bible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even read the article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Catholic Church's Theology of sex may be schizophrenic, I don't know because I am not Catholic.  You'd do really well  to just study your Bible and see what God says.  In case you haven't noticed the Catholic Church isn't doing too well in the sex department. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex is meant to be enjoyed within the confines of monogamous marriage.  It is important and powerful.  From your posts, though, you appear to be fixated on it to an unhealthy degree.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you are seeing cases from 20 years ago it is because it has taken those abused that long to come out and talk about it.  It is CERTAINLY still a huge issue, especially in the Catholic Church where predators gravitate, are protected, and serially repeat.  We will see the numbers from this decade in 20 years.  
I take it you are Catholic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm a real conservative.  We don't protest and can't stand liars like Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile, there's a lot of kids being raped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Gifts are meant for the edification of the body-so of course we should humbly submit to teaching and instruction.  The Spirit also grants a Gift called "discerning of spirits"-which trumps a PhD.  I resist the term "experts"- it implies that someone has reached an end, has grasped and mastered a subject.  The Bible will not be fully grasped our mastered by anyone in their natural lifespan.  It grasps and masters you!

Teaching within the Church is more of a Shepherding experience-it is best accomplished in intimate relationships over time.  It is not a didactic experience, it is not  a TED talk, or a podcast.  It is walking together and disciplining.

Jesus's point is that the Kingdom is granted to the non-experts (the experts were the ones calling him a demon-possessed bastard and trying to kill him), the simple, the unlikely, the children.  We should be encouraging MORE Bible reading-more questions-more individual study, and more small group study of the Bible for everyone.  Not discouraging it by implying people are ignorant.  We want them to dive in and be grasped and mastered by the Word, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Pope really wanted something to change, I am certain the Pope could make it change.  His secret clemency to collared predators the other week seems to indicate he doesn't take it very seriously in my view.  As a leader, you delegate what is less of a priority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible teaches that understanding is granted by the Holy Spirit.  You do not need an advanced degree to understand the Bible at all!
At that time Jesus declared, I thank you, Father, Lord of heaven and earth, that you have hidden these things from the wise and understanding and revealed them to little children;
Matthew 11:25 ESV
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he didn't want them to have sex he wouldn't have made them with a penis and vagina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
