<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1145</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! A bit under-confident! Here's the video:  

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FIYNyYidNWU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck this racist piece of shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you watch one of his workout videos with his trainer you can see the non-performer in him when he's talking to Joe DeFranco. He's very unsure of himself and needs every stroke of his ego he can get.  

EDIT: Changed Bill Demott to Joe DeFranco </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 22:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once showed Jim Cornette a video of me in a rest hold for forty minutes. He told me it was the best wrestling match he'd ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/MVPdV4a.gifv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so weird to be one of the youngest cultures in existence; I'm referring to American People of Color. To have such an obscured history is a blessing and a wrong. I've been lucky enough to be able to trace my ancestry; but what if you can't?  How do you identify who you are? In America, people of color have only been considered equal to white people for less than 60 years!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could too! Then I'd be a successful author; not just an author lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where the main characters are minorities but that's not their only identifier.  

THIS! This so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WM x-Seven: I lost faith in WWE. That day I learned that even WWE is making huge mistakes on the biggest stage of them all. My friend kept saying that the big thing was that Stone Cold went heel. I just kept asking "Why?"  

That Zayn/Nakamura match. I show people the entrance for both and they just want to watch the match...and then it's a great match! It's also the match where my SO figured out her favorite move is when a wrestler rolls out of the ring and onto the floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are great! Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smackdown was never the B show during any brand split lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good! I'd rather be Zitz or Pimple! And I better get the leg/pipe!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should wrestle again; though not the same way he did to injure himself. Why he headbutted Dolph off a ladder is only known between Daniel and the career he could have had. I'm almost certain the trainer was told not to pass him under any circumstances (See WWE politics).  

SCSA was able to wrestle a modified style. Daniel has developed his speaking skills so well as of late he'll be gold on the mic anywhere. Sometimes all you need is a good promo and a partner who can sell for you and you can create great matches! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Failed on three fronts:  

Lying in the title.  

It's not Kevin Owens.  

Missed a Sami Zayn joke.  

"Sami Zayn cheers on KO as he takes on Kofi in Kombat! w/Bayley" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you don't get any cake!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LEdAkWOXcVM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed! I usually write my comic book characters as mixed (like me) or some type of non-white background. Though the artist's interpretation is based in drawing white-ish characters lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This doesn't look like the usual body hair and cheese nuggets I'm used to." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm terrible for laughing so hard at this. But I'm mostly laughing because all this shit moving around could have been prevented with bolts and shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get an ice cream cake! It has ice cream on the inside! Ice Cream ON THE INSIDE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost it at the volcano xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 20:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not paying 15 dollars for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I occasionally have dreams with creatures like these. I've been diagnosed with PTSD after the war; but then again I've seen images like these...maybe it's PTSD from seeing these images lol!...LOL...or maybe I'm just fucked up!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The huge impact that having characters that kids (shit just people) can relate to is one of the most overlooked aspects of the grade-school literary world. If there had been more black or mixed characters in books for me when I was in grade school then I'd have read A LOT more!!! Fuck Sara Jane Plain and Tall! As a mixed male, how could I have related to something so far away from who I am? 

I'm glad that this program exists! More need to happen soon! And we need to provide educated black characters for children!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TAP ALL WATER!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GET ALL THE COOKIES!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it bother anyone that Austin didn't tell Blaze that every time you use the A button it decreases health? Am I the only one this bothered greatly? Where's Matt aka Cygnus the Destroyer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBB's Alex said it got him into wrestling. I really wish Woods would be pushed for a singles title. It's too late now; but it would have been awesome for him to have gotten "injured" then come back, be pushed for a singles title just in time for Power Rangers to hit the big screen, a movie in which he plays the Red Ranger!!! Fuck man slip me into that reality for a few seconds and I'll forgive all of Stephanie's overuse of the A Button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah! I meant to say: This is why ECW, WWE and WCW were on fire in the late 90s; if you get mad at one promotion then you go to the next one (another national outlet) and air your grievances. Today's wrestling world is like: if you get mad with WWE then you go somewhere into mark obscurity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've also figured out John Cena's career as Nia Jax's abusive father was what got him into wrestling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vince McMahon the Promo Man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with Seth chasing for a little while until he gets hurt  

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the deal with my pants? They're on the fucking floor; just lying there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 21:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my WCW ECW, and WWE were on fire. You get disgruntled, go to another national outlet and air your grievances. Now it's just like, you get mad at WWE...just go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast is not important. What you eat is important. Exercise, a healthy diet and scheduling are more important than breakfast. According to the documentary "How to Live Forever" the people that live the longest are Okinawans; they live so long because they do just about the same thing every day. So routine is the most important part of the day.  

There are diets where you only eat for a certain number of hours per day (say 3pm-11pm); the people that chose these diets can be pretty healthy. They work out before their appointed time to eat, so technically they're eating lunch or dinner and never even eat breakfast! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HSP stands for Highly Sensitive Person  

http://hsperson.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I set my internal alarm clock. Wake up about a half hour to fifteen minutes before I told myself I would (already ahead of schedule!). Drink water, work (write, read, etc); exercise (yoga or cardio); make a movement breakfast (oats and coffee, or something that gets things moving); meditate; pop a squat; take a shower; get dressed; brush teeth; leave my flat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BiPoar Type 2 and HSP among other things. Self harm for me only comes after a big change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For taste I like to blend up cashews, water and some cacao (like 75%). Tastes good man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this as well as the non-orange 205 Live Cruiserweight Championship belt. Perhaps this version could be used like a smoking Skull type championship, specific to a certain superstar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 00:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick- Chocolate Powder Flavor  

Ovaltine- Not Quite Quick Flavor  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a scale of 1-10 I'd give that an 8 thumbs up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bret doesn't get the concussion. Goldberg never lost.  

Bret loses against Goldberg at Starrcade. The next Nitro, Bret gets his rematch. The match is going as planned; then a masked man costs Hart the match. The same thing happens the next week, but Hart gets his hands on the masked man, takes off his hood and it's Owen!  

Bret and Owen have a fight the next week on Nitro. Bischoff says that the winner of the match gets to fight Goldberg at the next PPV. Owen uses all sorts of hilarious heel antics and some great wrestling holds, but his brother gets him in the sharpshooter...but Goldberg hops the rail and DQs Bret. The three men stand in the ring. Bischoff comes out and states that it will be a three way dance at the next PPV.  

At the PPV Owen and Bret put on a clinic; keeping Goldberg outside the ring. Bret bears Owen for the title. Goldberg was never pinned. In an odd turn, Owen lifts Bret's hand and celebrates. "I knew I'd help you get that title!" says Owen, "Now the Hart family is the greatest family in wrestling." Stu Hart celebrates with his boys. Goldberg spears Stu.Bret and Owen fight off Goldberg as the program comes to a close.  

Owen and Bret team up and recruit past members of the dungeon to become Hart Inc. With Bret as champ, Owen as US Champ and Benoit and Malenko as Tag Champs. Hart Inc. celebrates their success on an episode of Nitro. Owen can't bare to see his brother lead Hart Inc. anymore, he hates him as champion. Owen delivers the sit out piledriver to Bret, injuring Bret's neck. "I'll put my title against yours!"  

Next PPV is Owen's US Title against Bret's WCW Title in a no DQ. The match is popping the crowd when the NWO (Hogan, Nash and Hall) make a run in. Owen wins the big one with the help of the NWO. But the next night on Nitro he says he's not part of the NWO, he didn't need their help. Owen Hart is in it for Owen Hart and no one else. With Hart Inc and the NWO gunning for him, Owen only has one ally...Sting! Sting and Owen Hart fight off both factions on a weekly basis until it's Hogan vs. Bret vs. Owen vs. Goldberg in a four way dance.  

The title goes back to Goldberg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! This was the only water we hiked to and didn't go in while in Hana. The red sand beach was a hike along a narrow ledge making this hike easier...at first lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to scale a cliff down; cliff jump in; then use a rope to get yourself out. The other side is just a small shore leading to the ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were some guys down there. But it's in Maui so that's the only shore near this body of water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to climb the cliff with a rope to get out of the area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do the Jillian Michaels 30 Day Shred for a warm-up and Triple H's Guide to Building a Better Body workout in the free weights area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am bipolar 2 HSP. All the things that come with driving normally stimulate me. Combine that with the fact that if I had a car I might be driving during a hypomanic episode and I've been walking for over 30 years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk. In my experience churches are just full of pedophiles and fake people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's up for starting a Crowd Funded wrestling show??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait until Nakamura comes to the main roster...it's going to be a shit storm. Proof: Every Japanese star they've ever had on the main roster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I don't know. I didn't go down in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the right there's a place where you can sun bathe on a cliff. You scale down a harrowing cliff face. Then you can jump down into the Venus Pool. Your only way out is a rope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shore is only connected to steep rock faces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this game lol! It was and is still shit! Kind of fun back then but still shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From his first promo with Haas; I was absolutely sure Shelton Benjamin was going to be WWE Champion some time down the road....and now here we are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather not watch a Roidback match. I think I'll do something else while this match is going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How About a Video Game where... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd do a series of posters for this Wrestlemania:  

The first series being classic Once in a Lifetime 2 types of face offs.

Goldberg vs Brock  

Bayley vs Charolette  

Alexa holding the title high with her opponents in boxes at the bottom and WM logo under them.  

Bray Wyatt vs AJ Styles and Randy Orton  

Then make it collectible by folding them or something and have Taker vs. Braun as some Mad Magazine like image.  

But I'm just an out of work Graphic Designer so that should tell you something xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raw's women's division probably sells more merch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the wrestler story arch I believe it's important for the Champion or future champion to be able to be believable.  

Business wise, 50/50 booking makes sense. You have stock in both wrestlers, let one lose until the title is on the line. Neither wrestler will lose merch sales in the long run; thus bringing in more money for the company and wrestler.  

Story wise I hate 50/50 booking. If you have a champion they should look strong. Braun should be facing Reigns for a title since both of them have been made to look strong as hell. Kevin Owens should have lost to Goldberg, not because of Jerichonanegans but because KO didn't train hard enough (accented by his entrance where he's double fisting cheeseburgers); then Jericho should have showed up to laugh at him.  

There will always be vernacular that develops in any sports discussion thread. We call them memes now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if that Glen Jacobs gimmick will work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have extremely perky breasts and nice curves! Enjoy not having to wear a bra lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 22:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great body! Nothing to worry about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful and Inviting...until you realize you have to pull yourself out with a rope. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Follow the clues,  
Hear the voice of the dragon,  
Watch her eat chocolate,  
Find the strange penguin wizard,  
Who's in love with his cousin,  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want someone to come to the ring with fire raining down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lights go out. Undertaker is in the ring; Braun step up to him. Undertaker backs up. Lights go out. Undertaker is on the ramp and in the ring. Ring Taker slams Strowmen. Ramp Taker reveals himself to be Kane! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! I was like, "Oh shit! Braun's not afraid to step up to Undertaker! What!? Now Taker's backing up!? Is he playing mind games!? Wait...oh." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Owens vs Jericho would have been one of the greatest Universal Title matches ever! Now we get to see and old man vs Bane Lesnar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/thalassaphobia    ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decent match mate. Pulling the ol' Edge   Christian hide and recover until the end, eh? I know you know about the slight botch on the corner springboard (elbow?, that dam ref is in the way!).   

I like your crispiness (you come off as the veteran). Your moves look good and you're not afraid to set up for moves, which is what the vets do. I like the calling of the Cupid's Arrow.  

I'd also like a motion to go with the Arrow call; like Jake and his swirl before the ddt, or Reigns and his fist cocking before the punch. There's a definite lack of psychology to the match: the comedian guy was so lame it was fun, but when lads went to the outside they didn't seem to take a big enough bump. I don't say this often (this actually might be the first) but I'd like to see some rest holds (even Neville uses rest holds) if pro wrestling is like a roller coaster then rest holds are the line you have to wait in to get to the ride, without a line you can ride the coaster again and again but it loses value in its enjoyment.  

Good match for the location. Hope you do well in the tournament! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay to love someone that's not conventionally good looking...as long as they're conventionally good looking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice body! I'm a sucker for great curves and you've got great curves! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moral support? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope; just a non-themed table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is almost exactly what happened with Michael Jackson. When an underage person(s) is alone with someone unsupervised then it's always a bit suspicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kenny Omega makes me smile and makes me happy that pro wrestling exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Stephanie is married to a chickenshit heel. So I guess that answers that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 01:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't this Mikey Whipwreck's job with his time in ECW?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope Roman Reigns beats the shit out of everyone! He has the Superman power in his arms because of the ancient Samoan art of getting a tattoo! He loves caulking his fist and people watching him caulk it in public! Caulk caulk caulk! Roman Reigns is the ultimate fist caulker!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought of this when Jericho came out. "Why would he help Goldberg?" We all know Jericho can beat up Goldberg though; so it would be fitting that he wants the Universal title on a lesser opponent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads up! Maybe I'll try the fatal four way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an air hockey and table games enthusiast! This looks like a lot of fun! One of my favorite air hockey tables was in Vegas in the Camelot arcade; it started out as a regular air hockey game then a few minutes in all these small pucks fell out! Haven't played quad hockey yet, but this and some sort of table with sloped sides might prove to add another dimension to the game!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/truedownblouse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's slang. It means to run out of energy; but the origin of the slang comes from the idea of running out of gas for your vehicle. So "I'm out of gas!" while driving means exactly that; "I'm out of gas!" while exercising means you've ran out of energy. Out of gas= Gassed out. Gas can also be replaced by "juice". "I'm out of juice!" can mean you're out of energy as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you gas out, just switch over to back stroke for a little while to catch your breath and enjoy the sky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 43g of protein in each strip! 39g of protein in the black beans! Farmer's Market lemon sage pasta! For this week's groceries for two people it came out to less than $100 USD. With salad, snacks, 11 meals a person and a couple nut beverages it averages out to around $5 USD per meal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High protein meal prep with homemade no lard tortillas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] Kumquats, Strawberries, brussels sprouts and more from the Farmer's Market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walked a 5k dressed as Batman! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] Farmer's Market Food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farmer's Market Haul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tied to make a baby in a Dutch oven. It doesn't work and shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holding shift and using the arrow keys is fun, left and right highlight indiechat characters while up and down highlight whole lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 15:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A band comes up with the name Hey Please Stay after an epic battle against talking house cats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 14:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which sucks because his style doesn't injure people like Rollins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And I ru-uuun; I run so far away-ay-ay-ayayay" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn! I always look forward to Big Show's crossover matches! Always entertaining! Also, did you know Sumo Wrestling is a work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D-Lo Brown is going to be at SoCal Pro Wrestling! Maybe Swagger can swagger to San Diego and fight him. Come to think of it, Paul London was at SoCalPro last time I was there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clementine in the Telltale Walking Dead games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't make any sense storyline wise; but I really hope Styles wins it! He's more main event material than Orton. Orton had his chance and put on a piss match with Triple Nipple H. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why Uber is winning. The snacks and water are free if you go with UberX; which is a little more than a cab's rate. I used X when I didn't know how to use Uber. People thought I pulled up in a limo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta say that I saw Ambrose wrestle IRL a few weeks ago. He was soft, didn't seem to hurt anyone. He wasn't as over as The Miz (at this moment in time) but he was over enough. Ambrose is going to be big, but he's doing one of the hardest things to do in the spotlight: step back. Right now he needs to be the workhorse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is common in the San Diego neighborhood of North Park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lemon Grove, right down the street from Little Darlings "the best strip club under the freeway with a lunch buffet" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 06:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky! I took a two hour Uber ride to hook up with a big tittied pre op mtf; only to be greeted by a dude in a bad wig and a dress and a gal hiding in the closet. My penis wasn't happy with me. That was the first day I tried White Castle from the restaurant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
