<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cummings: 'A Lot Of People Assume That All Black People Know All Black People' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Christie: Trump Made Me Order Meatloaf At The White House (AUDIO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $10 million a month adds up to a lot of money, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you like some cheese with your whine?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the water fasts, a person is using their hormones at peak.  They are able to function well and the body is able to do its thing.  If a person is consuming some calories, the body will adapt to this and it will not be in total fat burning mode.  For myself, I found the water fasts to be easier because my body stopped craving food.  Juice has sugar in it and will spike insulin.  One of the things insulin does is block fat cells for releasing energy for 4 hours or so after consuming juice.  If a person ate something like fat with a little protein perhaps bone broth,  there would be no insulin spike.  Many people use bone broth on a fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Classified Memo Tells Intelligence Analysts to Keep Trump's Daily Brief Short - "Keep it short and free of nuancethat is the new guidance that has recently circulated to some intelligence analysts who compile materials for the President's Daily Brief on security threats around the globe." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to eat 6 small meals a day to keep the metabolism up to lose weight.  /s  Humans are able to store excess calories as fat more easily than other apes.  We are able to go 30 days without food and have no problems.  If the body fat gets to less than 4% then bad things start to happen.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 13:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The appendix is on the right side.  Usually, the first signs of problem is a pain in the middle right side then in moves lower.  You might want to see a doctor right away.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump says he only hires the best. Working with Trump is a shit sandwich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Jewish Reporter Got to Ask Trump a Question. It Didnt Go Well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pres Barack Obama never whined. He was respectful, generous, and had a sense of humor. Barack Obama was presidential. Donald Trump has the maturity of a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard on twitter last night that the snowflakes were attacking Shep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pres Barack Obama never whined.  He was respectful, generous, and had a sense of humor. Barack Obama was presidential.  Donald Trump has the maturity of a child.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Susan Rice Calls Donald Trumps Black Caucus Remarks Offensive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 11:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump says he only hires the best.  Working with Trump is a shit sandwich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, Donnie says he is a good guy and it is the media's fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, Donnie says he is a good guy and it is the media's fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flynn in FBI interview denied discussing sanctions with Russian ambassador </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is really hard to believe this guy is President.  What is crazy too is that Trump has been railing against Barack Obama for 8 years, and Trump isn't even near the same league as Obama.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of the people at the top in WH know how to get anything done in Washington.  Perhaps this is a good thing. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump wants a wall. Border experts want a fence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump gets his trademark in China. But he wont be reaping the benefits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Trump Can't Come Clean on Russia - "The saying "it's not the crime, it's the cover-up" may not apply here." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people like to live a shitty life.  They don't complain about things like small airline seats, and having to pay extra for bags.  Food at many restaurants is low quality, but it tastes good and is cheap.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did the two have ties? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donnie needs his bonus for the year.  Lets get this deal done!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did they have ties? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets all go to the pee party at the WH!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for one like clean money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is a good fellow. He is said to occasionally wave as he  passes by in his chauffeur driven limousine. "The common man is revolting" is his favorite saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 13:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is in the same vein as Krampus, who punishes children who have misbehaved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is really cold to rob Rosa Park.  WTF!  That is more cold than an assassin wearing a shirt with letters "LOL". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets all go to the pee party @ WH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tonight he will be having a pee party @ WH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They like the pee parties in Moscow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the wall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shortest term for a president is hard to beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assassin wearing shirt with text: "LOL". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump: "Grab them by the balls!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pod Save America - Awesome new podcast for Democrats. The hosts used to work for Barack Obama during his first term. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Insulting journalists and the intelligence community is full of win." - Richard Nixon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Predictably, the use of anonymous sources opened the door for Trump to call the reports "nonsense" and "fake news," though he might have inadvertently lent credence to the stories by tweeting that "information is being illegally given ... by the intelligence community."" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two explosive reports on Trump and Russia. Zero on-the-record sources. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 16:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Insulting journalists and the intelligence community is full of win." - Richard Nixon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Insulting journalists and the intelligence community is full of win." - Richard Nixon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets all go to celebrate at the pee party in Moscow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His true colors.  His people were contacting the Russians on his behalf.  Are this people going to take the fall for him?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Insulting journalists and the intelligence community is full of win." - Richard Nixon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump promised that he would hire the best people...LOL! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 14:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unleash the crazy.  It has not even been a month.  WTF!

[So Full of Win](https://i.imgur.com/ct7OWUl.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watergate was the biggest scandal in my life, but this appears to be even bigger.  I just hope that the USA is still a democracy after the liar leaves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The American Anarchists vs. the Islamic State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, Hillary's emails!  /s
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a reason why they are your "ex". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're making America great again...perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was Ben Ghazi sending emails to Hillary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CCTV of 'female assassin' wanted over Kim Jong-Un half-brother's murder - "Malaysian Police on Wednesday revealed a woman had been arrested in connection with the murder at the capital's international airport." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like #3 behind China, and Russia.  India is closing fast.  The British empire died many years ago.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Soviet Bear loves everyone on Valentine's Day](https://i.imgur.com/qbMBkXL.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Trump liked leaks.  Lets all go to the pee party in Moscow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald promised he would hire the best.  I for one am not impressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Flynn died in the Bowling Green Massacre.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Donald Rumsfeld available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin is messing with Trump's head.  Between Putin and Xi Jinping, Trump isn't going to out brain them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump said he would hire the best people. Instead we got the Trump administration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Cruise Missile, Deployed Secretly, Violates Treaty, Officials Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump doesn't pay attention to details.  Details bore him.  All he cares about is image and optics.  Facts don't matter.  Taking the time to figure out if something is really true in reality doesn't matter.  Good belly feel works for him.  He is not a critical thinker.  Just listen to him make a speech.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In research done by Satchin, he found that if you eat in a shorter window of 8-10 hours, a person will lose weight.  He did research first on mice then people.  It is interesting how he worked with people using a phone app.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-R-eqJDQ2nU
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI is busy investigating Hillary's pedophile ring at Comet Ping Pong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pelosi Calls On FBI To 'Accelerate' Probe Into Connections Between WH, Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico ready to retaliate by hurting American corn farmers - "And Mexican senator Armando Rios Piter, who leads a congressional committee on foreign relations, says he will introduce a bill this week where Mexico will buy corn from Brazil and Argentina instead of the United States." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Angry Town Hall Meetings on Health Care Law, and Few Answers - Dont talk about repealing something until you have valid ideas on the table for replacing it, she said. I mean, its causing me to literally lose sleep at night. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is from 2015. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The strange tale of how a false 2009 Obamacare claim ended up in a viral 2017 video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It often happens to people in power that they overplay their hand.  I just hope the USA is still a democracy after the liar leaves.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't do the time, don't do the crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets all go to the pee party in Moscow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When are they going to investigate Hillary Clinton's pedophile ring at Comet Ping Pong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad girl.  Very, very bad girl! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the WH is now a freak show.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pakistan bans Valentine's Day for being unIslamic - "It has prohibited all public celebrations and any media coverage because the celebration is not part of Muslim traditions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 13:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engineers have known for decades that Orovilles backup spillway was unreliable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Mysterious James Comey - "The FBI must have known that Michael Flynn illegally discussed sanctions with the Russian ambassador." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like conflict of interest goes both ways.  Funny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a rally in December 2015, Trump claimed Obama "played more golf last year than Tiger Woods." "We don't have time for this," Trump said. "We have to work."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butter and cheese made veggies taste good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Science is not a belief system like religion.  The scientific process is neutral.  It is objective and is looking to discover new information.  People make a hypothesis then test it.  Over time, more details and accuracy are made.  In the end, facts are true whether a person believes them or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck in 2018! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgian priest charged with conspiracy to murder senior clergyman - "Deacon Giorgi Mamaladze, found in possession of cyanide and firearms, is suspected to have been planning an attack on the head of the Georgian Orthodox Church, Ilia II" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is sure to make the top 10 list of worst presidents ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't do the time, don't do the crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why this is an issue because Trump doesn't read the briefings and does his own thing. "My IQ is one of the highest  and you all know it! Please don't feel so stupid or insecure; it's not your fault." - Donald J. Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Note: Flynn on thin ice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TN Republicans Introduce Bills Suggesting Kids Born From Artificial Insemination Are Illegitimate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TN Republicans Introduce Bills Suggesting Kids Born From Artificial Insemination Are Illegitimate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 15:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find white people to be scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pappy said, "Son, you're gonna' drive me to drinkin'
If you don't stop drivin' that Hot Rod Lincoln." - Commander Cody </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barack Obama is a Muslim Kenyan.  [Checkmate!](https://i.imgur.com/EzkvbYf.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget that Barack Obama is Kenyan Muslim for "Judgment day".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's job approval rating hits a new low - Trump's historically low approval rating continues to drop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's job approval rating hits a new low </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 13:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Heartbreak, A Happy Ending: 200 Whales Escape Stranding In New Zealand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 19:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela now leads US asylum requests as crisis deepens - "Venezuelans for the first time led asylum requests to the United States as the country's middle class fled the crashing, oil-dependent economy." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Standing Rock Sioux Ask Court to Halt Dakota Access Pipeline Construction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican green-card holder who voted illegally in Texas gets 8 years in prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't do the time, don't do the crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK offshore wind will lower energy bills more than nuclear - "RenewableUK chief says windfarms could offer cheaper prices than the rates government has agreed with new nuclear power stations" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "...endless forms most beautiful and most wonderful have been, and are being, evolved." - Charles Darwin - On this day, Charles Darwin was born in 1809 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In USA, thanks to fracking, coal power plants are almost a thing of the past.  Most have changed to natural gas.  It takes 2 train loads of coal to power 1 boiler for a week.  That is a lot of coal.  A power plant near Atlanta uses 10 train loads of coal a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently conflicts of interest work both ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waiting for Republicans to complain that capitalism is so unfair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chaffetz Said He Believes Town Hall Protestors Were Paid, Not From Utah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public Policy Polling: 51 percent of Trump voters say Bowling Green massacre justifies travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem: $20 billion dollar border wall
Solution: $50 ladder
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do Christians know what parts of the bible to follow, and which ones to ignore?  God commands people to not work on the Sabbath.  If anyone does, they should be put to death.  Christians ignore this command.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the "Art of the Deal". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Republicans were all about law and order.  Oh, well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 14:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our president is a paper tiger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bear patrol is doing a good job.  You don't see any bears do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump: "You're eyes are lying to you!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Republicans were all about free markets and the invisible hand. Oh, well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 15:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their Chili Cheese Fries Rock! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Coretta Scott King and JFK joined forces  and helped change the Democratic Party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Reportedly Wants Softer Towels on Air Force One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 12:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald said in his tweet that Ivanka is entitled because she is nice.  What?  I think Nordstrom's wants to make money, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 19:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ref was not fooled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump thinks his daughter is entitled because she is nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its pretty rare for the President to use the power of the presidency to go after a company. And to do so on behalf of his family's business interests is certainly something weve never seen before, Jordan Libowitz told the Daily News. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stockholm syndrome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Republicans were all about free markets and the invisible hand.  Oh, well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Obamacare more than the Republican "I Don't Care".
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, not all Muslims are bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stockholm syndrome? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleveland Clinic Doctor Deported Under Trump Order Comes Back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes 2 train loads of coal (80-90 cars) to keep 1 boiler running a week at a power plant.  That is a lot of coal.  With fracking, natural gas can meet the demand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was also the 1996 Olympic bombing, but that was caused by a white Christian terrorist so it doesn't really count.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Centennial_Olympic_Park_bombing
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ministry of Truth?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. military's stats on deadly airstrikes are wrong. Thousands have gone unreported </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 16:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My daughters death will not be used: Parents furious over Trumps false terrorism claims - Much nonsense is being spoken in the press about her alleged killer, Ayliffe wrote. He is not an Islamic fundamentalist, he has never set foot in a mosque. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 53% of Republicans dont know repealing Obamacare repeals the Medicaid expansion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 14:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, GOP says Milo Yiannopoulos should be allowed to speak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yemen Withdraws Permission for U.S. Antiterror Ground Missions - "Angry at the civilian casualties incurred last month in the first commando raid authorized by President Trump, Yemen has withdrawn permission for the United States to run Special Operations ground missions" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yemen Withdraws Permission for U.S. Antiterror Ground Missions - "Angry at the civilian casualties incurred last month in the first commando raid authorized by President Trump, Yemen has withdrawn permission for the United States to run Special Operations ground missions" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 12:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Bannon portrayed wearing Nazi armband in Chinese state media cartoon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Bannon portrayed wearing Nazi armband in Chinese state media cartoon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fueled by Bribes, Somalias Election Seen as Milestone of Corruption - "Politicians have been peeling off wads of hundred dollar bills to buy votes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fueled by Bribes, Somalias Election Seen as Milestone of Corruption - "Politicians have been peeling off wads of hundred dollar bills to buy votes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Christian school said it helped troubled kids. It covered up sex abuse instead, lawsuit says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps energy plan doesnt mention solar, an industry that just added 51,000 jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria's Secret Mass Executions - "An investigation from Amnesty International details Assad's attempt to create a phony paper trail to cover up mass executions in Syria." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Is Germany tired of Merkel?' asks mass-selling newspaper Bild </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the President doesn't pay taxes, why do other people have too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic senator: We may flip another GOP vote on DeVos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The authorities are renewing the city on behalf of the developers, not the people, said one of the explorers, who goes by the alias Ghost in videos and whose pollution mask and fingerless gloves gave him the air of a bank robber or graffiti artist." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using Stealth, and Drones, to Document a Fading Hong Kong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 12:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minnesota, Washington File Papers Fighting Trump's Travel Restriction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capital punishment for stealing diapers.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is a good fellow. He is said to occasionally wave as he  passes by in his chauffeur driven limousine. "The common man is revolting" is his favorite saying.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 18:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting.  One would think it would be hard to generate solar power with all the smog and stuff.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Snowflake Award Winner](https://i.imgur.com/HXzA02X.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 17:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Snowflake Award Winner](https://i.imgur.com/HXzA02X.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 16:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in all fairness, Trump's positions are very hard for a intelligent person to defend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony Perkins: The Johnson Amendment Must Be Repealed Because the Church Predates Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would quit and find a new job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you are living by yourself, you can do as you wish.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Building walls will not keep people safe.  What good did the Great Wall of China do?  Genghis Khan still invaded.  Same thing happened to Kings in their castles.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion promotes tribalism and doesn't make a person love your neighbor.  A person just becomes a member of that tribe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an idiot.  My eyes are not lying to me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 15:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is exactly what Trump stated: USA = Putin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romania Reverses Decision to Weaken Corruption Law - After "spirited mass protests, and predictions that a half-million or more people might take to the streets on Sunday, Romanias month-old government backed down Saturday and withdrew a decree that had decriminalized some corruption offenses." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 15:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super Bowl: Trump protesters and Lady Gaga prepare for Houston spectacle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Moore trolls Trump over tweet attacking judge - "Thank you, So-Called President Trump! I've been struggling for 2 weeks over what to call you, and your tweet here gave us the answer," Moore tweeted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, USA = Putin. Really??  I thought the USA is morally superior to any country on Earth.  What happened to American Exceptionalism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. military's stats on deadly airstrikes are wrong. Thousands have gone unreported </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kuwait denies it imposed travel ban praised by Trump - "Kuwait has denied a media report which said it had imposed a travel ban on citizens from several Muslim-majority countries, a story which U.S. President Donald Trump praised on Facebook." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 14:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who wins from Trump immigration policy? Robotic berry pickers, for a start </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny, the NYT is one of the few newspapers that still has investigative reporters.  In Trump's world, if you look at facts and evidence, you are lost.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The judge is a Bush appointee.  Apparently, Trump wants him to break the law and not follow the Constitution.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump slams so-called judge who blocked travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The math doesn't make sense.  The rooms would have been very expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a person does the math, it doesn't make sense.  What were the rooms, $5000 a night? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 15:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is a good fellow. He is said to occasionally wave as he  passes by in his chauffeur driven limousine. "The common man is revolting" is his favorite saying.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government reveals more than 100,000 visas revoked due to travel ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 19:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Military Convoy Sporting 'Trump' Flag Was Naval Special Warfare Unit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 18:46:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Live in fear, Sheeple!  Trump likes to have everyone living in fear. Fear Obama! Fear the Terrorist! Fear the Socialist! Fear the Chinese! The Chinese are out to get you, and so are the Socialist. Don't forget about the Iranians, Al-qaeda, or ISIS. You must live in fear. Arrggghhhhh! It is crazy. Amazing how scared the Republicans are, and how easily they think the rest of us scare. Some of us don't live in fear all the time.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is hard to believe god exists when certain people are not struck by lightning.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Terrorist Chart](https://i.imgur.com/K6dJPO4.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 14:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Al-qaeda in Yemen is not as strong as it once was.  The Houthi are legit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the USA, people who shot up shopping malls, offices, schools, or blow up Federal Buildings are homegrown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Frederick Douglass die in the Bowling Green Massacre? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nordstrom drops Ivanka Trump-branded clothing and shoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facts are true whether you believe them or not.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nordstrom drops Ivanka Trump-branded clothing and shoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 12:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update: public rejects bill that would have sold off 3 million acres of public lands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible says I can have slaves. When do I get my slaves? These federal laws preventing me from having slaves is a burden on my religious freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I can be the most presidential person ever, other than the great Abe Lincoln" - Donald J. Trump
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shocked Trump would approve of something without thinking things through.  Shocked! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is Trump the President or a fascist dictator? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 13:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible says I can have slaves. When do I get my slaves? These federal laws preventing me from having slaves is a burden on my religious freedom.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
