<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7026</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I got a word every time this story gets posted I'd have a short story by now...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No math either! And no bedtimes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steinbeck is one of my favorites, but I think you are right. That book is probably just not all that appealing to high school students. Start them on tortilla flat or cannery row. Both are fun reads that are full of wisdom and humanity and drunken shenanigans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I am becoming obsessed with them again though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 14:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would probably just keep the folios and bulk donate the rest, though it would be tempting to get a nice payoff from them. If you decide to sell all the folios together pm me what your asking price is!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 01:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like reading about the most disturbing internet videos you should read this.

http://creepypasta.wikia.com/wiki/Normal_Porn_for_Normal_People </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 200 folio society editions? Holy shit, that's some serious money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's philosophically in fashion now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man, it was a close call. I have a legit headache now from thinking so hard about it for those five minutes, lol. My brain almost convinced me it would be fine... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stopped smoking eight days ago. Found a single cigarette in my car during lunch break. Didn't smoke it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 21:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I held this cigarette in my hand and stared at it for a good five minutes as if it would start taking to me or something. I wanted to smoke it so bad. Then I destroyed it. I'm proud I didn't smoke it and know I would have felt guilty after but man it would have been nice to have one last one. But I guess it's never really the last one if you give in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I think so at least. They've edited some great anthologies and pick really unique stories. They are most well known in the weird fiction community. Jeff's book annihilation was really awesome if you are in the mood for a weird kind of biological roadside picnic-esque scifi/horror novel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure, over a thousand pages, 105 stories, picked by the Vandermeers, 15 bucks on Amazon right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have the Vandermeer's Big Book of Science Fiction? What's your favorite story in it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This book is huge! If you have it, what's are some of your favorites from it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 06:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread has nothing to do with a book recommendation request.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Ulysses get any easier after episode 3 (Proteus)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 15:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget an extension cord. Unless your coffee table has a power outlet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 17:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find out anything? I'll call them when I get out of work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 00:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you have a lot of time on your hands. Being sent to prison would help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 00:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little libraries of extremely offensive pieces of work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 13:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've loved their music for ages but don't know the name of their best album?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
