<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone translate the title? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's that dude on the top left????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People always forget rin kujou she should get some attention as well.


TEAM HAREM MOTHAFUCKERS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hide the amazon ad, it that doesn't help hide the other ads, it fixed for me :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUDE i think i found a fix, hide the amazon ad, if that doesn't work hide all of the ads, for some reason the amazon ad is blocking the videos..LOL

Upvote this comment so people can see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 11:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it fix for you? It's still the same, it keeps randomly pausing on it's own... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally exactly same explanation, i think the site's video files are fucked up lol. They need to refresh their data on the episodes on every anime  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can't be only on my end, something is stopping the video on it's own. Everything else works, other sites, i have no internet issues (stable 50 down 5 up), the problem is it works on my ipad but not on my iphone 6s, really weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It works on my ipad but not on my iphone 6s wtf, i don't know why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah what the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the site having problems? I have no internet issues at all lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 19:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently watching Hunter x Hunter 2011, and then suddenly the video, i mean i tried every random anime i could find the videos didn't load, they kept buffering??? Is there a problem??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has to god damn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 08:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, yami only sees rito tbh, since they first met and he gave the taiyaki, she started loving him, you can see that from both anime and manga.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey wtf, i didn't notice after looking at yui for a second  time, DAMN DOSE CURVES, i would like to see a chapter where she sleeps next to rito snd then gets attacked by the sleeping god rito xd  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IM ON MOTHAFUKING FIHAAAAAAAA (-- fire xd) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, i really want yami to be happy, like rito said "That's because..i want you to be happy yami" when she was getting groped by rito lol, i mean the scene from the anime where mea connects to yami's heart and sees the "bug" and then at the end he says "i want you to be happy" you can clearly tell that she from the first moment they met she fell in love. I support yami the most thb. She has been through so much, she needs to feel love. I want every girl to be happy, so many girls are depending on rito, he possibly can't choose one and break all the hearts of the other girls, it's SUPPOSED to end a harem. It must, otherwise the story will never be TRULY complete, so much character development would be all waste...TEAM MOTHAFUKINGGGG HAREM xd

(I've been reading this story for such a long time now, i'm really hoping that the author ends it the way everyone wants to it to end, HAREM.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ (i know that im technically supporting all the girls but still TEAM MOTHAFUCKING MOMO AND YAMI, yes im supporting the harem team) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 23:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you supporting team harem or only haruna? You point out that haruna supports it/is going to, but do you yourself? xd TEAM MOTHAFUCKING MOMO AND HAREM (i support yami too :3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rito lucky fuck ;-; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just hope it ends as a harem, so much character development would be a waste if he chooses haruna, still don't get 1 thing in this entire story, Rito fell in love only because haruna defended him because she told people that he didn't break the flowers...is that it? Is that supposed the be the best fall-in-love story? Run, momo, yami, lala and the others went trough so much character development and then fell in love but still rito loves haruna the most? Only because of that BS reason?? Really? I think the author made a big mistake with haruna as a whole, i mean she shouldn't ever been created in the story tbh lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AH fuk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that i'm asking the same over and over but,

Has the storywriter confirmed somewhere that it's going to end a harem? After so much that has happened and if it doesn't end a harem i think the whole story would turn out to be a failure, so much character development of the girls like yami, momo, lala and the others..rito can't choose 1 girl, he would break everyone's heart...we need confirmation that it is going to end a harem, right???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
