<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3726</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A while back I realised that most of the films (about 90%) that make up my top list can be considered spiritual or even religious on some level. This was a great surprise to me because I'm not religious in the slightest. Examples are films like *Taste Of Cherry*, *Bad Lieutenant*, Varda's *Le Bonheur*, or *The Act Of Killing*. All of my favourite films contain, at least, the questioning of the limits of human experience. Some, like *Syndromes And A Century* or *Mirror*, are almost spiritual acts in themselves - prayers or meditations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 19:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have an interesting counterpoint it's constructive to share it. Otherwise.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 14:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that Mamet should just not both write and direct the same projects. My personal view is that he is at heart a theatre artist. His dialogue is inherently theatrical and all his instincts are for theatre. If drama works brilliantly in the theatre there is no guarantee it will easily translate to film - just look at attempts to make great plays into films, like Miller's *The Crucible*, or the more recent *August Osage County*. With *Glengarry* you had a film artist as director who managed to pull off a very successful adaptation - although tbh I'm not really sure exactly why that text worked so well on screen. It had the benefit of probably one of the most talented ensemble casts ever assembled for a movie, all of whom (I think) were well seasoned actors of both stage and screen (not sure if Lemmon had done much on stage) and so knew well how to make the transition. It was also brilliantly directed by Foley. 

Mamet's stage writing is harsh, often bleak and frequently cruel. This type of writing works well on stage, because there is such an obvious level of unreality, and the audience have some distance on the thing - both physically and emotionally. Often when such writing is put on the big screen the coldness and cruelty is simply too much. Film is so much more of a literal, immersive form; and audience simply can't take it. And so directors often try and soften things. Characters become 'nicer' than their stage versions (this was very true of *August Osage County* - there's just no way a cinema audience could sustain the tragedy and cruelty of that play). When directing his own work, I think Mamet just does not know how to make this transition well. In toning down his own work he loses his way and creates films that lack an identity an audience can really relate to. His characters become strange or even bland. 

Probably *Glengarry* works partly because Foley managed to film the action with all of its original venom while somehow keeping the audience on side. I'm wondering if this is partly down to his camera work, which I remember being brilliant in that film. He focuses in on faces when he needs to, but at other times he pulls the camera right back so that we have some distance and can process what's happening without turning off. Sometimes he replaces the physical distance we would experience in the theatre with darkness - we are close, but the darkness gives us some element of protection from what we are witnessing. In addition, Foley and the production designer created a truly cinematic world for the action - the lights - the rain - the trains - it gives the action a context that uses singularly cinematic techniques to tell the story, and greatly helps the transition from a theatrical piece to a filmic one. This is something I have never seen Mamet manage to do on film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 14:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. 'Butter' is kind of a stationary squat performed with a very serious facial expression and his palms raised on either side of his head. It puts me in mind of a Native American Chief shitting in the forest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He never uses words to communicate a dairy product, but has invented a little dance for each item. My favourite is the 'semi-skimmed milk' dance. I also enjoy his 'butter'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 16:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What on Earth is this post about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I'm starting with 1 litre of whole goats milk (I think this is just over 4 cups) and 150g of sugar, plus 2 tablespoons of glucose syrup. Your comment interests me because I actually cut the amount of sugar in the recipe. The recipe asks for 200g, but I prefer the cajeta slightly less sweet. 

Just doing a brief internet search into making condensed milk, I notice the recipes online all include a significant proportion of butter. So I'm thinking Dulce De Leche also includes the butter (obviously!), which is going to change the caramel layer of the tart significantly in terms of fat content. Have I been labouring under the illusion that Cajeta and Dulce De Leche are basically the came thing? Weirdly, I have had the thought that adding butter to the cajeta might help stabilise it somehow - but I dismissed this idea as it seemed from of world of food science beyond my grasp! Maybe I was onto something! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe my oven is accurate - but I will double check. Yes the tart completely cools before serving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 16:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I have thought about this but have not tried it yet. Next time I will give it a go. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chocolate Tart Nightmares - help desperately needed! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! First time posting here. This is a cut-n-paste from a post I just made over at /askculinary. Someone suggested I post here too. Thanks for anyone who reads this - it's kinda long :-)
___________________________________________________

Gah! I need help! First off I apologise for posting about the same topic twice, but this particular culinary problem is fast becoming the bane of my existence.

It's [David Lebovitz's Chocolate Dulce De Leche Tart](https://chroniclingthekitchen.wordpress.com/2014/08/18/chocolate-dulce-de-leche-tart/) again.

OK I will try and make this as concise as possible. I adore Dulce De Leche made with goat's milk (Cajeta is its official name I believe) and would like to use it in this tart in stead of the store-bought cow's variety (which is not available in my local stores anyway). So I make my own.

First attempt at this tart was not good because (I now realise) my oven cools down very slowly, so when it came to putting the tart into the 150C oven (after it had been at 200C for the pastry) the oven was still too hot and the tart overbaked. Overbaking actually spoils the taste of this tart, as well as making it look ugly. But the overbaked version did not crack on top.

Next attempt - the tart was beautiful on top - dark, glossy, and thrillingly wobbly (I'm lucky enough to have two ovens so I used them both - one hot one cool) but on attempting to serve I watched in horror as the Cajeta ran out of the case in a steady stream and pooled on the table top. In front of guests. I asked you wise kitchen owls what might be the problem, and a very helpful redditor suggested condensation, and I thought that was a good bet because indeed I had let my tart case cool before filling with the chocolate.

To cut a long and painful story short, every attempt since has featured not only similarly runny cajeta, but in addition the top of the tart has started to crack about 5 - 10 minutes out of the oven and cajeta has oozed to the surface creating scary big K shaped cracks that mirror perfectly the slowly forming cracks in my mental health as a successful version of this potentially show-stopping tart continues to evade me.

Any ideas? FYI, my cajeta, when at room temperature, is the consistency of hard chewy toffee, requiring some gentle warming to even get it out of the bowl. Is my home made cajeta just a different animal to the store-bought dulce de leche, and will never work in this tart? I would so love it to - because despite the disappointing presentation, the combination of salty goat's milk cajeta and dark bitter chocolate is absolutely heavenly.

Help me......
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This chocolate tart will be the end of me.... Baking experts - help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 20:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gah! I need help!
First off I apologise for posting about the *same topic* twice, but this particular culinary problem is fast becoming the bane of my existence. 

It's David Lebovitz's [Chocolate Dulce De Leche Tart](https://chroniclingthekitchen.wordpress.com/2014/08/18/chocolate-dulce-de-leche-tart/) **again**. 


OK I will try and make this as concise as possible. I adore Dulce De Leche made with goat's milk (Cajeta is its official name I believe) and would like to use it in this tart in stead of the store-bought cow's variety (which is not available in my local stores anyway). So I make my own. 


First attempt at this tart was not good because (I now realise) my oven cools down very slowly, so when it came to putting the tart into the 150C oven (after it had been at 200C for the pastry) the oven was still too hot and the tart overbaked. Overbaking actually spoils the taste of this tart, as well as making it look ugly. But the overbaked version did not crack on top. 

Next attempt - the tart was beautiful on top - dark, glossy, and thrillingly wobbly (I'm lucky enough to have two ovens so I used them both - one hot one cool) but on attempting to serve I watched in horror as the Cajeta ran out of the case in a steady stream and pooled on the table top. In front of guests. I asked you wise kitchen owls what might be the problem, and a very helpful redditor suggested condensation, and I thought that was a good bet because indeed I had let my tart case cool before filling with the chocolate. 


To cut a long and painful story short, every attempt since has featured not only similarly runny cajeta, but in addition the top of the tart has started to crack about 5 - 10 minutes out of the oven and cajeta has oozed to the surface creating scary big *K* shaped cracks that mirror perfectly the slowly forming cracks in my mental health as a successful version of this potentially show-stopping tart continues to evade me. 


Any ideas? FYI, my cajeta, when at room temperature, is the consistency of hard chewy toffee, requiring some gentle warming to even get it out of the bowl. Is my home made cajeta just a different animal to the store-bought dulce de leche, and will never work in this tart? I would so love it to - because despite the disappointing presentation, the combination of salty goat's milk cajeta and dark bitter chocolate is absolutely heavenly. 

Help me......    

Edit: The latest version has a layer at the bottom of chewy cajeta, similar to how it was before it went into the tart, but still runny cajeta on top and oozing out of cracks. I notice that the tart top develops condensation about two hours out of the oven. There is definitely a condensation problem here I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 10:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So come back and raise the bar with your own fascinating post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean about *Brooklyn*, but I would argue conflict is introduced very early on with the scene with the nasty old shop keeper. This sets up the idea that the main character is being disloyal in leaving Ireland, illustrating her internal conflict that is not resolved until the very end of the film. This central conflict is the principle driving force behind the narrative. 

Your comment made me think of *Le Bonheur* by Agnes Varda. I'm not saying this film contains no conflict - but I'm suggesting its handling of conflict is highly original. **Spoiler Alert**  The central male character is unfaithful to his wife, and experiences no guilt or conflict within himself about this. The film proceeds to portray his relationships through what could be described as an uncomplicated experssion of conflict-free happiness (the joy he experiences with the tow women seems only to intensify and increase as a result of the situation). Although shit hits the fan somewhat in the final ten minutes of the film (and this tragic ending is itself deeply ambiguous), I guess for the most part conflict is experienced only in the minds of the audience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeh - big Herzog fan here, but this did nothing for me. It was rambling and failed, I felt, to communicate any interesting ideas. I didn't get what it was about, apart from... y'know... Volcanos. The exploration of the cultural mythology surrounding Volcanos was not nearly so interesting as the introduction promised. This was a terribly *male* film - I grew tired of these boys and their rather nerdy club. During the never-ending let's-look-for-bones-in-the-dessert segment I made myself not one, but two cups of tea. And just a personal quibble: I'm a little tired of documentary makers filming those poor North Koreans desperately acting out their grotesque pantomimes for western cameras. Yeh it makes engaging TV, but really, those are some of the most wretched individuals on our planet and I'm getting uncomfortable ogling them like creatures in a zoo. But generally I would describe *Into The Inferno* as a creative travelogue more than anything else; and rather a self indulgent one. I'm sure Werner had a great time traveling to all those remote places! Well, he deserves it I guess. 

Edit: Just noticed I wrote 'dessert' by mistake but have left it in because it's pretty funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 19:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I think you must have missed it](https://www.reddit.com/r/TrueFilm/comments/57z0j7/results_truefilm_21st_century_poll/)

I feel that if you look beneath the populist surface of Lee's films, there is often a fascinating, sometimes quite profound idea or set of ideas at play. I disagree that CTHD was a very straight story. It included an audacious feminist subtext that (I'm guessing) is pretty original for the genre (could be wrong there). Rather than submit to the patriarchy that sought to control her, Jen Yu chose instead a kind of suicide which was also an unknowable transcendence. In evading her masters, she also chose to turn her back on romantic love. The film's story is primarily a romance featuring two parallel romantic relationships, both of which prove impossible to realise. I find it fascinating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 16:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this awesome reply to my question! 

The 'mysticism' you talk of in your first point - I'm not sure I agree if audiences enjoy that kind of ambiguity as much as you claim, although you do describe them as 'feigning' a deep connection to a film like *Tree Of Life*, so maybe you are hinting there's an element of pretentiousness at play? Is this a large general audience, or a smaller *truefilm* audience of cineastes? Personally I very much enjoy feeling mystified by a film - connecting with a film on an abstract level but not really knowing what it's about. But I don't consider my tastes in any way populist when it comes to film!

I actually flat out disagree with your third point, that the CGI in *Pi* failed to transcend the medium. I saw the film in 3D on an enormous screen and pretty much *forgot* the tiger wasn't real. And no matter how impressive the CGI in *Tree Of Life* was, the episode where a dinosaur experienced a moment of divine empathy was one of the funniest things I've seen in the cinema for a long time. 

I would add the thought that 'flashy' need not confine itself to effects and action. Malick consistently ups the flash quota outrageously in the casting of his films, to the point where you have a huge star like Sean Penn wandering around from time to time doing little else than *being Sean Penn* (this was pretty hilarious to me too). This is the most superficial variety of flash I can think of. While Lee will include movie stars in his films, he keeps it relatively modest, and enjoys casting unknowns in major roles. 

You may have worked out by now that I despise Malick - although this is an area where I bow to his popularity elsewhere. The films must be good; they are just not to my personal taste. On the other hand, I greatly admire Lee. I enjoy his unique and confusing identity - a little bit Chinese - a little bit western - a little bit block buster - a little bit art house etc. I admire his ability to create really thrilling multiplex-friendly action, while at the same time creating narratives that always carry an equally thrilling intellectual thesis. I love the way he surprises me - *Crouching Tiger*, for example, was a film about love that turned out to be a film about patriarchy. *Ride With The Devil* was a film about American identity that turned out to be a film about race. Sometimes there's a moment in his films where I suddenly realise what Lee is really doing and, seriously, it brings tears to my eyes. 

And yet I didn't include one of Lee's films on my own top ten list - so maybe the only person that can answer my original question is me. Maybe I really am just a snob. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 11:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely someone has already mentioned Fellini's *La Dolce Vita - 8 1/2*? 

(I know this isn't what you're looking for, but if you enjoy a thematic trilogy in film, check out Cedric Kahn's 'cars trilogy' - *L'Ennui/ Roberto Succo/ Red Lights*) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Half of his films are too flashy to be considered "artsy,"

Here you describe the crux of the matter I think. 'Flashy' is an interesting word  - can you break it down? Is *Tree Of Life* not flashy as hell?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too am a huge admirer of Ang Lee - and yet I failed to include any of his films on my top ten list (If *Ride With The Devil* had been made this century I might have included that - I believe it to be possibly the single most underrated film of all time!). Do you think Lee's box office popularity keeps his films from rising too high on critics top lists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Most of the time we watch films about characters going on journeys, but sometimes films can take us on a journey too.

This is a great way of thinking about it! My problem with our (I include myself) slightly arms-length attitude to Ang Lee, however, is that I believe his best work does *both* of those things. *Crouching Tiger* or *Lust Caution* are, I would argue, just as rich in their subtextual themes as *Tree Of Life*. *Crouching Tiger*, for example, remains a poignant meditation on the eternal conflict between personal freedom and our need for romantic attachments - all viewed from a thrillingly post-feminist perspective. The intellectual exercise Lee demonstrates in that movie is, for me, equally as dazzling as the martial arts choreography! It's easily up there with the best of our 'top tens'. But at the same time *Crouching Tiger* was *so* popular, and is *so* easy to watch. My question is, does this popularity and ease keep us from appreciating the true value of Lee's work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your comment

 Personally, if all I'm getting is a cause-effect story

I don't think any of the movies in question, obviously narrative led or otherwise, are of this kind. Would a purely 'cause-effect story' movie even be possible? The audience would surely quickly start to impose their own subtext to the piece, probably without even realising it. 

But a lot of times, the most accessible work is the least specific or memorable. Mentioning Lust, Caution as your favorite Ang Lee film goes along with that - it received an NC-17 rating I believe and is likely his least seen film of this century.

Are you not confusing 'accessible' with 'popular' here? When I used the term 'accessible' I did not mean *physically* accessible (as in the film is easy to find), but that the film is 'easy to watch' in that the strong traditional narrative provides a familiar form a large audience will feel comfortable with. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes we are indeed splitting hairs! Are we not here to occasionally split some hairs? :-)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes this - sorry I didn't read your comment till after I had posted my own reply to *fuckyehnebulas*, but you describe what I mean better then I did! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 10:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your brief description of *TWBB* kind of describes what I mean. If someone were to ask you 'what's *TWBB* about?' you would probably have to think for a while before coming up with your answer. And if you asked many people, there would probably be many different answers. This is probably what makes it an interesting film. Compare this to *Life Of Pi* - the answer would probably start with something like 'well, this guy gets stuck on a boat with a tiger and...'. It's just a slightly easier narrative to access. Yes, you could, with some thought, go on to construct a far more sophisticated description of *Life Of Pi* which included the film's subtextual themes, but the basic 'guy on a boat with a tiger' thing would still stand. But *TWBB is* a narrative led movie in an obvious way - it does have a story (this guy discovers oil in the californian dessert...) which the majority of an audience will easily access. The differences are subtle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best of the 21st C lists and Ang Lee. Are we uncomfortable with 'story'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 01:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was chatting to a friend at work about the TrueFilm 21st century poll, going over my top ten choices and mentioning some of the other popular choices, as well as those that made the final top ten. This work friend is highly intelligent, but while she enjoys the cinema she's not a 'serious' film fan. She commented that many of the films I had mentioned seemed to lack a strong 'story', and she wondered if too obvious or dominant a story-line was something that discouraged film enthusiasts from considering a film 'great'. 

I have to admit I find this an interesting question. I have not seen all of the films on the top ten, but if those I have, only the animation *Spirited Away* contains what I'd describe as a strong traditional narrative. *Mulholland Drive* and *Synecdoche* are narrative heavy it's true - but in so c-rrazy a manner, to call them 'narrative led' becomes highly problematic. *There Will Be Blood*, *Lost In Translation*, and *In The Mood* downplay their narratives, while *Tree Of Life* barely has one. (To be clear, I'm very much talking about the literal sur-text here. Obviously these films contain rich and compelling narratives on an abstract level.) 

The whole thing got me to thinking about Ang Lee, and possible explanations as to why this award winning, critically lauded movie-making giant failed to feature once on my and so many other's lists. Lee occupies a unique position, making contemporary films many would class as 'great', and yet sitting in strangely awkward company with the somehow more easily adored auteurs of our time such as Anderson and Malick. The 21st Century has seen not only the barnstorming *Crouching Tiger* from Lee, but the monumental *Life Of Pi* and also the film I would suggest as his best of the century so far, the staggeringly beautiful *Lust Caution*. 

Is the near absence of Lee on our lists, I wonder, somehow connected to his tendency to feature such solid, effortlessly accessible narratives at the forefront of his work? Is there something 'old fashioned' about a good story? If a film is too easy to access, does this put us off? 

Thoughts. 

(I use Lee only as an example to explain my question - so please feel free to make general comments on the subject of narrative apart from Lee) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And finally, the birthday talk foreshadows the birth of the starchild later in the movie, but maybe that's a stretch.

em... just a little! But it's interesting what you say about HAL 'surrounding' Poole. I would suggest HAL's omnipresence is enhanced by Poole's red visor. The redness mirrors the red light of HAL's 'eye'. HAL influences and controls the human's experience of the world in every way imaginable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 00:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry I do not have time right now to read your entire post, but if you really want to expose yourself to a low point in Hitchcock's portrayal of women try *Frenzy*. It's just a horribly misogynist film on every level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this. I don't think Loach wants us to enjoy the landscape of *Kes*. If at times we do, that's not a problem, but it's not the emphasis. The emphasis is, as you say, on Billy's experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crew are entirely maintained by the technology that surrounds them - maintained but also controlled; made passive. In their inhuman environment, what we think of as 'human' qualities and traits are largely disabled, e.g. the human trait of communality and bonds between individuals (including bonds within the family group). In the future world of 2001, human endeavour generally has become subservient to the mechanisms of commerce - as exemplified by fact that Dr. Poole's birthday message from his parents is dominated almost entirely by talk of monetary transactions; salary; birthday gifts ets. In this way we can see Poole's emotionless reaction as entirely appropriate. His parents talk of nothing but money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 17:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP is, I believe, highlighting *Inside Out* here because of its innovative approach to narrative, so the argument is not so much whether or not *Inside Out* is a good film, but about the originality of the narrative approach. *Inside Out* is not one of Pixar's greatest, but whether you love them or not, I find it hard to buy an argument that suggests they have failed to provide anything in the way of originality when it comes to the kinds of narrative we find in family entertainment. (This is another important feature of Pixar I think you miss - these are *family* films, not *children's* films.) *Wall-E*? 

I agree that *Inside Out*, while appearing to be strikingly original from the outside, is, when you break it down, pretty formulaic, and I question OP's inclusion of it in a list of narrative groundbreakers along with *Nashville*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 21:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a fan of some of his films, and a couple of weeks ago he got on my bus and sat next to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 21:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the top ten lists I'm thinking I need to see *Yi Yi*, which seems to have passed me by somehow. Can't find it anywhere. Anyone have any ideas how I can see it without spending 35 pounds on the DVD? (UK here) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 12:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of your points can be explained, possibly, by the age group that generally characterises reddit users. I'm guessing it's pretty young.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 23:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. The toms are now in the fridge in oil + vinegar!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 15:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey - I was searching for whoever it was had *P'tit Quinquin* as their number one movie. It's on my top ten list. Great call - it's a magnificent film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 22:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Thin Red Line* was the start of his love affair with big hollywood stars, and for me the beginning of an ego-heavy bombasticism in his films. I remember Clooney's scene as being completely upstaged by the fact of Clooney's fame. There was no point to such a famous actor being in the film for so short a time - it's just ego. (Much love for Clooney otherwise!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 09:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've heard plenty of people talk about how he kind of masturbates himself with every movie after Thin Red Line

For me it's every movie after *Days Of Heaven*. *The Thin Red Line* bored my bum off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an interesting question! There are some directors, like Kubrick maybe, who strove endlessly for perfection in their work. It's an exhausting and laborious way to go about things, but when it work the results can be awesome. Maybe I'm giving away too much of how my strange mind works here - but I see it as kind of a 'masculine' approach to art (yeh I know - makes no sense probably). Other directors - including some I've come to greatly admire over the past decade - seem to seek to exert minimal control over their films. They know, perhaps, that a work of art does not belong to the artist, and is not 'finished' until it's seen by an audience. The audience completes the film. (Or maybe, since a film is a recording that in theory can exist for eternity, a film is never completely finished, because it can always continue to be seen by different audiences!). These directors are like good parents to their work. They create films and guide them, but ultimately they know their creation will have a life of its own, and they encourage them to take on their own identity. The french director Arnaud Desplechin springs to mind - he makes huge rambling films that sometimes vary wildly in style and tone. It's almost as if he's intentionally making his work as messy as possible, so that the very idea of 'perfection' is quickly forgotten and we can all relax and enjoy the ride. There's something modest about this style - the work is no longer about the director's ego perhaps! I will always love Kubrick, but too much of him and I feel weighed down by the ego of the man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 00:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you just don't *like* Malick. Without meaning to sound flippant, for me he is one of the most overrated directors of our time. I'm all about Anderson - all about Haneke - all about Weerasethakul - from Kurosawa to Kiarostami I'm down with the heavy-weights, but Malick leaves me stone cold. I found *Tree Of Life* hard to watch. Towards the end I kept trying to catch the eye of other people in the cinema audience to see if I was alone in my incredulity - such a deeply pretentious film! If you want to f*** your Mother that bad, go to therapy. Don't make a film about it. (Just to balance this out, obviously *Badlands* rocks, and I thought *Days Of Heaven* a monumentally beautiful film.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
