<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe so, but I'm actually good for the time being. If anyone else needs Enfamil checks, send it to them first! Thanks you though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sent you a PM! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 07:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for Enfamil Enspire Coupons. I have: $30 for Parent's Choice Checks (1-$15, 1-$10, 1-$5) exp. 11/21/16, $25 Similac Go   Grow Checks (1-$10, 3-$5) exp 1/21/17, $10 Enfagrow Toddler Transitions Checks (2-$5) exp 11/30/16

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 06:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not me, but a guy I knew had a Marine in his platoon who's sibling won the lottery. Being a good sibling s/he shared the wealth with said Marine. This Marine thought it a wise use of his funds to buy a car, (some kind of Lambo, I believe) only to later realize that the car did not meet the state's smog emission requirements, and therefore could not legally be driven on base to work. (At the time, you were required to have DoD decals on your vehicle, which required a smog test to obtain.) His elegant solution to this problem was to buy a 2nd car that he could drive on base, rent a parking spot from someone's house near the base, and drive the Lambo from his residence to his parking spot, and the 2nd car from the parking spot to his job site. Then do it all in reverse at the end of the day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 05:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First post to this sub. Be gentle, por favor! 

Recipe: 

1 cup lukewarm water
1 envelope dry active yeast
3 TB sugar 
2 eggs, room temperature
3.75 cups AP flour (plus more for kneading)
1/4 cup milk powder
1 TB salt
4 TB unsalted butter, softened and cut into cubes
egg wash
Sesame seeds for top (optional) 

Mix sugar and water, add yeast and allow to bubble (5 mins), mix in eggs. 

In bowl of stand mixer, mix flour, milk powder and salt. Add butter, 1 cube at a time until incorporated. 

Add yeasty-egg mixture to dry ingredients. Mix on medium with dough hook until dough just starts to pull away from sides. Transfer dough to floured surface and knead into a ball. Oil a clean bowl, or spray it with nonstick. Allow dough to proof in greased bowl until doubled in volume (approx 40 mins). Punch dough down, shape into buns of your choice. (I used the kaiser roll method. Rolled them into 12 inch long x 1.25 inch wide ropes, and knotted them). Place on baking tray and allow to proof for another 30 mins. Brush with egg wash and top with sesame seeds. Bake in a 325 F oven for about 20 mins. Throw about 1/4 cup directly onto bottom of oven when you put them in and shut door. OR you can use a spray bottle to mist them at the beginning and halfway through. 

Came out with a nice light texture, perfect for tonight's dinner of pulled BBQ chicken (Chicken breasts + sweet baby ray's bbq sauce in a slow cooker. Shred after cooking on high for 4 hours), and tomorrow's dinner of Burgers. 

Next time I make this, I will probably use all milk instead of water and replace sugar with honey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brioche buns I made for tonight's dinner (recipe in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 04:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "Made On" location on the back of this picture frame </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 04:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
