<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ctrl+F, Trump... hmm, nothing...  
Ctrl+F Brexit... hmm, nothing here either.  
Surprised! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 17:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I meant dry, as in alcohol free. Saloon in English means a bar. I believe you meant "salon" (as in, barber shop) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, option 2, a misspelling of "Salon"?  
This makes sense now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 07:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "to whom they cater"  
the "for" is superfluous, as you could have put "for whom they cater"  
Yours is akin to writing "to whom they cater to" or "for whom they cater for"... that shit just ain't right, brah!  
It's a slow morning at work... Okay? :p  
(oh yeah, and it's "whom" as they are in the accusative (I.E. they are the ones being catered to/for)  
EDIT: I just noticed your flair and realised English may not be your first language. If so, apologies for being harsh, your English is awesome if not native, and most Brits will make this same mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A saloon in Sharjah? I thought it was a dry Emirate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a fair point. But my commute is only 20 minutes in rush hour anyway, and 15 minutes on a clear run. Those 5 minutes would be spent getting all the gear on and off! (yes, all the gear, all the time!).  
So there's no point for me, but yeah, I hadn't considered that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 06:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grammatically, both are correct, you are correct. However, colloquially, the bananas version is not ever used. The term "peanuts" can mean "very little" or "of almost no value" so makes much more sense linguistically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Experienced biker here (in several countries). I hate riding motorcycles in Dubai. The only place one can enjoy them in this country is in the mountains after fajr, and in the desert.  
As soon as there is anyone else on the roads, it takes all the fun out of the twisty mountain roads. Inside the city, the roads are just long and straight, which are the most tedious on a motorcycle. (especially something like a Ninja). Plus there are cameras every 20 metres!  
Also, is this your first bike? Would not recommend a 600 Ninja for a first bike.  
Sorry if this sounds negative, I do honestly love riding! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  want to share with westerner  
  
This upsets me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 19:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The phrase is "if you pay peanuts, you get monkeys" ... just sayin'... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way for you to be sure of the current narrative? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 11:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must confess that I had this scene in my head whilst writing the above! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't read it with any religion connotation. I would have defined a ritual as something done routinely, or as a standard procedure; not something done as a one off (like in the case of Obama). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree with it being a ritual. But you make a good point about the connection. It's important for the one who issues an execution to at least witness it, even if they don't swing the sword themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make a good point. And actually, Islam (strongly) encourages the memorisation of the text, rather than reliance on written form. Mohammed (saws) was illiterate himself anyway. The revelation was. It in the form of a physical manifestation of a golden book, you're totally correct! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 14:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fundamental difference being one believes one is man written, whereas the other believes the other is divinely written... but yes, I agree they would be comparable tasks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 08:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she'd been Arab, this would have been ~~p~~berfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But have you met her brother Tod? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you want to be Loretta, Stan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 13:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clueless?  
You're talking to a guy who in the UK buys from Alchemy, Square Mile and Has Bean, whoch are roasted the day before shipping. I even have my favourite plantation (In Yirgacheffe, Etheopia). I have a pressure gauge portafilter for my Gaggia to calibrate it. I adjust my grind depending on how many days old the roast is. I do not buy coffee from a supermarket (such as Illy). So if I'm clueless, it's certainly not of decent coffee, but only of the price of old, stale supermarket coffee.  
Illy is certainly not for the connoisseur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't compare RAW with carrefour. They are worlds apart. I like the saying "if coffee has a 'best before' date stamped on it, then it wasn't good in the first place". Also, you don't want to buy ground coffee. Invest in a good grinder. It'll make your coffee SO much better.
RAW is actually top quality coffee, even comparing to top places in London (sq mile, alchemy, has Bean etc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Illy is expensive? It's crappy supermarket grade stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree with this for American imports. But the GCC specs are much better. Avoid US imports like the plague. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want a 4x4 I assume you will be driving off road (else why would you want one?)  
If that's the case, for that budget, get a Nissan Xterra. The leaf suspension will never break. Parts are readily available should you need them. Great performance off road, but an engine not so massive that it's silly for the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 07:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something something, broken arms... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was remarking upon the paradigm of a lonely computer geek who sits in his room all day. I know this isn't true, was using the stereotype in jest! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says the guy considering a career in computing... haha.  
However, I'll have you know that knowing basic grammar to be able to communicate well, and having a life are not mutually exclusive. If anything, the better the education, the better the career. The better the career, the more cash one has to spend on adventure and fueling one's adrenaline fix.  
However, this is a petty argument, best of luck in your career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good cheap bodyshop for car repair? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to get a crack in a bumper repaired. Does anyone know of a good place to get this done?  
I have heard tales of wizards in Sharjah who can work magic, and assume they'll be cheaper than Dubai, does anyone know who to contact these mystical beings?  
Muchas Gracias </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 06:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But surely the new Tesla models will also make competition outdated, not just Tesla models. That's like "Don't buy Apple phone because they'll release a new one next year, buy an android because they'll take 10 years, and it'll be the current model for so much longer". OK, yeah, but it's still superseded by competition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 21:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you like me to donate some punctuation? Here, take a comma ",". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Thank you!](https://www.reddit.com/r/tipofmytongue/comments/5pihzi/tomt_movie_looking_for_a_specific_weird_short/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Found it!](https://vimeo.com/141567420)  
Ok so it wasn't a dog farting confetti, but you see what I mean! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [MOVIE] Looking for a specific (weird) short movie but can't find it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 19:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has a scene where a girl switches on a light switch and a dog farts our confetti (I did say it was weird). It follows a number of scenes which change slightly each time they're shown, and have realistic, but odd, things happening to some great music if I recall correctly. I think there was even a gif of the dof confetti fart scene on reddit. Can anyone help me find it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old are you? I'm guessing less than 18? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lust.  
You know nothing about this girl, what she's like, how intelligent or interesting she is. Whether you'll like her sense of humour, or her bad habits. Yet you describe her as the "woman of your dreams".  
Lust confirmed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally this, it's a painful read! Basic communication skills are essential in anyone I look to hire. Not hired.  
Capitalisation is the difference between "Helping your Uncle Jack off a horse" and "Helping your uncle jack off a horse". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you get paid to do something, couple with all the politics and commercialism, you cease to enjoy it for what it is. I'm. Ot saying that one cannot enjoy their job, but it's still a job. Get a well paying one and you can enjoy the hours outside work more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get paid to take shit and do shit. The more shit you wanna give me, the more money you gonna have to give me. That's the deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 10:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rust? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 11:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't be that hard can it? I mean how many countries are there? Like, 5? 6? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 09:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we... inside a sitcom...?  
No, we can't be, I don't have an amazing apartment in the heart of the city with no logical explanation about how I pay for it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 09:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an interesting sentence structure, particularly with the choice of words. I hope no one mis-reads it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OneStopDegreeShop.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then who chooses? It's a democracy, right? Just vote in someone to change it! Simple! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 06:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then he may be comparing costs from massively disparate economies, nullifying his original argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So how does it make it more secure? If one company controls everything and nobody outside can view the code to verify how secure it is? Open source is inherently more secure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Middle East every toilet has a "shataaf", a little hand held bidet for exactly this. I miss them dearly when in other parts of the world. It's actually an Islamic practice, along with squatting to dump, which is SO much better, seriously [TRY IT!](https://youtu.be/YbYWhdLO43Q) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I have the image of a scary clown trying this... need ~~eye~~ mind bleach! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good... but isn't this all the basic stuff taught when learning to drive? I would have thought that anyone going for a test would know this, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the UK, this is what's written in The Highway Code. You should not leave the foot on your brake whilst at lights. So it should be the handbrake. As you should not keep the clutch depressed, should change to neutral.  
As such, this driving style transferred when I moved here, even though I (reluctantly) have automatics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30% is legal limit on front sides, correct?  
If so, leave it at that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't tip.  
Source: Brit staunchly against this American tipping culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 21:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to look for "card holders" rather than wallets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 10:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So? None of Van Gogh's painting looked exactly like the subject; doesn't mean it's not artistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Mustangs~~ Cars are notorious for being treated poorly in this part of the world  
  
FTFY

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  pay out of the ass

You excrete money? That's AMAZING! Although... paper cuts... there is that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you're doing 110 on the left lane where people go 140, you will be tailgated and flashed and honked

Amazingly, even if there's a massive queue of people in front of you. These guys can't see further than the car in front of them. Either that or they think that traffic jams shouldn't apply to them, and just get out their way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 08:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  dont tailgate just in case there's a police
  

Not because it's incredibly dangerous then and you're putting not only your own life, but the lives of many other road users at risk, but because you might get a fine? Please stop driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whilst I certainly do not advocate dropping out of education before getting a degree, and I do agree that it can be harder if you do, but it doesn't necessarily mean you're "f****d" but a long shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 06:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redditors don't leave the house, let alone have the ability to drive themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 12:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surname Lass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 07:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 Ds per transaction? That's steep! Or 2.5% on credit cards? That's also steep. I'd never pay that. Exchange cash if you need to avoid that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What eloquent use of language from this delightful young fellow!  
*sigh*  
I lament at today's youth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends what passport you hold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, withdraw cash in Dubai, and exchange at UAE Exchange (or similar bureau de change). NEVER at airport. Also, Japan is expensive (but totally awesome!) so advise changing before you go. Take some spare AED though.  
I don't advise withdrawing from cash point in Japan. The fees will be much more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had to do this. I travel a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered that he might not have a TV? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look so damn ugly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  unlimited budget

Sounds exciting. How's the shark tank under your office floor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like he's talking backwards.  
(For info, he's not... I checked!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audi, VW, Seat. Same company, same cars. The new tech and best trim starts with Audi. Then filters down to VW and when the final cost cuts are made, they brand as Seat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ariel, Lotus, Noble, Radical, TVR, Aston, Ascari, Ginetta, McLaren, Caterham, to name but a few... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 19:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even bother clicking it because I simply assumed it was xkcd until I read your comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 16:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't want to eat any of your cucumbers now...  
You can keep the tossed salad too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 16:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slow cookers are awesome! The chicken comes out so tender. Also great if you're working, can just throw it in in the morning and it's ready when you get home! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 15:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the comment wasn't a reply/response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 11:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's a shitty comment. It's like a flight attendant saying to an obviously Muslim person "it's ok, I know you're not a terrorist". Why even bloody mention it then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 11:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. Am Muslim  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVERY, DAMMED, THREAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a case of "we have to tell you that you can't sleep here. Can you confirm you understand this instruction so that if shit comes back after someone else finds out, we totally told you that you can't sleep here. That said, there is no limit to the time you can spend in your unit which has a bed, a sofa, and TV, and what you do in the is your own business"  
"Yes... I understand"  
"We cool" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a creep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 08:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half arsed. Not half assed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've taken to just ignoring the whole sentence.  
It happens less now.  
She left me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taken with, or without, food? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LEGO bricks, not Lego bricks, you have to shout it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!  
As does calling LEGO bricks "Lego" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 10:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the horn wasn't attached to the car, is that a loophole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 09:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming there is a specific law against this? Or defined limits on the loudness of the horn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 22:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a brilliant twist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  half asleep  
  
Stop. Turn off the car. Rest. Don't drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone wants a coffee "extra hot" a barrister I knew would simply make the coffee the way it's meant to be made (otherwise you spoil the milk/shot). Then he's just steam the rim of the cup to was hot when they put it to their lips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read another book which has had the same effect as 1984. I feel like my life is divided into pre-1984 and post-1984. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? Depends where you live I guess. In the UAE we just tell the cashier the PIN (helps when paying by card at the petrol station in summer and don't want to get out the AC car!). Most people have a default PIN which the cashier knows anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's exactly why I'm asking :)  
Wondered if anyone knew where I could get such a vehicle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Indeed, there is no superiority of an Arab over a non-Arab, nor of a non-Arab over an Arab, nor of a white over a black, nor a black over a white, except by taqwa" - Mohammad (saws) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You calling all Arabs racist?  
That's racist, man!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4x4 Rental to take to Oman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 13:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I rent a 4x4 (with low gears and diff lock) which will be allowed to be taken into Oman. Anyone know a good local place which have better rates than the normal Hertz etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 06:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meguiers are good. The clay bar I use is the Bilt Hamber one. Now get ready for a lot of rubbing! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
