<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9885</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best part about the reporting of this story: "Police said they did not know the motive for the vandalism" http://uk.mobile.reuters.com/article/idUKKCN12Q260 pretty sure I could have a good guess.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No tupaware?! Crazy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 10:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think this is particularly ugly, unless I'm missing something? the legend could possibly be made a bit clearer to show which series are plotted on the second axis but it's a pretty succinct and understandable way of getting a lot of information onto one chart - I like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's certainly not how I would categorise harassment, and this thread is 100% about women being made to feel uncomfortable, talking about those experiences and ways to stay safe when far from home. And I think the context of the posts and general conversation makes that obvious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 07:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's context specific, and a tame example of the things that will get said to make a point. The OP had mentioned travelling Morocco which was where I was thinking of from personal experience, although it happens in most countries in differing degrees of regularity. Especially in the cities, men will sit on the side of the street and yell things at women, often lewd things, and make disconcerting eye contact with you. In that situation it doesn't really matter what is being said, it's harassing because it's humiliating to be shouted at walking down the street. As I said, the man making the comments doesn't seem to expect or want a verbal response in my experience, so what is the purpose of the comment in the first place if not to harass?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 20:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing. It's so lovely to hear that origami is helping you, and to see one of  your creations too 
Origami can be such a soothing activity - I often do some folding when I need to get out of my head  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As annoying or unpleasant an experience it might be to have a confrontation over what is essentially your right to travel without harassment as a female alone it's the method I've found that works. Just tell them straight to leave you alone, if that doesn't work just repeat no - learn a couple of choice phrases in the language of the country you are travelling to as well. 

In my experience there are two types of harassment that you will experience as a female traveller. Street harassment where as much as he might tell you how good you look he doesn't really want or expect a response from you . And secondly, opportunistic men who think that a female travelling alone might be a good sexual target (these men exist everywhere but often target drunk women). In either situation showing that you are in control and assertive is the best approach. And being verbally aggressive if necessary.

As other commenters have pointed out, if you want to go out drinking then it doesn't hurt to find a couple of friendly fellow travellers from your hostel to go with.

Best of luck, it's an annoying part of travelling alone as a female, but I don't think it should put people off the many benefits and wonderful things you can learn and experience travelling alone. I think sharing experiences and strategies are a great step towards making solo travel as safe and a accessible for women as it is for men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 09:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mostly young, white, male, liberal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
