<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9822</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 18:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I AM BEN WYATT  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 18:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree with the trainer comment. I transitioned from Planet to a more serious gym and getting a trainer was the perfect transition. What you said about them being a buffer is perfect. No idea why you're getting downvoted, great comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work the most exciting of all careers, vastly dangerous and extremely risky. I'm an accountant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 22:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound preachy and I don't want it to come across as that but unfortunately that's what's going to happen. First off, awesome job losing 10lbs!

Cut the diet fad. Eat whatever you want as long as you are within your calorie limits. Screw what some "diet plan" has to say. A very large majority of people who undergo "diets" fail and most gain more weight back after their diet is over.

 However, cutting out bad carbs, fried foods, sugars is always a good plan. Just don't be restricted within the guidelines of what some diet plan found online/in a book tells you to do :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 16:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! I recently switch to a vegan diet in the middle of my weight loss journey and am so pleased that I did! It's been such a game changer! Keep it up! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Month Progress - M/23/240 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 16:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey loseit! Short story, started off at 331lbs about a year ago and currently am down to 240lbs. 90 down only 40 to go! 

About a month ago I kicked my lifestyle change into high gear and started going to a trainer regularly and switched over to a plant based diet. Here's the progress after one little month: http://imgur.com/fLx0qDW

I know it's not much, yes. However, it's a sign that I'm doing the right things and that the body I want is in the horizon. Now to get rid of that extra fat! I browse through this subreddit every day and just keep getting more and more motivated. Much love to all of you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrible Workout - Diet Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 03:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, cross posted to r/vegan and r/veganfitness so if you see this both places don't kill me pls.

I recently made the switch to a vegan diet and everything was running perfectly fine. Been feeling great, killing it in the gym, etc. I'm a 6 foot tall male weighing in at 240. I've obviously been eating at a calorie deficit to lose weight. My gym routine is MWF cardio, TR strength/body training with a trainer. I've been doing great but tonight, something went wrong. I felt drained, lethargic and just terrible. My workout showed also, it was terrible. Worst night I've had in the gym for awhile. 

The night before I slept a solid 8 hours so that's obviously not the case. Therefore, I looked to my diet. Could you all look over it and see if that's what it could have been? My workout began at 5:30pm and the following is my meals throughout the day:

Breakfast (around 6:30): smoothie with 1 banana, 1 tbsp almond butter, 2 tbsp PB2, 1 cup almond milk and 1 tbsp spirulina. Additionally, I had my multi-vitamin and my B12 supplement. 

Lunch (around 11:30): Tempeh chili (tomato juice, tomatoes + jalapenos, tempeh, black beans and vegan mozzarella cheese).

Dinner (around 3:30): Spinach salad (Spinach, chickpeas, brussel sprouts, sweet potato, quinoa with about a 1 tbsp of honey mustard).

All in all I ate perfectly at my calorie, fiber and protein goals. Could it have been timing? Actual food choices, etc. HELP ME PLS.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horrible Gym Workout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 03:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, cross posted to r/vegan and r/veganfitness so if you see this both places don't kill me pls.

I recently made the switch to a vegan diet and everything was running perfectly fine. Been feeling great, killing it in the gym, etc. I'm a 6 foot tall male weighing in at 240. I've obviously been eating at a calorie deficit to lose weight. My gym routine is MWF cardio, TR strength/body training with a trainer. I've been doing great but tonight, something went wrong. I felt drained, lethargic and just terrible. My workout showed also, it was terrible. Worst night I've had in the gym for awhile. 

The night before I slept a solid 8 hours so that's obviously not the case. Therefore, I looked to my diet. Could you all look over it and see if that's what it could have been? My workout began at 5:30pm and the following is my meals throughout the day:

Breakfast (around 6:30): smoothie with 1 banana, 1 tbsp almond butter, 2 tbsp PB2, 1 cup almond milk and 1 tbsp spirulina. Additionally, I had my multi-vitamin and my B12 supplement. 

Lunch (around 11:30): Tempeh chili (tomato juice, tomatoes + jalapenos, tempeh, black beans and vegan mozzarella cheese).

Dinner (around 3:30): Spinach salad (Spinach, chickpeas, brussel sprouts, sweet potato, quinoa with about a 1 tbsp of honey mustard).

All in all I ate perfectly at my calorie, fiber and protein goals. Could it have been timing? Actual food choices, etc. HELP ME PLS.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey /u/BluLavender! I began my weight loss journey about a year and a half ago and this sub has been so incredibly useful. Check out the FAQ for some tips and tricks, read it all the way there is TONS of great info in there.

I started with the low-carb diet and instantly had great results. The health effects of a keto diet are pretty up for debate but from a weight loss standpoint it's a good gig to start on. 

If you ever need some accountability or just someone to chat with, message me up. I'm extremely passionate about weight loss/fitness so you will never bother me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 19:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey /u/spacebrain20! I recently made the vegan switch a little under two weeks ago. I'm loving my new life and the weight is falling off quicker than it was when I was an omni. If you ever need any advice, recipes or just some encouragement, message me away! You'll never bother me talking about a vegan diet.

As so many others have mentioned, /r/vegan + /r/veganfitness are also great resources!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Vegan and Loving It! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 16:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transitioned to a full plant based diet shortly after reading a few books (Meat is for Pussies/Finding Ultra) and watching a few documentaries (Forks Over Knives, Cowspiracy, Earthlings.) In the beginning I was concerned as I was in the middle of a drastic weight loss/fitness plan and working out heavily in the gym. I've never been happier. I feel lighter, my workouts are 10x better than before, my recovery time is amazing and best of all, I'm losing weight at a faster clip than before. I feel more at peace somehow spiritually and am seemingly happier. It's all starting to mesh and I'm just overwhelmed with happiness. 

I browse this subreddit every day looking for new recipes, advice, motivation, etc. I can't say thank you enough to all of you! Keep fighting the good fight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 15:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES. I always take a peek at my new bones when I walk past the mirror. Awesome work. As people have said though, bump up those calories broslice. I was in the same general area you are (SW 331, CW 243, GW 190) and I ate consistently at 1,500 calories at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 18:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rumors by Fleetwood Mac. Hands down one of the best written albums of all time. The emotional turmoil and circumstances surrounding the members during that album will never be recreated again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 15:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegan diet. I'm not one to ever bring it up in a public setting/Reddit because I hate the conversation surrounding it. People instantly get defensive and see me as preachy, which I really, really try to avoid. While there are vegans that are your typically preachy whiny types, there are a few outliers of us that aren't. However, people are so quick to jump on the judgment train on here. If I don't judge your diet choice, don't judge mine you fucktwat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been slowly adding carbs back into my diet and still am losing weight so I think my fear has began to pass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
