<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4125</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 14:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to open-access [research article](https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e15175).

[Abstract](http://dx.doi.org/10.7554/eLife.15175.001):
We determined whether the mutations found in ovarian cancers could be identified in the patients' ovarian cyst fluids. Tumor-specific mutations were detectable in the cyst fluids of 19 of 23 (83%) borderline tumors, 10 of 13 (77%) type I cancers, and 18 of 18 (100%) type II cancers. In contrast, no mutations were found in the cyst fluids of 18 patients with benign tumors or non-neoplastic cysts. Though large, prospective studies are needed to demonstrate the safety and clinical utility of this approach, our results suggest that the genetic evaluation of cyst fluids might be able to inform the management of the large number of women with these lesions.

[eLife digest](https://elifesciences.org/lookup/doi/10.7554/eLife.15175.002)
More than a third of women develop ovarian cysts during their lifetimes. The vast majority of these cysts are harmless, but a small number are caused by ovarian cancers. These cancers often produce no symptoms until the disease has spread throughout the abdomen or to other organs, so many women go undiagnosed until their chances of being successfully treated are low. Currently, there is no reliable way to determine whether an ovarian cyst is cancerous without performing surgery. As a result, many women undergo unnecessary, invasive surgeries for harmless ovarian cysts.

Tumors shed cells and cell fragments into any fluid that surrounds them. Fluids from cysts in the pancreas, kidney, and thyroid are routinely examined to identify whether they contain cancerous cells. Now, Wang, Sundfeldt et al. show that ovarian cancers also shed DNA into the surrounding cyst fluid. Furthermore, mutations found in this DNA can provide valuable information about whether the cysts are cancerous.

The study was performed by extracting DNA from the fluid in ovarian cysts that had been surgically removed from 77 women. Of these cysts, 10 were harmless cysts, 12 were benign tumors, 31 were invasive cancers, and 24 were so-called borderline tumors, which fall somewhere between the benign tumors and invasive cancers. Only cysts associated with the borderline tumors and invasive cancers need to be surgically removed. Here, Wang, Sundfeldt et al. report that DNA mutations that are characteristic of ovarian cancers were found in 87% of the cysts associated with borderline tumors and invasive cancers. In contrast, these mutations were not found in any of the cysts that do not require surgery.

Fluid can be extracted from an ovarian cyst with a needle during an outpatient visit. Therefore, the results presented by Wang, Sundfeldt et al. suggest a relatively straightforward way of testing the DNA from ovarian cysts before deciding whether surgery is really necessary. First, however, larger studies that follow women with cysts over time will be necessary to confirm that this type of testing is effective and safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DNA test could avoid unnecessary surgery for ovarian cysts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 14:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 13:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Abstract](http://dx.doi.org/10.7554/eLife.15691.001)
Study design: Previous works suggested that neutralizing intratumoral lactic acidosis combined with glucose deprivation may deliver an effective approach to control tumor. We did a pilot clinical investigation, including a nonrandomized (57 patients with large HCC) and a randomized controlled (20 patients with large HCC) studies. Methods: The patients were treated with transarterial chemoembolization (TACE) with or without bicarbonate local infusion into tumor. Results: In the nonrandomized controlled study, geometric mean of viable tumor residues (VTR) in TACE with bicarbonate was 6.4-fold lower than that in TACE without bicarbonate (7.1% [95% CI: 4.6%10.9%] vs 45.6% [28.9%72.0%]; p0.0001). This difference was recapitulated by a subsequent randomized controlled study. TACE combined with bicarbonate yielded a 100% objective response rate (ORR), whereas the ORR treated with TACE alone was 44.4% (nonrandomized) and 63.6% (randomized). The survival data suggested that bicarbonate may bring survival benefit. Conclusion: Bicarbonate markedly enhances the anticancer activity of TACE.

Clinical trail registration: ChiCTR-IOR-14005319.

[eLife digest](http://dx.doi.org/10.7554/eLife.15691.002)
Surgery is the main treatment for liver cancer, but the most common liver cancer  called hepatocellular carcinoma  can sometimes become too large to remove safely. An alternative option to kill the tumor is to block its blood supply via a process called embolization. This procedure deprives the tumor cells of oxygen and nutrients such as glucose. However, embolization also prevents a chemical called lactic acid  which is commonly found around tumors  from being removed. Lactic acid actually helps to protect cancer cells and also aids the growth of new blood vessels, and so the trapped lactic acid may reduce the anticancer activity of embolization.

Previous works suggested that neutralizing the acidic environment in a tumor while depriving it of glucose via embolization could become a new treatment option for cancer patients. Chao et al. now report a small clinical trial that tested this idea and involved patients with large hepatocellular carcinomas. First, a group of thirty patients received the embolization treatment together with an injection of bicarbonate  a basic compound used to neutralize the lactic acid  that was delivered directly to the tumor. The neutralization killed these large tumors more effectively than what is typically seen in patients who just undergo embolization

Chao et al. then recruited another twenty patients and randomly assigned them to receive either just the embolization or the embolization with bicarbonate treatment. This randomized trial showed that the tumors died more and patients survived for longer if they received the bicarbonate together with the embolization treatment compared to those patients that were only embolized. In fact, four patients initially assigned to, and treated in, the embolization-only group subsequently asked to cross over to, and indeed received, the bicarbonate treatment as well.

These data indicate that this bicarbonate therapy may indeed be effective for patients with large tumors that are not amenable to surgery. In future, larger clinical trials will need to be carried out to verify these initial findings.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 13:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to open-access [research article](https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e15691) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Small clinical trial finds injecting sodium bicarbonate into the blood vessels that supply tumors shows promise to improve treatments for liver cancer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 13:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the science behind the headlines, here is a link to the research article. It's open-access and so free to read. https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e17092 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to the open-access [research article](https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e17092) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
