<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3268</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 19:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urgh. Even the face of AFB makes me angry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-04 19:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I DONT CARE IF ITS FUCKING NEW JERSEY OR FUCKING NEW YORK. BITCH ABOUT THE FUCKING PHOTO AND NOT THE FUCKING LOCATION YOU PUSSY ASS FUCKS!](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-HdKUCQSt0Mg/TlMYA9vjJZI/AAAAAAAAAgI/IXObGIc2N2U/s1600/rage_face.jpg)

Edit: I accidentally didn't give a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 13:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stability over happiness? Staying with someone because they would be upset if you left isn't a reason to stay with someone. You would probably have a few years of ruined relationships, but then you could meet someone wonderful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 13:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't see the meme catching on tbh :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 13:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Grandfather died at Burma. Fifteen years later, my grandmother only found out he was definitely dead when his dog tag was found with a metal detector, and the guy who found it made it his mission to track any relatives down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 13:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cannot. Unsee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 13:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could just hit Ctrl F and search for keywords such as ''OP is a faggot' etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 13:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If GGG was a redditor, reddit would be a much nicer place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 13:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 6'1 and my ''fat'' weight is around 13 stone, which on a short person would make them look like a sausage. My ''skinny'' weight was when I was about 8.5 stone and I looked like death. Currently I am about 11 stone and happy with my weight.

Edit: Pteranod stop downvoting other people's posts. Everyone else went to 0 and you stayed at 1. Upvoted everyone back to 1 and you back to 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-03 13:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Motherlovin Christ man. How can you keep all that locked away? Is it not eating you alive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-01 11:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I seem to have a boatload of downvotes for what I thought was an OK comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-31 13:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. I would probably start getting really would up when no one upvoted my comments or replied to them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 19:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave it with me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-21 19:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indubitably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-18 11:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know why this is being downvoted, I quite like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-17 12:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this gets deleted, the OP basically nearly fucked one of these water filled vagoos before being called a fag by someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Error: Post not submitted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-16 23:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-16 22:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like pickles on my samch too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
