<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9958</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And as intended is a buff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get over yourself. Just because something is bugged doesn't mean fixing it doesn't count as a buff. If you have a character that's shitting on everyone, and isn't even as good as it can be because of a bug, that bug fix is a fucking buff. 

Yes, I said it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breh... I love you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never understood balancing around the best players either. Look what happened to StarCraft 2. It's so catered to the professional scene it makes the barrier of entry immense and therefore the game is dead outside of competition play for the most part.

I'm sure Ubisoft will not only cater to high level players since frankly that makes up but a small fraction of the player base. They need to cater to the average player, the casual player, and not the "pro" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 19:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a conqueror main that doesn't play turtly. I was just wondering what assasins do now to open up opponents that refuse to engage whatsoever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because everyone hates us and therefore attack and defend us before ever attacking each other. Idk why us weebs get so much hate honestly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's one of the best games in a long time. All my friends are hooked and so am I. Friends that rarely ever stick to a game for more than 10-15 hours are pushing 80 hours. It's truly a unique and fun experience. Ignore all the complaints, it's mostly ppl that can't be satisfied and have a hard time just having fun. Buy it. You won't regret it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the conq specifically just used him as an example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ferl Out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One does not simply transition into a conqueror. It is a process that requires true dedication and patience. give yourself to the conq completely and only then will your hips thrust like they never have before. 

But these hip thrusts must be earned. I say begin with daily meditation of 2 hours. Once you are able to clear your mind and unlearn what you have learned will I give you the next step.

Oh, and stretch daily, your hips aren't ready for the thrusting ahead of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but I'm also saying even if I feint and you go for a parry if you just hold the heavy it makes your parry safe. Because if I didn't feint then you parry, and if I did feint all you did was charge a heavy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this change probably doesn't affect high level players but turns the majority of players into defensive turtles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't really feint a conqueror because they just charge their heavy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New GB change question as (Enter non shield class here) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been leveling my orochi lately and after the update I noticed a big problem. Hopefully some of you can enlighten me, but as an orochi fighting let's say, a conqueror. What do I do to open them up if all they do is block and wait for me to attack?

It used to be before I would GB them for an over head heavy into a ZA for hard damage. But now if I GB they CGB and if I don't attack they don't either. This leaves us in a stand still of no one wanting to attack. 

As an orochi with the new GB implementation how in the hell do you open up someone that goes 100% defensive on you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes this has to be the worst suggestion ever. No one read it. It cannot be unread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you. PK need to be more like you. because when facing they only do all sides and it becomes a thing of not wanting to go further because then you're dead and not becoming anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is at first they knew it was issue but lately there's so much net lag and waiting that it becomes not even worth a try to go until the end and then it's over so why do it? The LA of the PK is from all sides of you and when you try for reactions you get broken and what makes it more is they made her even more strength </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is at first they knew it was issue but lately there's so much net lag and waiting that it becomes not even worth a try to go until the end and then it's over so why do it? The LA of the PK is from all sides of you and when you try for reactions you get broken and what makes it more is they made her even more strength </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was useful at the beginning but with completion and networking that issued it has been such a bad that I just can't anymore and you should either because right now is so broken that you should just not even try to go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just don't be a knob and the problem solving is completion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same that's the worst lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posts like this make me glad I don't have many connection issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post of the year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. You just are, a knob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter much because if the shitters aren't happpy and leave well there goes your games support  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a dishonorable knob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're still a knob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dishonorable knob. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes for the most part you're right. It's a moba mostly and most complaints are unwarranted. Game is fucking amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It did mention it in the patch notes. Just not directly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the players at higher levels are significantly fewer than those who are not so in the end of the day why go based off of the top 10% when the game is being driven forward by the other 90%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a nerf it was a bug fix which is why they didn't specifically mention it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. They won't be needing anything. Just turn it off so the "pros" can play in a bland mode while everyone else can have fun in the regular mode. Easy fix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diamond and up, even more so why the casual player will be heard over the "pro". This isn't counter strike lol right now the player base size is the most important thing to keep this game alive and if they punish the majority by making it harder to win then it's a huge mistake. Which is why gear will stay so will revenge and why they made GB easier. C'mon man you know in right lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facts are just facts man. Sorry to break it to ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Which is the majority of the player base. Just like Blizzard implemented a new method to decay your rank but it only affects platinum players and up, which is only 10 - 15% of the player base. 

Changes will benefit me over you any time because I make up the majority of the player base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this legit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say I want to win games I don't deserve because I spent money or grinded more though.

Those wins are deserved and the rest is irrelevant. If I beat you I beat and it's deserved. If you can't hang with my main and his gear that's not my problem it's a regular and fun part of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree since that's not what I said but what you said. So I guess you think you're retarded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not taking it out of context. You are molding two different statements into one to fit your bias which is actually kind of funny. Just refer to the wall of text I copied from the article YOU linked and there is your answer. Not sure if you'll take the time to read it though since it doesn't align with your stance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They mention that it works well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then followed it up with:

Roman Campos Oriola:I personally think Revenge is completely mandatory in a group fight scenario. The issue you're facing in group fight scenarios is that you're getting overwhelmed and constantly interrupted. So you need a tool to be able to make the difference.

The goal behind the Revenge is if you're able to survive a little bit, then you will have a tool that will allow you to make a difference - but only for a short period of time. You need to time well your activation, and have a clear strategy for how you're going to use it, because you get that chance and after it's over.

In a group fight scenario it works well, and today when we look at the data about kill/death ratio in group situations, we are in a spot that I think is interesting. When you're against two players, one time out of three you can survive. When you're against three players, it's one out of five on average.

The tough part has always been to find the balance where when you're ganking someone, you need to feel that you're going to kill him, and it's not bullshit because you're actually two on one, or three on one. And when you're that person, you should always see the light at the end of the tunnel, like, yeah, maybe I can take one or two with me. Maybe sometimes - rarely - I can actually win. I think Revenge serves that purpose well.

In Duel it's an interesting debate that we had internally. Personally, I like Revenge in Duel. Why? Because Revenge is a little bit like the Ultra in Street Fighter. It's an event that happens at some point toward the end of the fight. It does not happen every time. But it completely changes the mind games at that moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice he said revenge is working as intended which is great news. He even likes how it works in a 1v1 scenario. Besides bug fixes looks like revenge isn't gonna change much if at all. Great news! Thanks for linking article gave me peace of mind since I love revenge and would hate for it to change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happen to have a link? I'd like to check out this interview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah the feat was thinking gear. That feat should be looked at then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate 1v1 and 2v2. But I don't say we should add gear stats and feats to those because I recognize there's an audience for that style of play. But don't touch my precious Dominion please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not nerf revenge because it's awesome. Plenty still play Dominion trust me that's all I play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
