<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5238</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Great Wall is a lot better than its critics are saying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whether it's Star Wars, politicians, or models, every sub on Reddit is trying to sell me something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Great Wall.

TGW's situation reminds me a lot of Edge of Tomorrow in that it got a lot of initial hate but the movie itself is pretty darn good. Reading the comments on Reddit, I went in expecting Dragon Blade or Warcraft quality but it was much better.

The first few moments I was apprehensive. There was a short chase we'd all seen before, then some fireplace banter, and the make or break moment where the Matt Damon and Pedro "Oberyon" Pascal first meet the Chinese at the Great Wall. It could've gone really cheesy and nationalistic but it didn't and soon we were just watching the story about a mercenary and his friend happening upon a crazy situation.

There were many things it did right and I'll jot each one down.

The relationship between Matt and Pedro was the highlight for me. Like Edge of Tomorrow, it's a shame the commercials didn't feature more of the banter between them because we were laughing each time they were together. Pedro defintely has a future in action comedies and Matt Damon's accent could pass as Brad Pitt's brother in Snatch.  Also, for a blockbuster, the characters were well defined and rich with conflict.

The visuals were absolutely amazing. Someone compared it to watching the opening ceremony of the Beijing Olympics and it's a good comparison. You'll get to see the Great Wall, inventive battles on it, the monster cgi was actually not distracting and look better than World War Z's zombies, the costumes are gorgeous and the colors help to organize the different groups of soldiers. Please don't watch it online because its visuals are such eyecandy.

For anyone worried about Chinese propaganda, the message of the movie is cooperation and trust over greed. There are both bad and good Western and Chinese characters. I never got the sense they were good or bad because of where they were from but because of who they were. Both Western and Chinese characters kicked major ass and equally saved the day. If scenes of Chinese people kicking monster ass unsettles you, then it's just you.

The marrying of Western and Chinese elements were really well done. We got a tight Western structure and the most Chinese things invariably were the dressings on it. So there's really sweet archery from Matt Damon and kung fu and Chinese battle tactics, Lord of the Rings-type pacing and suspense and monsters and a Chinese Forbidden City-like capital. My favorite scene was the singing and lantern scene because it was very Chinese and appreciated the filmmakers respecting us enough not to cut it.

I'm a big Hong Kong cinema fan so seeing Matt Damon and Andy Lau together was awesome (they starred in their respective versions of Infernal Affairs).

So those are my two cents on TGW. It's a fun quality blockbuster that I wholeheartedly recommend.  Grade: A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TGW's situation reminds me a lot of Edge of Tomorrow in that it got a lot of initial hate but the movie itself is pretty darn good. Reading the comments on Reddit, I went in expecting Dragon Blade or Warcraft quality but it was much better.

The first few moments I was apprehensive. There was a short chase we'd all seen before, then some fireplace banter, and the make or break moment where the Matt Damon and Pedro "Oberyon" Pascal first meet the Chinese at the Great Wall. It could've gone really cheesy and nationalistic but it didn't and soon we were just watching the story about a mercenary and his friend happening upon a crazy situation.

There were many things it did right and I'll jot each one down.

The relationship between Matt and Pedro was the highlight for me. Like Edge of Tomorrow, it's a shame the commercials didn't feature more of the banter between them because we were laughing each time they were together.  Pedro Pascal definitely has a future in action comedies and Matt Damon's accent could pass as Brad Pitt's brother in Snatch.  Also, for a blockbuster, the characters were well defined and rich with conflict.

The visuals were absolutely amazing. Someone compared it to watching the opening ceremony of the Beijing Olympics and it's a good comparison. You'll get to see the Great Wall, inventive battles on it, the monster cgi was actually not distracting and look better tha World War Z's zombie, the costumes are gorgeous and the colors help to organize the different groups of soldiers. Please don't watch it online because its visuals are such eyecandy.

For anyone worried about Chinese propaganda, the message of the movie is cooperation and trust over greed. There are both bad and good Western and Chinese characters. I never got the sense they were good or bad because of where they were from but because of who they were. Both Western and Chinese characters kicked major ass and equally saved the day. If scenes of Chinese people kicking monster ass unsettles you, then it's just you.

The marrying of Western and Chinese elements were really well done. We got a tight Western structure and the most Chinese things invariably were the dressings on it. So there's really sweet archery from Matt Damon and kung fu and Chinese battle tactics, Lord of the Rings-type pacing and suspense and monsters and a Chinese Forbidden City-like capital. My favorite scene was the singing and lantern scene because it was very Chinese and appreciated the filmmakers respecting us enough not to cut it.

I'm a big Hong Kong cinema fan so seeing Matt Damon and Andy Lau together was awesome (they starred in their respective versions of Infernal Affairs).

So those are my two cents on TGW. It's a fun quality blockbuster that I wholeheartedly recommend.  Grade: A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TGW's situation reminds me a lot of Edge of Tomorrow in that it got a lot of initial hate but the movie itself is pretty darn good. Reading the comments on Reddit, I went in expecting Dragon Blade or Warcraft quality but it was much better.

The first few moments I was apprehensive. There was a short chase we'd all seen before, then some fireplace banter, and the make or break moment where the Matt Damon and Pedro "Oberyon" Pascal first meet the Chinese at the Great Wall. It could've gone really cheesy and nationalistic but it didn't and soon we were just watching the story about a mercenary and his friend happening upon a crazy situation.

There were many things it did right and I'll jot each one down.

The relationship between Matt and Pedro was the highlight for me. Like Edge of Tomorrow, it's a shame the commercials didn't feature more of the banter between them because we were laughing each time they were together. Pedro Pascal definitely has a future in action comedies and Matt Damon's accent could pass as Brad Pitt's brother in Snatch.  Also, for a blockbuster, the characters were well defined and rich with conflict.

The visuals were absolutely amazing. Someone compared it to watching the opening ceremony of the Beijing Olympics and it's a good comparison. You'll get to see the Great Wall, inventive battles on it, the monster cgi was actually not distracting and look better than World War Z's zombies, the costumes are gorgeous and the colors help to organize the different groups of soldiers. Please don't watch it online because its visuals are such eyecandy.

For anyone worried about Chinese propaganda, the message of the movie is cooperation and trust over greed. There are both bad and good Western and Chinese characters. I never got the sense they were good or bad because of where they were from but because of who they were. Both Western and Chinese characters kicked major ass and equally saved the day. If scenes of Chinese people kicking monster ass unsettles you, then it's just you.

The marrying of Western and Chinese elements were really well done. We got a tight Western structure and the most Chinese things invariably were the dressings on it. So there's really sweet archery from Matt Damon and kung fu and Chinese battle tactics, Lord of the Rings-type pacing and suspense and monsters and a Chinese Forbidden City-like capital. My favorite scene was the singing and lantern scene because it was very Chinese and appreciated the filmmakers respecting us enough not to cut it.

I'm a big Hong Kong cinema fan so seeing Matt Damon and Andy Lau together was awesome (they starred in their respective versions of Infernal Affairs).

So those are my two cents on TGW. It's a fun quality blockbuster that I wholeheartedly recommend.  Grade: A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good enough for Sherlock Holmes two to rip off its ending </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American movies would never ever add chinese actors just to get more people to watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is why world war z 2 was cancelled.  cant fool an audience twice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mallrats, chasing amy, dogma are all classics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dragon blade was campy and crappy, chinese zodiac is probably the last great jackie film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and hillary had a 98 percent chance of winning  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hero was made by the same director as great wall and is a mainland  china movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Variety's take on Great Wall's performance is much more positive and takes more of a global account of its performance 

http://variety.com/2017/film/news/box-office-lego-batman-great-wall-fist-fight-1201992121/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad idea, too chinese, still will break even.  More co productions will come for the savvy producer who finds the right movie which balances western and chinese elements.  china as a market cannot be ignored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best and worst thing a person of another race has done to you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> media needs to stop reporting his businessmans hyperbole as fake news.  we still remember media and their 98 percent chance of hillary winning against trump and their unethical biased coverage against bernie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the volcano documentary on netflix too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how the heck are you seeing so many movies in theaters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more like a mainland china film than hong kong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> enough to water Africa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how's it different from any american war movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make a site like Reddit that bans shilling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> movie looks like a standard hollywood blockbuster, ill watch it later today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> movie gets repetitive after this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dont like trump but remember dnc leaks of dnc working against bernies campaign and lack of play on it in media, hillarys inevitable victory against bernie and trump, ap announcing before biggest states vote that hillary clinched dem nomination after a secret poll, super delegates factored into calculation giving hillary the edge though they were not supposed to. trumps policies are evil but let's make an informed decision here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 06:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just try saying Star Wars the Force Awakens was a rehash of New Hope and other parts of the original trilogy but with shittier everything on r/starwars and r/movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 04:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dont like trump but remember dnc leaks of dnc working against bernies campaign and lack of play on it in media, hillarys inevitable victory against bernie and trump, ap announcing before biggest states vote that hillary clinched dem nomination after a secret poll, super delegates factored into calculation giving hillary the edge though they were not supposed to. trumps policies are evil but let's make an informed decision here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Posts should have an upvote and downvote history so users can determine if votes are from shills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The John Wick series is overrated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Keanu and appreciate the stunts like that car chase in part two, but it's a generic movie with a bigger budget. The plot is bare bones, the action gets repetitive - shoot, break arms, head shots, get hit but hardly get hurt and looks overly choreographed, there's no depth to the characters beyond a gimmick like the mute girl. There's dozens of Hong Kong and Jason Statham and movies that do the same thing.

Personally I think the disproportionate love it gets is from corporate shills like the ones downvoting this now.

once I added the last comment about shills, suddenly the post gets replies.  hmmm

prove youre not a shill.  what happens in the last scene of the movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly no one liked the star wars the force awakens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shilling should be against the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like mods could mod for free?  still dont know anyone in real life who likes star wars the force awakens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know you grew up poor if you think fast food is safer to eat than fruits and vegetables </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trump is now hitler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thursday Box Office: Great Wall Topples Fist Fight, Cure for Wellness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jurassic world being a good movie is fake news just like star wars the force awakens, seriously.  theyre what happen when you take less talented people and try to make the same movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> john wick 2 was campy and plot was bare bones, so appeal for great wall should crossover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited to see this, critics wouldn't be entertained unless it was high falutin crap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's the dialogue that makes it sound like an accent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kinda annoyed they used another kid like in jack reacher 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best movie theater in Los Angeles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for something comparable to what I found elsewhere: plush leather seats, limited seating, reserved seating.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JJ Abrams is most like Kylo Ren - he's the King of Reboots, but hasn't found his own identity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which hand do guys when peeing hold their penises with? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You didn't try to search like you didn't try to think for yourself  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To start, are you actually asking for proof of dnc rigging which has been widely covered by every major media outlet?  Why are you asking for that or has your head been in the sand?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search "bernie" on Reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lotr movies great because it didn't treat source material as too precious, and you probably can't get a job telling the producer that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultimately, bad producers.  They set the vision for writer and director to communicate.  Of course having bad writers and producers don't help either.  It's tough, even some great authors make shitty screenplays and tv writers make cookie cutter screenplays and directors can be shitty storytellers.  If I were a producer I'd find source material I really love and the diamonds in the rough creatives  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keanu and his limited but determined acting is a perfect meta statement on the shallow mindlessness of action movies more than Liam neeson  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movie tentpoles are broadcast TV, independent movies are Cable TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that answers it!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have a ps2, I'd buy a game every few months, rpg and action games, so I'm looking for a similar experience with a new console but it seems so complicated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was rigged by dnc and media and as much as I hate trump we won't forget that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I wanted to get back into console gaming, how would I generally buy games, I hear about Steam and downloading through the console? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Altright are too stupid to know they're actually democrats  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's between my dysfunctional family and the more dysfunctional ones down the street, I'm choosing mine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conservatives stand for oil and one percent, only things they try to conserve  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deport! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet Russia wins if globe warms more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picking a war of words with a writer is almost as idiotic as picking one with a comedian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now you've offended vegans, great job or what was one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> obviously a gold digger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if that's how you get someone to laugh, you are scum and deserve what you got.  think about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> avatar was a must see for the technology but I cant see any reason to see the sequel much less four of them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Studio movies are broadcast tv and independent movies are cable tv </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> take the money, leave the agent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's okay but didnt blow me away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no thanks, female trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> watch contact if you want to see the movie arrival ripped off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> twd jumped the shark, no thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you sound like a gaslighter with an agenda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 02:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's on the front page, the gang shooting, do I have to lead you by the hand or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> added </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you want to see why Trump won, just read the comments section on The Eastsider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 00:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially any articles on gentrification and gangs.
https://www.theeastsiderla.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 06:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so that's what hand rape looks like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great way to get the rich donors to turn to repubs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can we give them the cows back so we never have to hear this story again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought he was Italian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's been accepting daily mail as a reliable source? fuck me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed.  it's human nature to laugh at something incongruous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 23:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no one can replicate wong kar wai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> enough pictures already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did everyone already forget bc of this season's media machine that steph choked on every game that mattered in the finals last year?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we created war on arabs and now we think theyre the bad guys, wtf  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you ever hear of The Tragedy of George Lucas the Father of Star Wars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 00:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> be george lucas

make star fucking wars

spearhead creation of indiana jones franchise

create ilm thats done cgi for every big tentpole like jurassic park

inspired james fucking cameron to get into movies

give fans up close look of how star wars was made because you want to share, knowledge they will later use against you because they have no fucking clue how collaborative movie and tv industry is, and later what an exec producer does

decide to fix a few things always wrong with ot, most good which goes unnoticed, some you prob should have left alone, but hey those fans will still have the originals 

but at this point no one says no because youre george fucking lucas 

decide to finally give fans what they want and creates the prequels

no one says no when you decide to push boundaries of film again and film mostly with green screen (though no one remembers you still used a shit ton of practical effects and sets and models).

no one says no when you create jar jar

no one says no when you go for a cinematagraphic look that is too clean which makes the cgi more sterile (though thematically makes sense, light to ot's dark)

but you got bombass music from john williams for ot

and ewan mcgregor as obi wan and liam neeson as qui gon and sam jackson with a purple lightsaber

and a story that parallels nazi Germany's rise

and does the exposition work needed for ot to make sense

also sweetass worlds like the wookies'

fanboys revolt and say you ruined their childhood, bully jake lloyd into mental illness

you get fed up with fanboys but still want them see your life's work continue and sell it to Disney

they reject most of your story ideas which is fine but instead rehash new hope which is opposite of what new hope was, intended to break new ground

you see fanboys love the rehash and start even comparing it to the ot

you see another director like peter jackson fuck up but not get nearly enough same hate

a minority of lucas fans know what you did, that midichlorians are just identifiers of a force sensitive person, not the source

but majority hate you

despite james fucking cameron, who has now internalized the star wars mantra of show them something new, coming to your defense and calling tfa a "reentrenchment"

fans become as emotional and ugly and controlling like the sith despite what you tried to teach them in the movies 

even make a sub on reddit hating on the prequels though with an undercurrent of love 

you have no idea why your work has suddenly become so unpopular

because you were george fucking lucas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> be george lucas

make star fucking wars

spearhead creation of indiana jones franchise 

create ilm thats done cgi for every big tentpole like jurassic park

inspired james fucking cameron to get into movies

give fans up close look of how star wars was made because you want to share, knowledge they will later use against you because they have no fucking clue how collaborative movie and tv industry is

decide to fix a few things always wrong with ot, most good which goes unnoticed, some you prob should have left alone, but hey those fans will still have the originals 

but at this point no one says no because youre george fucking lucas 

decide to finally give fans what they want and creates the prequels

no one says no when you decide to push boundaries of film again and film mostly with green screen (though no one remembers you still used a shit ton of practical effects and sets and models).

no one says no when you create jar jar

no one says no when you go for a cinematagraphic look that is too clean which makes the cgi more sterile (though thematically makes sense, light to ot's dark)

but you got bombass music from john williams for ot

and ewan mcgregor as obi wan and liam neeson as qui gon

and a story that parallels nazi Germany's rise

and does the exposition work needed for ot to make sense

also sweetass worlds like the wookies'

fanboys revolt and say you ruined their childhood, bully jake lloyd into mental illness

you get fed up with fanboys but still want them see your life's work continue and sell it to Disney

they reject most of your story ideas and instead rehash new hope which is opposite of what new hope was, intended to break new ground

you see fanboys love the rehash and start even comparing it to the ot

you see another director like peter jackson fuck up but not get nearly enouh same hate

a minority of lucas fans know what you did, and shit like midichlorians are just a sign of the force, not the force itself

but majority hate you

fans become as emotional and ugly and controlling like the sith despite what you tried to teach them in the movies 

you have no idea why your work has suddenly become so unpopular

because you were george fucking lucas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the problem is extreme media bias that forces people to turn to fake news  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There's a petition to get George Lucas to direct another Star Wars movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There exists a transcript of the conversation between George Lucas, Steven Spielberg, and Lawrence Kasdan where they come up with the story for Indiana Jones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has The Walking Dead become "torture porn?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gotta make that cheddar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and also boring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fans Petition for George Lucas to Replace Colin Trevorrow on Star Wars 9 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 17:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf this sub exists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where do you live </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> very close to being that inbred girl from iasip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this series was so overrated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 16:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol sounds like he said "im an uber driver" like it meant something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Lucas created Star Wars and Indiana Jones to be modern versions of movie serials from the 1930s and 1940s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played it today, this hate and claim of doom is only you and some others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this scene was cringeworthy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> white house down was so underrated, bad luck it came after olympus has fallen and cannibalized business </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early Wong kar wai movies are my favorite movies of all time.  This guy captures some of what it feels like but perhaps the best example for western audiences to relate is the scene from star wars a new hope when Luke looks at the two Suns and you get his sense for longing for a romantic adventure and existential validation and fulfillment as the music swells  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, many of my favorite comic stories are the ones in between the mayhem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 17:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it didn't have the name star wars attached, people would call it what it is, a generic action movie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we have enough potential neurosurgeons further down the ladder or in a few lower ranked medical schools or one inner city, who could succeed if resources were directed to them, our own moon shot, not saying foreigners shouldnt work here though, saying the resources available for both are unbalanced </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we'll be pretty great regardless while giving one more american a job and increasing their pay and like I said the American can become the best by training from another american </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> let me make it simple for you, American gets job over foreigner, if no american available, train one up from previous rung on neurosurgeon ladder  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you dont have to tip if service is bad, but ten to twelve percent is reasonable if it's good, dont listen to the others, they're either rich or waiters  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 08:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I volunteer as tribute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> americans should compete with americans, nothing a foreigner can do that an american cant or can't learn to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AP is fake news, ill stick with reuters...for now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> critics read tea leaves, what determines quality are audiences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and what about the neurosurgeon that now has to compete with a foreigner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Signing up to drive for Lyft and Uber is like the gold rush but for minimum wage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 07:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> argo was most overrated oscar winner ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what do brits think of boba? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol yes will correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch all the boys love Mandy lane, there's a reason why she was picked for that role 

I hope people are upvoting because they actually saw the movie because it's not just a "shes hot" statement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With five dollars, what is one thing you'd buy and one thing you wouldn't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 03:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ban any news sources from undemocratic countries on Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: if your male cat has a urinary infection and he's humping things even if neutered, try washing the thing he's been humping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our cat got a uti and was peeing blood, two rounds of antibiotics helped, cleaned litter, gave it more wet food, but it came back.  But then we tried cleaning his stuffed animal and it cleared up right away  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Get a fire extinguisher, you never know when you need it. I had to put out a fire outside that my neighbor started with a cigarette and another that my cat started by turning on the stove </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 20:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One station offers it for free by just pushing a button, another I've asked the attendant and it was free, this one wasn't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks Reddit, read on here gas stations must give free air and got into argument with gas station attendant after he said I had to buy gas first, like the law also says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 18:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 07:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't care about NASCAR but this movie was awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 06:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dragonballs are made out of weed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only thing bj beating up now is his legacy, plz stop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd rather talk to strangers on Reddit than in real life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 05:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's like digg but uglier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This sub is as if a million voices who watched the prequels finally got old enough to cry out on Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know shit about war but I will take the high ground </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 01:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> think of women as the missing piece in life, not the puzzle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> title sounds like a setup for a michael joke  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's just gonna rip off the other star wars movies like tfa, I guarantee it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love that jk grew up poor, you make it from that background and you develop empathy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good sites to find licensed contractors for small home repairs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seems like all of Florida is on meth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it me or does he seem like one step away from bennifer again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly lyft drivers are less shady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 01:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is a stupid common sense tip.  what the fuck happened to this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol this is why he lost to conor, his boxing skills suck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The prequels have gotten more popular because the generation that grew up on them are finally on Reddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the guys behind them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's more manly is being the guy in charge and never having to pick up a gun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So does this sub love the prequels more than The Force Awakens? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 00:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> toby wouldn't be welcome in any country.  yeah I have no idea why I hate him either but that makes sense in these times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 16:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/getmotivated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 09:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is it me or are flash's villains kinda repetitive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To my Latino neighbors and their friends and family </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> prequels were better than tfa, deadpool tries way too hard like ryan Reynolds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> goat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all reads should be blind  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would blacks trade rap music for never hearing another white person say "nigga (and its ok because you say it)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You either care about grammar on the internet and texts or not at all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 16:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a brit is having a German stand up for him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liberal elites are the same people who decry racism while ghettoizing minorities professionally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 07:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2020 Bumper sticker: I voted for Trump and all I got was a few immigrants out of the country (and lost everything else) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> most times all people need is that first chance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO, GO FOR REPUBLICANS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so true.  gatekeepers and mentors can make or break a career  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 06:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ironic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> stock market is responsible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all reads should be blind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
