<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2737</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The book is like 300 pages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 08:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This annoys me, I read 1984 a couple years ago and I was like, yeah I can see some of that, but now people are going crazy for it,  like it's some brand new thing, and I'm just thinking....No, this stuff has kinda been happening for awhile now. 

But, it is what it is, I better read The Handmaids Tale before the story gets ruined for me by everyone talking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished war and peace a couple weeks ago, it's amazing, skip the second epilogue, but the rest is phenomenal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In that case" he said "death must have come as a blessed relief" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just read an entire novel in one day, Flowers for Algernon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 09:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I've read books in one day before, but smaller things like Heart of Darkness, Yellow Wallpaper, Psycho. But this was my first novel in one day, usually it takes me 2 or 3 days, but I couldn't stop. I wasn't actually intending to read this right now, I just wanted a small book to take with me to the dog park and right away I was sucked in. It flew by and my heat was ripped completely out of my chest by the end of it. I have never felt such sadness, and I think it could be the best book I've ever read, so far.

I just don't know what I could even begin say about the story and what it's done to me, and I feel almost a small guilt that I haven't read it before. 

Whether you know what the story is about or not, read it, just consume it and then step back and take a look at yourself and just think for a bit.

Any thoughts on the story? Anyone read a novel in a day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Psycho really messed with me, the movie is nothing compared to the book.

I'm reading through Psycho right now and it's pretty unsettling, it's short like 120 pages. 

And at home I have The Exorcist which I'm actually pretty terrified to start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also any of the Discworld books should be a quick and light read, I think the top three are

Small Gods

Mort

Guards! Guards! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have them all but haven't made my way through, high fantasy is b kinda tough for me because it can sometimes drag, but if you're looking into it you should probably try some of the newer fantasy books, ASOIAF (game of thrones) or maybe the Mistborn series, I believe those go fairly quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I actually started with the 5th one, In the flesh, I read through all that in a day or so, but when ooh went back and read the first actually story The Book of Blood, it makes everything so much better since it explains the reasons for all the short stories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A question about Elantris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm getting to the halfway point and I was just curious about the chapter breaks, and maybe it's explained later on, but they're the magic symbols right? Also there's an alphabet for the symbols or meanings behind them right? So, do the chapter breaks tell you anything? Is there a hidden message or anything? I know in the chapter where he's learning about the light Aon, that chapter had the same symbol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmmm, I remember the part, but I don't remember exactly why he goes to the island, I want to say that he was told the hunting was amazing there by someone, which I'm sure Dantes told to tell him, but it could also be just by chance, but I don't think it was cause his little steward person is talking about all the goats. I do know everything is explained or at least hinted at as to how everything came to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was me like a year or 2 ago, I needed a change, I quit videogames, quit watching tv and made myself read.I stared slow, now I'm at like a book or two a week, I don't have a tv or at home internet anymore and I don't even miss them.

I started with books I've already seen the movie for, Dracula was the first, that way I had an idea of what was going on. And then slowly gravitated towards things I never saw the movie for 1984, Moby Dick, and then the momentum just kinda takes over, I think once you actually start getting into reading regularly your brain starts comprehending things easier and your imagination becomes more vivid.

So, maybe start with books they made movies out of. I know someone recommend I should try some easier books like Jurassic Park lol and I've yet to get to it, though I do have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have internet at home and cell phone speed is too slow to play lol, but I believe this is where he talks about how he doesn't consider himself a horror writer.

https://youtu.be/l8TkQvdJVbc
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm making my way through Books of Blood right now, I'm reading a couple stories when I need a break from whatever big book I'm reading at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 09:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Stephen king himself said he never identified as a horror writer, but more of a suspense writer. I think most of his stories just have some kind of supernatural element to them. 

That being said his jfk book, 11/23 whatever it is, is supposed to be amazing and I don't think that's an actual horror book, though it's listed as horror because he wrote it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 09:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The horror section of that lists has it down 26% which was much more than any other genre, I think the second highest loss was 15%.

Which just goes to prove my point that horror is not a popular genre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why isn't horror a more popular genre? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 08:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barnes and noble doesn't even have a horror section and half price books usually only has one small area. I think people enjoy reading horror, but maybe not. I have a buddy of mine who writes horror books and he says it's a very niche market. But people enjoy horror movies right? Anyway it was just something I was thinking about, when I go to half price and browse the little horror section I know that even if it's something I haven't heard of, it's still horror. But at the bigger stores it's just mixed with fiction or scifi, and it might make it harder to just come across a new horror book you've never heard of.

Do you think it's a popular genre? Do you have a favorite scary book? Recommendations for authors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm classic literature maybe, I enjoy everything overly detailed and the fact that most of what's actually happening isn't actually shown, it's all layers and the experience of the story comes after it's been indulged as a whole.

Moby Dick

 War and Peace

Count of Monte Cristo

Frankenstein (if it's considered classic literature) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Without spoilers, what's the fastest paced Brandon Sanderson book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started December 1st, so 3 months, but i also read 5 other books in that time.

The philosophy is the actual book book isn't bad, if you wanna read about Napoleon invading Russia then you might get what he's talking about better, it's just the second epilogue I had a problem with, he talks about the way history is written and just kinda beats a dead horse, but the rest of the book is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just didn't like the second epilogue, it came to a point where I was like, I get it, people don't know how to write about history lol. That was my only real complaint </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to it, I can understand it when I read it for the life of me, it's written to read well and in a certain style, I can't do that, I listened to paradise lost on YouTube, and understood it right away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I finally finished War and Peace yesterday, no spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an amazing amazing book. I loved the story, all the characters, well most of them, but I didn't like any if the philosophy, or I should say not all of it.

I will say though my absolute favorite character in the book was Denisov, I thought he was the most decent of everyone, his accent and his little charming self really sold him.

I will also say that the title War and Peace isn't about the war, though the war is in there, it's about the internal struggle the characters are facing during the story.

Now the boring part, well only one really, the second epilogue, I would say, if you going in for the story part of the book, avoid the second epilogue because it has nothing to do with the story and is all philosophy on history.

That being said, I know it's the most talked about book that nobody reads and I cannot understand why, the book was not boring, except for second epilogue, it didn't feel like anything dragged on, and I think Tolstoy captured what being a human and all your errors is all about perfectly, I also feel that there was way too much relatable material in the book that is going on now. 

Who else read this? Did you glisten with joy when you finished? Did you cry? Laugh? Weep? Do you know someone else irl who has read this? Cause I don't lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HG Wells, War of the the worlds, is usually always on top 100 greatest novels of all time lists, along with Dracula and Frankenstein.

Also Dune is highly regarded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I checked Amazon.co.uk the complete set had the picture of what you're talking about, but I can't find anything about that cover, so I have no idea, but I'll be at half price today so if I see any copies of the simple covers I'll try to see if I can figure out what they are and where they're from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this scene from Employee of the Month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this same thing when people say

I'm cute

I'm fun

I'm nerdy

I'm weird

I'm quirky

I'm like really smart

I'm amazing at this thing

I'm this thing or that thing


And I just think...no you're not, because if you have to say you're this thing, you're not.

It's especially bad on dating sites when you see someone say, "I'm just a real cute down to earth funny nerd."  



*Also people who say

I'm the nicest person you'll ever meet, I'm not an asshole

I'm not racist

I'm not homophobic

I'm not gay

I just don't understand why people have to try and justify who they are instead of letting other people figure it out.

** And people who say

I never lie

Trust me

I hate talking about myself

I always get a lot of attention

I don't know why everyone compliments me, like complete strangers just seem to want to come up and tell me something nice all the time

Animals love me, (which is a damn lie because cats are dicks and love no one, they only allow you to be near them)
    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just checked Amazon, hardcover for first book is $10 cheapest :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 03:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I might just go scavenger hunting, I know half price has the hardcovers around 7 bucks each and paperbacks are probably like 3 bucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone bought the complete 1-14 set from Amazon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.amazon.com/Complete-Wheel-Time-Set-1-14/dp/0765376865


Is there anything special about it, or is it just all the books shipped to you? 

I'm debating whether to just pay up front lol or go scavenger hunting at half price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you try this, I made a post about it lol which no one even looked at XD


"Centaur made a top 100 novels of all time list. It deals with the more traditional kind of classic novels, and this website 

http://www.listchallenges.com/centaur-editions-the-100-greatest-novels-of

has all the books and allows you to check off your progress as you go. Anyway I thought I'd share if anyone was looking for one. Also you can find this on Amazon "


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The shining, I really enjoyed it but it wasn't scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm going to buy these books, I enjoy getting collections and going on scavenger hunts at half price, plus I should actually read them at some point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they have deals with the publishers, I know the day Norse Mythology, or whatever that book is called, came out, half price books had them for sale at 20% off, which I'm assuming no-one went out, bought it, and immediately traded it in to half price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discworld series and Books of Blood </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take the small yellow legal pad, I start from the bottom, count 4 lines up and tear horizontally. It's the perfect size, I then write on the little yellow bookmark the day I start reading, and then I'll write the day I'm finished. 

I keep the side that has the date written on it facing towards the book on the opposite page from what I'm reading so when I close the book I remember which side I was on.

For example, reading page 98, I'll have the bookmark on page 99, with the date facing down on page 99, so if I close the book and open later, I see the date is on the page 99 side and then know I was reading page 98.

Yes, it's dumb, but it works.    


http://i.imgur.com/fLZqhuA.jpg

I felt this needed a photo reference
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naaa shinning, the one where the kid attacks ppls legs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 08:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't met one other person irl besides me, who saw this movie, I loved it, and no one I know had ever even heard of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
