<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5802</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pretty crappy spinebuster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't watched it yet cause of these comments, what happens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once had a dream I beat the undertaker in a ring in the middle of a street </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we put this post as an example for the rule "No low effort content" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JUST AS I THOUGHT I DIDNT HAVE TO SEE HIM THIS WEEK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HAVE NEVER BEEN SO HAPPY TO SEE DANA BROOKE IN MY LIFE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IM FUCKING TERRIFIED  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "GET OUT OF MY RING" - Braun Strowman to Sin Cara, **Outside the Ring** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 03:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the brogue kick he just used, and the cloverleaf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 03:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sirens are ambulances in his theme, his gimmick is he's gonna have tape all over  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 02:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deserve what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 02:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stephanie... You need to dial a number before you talk to someone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAMMIT my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best Co-Main Event Of WWE 2016 So Far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 01:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have made the Co-Main Event the match before the main event, so which was the best in your opinion?

Charlotte(c) def Becky Lynch To Retain The WWE Diva's Championship - Royal Rumble 2016

Curtis Axel def R-Truth - Fastlane 2016

Asuka def Bayley(c) For The NXT Women's Championship - NXT Takeover Dallas

The Rock def Erick Rowan - Wrestlemania 32

Charlotte(c) def Natalya For The WWE Women's Championship - Payback 2016

Charlotte(c) def Natalya For The WWE Women's Championship - Extreme Rules 2016

Rusev(c) def Titus O' Neil To Retain The WWE United States Championship - Money In The Bank 2016

Asuka(c) def Nia Jax To Retain The NXT Women's Championship- NXT Takeover The End

John Cena, Enzo Amore and Big Cass def The Club - Battleground 2016

Asuka(c) def Bayley To Retain The NXT Women's Championship - NXT Takeover Brooklyn II

Finn Blor def Seth Rollins For The WWE Universal Championship - Summerslam 2016

Fun Facts: 
8 out of the 11 Co-Main Events were for a Title
6 of those were for a Women's Title
A title only changed once
The Shortest Co-Main Event was The Rock vs Erick Rowan at Wrestlemania 32 at 6 Seconds
The Longest Co-Main Event was Finn Blor vs Seth Rollins at Summerslam 2016 at 19:24
The most appearances are joint between Charlotte and Asuka




 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 00:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's teaching like here in Leeds? I'm considering starting to learn to wrestle, any advice would be helpful for what I need to start </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dean Ambrose vs Chris Jericho at Extreme Rules wasn't too bad, just too long  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curtis Axel Vs R-Truth Fastlane 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 20:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like wrestling with wregret and some whatculture  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 19:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just got [worse](https://imgur.com/a/fG40N)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something Is Broken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 18:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 13:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AJ only went over Cena clean once </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 12:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that tru tv show Adam Ruins Everything is doing an episode about concussions and sports and stuffz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I've already got that one, the box sounded great but from yours I've already got the new day and John Cena shirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I've already got that one, the box sounded great but from yours I've already got the new day and John Cena shirt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny Card On WWE Supercard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 12:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm not sure if many people on this sub still play WWE Supercard but today their new event was announced, the people's champions challenge, basically you pick a superstar and earn points and at the end, depending on your rank you get a certain card, [these are this weeks cards](https://imgur.com/a/t3JUk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thinks it's the last set of superstars they will confirm is in, I think when the game comes out the roster will likely have some of those missing superstars </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aiden English is so pale, it looks like he's permanently got the black and white filter on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they didn't announce everyone in the reveals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maryse isn't looking as good as she usually is, she looks a lot older than last week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #ALL ABOUT THE SUPERSTARS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about those who haven't been announced yet, it's likely that superstars like Batista will be in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Coming from you](https://imgur.com/gallery/CJRMa)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 20:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chris Benoit spoke both French and English fluently if that counts as well as being from Montreal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 13:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xavier Woods was a 90s guy in NXT wasn't he </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 13:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then, now Big E's worked injury makes me cringe more if it was real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> COME ON KO, END THE REIGN OF THE SHIELD AT THE TOP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How you Doin'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 04:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elimination  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 03:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My back hurts watching that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job WWE, make her look even more like she should be doing porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of two reasons I think:
1: Zayn has just come off his feud with Owens
2: They want The New Era represented with one of the call ups and Finns injured, Apollo, Corbin, AA, The Vaudevillians, Mojo Rawley are all on smackdown, Carmella, Bayley, Nia Jax, Alexa Bliss all don't qualify as females and Enzo isn't a great wrestler on his own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 02:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cass is so much better on the mic, it's not sounding like he's a kid learning to read for the first time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #TeamBigCass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking a torture rack position but I hold them up like a gorilla press, then slam them down into a back breaker  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Wrestling Training Session </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my first training session to start my professional wrestling journey is on Thursday, in a gym nearby where I train with El Ligero and JC Thunder. Since there's a few pro wrestlers on this sub, I was wondering if I could get a few tips from some of you for starting out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want a tag team with Roman Reigns and Bo Dallas called Bolieve That </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 00:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a total bitch Brie is, damn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started watching around the end of the ruthless aggression era, honestly I vividly remember Jeff Hardy vs Umaga in a falls count anywhere match  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Football or American Football? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Problem With The Title Picture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone else a little bored with all three shield members always being in the main title picture, it's really boring now, I hope Kevin Owens wins and feuds with Jericho or Zayn or even Cass for that matter, I have nothing against Seth, Roman and Ambrose as wrestlers, I just wanna see something different, thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 14:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either Seth Or Kevin, Rusev distracts Roman, Cass goes psycho on Jericho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 13:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna admit, I'm not as familiar with TNA as stuff like WWE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 06:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a football/soccer fan aswell as wrestling, I don't watch TNA for the same reason I don't watch the MLS, it just feels like a retirement home for great wrestlers, when I think TNA I think, Sting, The Hardys, Bobby Lashley, Hulk Hogan, The Dudley Boyz, the only person that I think of that wasn't in the WWE before TNA is AJ Styles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 06:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only come back to watching since Summerslam last year so I'm gonna have to say Alberto Del Rio, I would love it if I'm wrong and can you recommend some good matches of his </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 06:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I honestly agree fully with you, the guy doesn't care anymore and it pisses me off that he gets booked higher than those with a passion for the business, him going over Ambrose at mania was the stupidest decision they could have made, nobody benefits from Ambrose losing, his matches are boring, other than the 2 matches with undertaker, name one good match that Lesnar has had since then. His matches are so fucking tedious, the mans a beast alright but why should he go over young talent like Ambrose, at least most of Romans matches recently have been entertaining, he needs to either switch up his matches or leave, because the hardcore fans have turned on him and eventually the casual fans will get light of how boring his matches are and they won't like him either. Its such a waste to pair heyman with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 23:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be Back next week, to reclaim the title that's rightly mine, the SAH World Championship, so watch out Bill Money, because I'm coming for my title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something Needs To Be Done </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 16:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was training up some WM singles when a guy appeared on the list, he had 2 wins and 1 loss, I picked him to see how that would work at the tier my deck was at, [this](https://imgur.com/a/HSOfc) was his deck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 15:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, although uninjured, he didn't have a match at last years battleground scheduled and although he was booked in a match at hell in a cell against the Wyatt family, Randy Orton got injured, cancelling that tag match  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 00:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What they should do is tie it to you Account so you get 5 bouts on that account, that's it, not on any other platform or anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 00:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank goodness, I pulled a survivor enhancement and was scared that would reset my counter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 23:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unpopular Opinion:
I don't want a Bullet Club rip off in WWE, 1: we've seen it before in the NWO 2: It would show a complete lack of creativity from creative, I would rather have Balor as the top face on raw, Styles as the top heel on Smackdown, Reigns as the top raw Heel and Ambtose as the top smackdown face, have Gallows and Anderson come into their own as a top tag team, these 4 are some of the best wrestlers of the world so why stick them all together, there's nothing to gain here for all 4 men, plus, knowing WWE, they'll probably just get buried like the nexus then have a new leader like Kevin Owens to try and get them back over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 14:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pulls have changes massively, I've been pulling a lot of epics at survivor plus, where as before I was pulling next to nothing, it's strange </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 14:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... Is he a Face?
He seems like one with the babyface reaction and him pandering to the crowd with the 10 chant.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 14:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think WWE are booking Seth in a losing streak in all these championship matches in an attempt to turn him face, since he's Stephanie's chosen one, him constantly choking in championship matches would make Stephanie turn on him, making him a face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 14:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Santino isn't American but he also isn't Italian, he's from Canada IIRC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 12:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I turned on Lesnar after Wrestlemania 32, he's just boring now, his matches are too formulaic to be anything other than mediocre. His matches are basically:
Suplex, Suplex, Suplex, Suplex, Suplex, Small offence from opponent, Suplex, Suplex, Suplex, F-5, Pin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Real Destined To Do This Forever Feud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roman Reigns vs Rusev:

We start at the 2015 Royal Rumble in which Roman Reigns last eliminated Rusev to win the rumble, they went their separate ways for a while with Rusev feuding with Cena and Dolph, and Roman feuding with Brock, Seth and The Wyatt family, then we come to the November 23rd 2015 Raw in which Rusev attacked Reigns, Joining the League Of Nations, after feuding with Reigns as apart of the League, we get to The 2016 Royal Rumble in which both Reigns and Rusev start the match and Rusev later splashes Reigns through the announce table. After this Rusev takes a step back along with the other members of the League of Nations to Feud with The New Day while Roman feuds with Triple H over the WWE WHC, after Wrestlemania the LON began to fall apart and on the April 28th episode of Smackdown, the group disbanded. Rusev then appeared on the May 2nd episode of Raw, winning a US Title #1 Contenders match by last eliminating Zack Ryder. During this, Roman would feud with AJ Styles. After Rusev won the US title from Kalisto at Extreme Rules. As Rusev retains at MITB against Titus O' Neil and at Battleground against Zack Ryder, Roman drops the Title at MITB, gets suspended and fails to regain it at Battleground, Then on the August 1st episode of Raw, An old rivalry is renewed as Roman attacks Rusev, signalling his chase for the US Title, they feud for a few weeks when at Summerslam, Roman hates Rusev so much over the last year and a half that he snaps and the match is thrown out. I honestly can't wait for the next chapter in this epic rivalry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 03:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 2 Years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're saying goodbye tonight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Complain on the internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I forgot Cena haha, 3 or 4 then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UGHHHHHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3? 4 if you count himself I guess

Edited the numbers, forgot Cena  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DICKS OUT FOR BALOR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC Stardust did the same, his paint was almost gone by the end of the match </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Takeover Spoiler) Injury Confirmed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samoa Joe just tweeted out [this](https://twitter.com/samoajoe/status/767669326501543936) confirming what happened during the match </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was one prediction off perfect, dammit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cool man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 13:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dean almost winning the titles was roadblock IIRC, In my opinion, roadblock was better than Fastlane  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 04:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any guess for joes injury, broken jaw probably, that's all I can think of </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 04:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 minutes out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 03:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful story telling, the passion Bayley has for that championship, she just kept coming back, fantastic match </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 02:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else notice Grims Toy Show in the front row </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not claiming you stole it, don't worry, I was more implying they stole it haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/IDontKnowWhatCardSubjectToChangeMeans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me or does [this](https://twitter.com/wwegames/status/767141374760222720) photo look familier </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summerslam 6 woman tag prediction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 20:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gonna be Tamina returning from her injury, only one that makes sense to me as I think Nikki is gonna be training more for her return first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 18:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with him on Brock, he's really boring now, I feel like the last good match he had was Vs undertaker at hell in a cell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 12:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I saw nothing of the attitude era as I started watching afterwards, I'd be interested if you're looking for hosts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 12:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have to ask you obviously don't get *it* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 04:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MITB Help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 04:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want it to be a shield type situation where first Kofi wins it, then Big E, then finally after coming so close and just losing out, Xavier wins it to a big pop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carmella's intro completions: 0-2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
