<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4772</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 11:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh dang thanks for the heads up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a hiatus from nerf when not many of the new released interested me, and completely missed out on buying a rapidstrike!

Anyone in Aus know if it was stocked on shelves prior to christmas?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was very interested in the worker one to do a sealed longstrike, however I came across a couple comments on reddit while researching that the worker kit is not a 100% air tight breech system. 

I wish I could buy it to find out though, i'd personally go for the artifact kit as it is extremely high quality and well priced... would look dope in a ice retaliator or clear recon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regular cinemagoer on found footage: "How can you stand the shaky cam, I get a headache from it"

Same guy later watches any big budget mediocre action/superhero movie with messy quick cuts: "Wow that was amazing, deadpool was the best movie of 2016"

:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 11:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen much of him, but this goes for everyone... if you can't cement a spot there must be a lack of confidence from the coaching staff that this guy can be a 250 game first grader and worthy of a spot.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 12:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and after his stint he'll come to the broncos on 200k and TPA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 12:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blair witch honestly was not that bad, but not good either.

I'm not too high on the original blair witch, which benefited from the pre widespread internet status of today, otherwise their blair witch was a solid sequel... 

Goodbadflicks did a video on the book of shadows, and I reckon even if done properly people mostly wanted to see a re-tread of the original. Which this one was but was more eventful. 

However as a horror/found footage movie on it's own it's rather forgettable,and yes hopefully they work on their own projects for future movies.

Just wanted to get my opinion out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair enough, I like his videos though... does the best reviews and testing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 23:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same for the rapidstrike? anyone in aus able to pick up a rapidstrike from retailers pre christmas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 10:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so buying that when it comes out in black! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 08:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> drink everytime coop says "i'm 6'3 and have rather large hands"

passes out.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 12:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sequels must be considered canon and watched to get the entire story... then i realized some franchises will never be left to rest in peace despite the what the ending concludes with.


For example:


I only recognize 2 blade movies, trinity never happened!

I only recognize the first 2 terminator movies.

I only recognize alien and aliens, the shitty sequels don't exist!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 04:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also I wanted to add, Watchmojo released their top 10 movies of 2016 video without deadpool in it.... The comments section gave me cancer with the amount of people insisting it was amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 04:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stay away from superhero movies except blade 1 2 which are awesome... I have not watched the dark night trilogy considered the bar for them! I might eventually. But when I found out deadpool was a R i hoped it could be aesthetically similar to kill bill but with a spiderman looking dude that can convert me..... but boy it was just a generic CGI tentpole flick with quick cut action sequences :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deadpool... its just another superhero movie but with naughty language and tons of CGI blood. The rave reviews from fanboys has entirely made me discredit any and all future superhero movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 below </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Torture Porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you end up painting the inside of the shell? if yea how did you go about it?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 06:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wish roth would do that thanksgiving trailer into a movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 07:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for linking me to that.

Oh well, will still patiently wait for a molded pump grip and stock.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone bought the f10555 longshot stock? plz share feedback... 3D printed? also is it creaky? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 06:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 09:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drama - Swiss Army Man

Comedy - Observe And Report

Action - Crank

Sci Fi - The Thing

Suspense/thriller - The Gift

Comic book - Blade 2

Romance - 500 Days Of Summer

Crime - Tokyo Drift

War - Inglorious Basterds

Horror - Hostel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 09:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely hated the ending of "under the shadows"... the protagonist literally found out what to do to be left alone by the entity, yet drives off anyway where the entire movie will happen all over again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 13:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you can put your weed in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triple 9 - Was also one of the worst movies of it's year considering all it had going for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 10:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, I am two seconds from being on you like white on rice in a glass of milk on a paper plate in a snowstorm. I'm gonna put my foot so far up your ass, the water on my knee will quench your thirst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 07:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the fundamentals are the same which is why i don't really mind when league just gets called rugby, but there are different rules   mechanics to separate them... rugby union is the traditional rugby where its stays the same forever, league is open to changing rules and mechanics that experts/ex players deem necessary to make it better and more exciting.

There are youtube videos that go into detail and the history behind it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 04:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm australian and find it draining how much guys need to correct that every single time.

Also Taumalolo is a freak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 03:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh awesome thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 02:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He definitely would have seen game this year, Ellington went down so he would have wrapped up both returning positions. Also Hyde went down for chunks of the season and Mike Davis got overlooked for being overall shit. IMO hayne could have been the #2 RB for the 9ers year.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do any OMW springs fit inside the Clearshot/Stormfire? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 22:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If no-one knows are you able to reply with the outer diameter and length of the stock spring? If I get this info back to OMW they'll check if any of their springs fit those measurements.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 08:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is nerfperks and the rewards open to australian residents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 23:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 vote for ardbeg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Peaty Scotch To Buy Ardbeg 10 Or Laphroaig 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ardbeg is $85aud and Laphroaig is $88aud, i'm looking to venture into the islay scotches for the first time and was wondering if the extra $3 is worth it for the Laphroaig. Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jody Hill is a freak of a talent, Observe and report is my favourite comedy movie and everything he's done so far has been excellent... not good, excellent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scott Waugh: He did the need for speed movie which suffered from a ridiculous screenplay but his direction was amazing. This guy had a background in stunts on some classic movies like xXx and it shone through in need for speed.

He's helming this drama/thriller with josh hartnett leading and hot girl from scouts guide to the zombie apocalypse (sarah dumont) i'm really looking forward to. 

http://www.imdb.com/title/tt5503688/?ref_=nm_flmg_dr_1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVED his cabin fever sequel, but I found in the valley of violence lackluster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tree Of Life
The Neon Demon
The Wailing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can not think too hard to a movie like Crank 1 2 and be rewarded with great film-making, suicide squad played it safe turned out a mess... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 02:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was relying on gross out, but c'mon its sacha anyone expecting writing/jokes on par with Dan Harmon, Jared Hess shouldn't have seen it.

Also comedies are going terrible in recent times, IMO we're lucky to get a couple good ones a year so grimsby was not a bad addition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
