<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8607</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta start watching Veep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What neighbors have liberals made you hate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just remember that most of America is made up of I's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's put the wealth gap into overdrive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even fucking handshakes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knew the Democrats would become the party of national security?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascist solidarity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.rferl.org/a/kara-murza-russia-opposition-us-senate-committe-testimony/28399196.html

http://abcnews.go.com/Politics/poisoned-russian-activist-delivers-rebuke-putin-regime-senate/story?id=46455901

 "For too many years, for too long, leaders of Western democracies have been just ignoring and moving on from what Mr. Putin has been doing," Kara-Murza said.

 He said there are currently 100 political prisoners in Russia and, after tens of thousands of people marched through the streets in different cities across Russia over the weekend, more than 1,500 people were arrested.

 Kara-Murza said he thinks the U.S. should be honest about whats happening in Russia and not "enable corrupt or abusive behavior" and "continue to engage with Russias civil society."

 He said he believes Western democracies have given Putin a pass to interfere in elections because they "have not taken a principled, firm stand against Russia's actions."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, we have to ask if *they* have memories... 

Merrick Garland, 3/16/16 - 1/20/17. Never forgive, never forget.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America, where the billionaires are on welfare and the poor eat budget cuts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come take me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he certainly knew about the Vietnam War! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Republicans are flushing America's intelligence down the toilet...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone needs to tell Trump they're not on court TV... you can't just rebrand your way into constitutionality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a Clinton Foundation thing to do. Where's the outrage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would *LOVE* to see Donald J. Trump in court, but something tells me he's a coward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carlos Slim could buy Donald J. Trump and all his properties and barely notice a difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'm pretty sure it's 200,000 signatures now.](http://www.syracuse.com/politics/index.ssf/2017/03/melania_trump_petition_move_ny_washington.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Republican dream for ~~multiracial~~ liberal America is to literally turn neighbor against neighbor in a rage-filled witch hunt against the poorest people in our communities. Well all the ~~neo-fascists~~ right-wing statists can go choke on their spite and die, because we are not going to turn each other in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Steve Bannon confronted members of the House Freedom Caucus earlier this week during the White Houses push for the American Health Care Act, Axioss Mike Allen reported Saturday in his newsletter.

 **This is not a discussion. This is not a debate. You have no choice but to vote for this bill,** said Bannon.

 A Freedom Caucus member reportedly replied: **You know, the last time someone ordered me to do something, I was 18 years old, and it was my daddy. And I didnt listen to him, either.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is gonna have the most pissed-on grave in America. People will go to jail to piss on Trump's grave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for one have no sympathy for Barron's struggle with education. His needs aren't *that* special. And Barron is the billionaire son to the president of the United States. He could get Harvard professors to baby sit him. He doesn't need our money, and he should be living on the generous federal property called the *White House*, not in a luxury New York apartment at taxpayers expense, and misery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extreme weather events linked to climate change impact on the jet stream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignorance is one hell of a drug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They *are* sending in ICE agents to punish sanctuary cities and raid them into submission. Look at Austin Texas, for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Indians travel to the graves at Wounded Knee to mark one hundred years since the massacre. December, 1990 [1052x704] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think our country is so innocent?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The studies you're posting are claims about bias, I'm talking about the likelihood of events. A white person is statistically less likely to be shot. 44 is less than 77. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The paper cited in that article also points out 44% of police shooting victims are white, and the US white population is 77%. So the non-white 23% of the population takes more than half the bullets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd settle for a stockade and some tomatoes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you heard of statistics? There's this thing called probability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing fascist about that all, no siree. Just a knock on the door and a bullet in your dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, Donald Trump does have a record of mocking the disabled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Identity politics" in right-wing doublespeak is just code for "uppity minority." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only people surprised by Trump are the ones who voted for him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this dream where I'm not afraid to hold your hand in Texas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a V for Vendetta scene </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder how far up the chain this'll go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some, I assume, are decent people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  no Warrants shall issue, but upon probable cause

Read the fuckin Constitution. They busted down the door of legal residents and shot an innocent man. No illegal Jews in the basement. What kind of shit federal policing is that, where you can't even confirm the residency of the home you're gonna raid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Leave Bill alone!! ;__;" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's fine as long as he jerks their egos off on the way down... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still couldn't win him the popular vote. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coal is the dirtiest fuel in America -- hell, the dirtiest fossil fuel period. It is the tip of the spear for the fossil fuel industry, the vanguard of their pollution revolution. If he can save coal, he sets the environmental movement back thirty years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or storm troopers.

(The ones that can't aim) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They weren't too keen on the Black Panthers arming themselves in the 1960s, I doubt they'll want immigrants to arm themselves either. When the NRA talks about self-defense, rights and freedom, it's using doublespeak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why keep a Republican congressman for blackmail if you can replace him instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wants to sell America, not save it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Billionaires of the world, unite! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TLDR, Democrats resign for organizational flexibility, Republicans resign because of organizational crisis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many Mexicans who don't speak Nahua still take on / are given names to reflect their indigenous / colonized heritage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Shoot! Steve Sack, U.S., 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawsuit: DC police withholding reports on protest response </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you're not alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Governor Reagan orders the first tear gas attack by helicopter on U.S. soil over the campus of U.C. Berkeley, during the People's Park protests in May 1969 [920x611] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 11:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teachers at a fifth New Orleans charter school seeking a union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DC Police Sued Over Inauguration Day Arrest Records </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you court a vote you can't count? You could just say "there are no gays in my district," and as far as the census goes, that's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there are benefits that accrue from census representation then it abridges equal protection not to include LGBT people. And there are. The census is used to help determine where to build new schools, roads, health care facilities, child-care and senior centers - not just the size of congressional districts.

And even in congressional representation, what obligation does a representative have to a constituency he can't measure or see? How would we know about districts being gerrymandered if we didn't have demographic data besides just population count? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet, you include gender, age, income, family size, etc. into the census because it's used for a whole slew of governmental and private purposes, not just counting. 

You also don't - *can't* - see an LGBT person if you ignore their sexuality. That's as literal as ignoring gets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does that represent LGBT people if you can't see them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Equal protection includes representation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...so skip the question. Don't force everyone else into the closet with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only conservatives could learn from progressives, instead of being stuck in their rigid ways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They cannot, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Pence *wants* to know. This is like when Iran declared, "there are no gays here!" Except we actually have research and public health programs that need this data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the 14th amendment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lulz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're privileged enough not to care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "crayon sniffers for Trump" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because you're talking about a law passed by Congress. Congress has the constitutional authority to withhold and appropriate funds, the executive branch does not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the way it is with most parasites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like Trump has been helping Russian billionaires dump their money in U.S. real estate, driving up rent and the cost of living for residents along the way. Classic Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 47 more Republicans than Democrats in the House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been lying since the Vietnam War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America's sick and dying need you. But it's not an easy job, to pick up the workload meant for a thousand extra hands. A survey of 600 nurses in the U.S. found that 49.8% say they are thinking about quitting right now, mostly due to exhaustion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *Herein lies the tragedy of the age: not that men are poor,  all men know something of poverty; not that men are wicked,  who is good? not that men are ignorant,  what is Truth? Nay, but that men know so little of men.*

W.E.B. DuBois, *The Souls of Black Folk* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like nobody took the GOP's threats seriously while there was still a liberal in the White House.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S., Britain, France, others skip nuclear weapons ban treaty talks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's that got to do with sean Sean Spicer's denial of this hate crime? De Blasio is just saying what we're all thinking. Call it pandering if you like, but it's still true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our government is so stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red state legislatures are taking away workers raises and paid leave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this every murder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, why does the White House have to do its job?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U.S. is currently looking down the barrel of the largest nursing shortage since the implementation of Medicare in the 1960s. It's projected the U.S. will need a workforce of over 4.2 million registered nurses (RNs) by 2022, due largely to the aging Baby Boomer population. 

But the nurse labor market isn't growing fast enough, and less educational spending plus fewer work visas aren't helping. If current trends continue, then there will be a shortfall of 260,000 unfilled nursing positions by 2025. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tens of thousands of people in Harlem come out to greet Nelson Mandela on his first visit to the U.S. in June of 1990, four months after his release from prison. [3029x2013] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
