<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8631</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any Reccomendations for a Good Publisher? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 06:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So after weeks of thinking, I have decided that I would like to write my first novel. I already have the content and it's a matter of just piecing the parts together. 

The next step for me is to find a good publisher, but I would like to know who you think would be a good fit for me. (Newish writer with big hopes and dreams) Thank you for the help in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feel Free To Post! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is a topic you feel like you want to discuss with others feel more than welcome to post on here. However, if it is related to any type of pornography, racism, or just plain assholery it will result in a ban. 

It can be about any other topic though! Ask us what our favorite movies are, rant about a story, sacrifice a duck. ALMOST Anything goes!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't even know. 

I think they were toying with me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wrote what it said. Honestly i just wish it wasnt cheesy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Suicide that didn't go through and a viral video unwillingly uploaded. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Wish I Was Never Unknowingly Recorded For A Viral Video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Martin and before today I was a nobody. I tried talking to the kids in my classes, but for some reason I was just deemed the school loser. My only friend was Dave, but he would ignore me whenever we were around other kids. Two months ago I tried asking Stacy to the homecoming dance, but by the next class I was laughed at for even thinking I had a chance with her. As you know when youre 15, social acceptance makes the difference between having a good high school experience or 4 years of temporary prison. 

I wanted more than anything to have a real friend, to have a girlfriend, or even an occasional conversation, but with each passing day I knew I had almost no chance. 

Yesterday, Dave started avoiding me. Every time I got close to him he would loudly say a joke about how ugly I was and quickly walk away from me as kids surrounded me and laughed. That is when I just gave up. I didnt want to live anymore, and I knew that the only for me to be happy is if I just took the rest of my mothers heart medicine I could escape the hell hole called earth. 

With tears rolling down my chin, I set the pill bottles on my desk and grabbed my guitar. I was going to play my final song. As my fingers plucked the final notes I put the guitar down on the ground and picked up the bottle of pills, but I saw a tiny red light in my bedroom window turn off. I ran up to the window and caught a glimpse of a shadow running around the corner of my house. 

Curious, I ran out of my house and walked around the neighborhood. After I walked around for an hour I noticed how perfect the weather was. I took a deep breath and exhaled slowly. The feeling of calmness filled my body and I looked up at the starry skies. I dont know how long I stood there and stared at the skies, but by the time I walked back into my house I felt better than I have ever felt in my life. 

When I walked into my room I hear my phone buzzing. I thought it was a phone call at first, but the buzzing was far quicker. With just three steps I got to my phone and I noticed that it was an endless amount of notifications from facebook. Using my thumb I swiped right and got to my home screen. Next to the facebook app 99+ was on the top right. I tapped on the app and my mouth dropped. There were 48 friend requests, 71 messages, and the same 99+ symbol next to the notifications. 

I tapped on the notifications and my eyes landed on the fifth notification. Stacy commented on a video that was shared on my profile. Without a second thought I tapped on the notification and the screen bounced to my profile page and onto a video. A mixture of fear and excitement spread across my body as I saw myself playing the guitar just 2 hours ago. It was titled Look at the raw emotions involved in this private guitar solo 3. I wanted to be scared, but the adrenaline that filled me was impossible to ignore. There were over 300k views already, 13k likes, and 6k comments. My thoughts of suicide were quickly dismissed and I went to sleep happier than I have ever felt in my life.

This morning when I woke up I checked my phone to check that it wasnt all just a dream. Even after seeing that there were over 4.5 million views I just couldnt believe my luck. This morning I ran out the door before my breakfast and ran all of the way to the bus stop. The two guys that used to make fun of me while we waited greeted me with high fives and excitedly spoken compliments about how amazing I was at the guitar. When we got on the bus all of the kids that were sitting by themselves quickly made space for me and begged me to sit next to them. 

Still in shock by the sudden burst of popularity, I walked past all of them and towards my seat in the back. I stopped when Stacy grabbed my arm and patted on the seat next to her. Nervously, I sat next to her and stared at the back of the head of the kid sitting in front of me. The whole bus ride she tried to talk to me, but I just couldnt think of anything to respond back with. When the bus stopped in front of the school she turned to me and teasingly asked, You too much of a big shot to talk to me? I smiled at her and walked off of the bus and walked to my English classroom. Mr. Smith looked at me and smiled as I walked to my desk and when I sat down, he clapped his hands together and said, Now its time to begin! Remember to keep question for our little celebrity until after the class!

The whole class everyone stared at me. I caught Dave glancing at me a couple of times, but he would turn around whenever he saw me looking at him. After the class was over Dave tried coming up to me and started to say he was sorry, but before he got to me the rest of class surrounded me and asked me how it felt being famous. I tried responding to their questions, but a mixture of happiness and excitement overwhelmed me and I ran to my locker. There were still kids surrounding me, but I managed to get my locker opened and a little white note fell out. I picked it up and ran to the restroom and into the first stall that was unlocked. I unfolded the letter, secretly hoped it was Stacy, and started to read it. After I was done with the last word I dropped the letter and stared at the door to the toilet. 

It said, You owe me for the viral video. Find me after school. One favor for loneliness is worth more than the part I ask off of your body.

The rest of the day was filled with excited adolescents asking for my autograph and questions of how long I have been playing the guitar. A couple of kids asked for a shoutout for their page, but I was far too distracted to give them any attention.

Before the final bell rang I received two more notes in my locker.

One was before lunch and said, I really hope you show up. Im looking forward to it. Lets up it from a body part to your dedication. That okay to you?

The next one was before my final class. It said, If you dont show up you will die. If you dont do what I tell you the consequence is death. 3

After school I checked my locker and saw a final note. I quickly opened it. By the third tree at the end of the school parking lot. That is where you will find me. Dont bring anyone. That is just asking for death.

There were a couple of kids surrounding me, but I ran through them and through the parking lot. Dave was standing at the end of the parking lot and grabbed me before asking, Bro Im sorry for ignoring you. I just wanted friends. I was tired of being an outsider, and being your friend was making me lose out of other friends. Im sorry. Are you okay man? Youre pale as fuck. You need any help? I shook my head no and told him to leave. Regret apparent on his face, he got in his brothers car and they left.

I ran to the third tree at the end of the parking lot. 

I looked around, but I didnt see anyone around. After two minutes I started to feel relieved. That feeling was shattered when I heard a voice. It wasnt a humans voice. It belonged to what seemed like a computer. In a male voice it said, Kill Mr. Smith and come back to this spot. We will take care of the rest.

I tried asking how it would take care of it, but in the middle of my sentence it said, You dont kill him we will kill you. A question started to form in my head, but the air rose out suddenly right beside my right foot. I yelped and jumped up when I saw the remains of a bullet right where the ground rose up. 

With a stern voice it said, Three days. You have three days to kill Mr. Smith. After you kill him come over here and we will take care of it.

Im home now, and I decided to tell you guys what I just went through. I like Mr. Smith. I dont want to kill him. I dont even know how to kill him if I wanted to. 

Please help me. I just wish I ended my life before I put others [in danger] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)

[Next Part] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wvk9d/toddlers_are_disappearing_after_my_unwilling/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha maybe later, but there really isn't much i could make it into as of right now. how about a couple of days later? lol i have something planned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 08:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmmm that is a really good question... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 08:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing what? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But i did say he was going to daycare... Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice. well for us kindergarten starts at 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can't just take my son to a doctor for throwing a fit:/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i really think he is right now. he is avoiding me now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never acted like a big deal. I never said I was. If i'm a shit father for telling you what a dumb ass you are (which you really are) then I guess i am, but don't fucking say i tried to act like a big deal. I know I'm an amateur (isn't it fucking obvious anyways? It's the fucking internet dipshit), but you're definitely someone that would be better off not coming back here. ever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it kind of annoys me when people don't read the rules from a subreddit and act like a pompous dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasnt for my son. It was for the kid that was thrown down the stairs and eaten by a creature. Idk if that isn't close enough to abuse to you but to ke. That is definitely abuse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the nosleep rules and find out:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is definitely something i am most proud of writing so far. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Son Has Been Acting Strangely Since His 3rd Day of Daycare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even for a 3 year old, my son Henry showed his emotions far more than any kid his age. If anything made him happy he would scream with glee and laugh until his voice became hoarse. We loved it when he was happy, but his fits had become a problem. I know that it is very common for his age, but we wanted to find a solution. We were worried about how he would slam his head on the ground and claw at his arms. 

The online searches all pretty much told us to just be patient with him and that he would get over the phase, but it truly broke our hearts and we wanted to get some kind of help. 

One week ago I was at work and browsing around a parenting website when my manager came up to my desk. I tried to close out of the page, but he asked, You having kid problems? Without turning around, I nodded my head and told him that my sons fits seemed to be getting worse and worse. Chuckling, he put his hand on my shoulder and told me to give him a call after we got off of work. 

I got home around 7 and called him immediately. He asked me if it was a good time to stop by my house. After I got the confirmation from my wife I told him that it was fine. He quickly said, 15 minutes and hung up the phone. I helped my wife clean up the living room, but before we could finish cleaning my manager knocked on the front door. 

Right when I opened the door he rushed in and told me that he would make it quick. He handed me a pamphlet to a place called A New Me Daycare Center. The pamphlet had a bunch of pictures of kids happily playing with each other, but other than the title there were no other words written on it. I gave my manager a weird look, but before I could ask him, he told me that this is the place he took his son. It is only $450 a month, and he could see an improvement in his sons attitude within the first couple of days. 

After his mini pitch, he told us that his wife was waiting for him and told us to think about it before leaving.

That night my wife and I talked for over an hour about if this was a good idea or not. By 2 am we reached a mutual decision to at least try it out for a month. If he started acting better we would keep him there, but if anything seemed off we would just pull him out. 

Five days ago we dropped him off at the daycare center for the first time. He started crying at first, but when he saw the toys that surrounded him he became distracted. While I was watching my son playing I felt a hand grab my arm. I jumped in surprise from the contact, but when I turned around I saw a cheerful woman standing behind me. She started off by talking about how cute our son was, and asked him how old he was. We told him 3 and she started squealing while running up to him and gave him a hug. We expected him to push her off like he did with every stranger, but for some odd reason he hugged her back and started laughing when she spoke to him in funny voices. My wife and I looked at each other and smiled. 

Once she was done playing with my son she walked back to us and pointed to a room in the back. We followed her into the room and sat down on the chairs placed in front of a bright blue desk. She sat down behind the desk and took out a piece of paper. We started reading it, but she started asking questions about his allergies, weight, height, and if he was having any problems. I told her about the fits that hes been having. I expected her to get serious, but she just smiled and told us that they would try their best to make him stop having fits.

The next three days we took him to the daycare center at 7:45 am and I would pick him up after I got off of work at 6 pm. He was still having fits, but it was still helping my wife. She finally had time to work on her novel, and finally had some time to truly relax. We were happy for just that reason, but it all changed two days ago. 

On the ride home from school Henry was strangely quiet. I asked him if he was quiet, but he just stared at me with wide eyes without saying a word back. When we got home I started to get his toys out, but he just walked into his room without giving his toys a second glance. My wife made his favorite dinner that night, grilled chicken and broccoli, but instead of showing the same excitement he used to show he just sat at the desk and started shoveling the food into his mouth. It got to the point to where he had three pieces of broccoli and a huge chunk of chicken in his mouth. I tried to tell him he was going to choke, but he just swallowed the food without chewing it. I took the plate away from him. Instead of crying like he would normally do; he just looked at me and asked, Dinner over? I nodded yes and he hopped off his chair and walked to his room. 

After I finished eating I gave him a bath and got him into his pajamas. I got out a book to read his nightly story, but he just said Im tired. Im going to bed. Teasingly I asked, Oh youre too big for the stories now? In response to my question, he rolled over to his side and started to snore. 

I know I may seem weak, but I wanted to cry. I wanted to shout at him to just give me a smile before he went back to sleep, but I pushed my emotions aside. I reasoned with myself. He must just be tired from having such a long day. 

Defeated, I walked up to my room and went to bed. My mind was filled with too many thoughts to stay up anymore. 

Yesterday, I was a walking shell at work. My manager tried to joke with me, but I was far too distracted. He asked me if I was fine, but I just told him that my son was acting a bit weird. He didnt talk to me for the rest of the day. 

After work I stopped by the local toy store and got the toy airplane he had his eyes set on for the past 3 months. It was $800 because it came with a camera built into it so you can shoot videos while it flew in the sky. While I was checking out, the cashier told me that the plane I was purchasing was amazing and how he had one. I asked him what made it so special, and he told me how it was built to fly long distances and the camera could take up to 11 hours of videos. 

During the whole car ride home he was silent again. I tried making hints to him that I got him the plane he wanted, but he just kept his eyes on the road without giving me a single response. 

When we got home I told him to close his eyes and hold out his hands. Once he had his eyes closed and had both his hands out I placed the plane in his hands. When he opened his eyes he looked at the plane and said, Thanks before walking in to his room. He tossed the plane on the ground and sat on his bed. 

I was crushed. I didnt know what to do anymore. My son wasnt throwing fits anymore, but I wanted him to. I just wanted him to be my son again. Whatever was in his room was not Henry. For the next ten minutes I stared into his room to see what he was doing, but he didnt get off of his bed the whole time. I quietly walked up to his room and peeked inside. Henry was just staring at the wall while sitting cross legged on the middle of his bed. My wife walked up next to me and told me that dinner was ready. I walked in and told Henry to come eat, but he just shook his head no. That is when I lost it. I grabbed him by the arm and hugged him as hard as I could and plead with him. Please Henry; daddy is sorry for wanting you to be different. Please. Please do whatever you want. Just stop doing this. Im begging you. Please Henry please!

He shoved off of me and said he was tired before rolling over to his side and started snoring. When I turned around I saw my wife sitting on the floor crying. I tried to comfort her, but before I knew it I was sitting right next to her crying and pleading to any god that could hear us for our son back. We didnt eat dinner last night. We couldnt. By 9 pm we were both asleep.

I woke up two times last night. The first time was at 2 am and I saw Henry standing in front of our door. I tried getting up but sleep overtook me. The second time was at 5 am and he was standing right next to me. I asked him if he needed anything, but he just shook his head and ran to his room. 

This morning when I woke up I took him to daycare. My wife was still asleep and I knew that she would need the extra rest. I took his new plane with him and turned the video feed on when I dropped him off. 

I took the day off of work today. My wife and I sat in the living room all day today and stared off into space while our favorite shows played on the tv. At 4 pm I decided to pick him up early today. 

He came out without his airplane so I walked back in and grabbed it. I turned off the video feed and we drove back home in silence. Once again, when we got home he walked into his room. I gave my wife a kiss and walked up the stairs into our room and plugged up the cable from the plane to the laptop, and sat while the video loaded on the screen. 

Once it was done loading I opened up the video and started skipping around the video until I found what I was looking for. A kid I didnt see before in the daycare was throwing a fit. He was crying and hitting anyone that came close to him. The lady that we saw the first day we dropped Henry off came up from behind him and lifted him up. She carried him over to a bright yellow door and opened it. The first thing that caught my eye was the stairs that led into complete darkness. She held the boy in front of her face and gave him a smile before throwing him down the stairs. I heard a soft thud and she turned on the lights. A small white lump came out of the corner of the screen and slid forward. 

I looked away from the screen. When I looked back I saw the boy trying to crawl away with his face filled with fear. A skinny naked figure slowly filled the screen; the feet started from the bottom of the screen and its chest surpassed the top of the screen. There were cuts all across its body; it had pasty white skin, and arms that only stretched halfway down his midsection. As it slid closer to the boy the thing bent down to take a better look at the boy. I could only see the side of its face, but it sent chills down my spine. The body was white, but the face was unnaturally yellow. Its hair was a sort of neon blue, but there were only tufts of it on the top of its head. 

Feeling sick I thought about shutting the video off, but before I could even think twice the creature pounced down on the boy and swallowed him whole. Once it devoured the boy the creature looked up at the woman and I cried out in fear. The creature may have been taller than anything I had ever seen before, but it had a face of a newborn baby. The lady gave him a nod and the creature let out a laugh that belonged to an infant, but before it could finish laughing the creature started screaming and fell on its knees. The midsection started to bulge out in several places before an arm penetrated its flesh. The creature started to scream in pain as the rest of the body came out of its body. 

The creature slithered away and the body stood up. It was the boy that was just devoured, but he was calm. He only moved when the lady told him to. She snapped her fingers when the boy came upstairs and a man came up and carried the boy away. After a quiet 5 seconds she walked up closer to the screen and her face quickly filled the screen.

With a smile and the enthusiastic voice she used on me the first day she said, George, dont you think I would spot a camera from a mile away? I just wanted you to see that your son is, in fact, your son. Hes just a cleansed version. Dont be like the last guys that called the cops. They wont find anything. She set the camera down on the ground and opened the yellow door again and all I saw inside was a normal looking closet with old board games on the ground. She picked the camera back up and said, I think it would be best if Henry kept attending A New Me Day Care. The video program shut down and I found myself staring at the empty folder the video was just in. I tried unplugging the cable and plugging it back in, but the video is gone. I tried looking in recent files, but the video has completely disappeared.

I feel helpless guys. I really do. The regret I feel from even getting annoyed at my sons fits is overwhelming me. I cant even think straight. If you guys have ever come across anything like this or even have any suggestions please let me know. 

It may not be possible, but I will do anything to [get my son back] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).  


[Next Part] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wgvoc/i_wish_i_was_never_unknowingly_recorded_for_a/)

[Third Part] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wvk9d/toddlers_are_disappearing_after_my_unwilling/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg i know. Thank you so much for being there when i was in the building phase haha well, I'm still in the building phase but that just means I'm still growing!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, read all of the popular posts. You'll notice something. Alot of them vary in length, description, and even a lot or no dialogue.

It's all about how You feel is your best style of writing. Make it your own brand and then blow their minds with a story that is just as good with a different style, but always make sure you're ready to try a different style of writing. 

To summarize. Write how you think is best and always love the work you submit no matter what the end result is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All good ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 10:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father has been acting really weird guys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 08:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Think My Father Is Becoming Something Worse Than Just Senile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 08:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of days ago my father walked inside of my house wearing a crown. I started laughing as soon as I saw him, but he looked at me with pure hatred in his eyes. He pointed his index finger at me and asked, Did I give you the permission to laugh? I got up and gave him a fake bow, but as I bent down he grabbed me by the hair and slammed me onto the ground. When I tried to get back up I felt something sharp cut the back of my neck. In between his uneven breaths my father bent down and said, You can get up now, but the next time you make a mockery out of me I will end your life.

I tried asking him if he was feeling okay, but before I could even finish my sentence turned around and walked towards his room. I walked upstairs to my bedroom and saw my wife lying on our bed and reading a book. She looked up from her book to give me a little smile, but a look of concern immediately took over. In a shaky voice she asked, Drew, are you okay honey? Why are you so pale? I told her I was fine. She was pregnant; I didnt want to get her worked up with what could just be a senile moment from my father. 

As the days went by my father progressively became more and more obsessed over his new made up status. It got to the point to where I would have to stand up whenever I saw him. Thankfully, I was the only one he treated like a servant. He acted completely normal around my wife and even acted excited whenever my future son would come up in their conversations. 

I figured I could just deal with my father until May 12th, the day my son is expected to be born. The next couple of days I did a good job of avoiding him, and things slowly started to go back to normal. My father even started to calm down, and I thought he would snap out of the phase. 

I lost all hope yesterday.

We had just purchased one of those assemble it yourself cribs for my son. I was setting it up in his future room when my father came in and sat next to me. Putting on the biggest smile I could muster up at that time I told him that I had everything under control. He didnt answer back; instead, he just stared at the part of the crib that was already built. With each piece I attached to the crib I could hear his breathing get slower and deeper. By the time I was halfway done he got up and started walking out of the door. With a sigh of relief, I started working on the crib in peace. About 10 seconds later I heard the sound of fast footsteps coming from behind me. I looked behind me, but there was no one around. My father ran in a couple of seconds later, grabbed me by my shirt, and asked, Where the fuck is Jerry? I know you know where he is. I shoved him back and told him I didnt know anyone named Jerry. He walked back up to me and said, Listen here peasant, youre lucky youre even alive right now. Just tell me where Jerry is and this can all stop.

I pushed past him and walked into the kitchen. My wife was eating a sandwich when I sat next to her. She tried asking me what was wrong, but I told her to finish her sandwich first. Once she was done eating I talked to her about what my father was doing. After I was done telling her she told me that we should look into a couple of retirement homes once the pregnancy was over. The conversation was put on hold when my dad walked into the kitchen. He sat at the table and snapped his fingers at me. I asked him what he wanted but he just pointed at the loaf of bread and then at the fridge. 

I made him a sandwich and placed it in front of him. After a couple of bites he spit out the last bite he took and threw the rest of the sandwich on the floor. Annoyed and a bit pissed off, I walked over to the counter to grab a couple of paper towels. When I walked back up to my father I threw the paper towels at him and told him to pick it up. With a sly grin on his face he retorted back, Clean what up? You feeling okay son? I started to point at the floor, but the sandwich was gone. There were a couple of streaks of mustard and mayo on the ground, but other than that it had vanished. 

I looked over at my wife, but she just shrugged her shoulders. Her face had gone completely pale, but I could see that she was just trying to rationalize what just happened. 

Nobody ate dinner that night. My father just forgot about having to eat, and my wife and I just did not have any sort of appetite anymore. My wife fell asleep at 8 pm. I was in the middle of a movie when I started to hear a noise coming from outside of our bedroom. When I opened the door I could hear what the noise was. It was the sound of a baby laughing. I slowly walked down the stairs and pressed my ear against my fathers bedroom door. The laughing was coming from inside of his room. 

I started to open the door but stopped when I heard my father talking. With a voice filled with happiness he said, I knew you werent gone Jerry. I knew you would come back to your papa. Your little brother is quite the disappointment isnt he? Hes just a peasant, a nobody, but you, you are everything I ever wanted. 

I swung the door open and saw my father sitting on the middle of his bed while tickling the air. He didnt even notice me stare at him for a couple of minutes. I closed his door and walked back up to my room.

Im sitting on my bed with a laptop now. I know at least some of you guys will know what I should do. I really need help right now guys. I dont think I can keep living with him for the next couple of months. 

Even as I write to you guys. I can hear the sound of [light footsteps running around our house] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 04:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha thank you very much:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was walking around the great fields of Nosleep.

Naive and lost, I kept digging deeper and deeper. You see, I just never really dived very deep into horror before. The more i read I started to fall in love with the stories and above all, the community. Though we fight and we squabble we always manage to come back as a unit of one. 

With determination filling my head I started to slam my hands on the keyboard and wrote my AWESOME, not really, first series and felt very proud to have finished something and put it out to the public. The upvotes were scarce, but i was hooked. 

I kept writing and i kept reading these amazing stories.

Here i am now. Afraid of scary movies, but loving the NoSleep community and everything that is within it.

TLDR: Not too much in to horror. Just NoSleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh me. Pick me! I'm 23! 

I think that's what this was really about tbh though. Some author with a throwaway account trying to see if they are mentioned hahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont get to pick my team :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just being honest here. I started getting less upvotes after i won the contest XD thank you u/-Manorly- hahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are all friends :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an old comment. It was before you went to bed. Just drop it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure those were always my favorite! 

Also could you send me a list of your favorite Asian writers? 

I'm tired of stories written by other races.

It's an Asian World now Bitches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really feel like i'm gonna cry right now.

Painful. Gonna go down from the saltyness of the comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> agreed thank you very much for the wonderful comment u/OsoBrazos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kind of like a huge "Ouch" moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh shit,,. O.o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pop open your champagne or whatever it is you plan on doing.

just saying. i can tell you're getting worked up about it too.... 


sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lemme just copy and paste. Cause you really do seem like a negative person.

why the sarcasm???

I swear everytime i see you post on here it's just negative shit.

Or you're trying to correct another author. No matter what the topic is. 

Why not just relax dude?

Shit isn't that serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why the sarcasm???

I swear everytime i see you post on here it's just negative shit. 

Or you're trying to correct another author. No matter what the topic is. Why not just relax dude? 

Shit isn't that serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but isn't it kind of like throwing a big heaping pile of shit into something that is supposed to be a celebration? 

We still leave the door open for them. They aren't kidnapped. We don't force them in. We just open it for them. They have the chance to close the door and walk away. 

Plus i have a lot of people read my stuff that doesn't even have a reddit account. We don't account for those people.

TLDR: Let's just celebrate and be happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how 'bout we just celebrate getting 10 million instead of getting into the specifics.

It's still eyes that have glanced at the sub name at least.

It's all about name recognition and we got it.

so hooray! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as well as u/Sailorscarlet :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/d0nutblink of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh shit. that escalated in a very good way O.o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh well that means a lot to me!! Haha dont be afraid to ask me for any pointers lol 

Just message me and i can see what i can do! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about what the audience wants. Worry about what you want to write and how you feel about the end result. 

The only way to get attention is by getting lucky or by constantly submitting quality stories.

If you start worrying about the audience you lose the momentum you have now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is what it seemed like. But i can still see here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This one is actually pretty sad. shit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Will Never Forget The First Time I Fell In Love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two days ago I woke up to the loud noises coming from the house next door. By the time I got up and looked out the window I saw a moving truck peeling out of my next door neighbors driveway. Normally for a fifteen year old boy that doesnt really matter, but for me it was the worst day of my life. It was my girlfriends family. Her name was Carrie, and she was the best person I had ever met in my life. The day before was our 1 year mark and she bought me a bright yellow balloon in the shape of a heart. It wasnt much but it meant the world to me. When they left without even a word I was filled with a mixture of anger and sadness.

I tried calling her 12 times, sent her over 20 messages, and tried messaging her on Facebook several times, but I never got a response from her. By the time it was 11 pm I gave up. I put my phone on the charger and just sat on my bed while staring at the house she just moved out of. I thought of all of the times we would just open up our windows and talk to each other. Her mother and father would sometimes walk up behind her and yell at me to stop bugging them at 12 at night, but we would never stop our nightly conversations. 

That was really the only times we got to talk. She went to a private school while I went to the local public school. So we would just walk around the neighborhood from 6 pm to 8 pm and talk from our windows for about an hour before we would both go to bed at around 11 pm. As my eyes started to tear up from losing my first love I saw the curtains from her window move. I sat up instantly and stared at the window. 

It started off as little movements, but after a couple of minutes, the curtains swung to the right side. I could see her figure standing there. I opened my windows and called out to her, but she took a couple of steps back and vanished in the shadows. I rubbed my eyes and tried to get a better look, but the curtains were back to where they once were and I couldnt look through her window anymore. That night I could barely sleep. Every time I would start to drift off I could see the curtains moving and my eyes would snap open. As the sun started to peak out of the clouds I finally managed to sleep. 

Yesterday was a Sunday, and I didnt wake up until 1 pm. When I walked into the kitchen my mom laughed at how tired I looked and made me a sandwich. I checked my phone while I ate my sandwich and saw that Carrie never messaged me back. I wanted to really believe that I saw her last night, but I knew it was just my mind playing tricks on me. Once I finished my sandwich I stayed in my room for the rest of the day. I didnt want to do anything. If I walked outside I knew I would just be reminded of the walks we took. If I even saw her house I knew that I would just feel depressed once more. I kept my curtains closed for the rest of the day and listened to some music while I read books on my bed.

At 5:30 I walked downstairs and ate dinner with my mother and father. We were pretty much quiet for the whole meal. My dad tried to say a couple of things, but after a couple of failed attempts to get us talking he finished his meal and went to his office. I was back in my room by 6. I started to read Grapes of Wrath when I heard the sound of whistling coming from outside. I walked to the window and pulled back the curtains. Carrie was walking around the neighborhood whistling the same little tune she always did. Excitedly, I opened the window and called out to her. She looked up and I fell back onto my bed. When she looked up at me I could see that half of her face was torn off. The exposed flesh on her face looked to be rotting. 

I sat on the floor in front of my window and tried to calm myself down. I looked back up and she was gone, but I could still hear her whistling coming from the distance. 

I tried. I really tried to keep my mind off of her, but no matter what I did I would end up thinking about the rotting face of Carrie.

I fell asleep at 11, but I woke back up around 3 in the morning. I could hear her calling out to me. I dont know how I could possibly explain how, but it just felt like it was coming from inside of my head. Groggily, I got out of bed and walked to my window. Carrie was standing in front of her window waving out to me. Her face was still in the same shape as when she was walking around, but she was still beautiful to me. She was still perfect. I was just happy to see her smile. I opened my window and waved back at her. 

The happiness lasted for five seconds. By the time she put her hands on the bottom of the window her parents walked up behind her and grabbed her. They closed the curtain and I heard her scream as loud as she could.

I dont know what came over me. It might have just been the exhaustion or the fear that has taken over me the last two days, but I grabbed my cell phone and I called the police. When they answered I told them about what was happening at the address Carrie used to live at. 

The world became silent after I hung up the phone. Peace overwhelmed every fiber of my being, and I finally slept peacefully. 

I woke up to loud sounds again this morning, but I felt a certain level of peace. A peace I never felt in my life. I walked downstairs and when my mother saw me she gave me a hug and told me that everything would be alright. I asked her what she meant, but she just told me that whatever happened for the last 6 months are finally over. 

I sat in my room while cops walked in and out of the house next door.

Carries house.

My father walked in and told me how proud he was of calling the police. How he was proud of me for finally moving on. 

6 months ago Carrie went missing. She was never found. The cops stopped looking for her, and her mother and father thought it was the perfect time to leave. 

Carrie was found in the attic. Her body was stuffed in the trunk. The police were looking for her parents now. 

Tonight as I stand in front of my window I can see Carrie. With the beautiful face I fell in love with we open our doors at the same time. Its time for me to get off of here, and talk to my [first and only love] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh man, I really love the title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you very much!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About that...

I killed the help. With maxwell and his silver hammer. We made sure they were dead. Even gave it a couple more bang bangs, but maxwell and i will be the new help.

I trulu am sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh thank you for the gold kind stranger:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a great friend:)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually is it possible to just change my submission and come back in as captain?

If not I'll go back to my original status and take the bullets!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's cute watching people debunk stuff when it is against nosleep rules:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> unknown trails:/ ughhh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please Don't Walk On Unknown Trails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the past six months, I have started to obsess over a little trail I passed by on the way to church every Sunday. I know it seems odd that someone would become so obsessed over a trail, but it was mostly the build-up of curiosity. It was far too small for a car to enter, and the trail was just a combination of brown dirt and large rocks. Another thing that interested me about the trail was the same three cars parked right in front of the entrance to it. They never moved from where they stood.  

I knew it was a dumb idea, but I just had to check it out. Today I left an hour earlier for church. That would give me more than enough time to check out the trail and get to church on time. I parked behind the other cars. 

I took my phone, a pack of cigarettes, and my extra battery with me and walked up to the trail. This may sound weird, but the ground looked to be a bit off. The dirt was gray with a bluish tint, and all of the rocks were perfectly white. As soon as I stepped onto the trail I felt a rush of emotions. 

I was suddenly hit with the need to cry, scream, and laugh. At the same time, I felt the absolute need to run. Confused and fearful, I unwillingly ran further down the trail.

I wanted to stop running, but it felt like my body was taken over. The trees started to surround me, but whenever I glanced down on the ground I could still see that I was on the trail. By the time I came to a stop there was only space for me and one other person to walk on the trail. I checked my phone, but my phone wouldnt catch any sort of signal. I turned around and tried to run back to where I came from, but I could barely move. After three steps I couldnt handle struggle anymore. I got on my knees and tried to crawl, but I found myself laying on the ground only a couple of seconds later. 

Regret was the only thing I felt at that point. I started to yell at myself, slammed my head on the ground, but nothing made me feel better. The only thing I could do now was to keep walking. 

After a couple of minutes, I saw a person walking the same direction I was, but he was moving at a much slower speed. As I got closer I realized how bad of a shape he was in. His back and his legs were covered in small cuts and deep lacerations. I ran up to him and tried to ask him if he needed help, but before I could even finish my question he grabbed me by my shirt and tried to throw me on the ground. It was easy to get out of his grip and I jumped away from him.

I tried to just walk away, but in my mind, I saw the man lying on the ground with his head ripped off. I have never been a violent person, but the very thought filled me with joy. I shook my head and tried to take the thought out of my mind. The man kept walking towards me but I ran off before he could even get close to me.

Once I got far enough away I checked my phone and saw that there was still zero signal out here. The time read 13:34. That couldnt have been right. I got to the trail at around 9:30. I was scared. I didnt have a grip on time anymore. The trees kept feeling like they were starting to surround me. I dont know when I blacked out, but a man was kneeling beside me when I woke up. I tried to run away from him, but he just calmly stood by and asked if I needed help getting out of here. 

He walked up to me, but I know he could still see I doubted him. With a calm and smooth voice, he said, If I wanted to kill you I would have done it while you were knocked the fuck out. He laughed a bit, and I felt my panic start to fade away. I dont know how, but before I knew it I was filled with rage. How fucking dare he tease me like that? Who the fuck does he think he is? I started running after him, but he wrapped his arms around me and slapped me in the face. He yelled out, Listen! This trail. I dont fucking know how or why but it is going to bring out your emotions. Mainly anger. You cant leave if you kill someone. Ive seen people try to leave. They are ripped to shreds. Not by anything, but by whatever the fuck is in the air. Get a hold of yourself. If you want to live, you have to focus on leaving.

We walked deeper and deeper into the trail. The deeper we went the worse it started to smell. I didnt look around. I already knew what surrounded us. While we walked we talked about what he used to do. He was a police officer, and he had a wife and three kids. He asked me what the date was and after I told him he slowly nodded his head. I could have sworn Ive only been here for 2 weeks, but I guess its been 3 years now. I could see the tears start building up in his eyes, but before they had a chance to drop he wiped them away. After a couple of seconds, he reached out a hand and said, The name is Gerald. I shook his hand and told him my name was Jake. 

As our formalities ended I saw a guy walking in front of us. Gerald stuck an arm in front of me and walked forward. I followed closely behind him. As soon as Gerald got close enough he punched the back of the mans head as hard as he could. The man fell on his knees and we started to run away from him, but the man quickly got up and started to chase after us. I looked back and almost threw up when I saw his face. His cheeks were completely missing. His teeth were black and it looked like his gums were rotting. Before I could take a better look the man stopped running and we got away. 

We kept running for what seemed like hours. I wanted to give up, but then I saw it. There was a clearing in the forest. I looked over at Gerald and he nodded his head weakly. We stopped at the end of the woods and noticed that there were fewer trees than what I remembered. 

I asked him if he was going to go with me, but he looked at me with what seemed like far more regret than I felt on the trail. You should go. Just remember to never come back in here again. It makes you into a different person. I loved my family, but we came into the trail together. My wife thought it was a good idea. Before the first sunset, I killed my wife. I tried to resist as much as I could but I blamed her for bringing us in. I dont want to talk about my two boys. I just cant. He started to sob and I walked up to him to comfort him, but with a scream, he grabbed me by my shoulders and threw me out of the trail.

I looked around and saw that I was back to where I began my trip. I walked to my car and drove home. It is now 3 in the morning, and I know I wont be able to go to sleep. So that is why I wrote this warning for you all tonight.

Please do not wander into [unknown trails] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/).










 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 10:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh man thank you so much!!! you definitely will lol you already did it once! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha i was definitely awed! i know you'll just drop another story that kicks my story's ass soon lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No posts about specific authors or stories in this subreddit- "

Not really a place now. Just gotta wait and see if you get the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuckk i really thought you guys had it over me. I loved your story btw. Way to make me afraid of children books lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 09:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wrong sub bud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 04:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trying to try a clever retort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah no female narrators in mine... yet

maybe next time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 03:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that too.

Can confirm: Is a fog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speechless. Super fucking speechless.

I can say that I am very, very, very happy. 

Seriously though, amazing stories filled up the contest this month. I did not even think I had a chance in the world.

TLDR: Happy and Grateful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what do you mean? lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit o.o that was great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 00:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should cpt. This time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am ready to enter my 2nd nosleep teams thingy!
Let the thingy begin!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah he only got 6 views on mine haha thank you for the heads up:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm:/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :/ it really is scary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh need to check it out if I'm still alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm don't see that app. What is it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spilt my korean gravy eerwhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 11:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I'm not sure where this writing is taking me. I would love to create something huge like that!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 11:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is more to it. Lol like another series and another story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wrong sub bud:p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mwahahhahhahah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 06:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh well thank you very much kind reader:D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha awesome! 

good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahhh thank makes sense too.

Hm maybe browse around the Reddit front page? There are plenty of other little inspiration pieces on there. I like to make stories out of some things i find on r/Funny. Well base very, very, very  loosely off of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 05:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> waiting for the next one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just try to think up of any type of title and just write away.

good practice and somehow ends up being a decent story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha just reading it is more than enough for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [1st character] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i87cr/im_12_and_i_met_a_nice_man/?utm_content=title utm_medium=user utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage)

[Life is Beta] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5pmu3w/my_strange_experiences_with_an_app_called_life_is/)

[Next Character] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5r05w8/i_just_came_back_home_after_being_missing_for_15/)

[2nd to Last Series] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sk87k/out_of_9_people_only_1_will_get_to_live_part_1/)

The last three are series. They will have links to the parts.

Not really all over the place lol they went in order.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Series Finishing Relief Overload </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 01:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have a feeling of actual bliss when you have finally answer the necessary questions about your series, and still leave the readers thinking about later outcomes?

Truly an amazing feeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck those stairs omfg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hhehhe sorry XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paging- u/EtTuToritalla ummmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something something hint something "beta" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Coma Has Introduced Me To A Different World </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 09:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly just felt like I was waking up, but the look of excitement on my mothers face told me a different story. 

I tried to get up, but several hands swarmed around me and gently pulled me back onto the bed. I tried looking around but became very dizzy. 

I asked my mother, Where am I?

She just grabbed my hands and started to cry. 

My mother tried to go in for a hug, but a man dressed in white held her back and told her that it would be best to just give me a little bit of space. She nodded at him slowly and sat on the chair next to me. 

I blinked once and the room was empty. I tried to call out for help, but no one came. I looked around and saw a little remote on the side table and viewed my options. There was a couple of generic tv buttons and a button on the bottom right with a little face on it. I clicked it and turned on the tv to see if anything was on, but the channels wouldnt change. It just looked like some sort of weird reality tv show. The camera was pointed to a sofa and did not move. One boy suddenly got up from the couch and started to run towards the left side of the camera. 

The other boys on the couch looked terrified, but they didnt move a muscle. I tried to turn the volume up, but even at max volume, there wasnt a single sound. 

The nurse finally came in and asked me what I needed. I told him that I wanted to call my mother, but he just sighed and walked up to my bed. Hey man your mom will be back tomorrow. She said she was busy, but just try to get some rest. Youve had a rough 3 weeks. I tried asking him what happened, but he just turned around and walked out the door. I called out to him, but he completely ignored me. 

Slightly pissed off about being ignored, I grabbed the remote and pressed the nurse button three times; after that, I watched the tv. Three large adults with monkey masks came onto the screen and grabbed the boy who ran off the screen and threw a white cloth bag over his head. The tied his arms and legs together and then carried him off somewhere. 

Three minutes later the nurse came back in, but when I saw him I couldnt help but let out a scream. His forehead had a huge hole in it and blood was pouring down his face. He swung his head around the room and bits of his brain flew everywhere. I closed my eyes and tried to crawl off of the bed. I felt a hand touch me and I slapped them off of me. 

Cmon guy. I know something scared you, but you gotta talk to me. What is going on? What scared you? I started to crawl away, but he grabbed my knee and held it down against the thin mattress. I opened my eyes to find a way to get out of his grip when I noticed that he was completely fine. 

With a concerned look on his face he asked, You okay now? I nodded yes and stared back at the tv. The boys were back to just walking around the room and sitting on the couch. The nurse stared at me for a couple of minutes and finally broke the silence with another question. You keep staring at the tv. You want me to turn it on for you? 

I told him that it was on while I pointed at the tv. He chuckled and walked up to the tv and pressed the power button. What I was originally watching slowly faded away and was replaced with an overly excited woman talking about how to make the perfect Panini for your dinner guests.

That is when I knew something was wrong with me. Why was I seeing things? What the fuck was wrong with me? Why was I even here? What did he mean by a rough 3 weeks?

He asked me if I needed anything else, and I just shook my head. He gave me a pat on my shoulder and left the room.

I looked back at the tv and saw that the woman looked a lot older than before. I thought she was in her mid 30s but now she looked to be around 60 to 70 years old. Right as she put the Panini in the over she grabbed at her chest and fell onto the ground. The camera kept rolling and I could still hear her voice talking about what side dishes to make. I closed my eyes and opened them again to see that the woman was back to her 30s and shouting excitedly that the Panini was ready to get out of the oven.

I honestly didnt know what the hell was wrong with me. I just wanted to get some rest. 

Rolling over to my right side I closed my eyes, but I just couldnt sleep. The stress of every single unanswered question was killing me. Thought after thought kept coming in and I knew that sleep was impossible, but I still kept my eyes closed. At least this way I wont keep imagining any of this fucked up shit. 

After a while, I finally managed to clear out my head and started to drift off to sleep. Right as the first line of drool started to escape out of the corner of my mouth screams and the loud sound of gunshots erupted from the hallway. I immediately woke up and ripped the IV out of my wrist. 

I was trying to get up when a boy ran into my room. He ran up to me with a gun to my head and asked me if my name was Wes. I nodded at him. He yelled out Grant! Get your ass in here. A man that looked to be in his mid 30s ran in the room and smiled. He looked at the boy and said, Well Phil, didnt I tell you that he was gonna be in here? Dont mess with the mastermind. The boy punched Grant on the shoulder and they walked up to me. 

Before I could even move Grant grabbed me and slung me onto his shoulder and ran out of the room. My nurse tried to run up and stop us, but the boy shot him in the middle of his forehead. 

Once we got out of the building I realized that it wasnt a hospital. It looked more like a warehouse from the outside. I tried asking Grant what the fuck was going on, but he just told me that he would explain it in the car.

We got to the car and he threw me into the back seat. The boy got into the passenger seat and Grant sat in the front. It wasnt until 2 hours of driving when Grant finally started to talk. 

I know you must be full of questions right now, but I cant answer all of them right now. You needed to get out of there. You were one of 8 people they have kidnapped. They gain your trust by seeming like a completely legitimate hospital. 

I tried telling him that my mother was there, but he put a hand up.

Wes, try to remember. Close your eyes and try to remember what happened.

I closed my eyes and tried to concentrate on my mothers face. At first, it was the woman in the hospital, but then her face started to change. It kept changing until I saw the actual face of my mother. The mother who was shot 5 times in the chest; the mother I ran up to as she took her final breaths. My memories ended there. I couldnt reach back any further. My mind was blank.

When I opened my eyes back up Grant said almost in a complete whisper, I dont know how they made you forget everything, but you have a gift. You know how people die. We have several people like you in our organization. Join us. We will get rid of evil one person at a time. You can leave now if you want, but I think you need us as much as we need you. Here. Hold onto this.

He handed me a cell phone, and I tapped on the power button. 

It instantly came on and had only two apps.

The regular browser app which I am using to tell you guys what is happening.

Then the next app. Which I used to make the decision [To Kill] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's what some people say about my series XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmmmmm. lemme browse around and see if i have anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omfgggggg i love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck... well i'm going to need my ear back guys... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you do know me haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UGHHH I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> chop off your ear and send it to the mods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 04:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are indeed a clever girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 04:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao well there is always an option for a very good bone stew!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 03:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha i need to get back into the cannibal stories lmfao i have just been stuck on trying to make sad horror for some reason. 

You can be my dad. I will kill you first though. Don't worry I'll eat you after you're dead, but i don't eat the feet or hands so I'll donate it to the local gfood banks :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 03:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really need to branch out and do female perspectives, but i dont wanna mess up:/ 

Hey kill me, but make sure you eat my brain. I have a couple more good ideas for stories. Well more like i make them up as i type randomly on the computer haha.

I assumed you were a monster-.- 5"1 is the ideal height for a killer. You can gut anyone with ease. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of the time for me. Charlie and the chocolate factory, of mice and men(john steinbeck is the greatest author of all time) and many more.

I honestly didn't grow up reading a lot of horror(parents didn't let me) and just now really got into horror in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 01:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk what people think i am. Probably a creepy korean girl that sacrifices animals.

What i am: 23 yr old editor. I'm male. About 5 foot 8. Likes comedy movies and closes my eyes and covers my ears on scary parts of movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 11:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 11:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha i honestly sit in front of a computer and try to think of a title. 

Once i have a semi decent title i will build a story around it! Very little of my stories are ever planned lol.

I do need a day break sometimes(like today), but on a normal day i can shoot out a story in about an hour to two hours haha.

I don't have epic preparations like the great authors of nosleep:( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
