<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8145</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the line bn constructive criticism and unwanted advice that could be deemed "offensive"? Start with that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 23:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love chilling and watching tv. But I also know that exercise is good for me. So I have a lot of times where I would rather watch tv than exercise. But I know tv will be there later and "now" is the time that I traditionally exercise. So I work out and watch tv with whatever leftover time I have at night. 

And that's the same with writing. I personally have to divvy out time to write. I know that internent, tv, food, will all be there later. But if I don't plan a time to write, then I won't do it! 

I know that the payoff for writing fanfic + 1.5 hours of tv is better than watching 3 hours of tv. There's just a greater sense of accomplishment with fanfic than what I'd be doing otherwise with my time!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 22:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ninth Gate, The Devil's Rain (w William Shatner, oddly enough)

Edit: Bad Dreams too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 17:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the Nike Romaleos. I'm female and got the men's version. I'm like a large size 10/small 11 and the 9.5's fit well (I think, I can verify that later). I got the white ones with the red Nike logo. I LOVE THEM. 

My friend got the purple adidas powerlifts and after 3 months the sole is starting to disconnect from the rest of the shoe. Yeah, she can glue it but 3 months? 

I think the Romaleos are a little much for a casual crossfitter? But if you treat the shoes right, they last forever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> motivation for monsters would be their own survival, probably. maybe they need a new space to live. Maybe they need a place for their eggs. Or maybe people are just tasty to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like an amazing writing experience!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! It's my biggest pet peeve about this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "do not then attack the creator if it wasn't to your taste"

I get not attacking the creator. But not calling people out on their shitty writing or illogical plots and just coddling them with favorable reviews does no one any favors either, right? 

At the end of the day, you're posting your works on the internet. So you have the right to post and others have the right to to comment. Poster beware.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 11:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has a little bit of a Far Side vibe to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I know I'm bad cuz I do the Bartman 

I had the cassette tape  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ceiling cat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 05:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't they all be one book?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The audio commentary for CHUD is hilarious! Daniel Stern, one of the bad guys from Home Alone, is on it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes they come back? Written by Stephen King

Edit: why the downvotes? go to the Wikipedia page, "a gang of greasers" and released 15 years ago. what's your guess if you're any better .... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do that ALL the time with my Vampire Diaries fics Jesus help me. 

Caroline investigates a new drink she's found - Tru Blood. It must be a joke, right? Synthetic blood for vampires? But unbeknownst to Caroline, there's another breed of vampires out there with a shaky alliance with the Mikaelsons. How will Caroline handle being in the cross hairs?

and 

Caroline Forbes is an energetic young vampire who finds herself being drawn to moody, aggressive Klaus. Klaus knows "there is nothing new under the sun" when it comes to women and vamps; he's seen it all. Can she tame him or is Caroline too far over her head? Will Klaus use Caroline and watch her life shatter or can he selflessly love?

My other ones ... I havent ended on questions. I dont know, I just remember Sweet Valley High books and they all seemed to do that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe they're like ... check out my profile, follow me, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HATE when they don't put the fandom in the title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 15:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still not as dedicated as [this guy](http://editorial.designtaxi.com/news-woodist260115/2.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 23:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to stop reading those $2.99 books with high ratings on amazon. What I found out was they were part of a series. So the book would end with one part of the story ended but leave a big question open or, even worse, just a flat-out cliffhanger. And then the 2nd book would be like $9.99 or normal-ish price. 

So I definitely try to stay away from series. I'm not really trying to get into Outlander. But I'm not completely opposted. I'd read Deborah Harkness books or I'd try out that Annihilation series. It really depends on the story. 

But with most series I want to read - most of the books seem to be: 

- on a quick schedule to be released (like Miss Peregrine, Harry Potter ... but not GoT or Name of the Wind - which I read NotW)
- they've been heavily vetted by blogs and /r/books (like the Annihilation series). 

- or the description just really piques my interest (like the All Souls trilogy, WITCHES!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 22:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, it was the same with 50 Shades. I found myself cringing during the awkward writings or would notice the "instant chemistry" that would literally never happen (like Anastasia Steele tripping and billionaire Christian thinking it was SO hot .... or when Bella was just so average but Edward Cullen was obsessed with her anyways). But I read the books SO fast and I still enjoyed them.

And it's just like candy or dessert. It's okay to have it every now and then, right?! 

edit: And when Edward broke the bed while having sex with Bella ... I'm starting to laugh right now thinking about it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Announcer's voice: *And Infinite Jest's challenger, Jerusalem out of Alan Moore's camp, has just entered the ring.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the AMA! 

Do you have a writing routine when you're in the process of writing a book? Do you write at home in a study? Go to a coffee shop? Eat the same thing? Word goals? 

Whatever you'd like to share about your work day would be very interesting!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do hope they go through with a series on Showtime for the You series by Kepnes. I think it will translate really well to a tv series! Joe is such an ass I dont know why I find him slightly likable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one difference I notice with reading on an ereader ... 

I read Tom's River on my Kindle. And I was like damn this is taking forever. I walked by the actual book in a Barnes and Noble and actually saw how thick it was and I recall thinking to myself "Wow, I would have kept pushing this book off for 'later' because of how thick it is." 

I look at long books like a long run. Just one foot in front of the other. Don't think about reading the whole thing while picking it up. Just read the first chapter. Read a few pages every night. And eventually you'll be halfway done! 

What's that saying? What's the best time to plant a tree? 10 years ago. When is the second best time? Today. 

Idk I might have fucked up that quote Im pretty sure I did. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a general rule, I do not. 

I find when I read books, the experience and visuals of the book are still fairly amorphous (plot aside). But once I SEE a movie (with the actors and settings, etc), those things get locked in. And then I find it really takes away from my book reading experience! So I try to read the books before I watch the movies. Especially with thrillers. 

I would not have read A Walk Among the Tombstones (by Lawrence Block) if I saw the movie first. But Oh man ... the book was great! You got a great NYC vibe, with the accents and things (reading the book, that is). But when I saw the movie, I didnt really notice the "hustle" of NYC, the differences of cultures, the burroughs, the subway ... and I wasnt picturing Liam neeson as Scudder. The movie lost the New Yorkness of the book!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 13:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a full plot laid out (beginning, middle, and end?) or just an idea for a story?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still haven't seen ST! Like how long should I expect for ppl to assume *everyone* has seen it? I haven't had the ending or gist spoiled for me yet ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for asking! Because I didn't know either. When I think of lemon, I think of the fruit or a car you but that has mechanical problems quickly after. So I assumed lemon fics were "bad" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 00:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your good *and* bad version  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coworker elicited an eye roll out of me this morning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 18:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me: I have to go to the bathroom. 

Coworker: Shouldnt drink all that beer in the morning; it's full of Vitamin P.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shyamalan did The Visit as well, which I thought was a preeeetty good fun horror flick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seven - David Fincher 

Silence of the Lambs - this one had the most similar visual quality to Don't Breathe. Tak Fujimoto was the guy probably responsible. He also did The Devil (one where they were in the elevator almost the whole time!) 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so I might have basically copy and pasted the whole interview ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great NPR interview with Jason Blum. Talks about the state of horror, why low budget horror is doing so well, and the three things that affect movie budget </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was listening to NPR last night and there was a great interview with Jason Blum of Blumhouse Productions (think Sinister, Purge, Insidious). He put a lot of things into perspective about the state of horror movies at the moment.  [Here is the NPR Link of the transcript](http://www.npr.org/2016/08/30/491984305/with-a-little-magic-small-budget-horror-films-pack-a-big-punch). And here are some excerpts from the interview.

Why low budget works for horror in the first place.

Scary movies benefit from lower budgets. And that's because the scariest things are things that seem the most real. And when you take out all the bells and whistles in production you really have to focus on, you know, small stories that take place in a house. And that's, I think, where people usually feel most vulnerable, in their house. And the room in their house they feel most vulnerable is their bedroom. And if you don't have a lot of money, you kind of have to force - it forces the director to tell these very intimate stories, which I think are much scarier than big effects extravaganzas.

Jason Blum also talks about the THREE things that affect budget

But I think there's kind of a triangle, three things that affect budget - the number of characters, the number of locations and the number of stunts and special effects. And I tell the directors they can kind of choose one of those three things. They can either have a lot of speaking parts, you know, a handful of locations or we can do a stunt or two, but only one of the three.

And if you actually went back and kind of looked at our movies, you'd kind of see that play out. I actually believe, though, that when you really forced parameters from the beginning, it leads to interesting things. And I can't say, you know, the movies are always - always benefit from it, but more often than not I feel like the movies benefit from the lower budgets which push directors to make unusual choices.

He continues, contrasting horror movies with other genres. 

Well, I don't - I actually don't agree with that. I think when you go to see a romantic comedy, I think a couple things are different. First of all, you want a movie star in a romantic comedy. A horror movie is almost better with someone who you don't see every day in magazines because it's kind of scarier. You don't know them, and you can put yourself in their position more easily. I think when you go see a romantic comedy, you want big, big stars that you know well and you want to see them fall in love. And I think that, first of all, right there, it's more expensive.

When you go see an action movie, you want a great action sequence. And that costs money. So it's easy for me to say, you know, I keep my budgets low, but I have a big advantage because I think horror benefits from that. And I don't really - I think most other genres, you actually do need a lot of money to deliver what the audience wants.

Are the big studios going to get in on the action? 

Two or three years ago, everyone used to ask me, are you worried about people copying your model? And I used to say no, I don't worry about it. It seems no one's doing it. If you ask me that now I would say I'm certainly concerned about it a little bit more, for sure. I think studios are - they're - you know, they're oil tankers. They're slow to react, but I do think they're beginning to react now. And it'll be interesting to see what happens in the next year or two. And I bet there'll be a lot of great scary movies, which I'm certainly looking forward to seeing and hope some of them I will have made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 17:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a contrast, I felt like [REC] made me feel confined and I always was trying to "look around the corner" bc of the camera shots. 

I typically don't like shaky camera, documentary style things ... but this worked for me in creating the atmosphere. 

I loved It Follows. Also set in Detroit. I felt it was very dreamy. For some reason I loved [that shot of her in the pool](https://thoughtcatalog.files.wordpress.com/2015/08/8ca0fd9e-e409-4f69-a7f2-d902e94d077a.jpg). I dont know why I think about it. 

That first long shot in Don't Breathe was amazing. It focused on the locks and you felt your eyes lingering on things as the camera slowed down. Fantastic long shot!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a book by Caroline Kepnes called You. but it's about this stalker guy named Joe. He's very in love with himself and looks upon others with disdain. He's definitely an interesting character that gets himself into trouble. 

You can't even find a fandom for it! But it should be a Showtime series eventually so I bet we'll see some stuff then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a movie called The Net with Sandra Bullock that came out around 1995. I'm sure it would be hilarious to watch considering how the "net" has changed so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if that person is like .... so sad and then they get a notification on one of their old stories and they feel joy?! There's so much hiding and negativity in the world, who cares if you put yourself out there (by gushing over an antiquated story)? Just do it and spread joy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mixed up your brackets and your parenthesis! but welcome to ao3!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this book going? A friend keeps suggesting it to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read some thriller/horrors over this summer!

THE TROOP by Nick Cutter - a group of boy scouts and their scoutmaster go on a camping trip to a secluded island when a stranger walks upon their campsite. It has a lot of body horror if you're into that type of thing. And the kids have different personalities so they're easy to tell apart. 

HIDDEN BODIES by Caroline Kepnes - Joe, the passive aggressive stalker/killer we all grew to love in YOU, is back! And he's in LA this go round. More of the same as YOU, but even more incredulous at times. But it's a good thriller with a sense of humor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that rage bladder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 20:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got to the parade a little too late and could not see much. So I would also suggest to get there at a decent time!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 20:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really good one. I'm going to be like "excuse the mess, my desk doesnt normally look this way" if other coworkers are around as well, so I can see what their accusatory-but-silent-"you're full of bullshit" face looks like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 20:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is a silent disco where you wear the headphones? like at bonnaroo?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 20:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started reading My Southern Journey and it seems to be a collection of articles he wrote for various magazines. The book seems to be a great read in small doses. I think if I sat and read it for an hour, I would get a headache from all the Southern references! Huddle House, magnolias, mosquitoes, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/books 
/r/FanFiction 
/r/sixwordstories 
/r/writing 
/r/WritingPrompts 
/r/WritersOf500Words /r/nosleep /r/promptoftheday 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I accidentally got this bittering agent in my mouth right before lunch. It's a chemical we put in our cleaning products to make them taste bitter so kids won't eat it. A little of it goes a LONG way. *cries*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got Scrivener for $20. I can't remember the website though ... But I havent really used it bc I don't understand it and I just always end up reverting back to MS Word. 


edit: appsumo? 

edit2: yes, it was through appsumo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you definitely need a notebook (I'm surprised they didnt hand you one when you joined!). Just a composition notebook will do. Record your weights, how many times you lifted the weight, and a general comment on your perceived exertion. 

You'll get it :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's two types of boxes ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring a 2nd shirt to change into when you leave the gym. It wont help during, but it's just nice to have a not sweaty shirt to change into after the workout for your drive home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My current gym programs on cycles. So we'll see the lifts repeatedly so we actually have a chance to get better at them! 

I definitely understand where you're coming from though. It took me over a year to get the difference between a snatch, a power snatch a hang snatch and then a hang power snatch ... THEN I wouldnt know what weight to even start off with. And the class would move so fast sometimes ... I would always have a moment of panic when I chose the weights for the conditioning. Hopefully I had chosen wisely. 

It was very frustrating. So I was able to make things A LITTLE better by taking better notes in my notebook ... I'd record the weights and then a smiley face or a frowny face (or something in between). That way, when the movement came up again, I'd know if I should hold at that weight or go heavier/lighter.  

And before class, I would start watching youtubes of the movement just so I would know wtf I'd be doing when I got to the gym. 

Later, I took about half a year of olympic lifting with a barbell club and that made ALL the difference. If you know how to snatch and clean and jerk, the other movements are intuitive or you're just more familiar with them. 

Sometimes Crossfit programming isnt direct and focused, so it leads to experiences like this with new people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 16:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joyce Carol Oates writes some dark dark things. I finally read some of her books recently and they are downers that seem from the viewpoint of  lower middle class white females. With globalization and such, I just don't see her winning it. I felt like I was reading stuff from the 70s. The books I've read of hers don't seem current and relevant at all!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read Eat Pray Love and didnt like that either. I ended up liking it better than Wild bc I felt Gilbert actually emotionally and mentally changed on her journey. Strayed, I felt, was the same selfish person coming out of the PCT as she went into it.  I also think that Gilbert was a much better writer. I think Gilbert has other quality books in her ... but I doubt Strayed has other good books in her. 

But after reading EPL and then Wild ... I stayed away from the "girls finding themselves on a solitary journey" genre for a bit! I did read Walk in the Woods by Bill Bryson and loved that! 

Thanks for the book rec. I put it on my ever growing list of to read pile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a completionist; it's a curse. I hardly ever abandon books I start reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 07:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically an ill-prepared woman hikes portions of the PCT. She did heroin and cheated on her husband but we're supposed to feel bad for her bc her mom dies and she had a difficult time coping. 

Spoilers: We have to hear about her bruising from carrying a frame backpack. She won't stfu about it. Like we get it. You are not built for hiking. She also loses one of her shoes (that didn't fit in the first place) on the trail. I think it fell off the mountain. How does that even happen?! And then she gets mad at REI for the replacement shoes taking a few days to get to her remote location (she paid $0 for the replacement ones; some REI rep gets bitched at when Cheryl calls them crying about her free shoes not getting there overnight). Whenever she came across money, she'd spend it on something dumb and then we'd hear her complain how unfair it was that she didn't have money. I think she even left stamps as a tip for a waitress. STAMPS. And she was like addicted to fucking guys, so while she was hiking, she fucks a stranger to create new habits I guess. And then she is done hiking the trail and stops by an ice cream place and laments that no one is buying her a fucking ice cream. 

God it's been so long since I read this book, I'm sure I'm messing it up. I'm also on mobile so lord knows how this post reads. But the author wrote this "memoir" like 10 years after her hike so who knows what liberties she took with her retelling.

And for some god damn reason it became an Oprah book club selection and a movie.

I cannot begin to describe how insufferable I found the author while reading this "memoir". 

And her last name isn't even Strayed. She changed it bc 2edgy4me fuck if i know

edit: and she KNEW she had no money and she still ate out at a diner. Like go to a fucking vending machine!! Why you gotta leave a waitress STAMPS?! So yeah I'm not surprised at all Cheryl racked up some CC bills while writing this book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 05:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this doesn't surprise me one bit after reading her book. it should have been named "entitled" instead of "wild." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 05:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Fates and Furies, by Lauren Groff**

I just started this one, less than 10% in and it's not really gripping my attention. So I just opened up **My Southern Journey, by Rick Bragg** bc it seems to have easy to digest, short chapters. I seem to always go back and forth between books depending upon my mood! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 01:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has been many articles about why Georgia has SO many counties (only 2nd to TX ... where the size at least makes sense). 

http://news.wabe.org/post/why-ga-has-second-highest-number-counties-us

TLDR: GA has so many counties so rural GA could have control over the state. 

How do you get rid of counties?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was free on audible! (Moby Dick, that is).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got Team of Rivals on audiobook! 41 hours .... Most books are like 8-11! But people complained the abridged was TOO abridged.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 21:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I added it on my to-read list  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enemy with Jake Gyllenhaal was one of the better movies I've seen recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 18:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the hair was a great touch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 17:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave Tom where?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Troop by Nick Cutter is relatively new and full of body horror! A scoutmaster and his boy scouts troop are camping on an island when a mysterious ill figure walks upon their camp ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Yorker has a podcast of short stories I think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 05:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God theaters are dark  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 04:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping it was going to end with him dragging her back to the house, like it started. She shouldn't have made it off Scott-free. But she's still kind of in fear. And in a weird way, she picked up a kid (just didn't take 9 months).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 04:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not a rapist but..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 04:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew that white guy with the cornrows wasn't making it out alive  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 22:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kohls, Marshalls type store. In the US.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 22:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did that in middle school. We'd pass notes back and forth but the notes were stories we'd write for each other where I'd write about my friends having sex with their crushes. And then I'd get one back from them about me having sex with my crush. I think this is now known as PWP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 22:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to see Don't Breathe tonight. I've heard great things! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any early birds? Was reading this article called "Why 4 a.m. is the most productive hour" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.wsj.com/articles/why-4-a-m-is-the-most-productive-hour-1471971861

One of the most common challenges to productivity, Dr. Davis says, is that people booby trap their offices with distractions: Desk clutter, email pop-ups, cellphone, Facebook, news feeds. By waking up at 4 a.m., theyve essentially wiped a lot of those distractions off their plate. No one is expecting you to email or answer the phone at 4 a.m. No one will be posting on Facebook. Youve removed the internal temptation and the external temptation.

That really struck me. I get SO distracted if I'm at the computer at 7pm. But like ... 4am is a commitment!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egyptians Take to the Streets Again, Now in Workout Gear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Katrin Davidsdottir gets startled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 14:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 19:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> when you and your cellphone aren't in the same time zone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I about to write a fluff chapter? Fandom is The Walking Dead but looking for suggestions from fanfic writers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 18:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need help! 

In The Walking Dead story, the characters are in a huge group. So I wanted to whittle them down to a smaller group so things are riskier and there's more at stake! So I had my otp and a few others go on a scavenging hunt to get separated from the rest of the group. 

But now I'm stuck. Things are supposed to ramp up in the next chapter or two, but I find myself in the "quiet before the storm".  

It doesnt make sense for them to head for a scavenging run at dusk, so they went early in the morning. And my last chapter literally ends with them like "let's get to scavenging!" 

And so now I set myself up for this boring ass chapter, I feel like. Scavenging for supplies is an excuse to get them to another important part of the story. But I dont want my readers to know that!  

So now Im dealt with writing this chapter where they're looking for supplies. It has no impact really on the plot. So Im not really sure what to do with the scene. I don't want to skip it because I think it would affect the flow too much and be kind of abrupt. 

Is this a fluff chapter? Any advice to make it not just a line to get from A to B? Halp.  

Examples of what you did would also be helpful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> on using words that don't exist in your world (xpost from r/writing) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sade - No Ordinary Love. What type of person are you - end in a happy ending or a wound that will never heal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 15:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was reading this article on [the Guardian](https://www.theguardian.com/music/2012/feb/17/sade-no-ordinary-love): 

there are two kinds of people in this world. Those who believe that Sade's love affair, as sung in her 1995 number No Ordinary Love, will pull through  and those who don't.

Just wondering what reddit thought. Everyone I've asked so far (two people) were pretty adamant the "no ordinary love" doesnt last. 

Here's the [music video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_WcWHZc8s2I) with a little mermaid vibe. 

Let me know if you have any suggestions to make a sweet playlist inspired by this song! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Makeup Tutorial- when you kind of know what you're doing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 06:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writers - do you write across multiple fandoms? Or do you mainly write for one? How do the reviewers differ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What type of feedback you get from separate fandoms? 

I know that my TVD ones tend to get teeny bopper "omgzzzorrzzss luvs it" comments (and I think it's so cute!). But the Homeland fic I wrote has comments with whole sentences (but the reviews are few and far between!). 

Can you comment on the fandoms you write for? And do you prefer to write for one or the other because you prefer the canon or the fandom? 

Hope this makes sense, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a good book about an animal that you've read recently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 17:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

I just checked out [Soul of an Octopus](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/22609485-the-soul-of-an-octopus) from the library. I've learned octopuses are organized body, head, legs whereas we're head, body legs. And they can taste through their skin. And they can make eye contact with you and they're super smart. They also are in the same animal groups as clams and snails (which are animals that are known for being kinda not smart). And I'm just 5 pages in. 

I also recently downloaded [a book about bats](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/23719330-the-secret-lives-of-bats?from_search=true). And I know there was that book one time about the bees (the name escapes me but I remember there was a lot of viral content going around about bees and the end of the world!). 

Anyways, can you share a book about animals that you've read recently (good or bad) and let us know what you learned or thought about the book? 

edit: the plural of octopus is octopuses and octopi because octopus is greek and the -i ending happens after latin stuff. internet, correct me if i'm wrong bc I'm going off memory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this a joke? Brendan Fraser on the next season of The Affair?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 20:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyones Saying The Same Thing About Cursed Child Being Fanfic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone's Saying The Same Thing About "Cursed Child" Being Fanfic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 16:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An open letter to J.K. Rowling: Please, just stop. - The Boston Globe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're going to go CrossFit themed Wedding, you cant beat dave castro officiating and bride/groom nanos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/fanfiction prompts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 20:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I've been in and out of the sub recently. I was just wondering if someone could let me know how the prompt challenges work now? 

I see that the stickied thread shows where to post and where the collections are. I'm more curious about the timetable. How often are they posted and how long do you get to write them once the thread is posted? 

And is the thread typically stickied??

THank youuuuuu-hooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> monica brown shoes  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 14:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FloElite Fantasy League Reddit 1 - first Round is over, submit 2nd picks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First round has been chosen, so the draft order is locked. I will have a google docs up by the end of the day today which will show the available athletes you can still choose! But for now ... [just browse these comments](https://www.reddit.com/r/crossfit/comments/4si4o7/floelite_fantasy_league_reddit_1_peeps_make_your/) and choose someone who hasnt already been chosen. 

Here is the order of the draft for this round: 

1. John H
2. JSRRR
3. Badblood44
4. John M
5. yannism
6. Blok1
7.  Bobackopolis
8. Richiemiz44
9. deppsepp
10. flowseidon
11. Cat
12. subject8145

A few housekeeping things! 

- because we all have lives and schedules, if it's not your turn to choose, feel free to post anyways and give me 3 to 5 choices in the order that you want. if your top choice has already been chosen, i will move to the next available athlete. 

- i need the FloElite usernames for the following redditors: deppsepp, bobackopolis, blok1, yannism, and JSRRR

- if you're in the previous list of names and you signed up for reddit 2 and want to stay in this league, you need to sign up again with a new email address and tell me your name so I can assign you the athlete you've already chosen. (if they don't show up later ... i guess we'll throw that athlete back into the mix :/ ) 

- JSRRR - bill grundler? is he masters? your options are just men, women, and teams. So you get TWO choices. One for your next turn and one to replace Grundler. 


edit: [Google Spreadsheet of available athletes](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1VZjf2YoJvxCeyQy1LFJ0WqIccx8sUHz4Co5IxzqHaV8/edit?usp=sharing).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FloElite Fantasy League Reddit 1 peeps, make your draft picks in this Post, Please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 19:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont mean to cloud up the sub or anything! But since we don't know each other irl, this is the best way I know how to make the draft picks.  Because I'm the commissioner, I have to input your draft picks. 

The order will go like this ... whoever posts first, gets the first draft pick. Second, gets the 2nd draft pick, etc. Once an athlete is chosen, that athlete is no longer eligible for selection. 

For the 2nd round, selection will go from the reverse order. I'll try to tag you guys for the later rounds and post which athletes are still available as pickings go down.  

**Your team will consist of three men, three women, and one affiliate.**

You have by July 14th to make your first pick. If you don't make it, we're moving onto the 2nd round on Jul 15th. Selection should go faster from that point on. Games start July 22nd so hopefully we can figure it out by then!

MAY THE ODDS BE EVER IN YOUR FAVOR

edit: if someone has a good google docs idea, lemme know. 

edit2: After the first round, I will have a google doc up of the draft order and the men, women and teams still available. 

edit3: [Make 2nd draft picks here](https://www.reddit.com/r/crossfit/comments/4su7bf/floelite_fantasy_league_reddit_1_first_round_is/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ideas for stories. Do you have too many? Not enough? Where do they come from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 18:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I was browsing /r/writing and came across this [BLOGPOST](http://www.neilgaiman.com/Cool_Stuff/Essays/Essays_By_Neil/Where_do_you_get_your_ideas%3F) by Neil Gaiman. 

Every published writer has had it - the people who come up to you and tell you that they've Got An Idea. And boy, is it a Doozy. It's such a Doozy that they want to Cut You In On It. The proposal is always the same - they'll tell you the Idea (the hard bit), you write it down and turn it into a novel (the easy bit), the two of you can split the money fifty-fifty. 

I'm reasonably gracious with these people. I tell them, truly, that I have far too many ideas for things as it is, and far too little time. And I wish them the best of luck. 

The Ideas aren't the hard bit. They're a small component of the whole. Creating believable people who do more or less what you tell them to is much harder. And hardest by far is the process of simply sitting down and putting one word after another to construct whatever it is you're trying to build: making it interesting, making it new. 

I have more ideas than stories in progress ... so I'm good on ideas right now. I dont need anymore at the moment. But they still come. So I just write them in my iPhone Notes and we'll see which one gets to ever see the light of day ...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fantasy League on FloElite for CrossFit Games. Come get some </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 16:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The It Movies Have Just Started Filming and They're Already Freaking Us Out (The Balloons!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 20:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will The Drug Scandals Get Weightlifting Kicked Out Of The Olympics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 16:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maryland woman Lauren Conner found alive after falling overboard on Sassafras River "CrossFit training saved my life" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 19:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do crossfitters follow paleo because of science or belief? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just browsing the NYTimes and came across this article [A Study on Fats that Doesn't Fit the Story Line](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/04/16/upshot/a-study-on-fats-that-doesnt-fit-the-story-line.html). And I came across this quote: 

It has also added to the growing concern that when it comes to nutrition, personal beliefs often trump science.

Do you feel the Crossfit community tends to do this with the Paleo diet? I feel like a lot of crossfitters stick with paleo, but then you read about heart healthy diets, the paleo lifestyle is not really promoted - [Mayo Clinic](http://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/heart-disease/in-depth/heart-healthy-diet/art-20047702)

Thank you in advance for your insights! No judgements, I promise I'm not trying to trap anyone here. Just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue Apron meal from a cooking newb - catfish and potatoes. This is my first time making a meal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 04:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Condensed, or just dense? The apps that turn books into 15-minute reads. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 17:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you run a book club? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 16:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have like 3 or 4 friends that are all interested in the same book. 2 of us already have the book. 1 is pretty willing to buy it. And the last girl will definitely join in from peer pressure. 

I have the perfect storm to set up a book club. But I've never really done one. 

Do I set up a facebook event? What is a fair length of time to read it? What do we do when we actually meet each other to discuss the book (preferably with alcohol and food)? Where do we get questions? Or do we just talk plot and characters? 

What makes a successful book club?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First day of summer! Share </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello r/books! 

It is the first day of summer, the longest day of the year, summer solstice. It is also a time of renewal, a time of freedom, of growth! 

I was curious if you had any books or quotes that reminded you of summer bc F**K WINTER. 

And so with the sunshine and the great bursts of leaves growing on the trees, just as things grow in fast movies, I had that familiar conviction that life was beginning over again with the summer. 

The Great Gatsby

edit: Was not meaning to just put "Share" in the title like that. I was going for a complete sentence ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crab Island on Friday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 02:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're in town for the weekend and we're trying to share a pontoon or boat with people just to save a bit of money. So in the off chance that someone else is here looking for the same ... plz message me. 

We are 3 Atlanta early 30 year old females. Looking to go during the day tomorrow. 

Or feel free to give us some tips! Not looking to swim or jet ski ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Girls (Emma Cline) and American Girls for YA readers: Was this planned? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 17:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people have recently posted about Emma Cline's The Girls. Essentially Emma Cline writes about a girl getting caught up in a "Manson-like cult".

Well, I was browsing Amazon and found this in an upcoming June YA releases. The book is called American Girls, about a Manson obsessed 15 year old. 

From the summary: 

Anna is a fifteen-year-old girl slouching toward adulthood, and she's had it with her life at home. So Anna "borrows" her stepmom's credit card and runs away to Los Angeles, where her half-sister takes her in. But LA isn't quite the glamorous escape Anna had imagined.

As Anna spends her days on TV and movie sets, she engrosses herself in a project researching the murderous Manson girlsand although the violence in her own life isn't the kind that leaves physical scars, she begins to notice the parallels between herself and the lost girls of LA, and of America, past and present.

Anyways, I thought that was odd to see two buzzy June books coming out concerning very similar and specific subject matters - one catered to adults and the other to YA.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] Ethan and Brona - quick question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have they not met up after she was changed? Does Ethan think she's dead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel bad for saying this but Josh Hartnett is horrible. He takes me out of the immersive experience of the show! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 17:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just caught up on the season and after hearing all the rave reviews of the acting with "A Blade of Grass", it got me to thinking about my distaste for Hartnett. Is this just me?  

Ethan is a great role for any actor but whenever Josh Hartnett is on screen, I feel like he knocks the dynamic tempo off between the actors. He has no emotion, no range. He's boring, he's flatter than a week old diet coke. 

It's like Hollywood tried to make Hartnett relevant but Channing Tatum came. Joshua Jackson is another actor in a similar vein of Hartnett's but I feel that Jackson can show a wide range of emotions (like he did in The Affair). Hartnett rarely shows a range of emotion and when he does, he's transitioning into a wolf and the CGI covers up most of that. 

Black Dahlia and Wicker Park were generally viewed as huge disappointments and I don't see Hartnett ever getting the shot at carrying a film again. I think he's lucky that he can piggy back off the great Penny Dreadful cast (even though he's such a vacuum onscreen. It's like ... DO SOMETHING WITH YOUR EYES ... YOUR MOUTH ... CHANGE THE CADENCE TO YOUR SPEECH ARE YOU A WALKING CORPSE? WAKE UP, MAN.). 

Regardless, love the show! Team Dracula though. ANNNNNNND that guy went to Julliard. Very excited :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MAIN SPOILERS] Is there an ELI5 version of the episode recaps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 16:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, 

I browsed the wiki and didn't see any links for what I'm looking for specifically. So I'm just posting!

I've been watching GoT casually since it's inception (the tv show, that is). And each season is building on the previous and I keep losing names/faces. 

So with the most recent episode, Jaime seems to be fighting a Tully's uncle. WHY? Who is he? Have we met him before? And then Sansa and Jon went to that 5 year old's place; have we heard of them before? And then they went to that older guy's place and I totally don't remember his connection to the Boltons. 

And I'm totally lost on Bran and him going into that fugue state where he's observing Ned fighting (and Ned lied about how the fight ended? What was the significance of that?). And then Bran saw the inception of the White Walkers ... I heard there was a Stark connection, but I missed that too while watching the show. 

I get the big picture, but I am definitely missing a lot of information. Is there some type of recap or blog that's available for people like me ... someone that goes through the episode and, perhaps, over explains things? 

Thank you! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Being with Krista Tippett: The Theology of CrossFit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 02:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rings Sadako and The Grudges Kayako Play Baseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 17:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's been on your to-read shelf the longest and you still have a genuine interest to actually read it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 00:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have owned Jonathan Strange and Mr Norell since 2006 or 2007, just sitting on my shelf. I *want* to read it. But I havent. I'm always like - oh, that'll be there when I get back.  I think there's the whole length of it that intimidates me as well. But if I would have read it when I bought it, I could have been way ahead of the tv show. And now I refuse to watch the tv show bc I have the book sitting on the top shelf of my bookcase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horror magazines/anthologies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 21:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do any of you guys read horror magazines (or even online magazines) with submitted horror fiction? 

Who are some of the big, established players? I wanted to check one out but wasnt sure where to start.  I'm looking for horror short stories essentially. Nothing longer than like 10,000 words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Heather can write (Spoiler: bc of her HP fanfiction) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 21:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a fandom you're afraid to write for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 16:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mainly thinking of fandoms where the readers are probably smarter about the universe than you are? 

I have a general, superficial love of Doctor Who but I feel like the fandom would rip me to shreds when I inevitably would get the physics of the universe wrong. Or get a relationship wrong. 

I will NEVER know that fandom well enough to write fanfics for it. Same with like ... Star Trek or Star Wars or GoT. The universe is bigger than my capabilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Fun] Jared Enderton shows us the top snatch start positions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 17:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> that's what i thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 12:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fantasy Regionals for this weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 03:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who did that last time? Can you do it again? 

Sincerely, 
53rd place girl.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FANFIC WRITERS: Have you used weather to create more symbolism or atmosphere in your works? Let us know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 23:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it spring and beautiful? Or was it a dark and stormy night? Was it snowing severely? Or a mysterious cloud of fog? 

Rainbows??? 

Describe a scene, then let us know how the weather was.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [xpost r/funny] Game of Thrones crossover, I'd check it out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 21:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Nick in Blood in the Streets [spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 18:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Its Like to Compete at Regionals When Youre Not a CrossFit Superstar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 17:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do any of you play around with writing an original work? What would it be about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 15:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one where these girls go to a meditation retreat ... those ones where you "disconnect" and turn off your social media, turn in your phone, sauna teepees in the desert, clean the place, eat minimal/clean diet ... and then when it's time to go, the leaders don't let you leave! And you dont have your cell or anything to get help. It's in a remote location.... 

And it would be a thriller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Capturing Kids: How to write horror stories for children/teens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 23:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! I'm currently reading Writing Horror: A Handbook by the Horror Writers Association (edited by Mort Castle). I wouldnt bother picking it up unless you're REALLY interested in the title. But I really wanted to share this essay about writing horror stories geared towards MG/YA (Middle Grade, Young Adult). Even if you don't write horror, there's great advice here geared towards MG/YA writers generally. Also, this was compiled around 1997 sooooo I'm sure the landscape has changed. 


This particular post is heavily plagiarized from "Capturing Kids" by Jill M Morgan

A few WARNINGS

1. Be wary writing about witches (the occult); the editors won't buy it. 
2. Don't write on-stage violence in books for kids. Most editors want you to evoke that scary feeling without drawing a single drop of blood from your characters. 

Books exist that break these rules (and they're good books!) but they're not the norm. 

**THE MIDDLE GRADE MARKET** 
(Think "Goosebumps")

Turns out, young readers are loyal. Once they find an author or series they like, they want to read everything from that author or series. Books for kids also have a long shelf life (months, even years compared to adult horror which hovers around 6 weeks). 

A few guidelines for the MG market (8-12 year olds)

1. *Manuscript Length*: Typically, 120 pages. Double-spaced with one inch margins. 
2. *Length of chapters*: Ten pages is about right. Close to ca. 12 chapters per book. 
3. *Point of View (POV)*: Typically, a single-character POV. The protagonist won't know what other characters are thinking but she can observe their actions and expressions and draw conclusions based on that. (Again, this is/was the NORM. Doesnt mean you cant do multiple POVs)
4. *Illustrations*: Not many. Novels that have illustrations at the beginning of each chapter are called chapter books, meant for younger readers. 
5. *Where to begin*: Start on a day that is different. When the 1st chapter opens, the MG reader wants to step right into the setting and the plot. 

*WHERE TO BEGIN EXAMPLES*

"I don't want new friends," said Jenny.

You have a girl with a problem that kids can immediately understand and relate to. They know how miserable she's feeling. What kid hasn't been lonely or afraid to make new friends? 

Another example from Jill Morgan's own book: 

In the morning's rays of sunlight, when the Spider's web ladder was sparkling with dew, Mr. Ambrose descended from the now hidden moon, climbed down the lacy rungs of the Web, and stepped onto the sidewalk before the shop, Broadmore's Used Books and Antiques. 

MG readers have shorter attention spans than YA readers. The horror fiction should be fast paced. They typically want to know what happened, not necessarily why it happened. YA readers enjoy building tension of what might be lurking in the woods, *MG readers want to see the bear*. 

Doesn't mean you write something shallow and hectic. MG readers can be discriminating and they can appreciate rich subplots with fully developed characters with a past, present and future. They like to identify with characters in their fave books and empathy is one of this age group's strongest traits! 

*THE FOLLOWING IS GENERALLY TRUE FOR CHILDREN'S LIT*

1. The main character needs to show growth. Kids' lives are about learning. They are constantly changing, becoming wiser, stronger. The main character in a MG book should demonstrate that type of progression. 

2. The protagonist needs to solve the problem. Not the police, not the parents ... it should be the child protagonist. 

3. Show and not tell. Would you rather read a character telling us how scared they were when the flash flood knocked his house off the foundation OR *showing* the kid falling off the roof of that house, right into the churning water? BE THERE. 

**THE YOUNG ADULT YA MARKET**

1. *Manuscript length*: YA novels are b/n 150-200 pages. (Again, this might be outdated!). 

2. *POV*: It's common to have more than one POV. Keep the POV shifts in separate chapters or sections of chapters. Use a drop down/white space transition or chapter breaks to mark a change in POV. 

3. *Length of chapters*: 10-15 pages is normal.

4. *Setting*: Always seen from the teen's perspective - school, friends' houses, their cars, their rooms, the local pizza joint or other teen hangouts. 

5. *Fear level*: In YA horror, the stakes are higher. The roller coaster thrill ride isn't enough. Keep upping the odds. 

6. *Parents*: YA protagonists should have parents who are like sturdy trees in the background, around for support but rarely noticed. YA horror novels rarely deal with parents. Consider them on vacation from the plot. Parents play a bigger role in MG novels, since younger characters need parents to drive them places. 

7. *Keep it clean*. It's best to keep swearing and 4-letter words to a minimum. Beware of using the latest phrases too. Peppering your dialogue with current slang will date your novel quickly. "Current" doesnt last as long as it used to. Strive for "young but not trendy". 

8. *Sex*. Thinking about the opposite sex *is* the stuff of YA novels. Secret crushes, budding romances are wonderful subplots. Stick to shared glances, a few well-chosen words, hand holding - and THEN: *The* romantic kiss and suggestion of future dating by the book's conclusion. Characters remain chaste. Think of your MG reader as a 9-year old and your YA reader a 12 or 13 year old. But realize that many 10   11 year olds are sampling YA books. The audience is getting younger and younger, which is why it's important to temper violent or sexually explicit scenes. 

**RANDOM ADDENDUMS**

- A large percentage of the kid novel space is dedicated to paperback originals. At paperback prices, kids are able to choose books they want to read, rather than having parents buy the (expensive) hardcovers. Kids know what they like, and they like chillers. 

- Make a point to hang around a group of the age range you're shooting for and listen to their conversations. Are the sentences constructed in the same way adult conversations are? Or do the kids speak to each other in a more choppy, abbreviated style? 

- Recent name-the-baby books can give you good current sounding names (or some buzzfeed list ...). Consider multinational, old-fashioned names or biblical names as well, giving you a chance to really consider your character's traits before you name him or her. 

- Before writing, think about where the real action or excitement begins. Is it where you planned to start? If not, maybe rethink the order of your novel. Kids want to find "the good parts" as soon as they open up the book. 

- Consider where you're going to sell your story or novel. Writing for a specific market will tremendously increase your chances of selling your finished work. 

- You may not have access to an editor, but you do have access to the kinds of novels a particular publishing house seems to prefer. Study your market. Look at what the company is *successful* at publishing. A lot of valuable time can be wasted by sending the wrong kind of proposal to an editor. 

- Pay attention to what *isn't* there. That can mean a lot in publishing too. 

**TLDR;** Know your readers and give them dramatic openings, realistic and likable characters, fast paced chapters and a steady dose of excitement leading to high-peaked thrills. And always remember to keep it clean. Combine this with studying the market, focus your writing on the requirements of specific editors or publishing houses, and noticing what isn't out there as well as what's been overdone. YOU MIGHT GET FAN MAIL FROM KIDS!!

**EPILOGUE:** Turns out capturing kids was more of a hassle than I originally thought. I read this and really wanted to share with the writing community. 

I have posted other excerpts from this book in /r/FanFiction  

1. [How to write believable horror](https://www.reddit.com/r/FanFiction/comments/4dbqcn/saw_this_writing_advice_for_horror_writers_i/)
2. [Writing Dialogue](https://www.reddit.com/r/FanFiction/comments/4fdbji/some_thoughts_about_dialogue/) - this one didnt go over so well! 
3. [Writing Action Scenes](https://www.reddit.com/r/FanFiction/comments/4gk1io/writing_action_scenes/)

If you ever want to chat writing and don't want to worry about your grammar in the post, head over to /r/FanFiction and shoot the "crap" with us. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing Action Scenes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 19:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the better essays from Writing Horror: A Handbook by the Horror Writers Association (edited by Mort Castle). I wouldnt bother picking it up unless you're REALLY interested in the title. 

This particular post is heavily plagiarized from "Keep It Moving, Maniacs" by Jay R. Bonansinga

**Establishing a Rhythm**

Find the internal "beat" of the scene and let it drive the prose as a percussionist would drive a band. 

Example: "He cocked the Python as he brought it up *snick snick* and the figure blurred, bloomed bloomed green in his vision . . . . " - Silence of the Lambs

The previous had a bit of a rhythm to it, right? Jay R. wrote an example just for his essay (again, we're not expecting Nobel Prize winning writing from these examples that he puts out). He starts us out with a writer trying to write an action scene: 

Something ominous was brewing. the horror writer had been sensing it for weeks. An imminent change in the weather. 

Jay R. wants to build up tension and excitement, so throws in a little bit of run-on sentences to match the thought patterns of the character. 

... the action began to flow like furious river-rapids, flowing, FLOWING, furiously, carrying the reader away in its currents, and the storm raged in the writer's mind, and the thunder rumbled ... 

The technical tricks you can use are: 

- abruptly inserting an ALL CAPS word to suggest an abrupt change/frenzied chaos 

- alliteration at the right rhythmic point to drive home the unstoppable aspect of your juggernaut 

- sing-song style ("floorboards beginning to quake-quake-quake) to drive home rhythm

- break the scene up using a dash at the end of a sentence and have it open up to a new single phrase paragraph.  (not shown)

**Getting Inside the POV Character**

Example: "When he woke up he was unaware of his consciousness. There was darkness everywhere, on all sides." Clive Barker

Suspense looks boring form a distance. But when viewed up close, things can get dramatic. Look at an anthill from a distance, it ain't no thang. But get to their size, woah, shit's real cray.

Jay R's example: 

At first, it was nothing more than a subtle, metronomic beat in his head, a rhythmic ticking that began to build as he wrote the next suspense sequence. He began to hear a sort of internal percussion, complete with cymbal crashes, tempo changes, drum solos and a constant beat underscoring it all. . . . 

When the action kicks in, the scene should always be perceived (when possible) from the inside character. When gunshots are fired, don't merely describe how they sound to the characters, describe how they feel. When someone is hurt, dont merely describe the blood and guts, describe the mind ... what the pain and the fear feels like. 

"With apologies to Galileo, in action scenes, the universe revolves around the central characters."

Action can only be generated through *character*. We must know your characters quirks, we must know he has an adjustable rate mortgage going through the roof and his kid just got back from the orthodontist with a mouth full of metal. Then, and only then, do we care about the character. 

And action is a virus .. it spreads. So if you jump from one poitn of view to another, you can really tighten the suspense and intensify the action. 

**Engaging the Environment**

To prevent your work from getting into slapstick comedy use your environment. 

If we go back to Silence of the Lambs (Spoilers ahead if you havent watched the movie and yes Im judging you) ... Clarice Starling is in the killer's cellar. She has just found dead people and and she knows the killer is hiding somewhere in the basement, waiting for her. Suddenly, the lights go out and we see Starling stumbling around in the dark, banging into things, etc ... add a laugh track to that and you have a screwball comedy! But watch her touch the hot furnace pipes and trip over her own feet through the infrared green of the killer's gaze and now it's frightening.  

One of the tricks is to find artifacts in the environment - hot furnace pipes, wallpaper separating, plaster crumbling - and integrate them into the action. It reinforces the authenticity of the action scene (this kind of stuff naturally occurs all the time, right?) and it also can intensify the experience for the reader. 

**Seasoning Your Scenes with Detail**

Horror Fiction (and probably scifi) perhaps more than any other genre depends on a suspension of disbelief. 

In the short story "On the Slab" by Harlan Ellison, our hero has to fight a giant bird that has arrived from the netherworld and crashed through a skylight. Our hero rips a fire extinguisher from the wall ... 

 ... the virulent Halon 1301 mixture sprayed in a white stream over the bird's head. The mixture of fluorine, bromine, iodine, and chlorine washed the vulture, spurted into its eyes, filled its mouth.

Amid the action, we get the chemical minutiae of the fire extinguisher. Because we get the detail, we can almost see smell and taste the terror through dreamlike reportage. These minute details can give us texture to a story. 

**Funneling Time**

Good literary action should feel like an inverted funnel. So as a scene progresses, time should compress in on itself. 

Jay R's examples starts off describing weeks. Then, days. Then, hours: 

The horror writer had been sensing it for weeks. An imminent change in the weather .... 
Then, late one night, alone in his cluttered little garret, he decided to let it happen. He felt a weird certainty deep down in his marrow as he poured the first few fingers of the evening's espresso and lit his first Camel straight .... 

And then he starts to compress the time further. Tension mounts, and as the words start flowing, the passage of time is tightened down to a moment by moment roller coaster: 

At first, it was nothing more than a subtle, metronomic beat in his head .... He began to hear a sort of internal percussion ... 

... and the action began to flow like furious river-rapids, flowing, FLOWING, furiously, carrying the reader away in its currents ... 

**The Final Blow**

You're in the car accident. You, the writer, are in the driver's seat. You feel everything; you sense time is slowing down and all you can do is watch the horrifying movie in your mind. "Think of that feeling - the way movement seems to blur and get all bogged down like a taffy pull. That's the moment just before impact. Find the literary equivalent and you'll be holding your reader rapt."

**FINAL THOUGHTS** 

The key to writing excellent action is PERCEPTION. The rhythm, the POV, the environment, the detail ... it's all filtered through human perspective. 

That's what action is. 

A human being in peril - forced to *perceive*. 



Comments? Thoughts? Additions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the last nonfiction book you have completed reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not looking for the coolest or the best, just the most recent. So don't cherry pick! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/FanFiction's Daily Discussion - April 25th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 16:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl Through Glass, by Sari Wilson [Kindle] - $1.99 young ballerina falls in love with her much older mentor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 15:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Thoughts About Dialogue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 20:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

Again, I'm reading this collection of essays on writing horror. And I came across this one. Always use your best judgment when writing! The following is stylistic advice from writer David Morrell. 

These are mainly DO NOTs. However, there are exceptions to every rule! But if you find yourself repeatedly making these mistakes, you might want to live by these "do nots" for awhile until you can get away from some of these common crutches that aren't doing your dialogue any favors. 

**BE CAREFUL REPEATING THE PERSON'S NAME WITHIN THE DIALOGUE. PEOPLE SELDOM ADDRESS EACH OTHER LIKE THIS ANYWAYS**

"Jane, I'm going downtown to the library," Dick said.

"Okay, Dick, I'll see you later," Jane said. 

Reads a little silly, right? People tend to address other people by their names in movies. But movies have to identify the characters on screen. And fiction writing is not movie writing. 

Try to use names in dialogue only when it's unavoidable - egs. the start of a telephone conversation, during a dark scene in a basement, or when there is no other way for the reader to find out a name. 

**LIMIT YOUR SPEECH TAGS**

"I'll track you down and kill you!" Jane hissed. 

You can't hiss if you don't use sibilants (and there aren't any in this speech). "Jane growled"? It won't work. "Jane spat"? Have you ever seen anyways spit while they speak? Similarly, characters shouldnt bark, rasp or rumble their dialogue. At the end of the day, this draws unwanted attention to your dialogue. 

Restrict the verbs used in speech tags to "said" and "asked." In extreme cases, use "demanded," "insisted" or "shouted" and "screamed"? Maybe "whispered" or "murmured." But don't use many.  

**DO YOU EVEN NEED YOUR SPEECH TAGS IN THE FIRST PLACE?** 

"I'll track you down and kill you!" Jane said.

"I'll track you down and kill you!" Jane shouted.

"Said" is an understatement after the exclamation point. And "shouted" is redundant. 

Do you even need the speech tag? 

"I'll stab you in your sleep." Jane's eyes meant every word. 

No one is going to win any writing awards with that sentence, but why not include description a little at a time ... where you would normally have a fill-in-the-blank speech tag? Speech tags are intended to just identify the speaker. If you don't need it, don't use it. 

But, no one is against speech tags completely! They're needed at times, as we mentioned. And they can create interesting effects - like a pause, for example: 

"I know he doesn't believe I'll come after him," Jane said. "His mistake." 

**SPEECH TAGS: ADVERBS**

"I gave that jerk the best three days of my life," Jane said bitterly. 

It's redundant. Resist using adverbs. Having the dialogue communicate what it is supposed to will help you not have to use the adverb. The adverb just points out that you failed in communicating what you were supposed to. 

Exception: A speech tag's adverb might be acceptable if the dialogue is meant to be spoken in contradiction to its apparent sense. 

"I gave that jerk the best three days of my life," Jane said proudly. 

**PUNCTUATION**

"You son of a bitch, I hate your guts" Jane shouted. 

The speech tag is redundant, and so is the exclamation point, which is implied by "You son of a bitch." With the following example, the intensity is there, but the staginess/camp has been eliminated" 

"You son of a bitch, I hate your guts." Jane's gaze never left his. 

Now, onto the exclamation point. 

"My God, she's got a knife!"

vs. 

 
"My God, she's got a knife."

I don't miss the exclamation point. And you don't want your page littered with exclamation points; you don't want to stab your reader's eyes with !!!s. 

If you would like to add emphasis to a question, resist the following:

"What am I going to do?!" Jane exclaimed. 

Let's try: 

Jane could barely get the words out. "What am I going to do?" 

or 



"*What am I going to do?*" Jane stared at every face in the library. 

The italics can serve the same function as an exclamation point. Just use it in moderation. But if the question has some for of cursing, the italics become redundant just as an exclamation mark is redundant after a statement that contains cursing. 

**COLLOQUALISMS**

William Strunk's Element of Style - also very much against colloquialisms and slang! 

Use them in *extreme moderation*. 

"Well," "Yeah, "You know," "okay," and the like are necessary to create the illusions of verisimilitude, but unless Jane is a Valley Girl and vapid expressions are a method of characterizing, writer beware! The words don't say anything, after all. They are blank spots on the page and impede the flow of your story. 

Slang is also a form of colloquialism. It's necessary to enliven dialogue, but unfortunately current slang quickly becomes dated. 

"That's cool. Give me a high five." 

Unless you're writing a parody, most writers distance themselves from slang. 

Next, don't upstage your dialogue with trying to imitate accents. 

"Dinja know he wuz gonna gitcha?" 

Your character might talk like this, but most of the time, your reader will note the unusual spelling and have to slow their reading to understand what the character is actually saying. Use it when you need to, but perhaps you don't have to use so much of it? 

"Didn't you know he was gonna get you?" 

For some people tastes, the single misspelling adequately conveys the character's illiteracy - without obstructing your narrative. 

That being said, we are writing fanfiction so you are allowed to throw all these rules out the door! Just passing out food for thought, I said. 


**WHAT ARE YOUR DIALOGUE TIPS?** 

(I've suggested people read their narrative out loud to see if it flows, and this particular guy suggested *against* that. He's like - write the visual cues because you cant guarantee your reader will add inflection and tone where you're adding it.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler inside] Can you help me figure out which season I watched based on the last cliffhanger I remember? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 16:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the one where Keri Russell got shot. And I think the season ended. 

I really love the show and I have the current season recording but I dont know which seasons I need to watch to catch up!

edit: thanks guys! I have season 3 and this season recording ... just gotta find season 2 I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL no Backstreet Boys song ever reached number one in the United States. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 18:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well Fed: Paleo Recipes for People Who Love to Eat, by Melissa Joulwan [Kindle, Cookbook, Paleo] - $1.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 23:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/FanFiction Daily Discussion - April 8th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 15:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Rage Yoga' encourages posing while cursing, drinking, and listening to metal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 17:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audible App new feature: How do you delete clips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 18:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I accidentally made one and I dont want it!!!

edit: I kept clicking the ellipses ... I didnt even think to swipe. Duh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this writing advice for horror writers (I think it applies to crossover fanfic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 18:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading *Writing Horror*. The book essentially gives pretty standard, duh writing advice so I would not recommend it for most readers.  But after coming across [this thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/FanFiction/comments/4d1vbl/has_anyone_ever_told_you_your_writing_is_not/) AND after reading "No Shield of Disbelief by Dominick Cancilla, I thought I'd share this viewpoint with you guys. I think it applies really well to crossovers and even some of the existing universes that fanfic writers deal with ... but they like to add their own twist on it.  

Here we go: 

- It is usually a good idea to keep a fictional universe as close to reality as possible. A short story should differ from accepted reality in *a single way*. Too much deviation from our accepted world as we know it will strain the reader's credulity or demand too much explanation. 

- Once you decide how reality will be twisted, you must stick with it and keep it in mind for the duration of the work. That means not changing the rules midstream or introducing additional unbelievables in the last sentence to create a "surprise" ending. 

CONSISTENCY IS THE CORE OF BELIEVABILITY. 

A reader will find no tension in a world where everything is apparently possible. Or they will wonder why fantastic things are so little used. (So, if you have no limits on a witch's powers, the reader will wonder, "Why is the witch making things so hard for herself, why doesnt she just make herself beautiful and give herself a lot of money?")

An extension of this: You have a group of vampires that decide to use a town for "cattle". How do the vampires keep the town in check?  What are the vampire's supernatural powers in YOUR world? Were they made by science? This might seem like a TON of work. But how are you going to feel when you write a nice story and your readers undermine it all because they start commenting, "Why don't the villagers just leave during the day when the vampires are asleep?" 

Also, though the unusual exists in your fictive universe, the inhabitants, your characters, might not necessarily know it. They should react appropriately. 

egs. Muggles being exposed to wizardy in the HP Universe. How would they react? 

Or if you have a Mummy/House MD crossover, a  skeptic, like House MD (he is a skeptic right?) sees the mummy ... he will think it's a person in monstrous makeup rather than a supernatural corpse. 

Or if a portal opens up and sucks the a building into it and those are NOT the mechanics in the universe, your character is probably NOT going to be merely curious ... they're going to run, scream hysterically, whatever ... they're going to freak out

If a story 

- believes in the unreality it is presenting 

- the characters react appropriately 

- the logic and mechanics are consistent 

- well-defined limits for man, nature and monster are set

THEN your tale will not be overburdened by the unbelievable. The reader will be DENIED their shield of disbelief, and the horrors you present will strike marrow and bone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the Game of Thrones fans (via Team Coco and my Facebook memory from 3 years ago) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 17:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/fanfiction Daily Discussion - April 4th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 14:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's on your mind?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/FanFiction Daily Discussion - April 1st </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 15:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Walking Dead Ace Ventura mashup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 14:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/FanFiction Daily Discussion - March 31st </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 15:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's on your mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wolf Creek franchise is premiering six 1-hour long episodes in Australia ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 18:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General Discussion - March 30th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 15:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I'm on the east coast, thought I'd follow in /u/MovePastTheFeeling footsteps and try the daily discussion thread out again.

How's it going? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have a notp? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 03:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a least fave pairing? Let it out here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Patterson donating another $1.75 million to libraries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 19:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book of Ages: The Life and Opinions of Jane Franklin, by Jill Lepore [Kindle] - $1.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 16:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Posting as you write versus Writing the whole thing then posting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 16:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've posted drabbles and short 4-5 chapter things after I've writtten the whole thing. But with my longer work, I'm posting chapters as I write them. I have a direction I want the story to go. And I know some things that will happen that I'm trying to foreshadow. But, once I post a chapter, like ... it's locked. And I can't really "fix" anything. 

Have any of you guys tried both? Posting as you go versus writing the work out completely then posting chapters frequently? 

I see that having it completely written out and posting it with regularity is probably best for everyone. Butttttt as I'm writing, I like the rush I get from posting a chapter!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There has to be a starter pack for this chick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 21:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have a great idea for a movie? What is it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 15:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get Over Yourself by LBEB (see also: stop putting other people down bc they dont do what you do) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 16:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] What should the establishment do if Trump wins the nomination? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they surrender and just support the candidate? 

Do they get someone like Romney to run third party?

Are there options for them at the convention? 

What will they do? What *should* they do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Library Sale $17.50 - includes All Souls trilogy, Big Little Lies, and Annihilation by Jeff Vandemeer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 20:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Win your Wish List is back ... link inside. Just enter in your email </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 20:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.audible.com/mt/WL-Sweeps-March2016?bp_ua=yes source_code=TWTGAAP0108169062#

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Library has its book sale this weekend - Mar 11-13th. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 20:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which author do you write like (x-post from r/writing) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 16:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggested vid from amazon: SOUND OF MY VOICE. Has anyone seen it? No spoilers please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 21:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I searched the sub and didnt find anyone mentions so I'm assuming it's not any good. 

But if anyone has seen it, would you recommend it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ready Player One movie has found its Wade Watts (Art3mis and Sorrento cast as well) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 17:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some rising fandoms? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 16:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What fandoms or pairings are trending? Do you know a website that updates on rising fandoms/pairings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake Trailer: BROSSESSED (just hits the paranormal activity style spot on!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 00:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Universeal to reboot its classic "Monsters" like Frankenstein, The Mummy, Invisible Man, etc. First film to be released around 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 00:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Nightmare Behind The Gayest Horror Film Ever Made [A Nightmare on Elm Street 2: Freddys Revenge] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 18:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a Horrifying Amount of Amputations at Tyson's Meat Processing Plants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 23:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE get super annoyed when people write "I dont own these characters" or whatever in the A/N? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 16:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading this story on fanfiction.net or ao3. Duh, I know you don't own the characters. 

I feel like it's pompous or self important of the author! I start off reading the fic with a very nasty attitude when I see this note. And if they're not on Shakespeare's level, I'm like FUCK THIS GUY FOR EVEN THINKING SOMEONE WOULD SUE THEM OVER COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT and I close the tab in disdain. 

Everyone has their "thing" and I guess this is mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> kids prom pics these days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 18:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Clines did an AMA in r/books. Someone asked about fanfics and he says: fanfic good, just please dont ask me to look at it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 21:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the biggest child-like thing you've seen a grown up do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers and Speculation] Predictions about Maggie in 6B? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 17:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lauren Cohan was just in The Boy. It didnt do horrible at the box office. She's also Martha in Batman v Superman ... 

Now she's pregnant on the show and there is just NO WAY I see them introducing another apocalypse baby. 

Considering how her acting career is starting to go and how her character is inconveniently pregnant ... do you think Maggie might be one of the deaths this season?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you come up with chapter names? Is it even worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 22:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who here suffers from "Idea Debt"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 17:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was reading a wonderful blog post by Jessica Abel [Imagining your future projects is holding you back.](http://jessicaabel.com/2016/01/27/idea-debt/) and idea debt is basically where you're doing [too much thinking and too little making](http://jessicaabel.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/idea-debt-header-FB.png)

If

- You tell 15 friends about your screenplay idea, but devote zero time in your week to facing the blank screen.
- You buy a domain name, spend weeks or months researching and reading up on how to build a website, but you dont actually install WordPress.
- You have a drawer full of half-finished stories and novels and a to-do list item every week that reads, work on writing.
- Youve read 15 free online guides to blogging, built three editorial calendars, have notes on a dozen posts, but you havent gone live with your blog.
- You have binders of lore and no book.

^^ thats all c/o the linked blog post. 

Anyways, if you're thinking too much about a project, maybe pull yourself out of perfecting it in your head and get to working on the darn thing! Which goes for me too. Since I'm posting on reddit and not working on my magnus opus right now ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Power of Daily Writing in a Journal - Charley Kempthorne claims to have written 10million words in his. Do you have any daily rituals that involve writing routines? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 20:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was reading this article in Wall Street Journal (sorry it's a pay to read but here's [the link](http://www.wsj.com/articles/the-power-of-daily-writing-in-a-journal-1453837329) ... )

I'm going to recount the beginning of the article (ie, plagiarize). Charley Kempthorne started journaling in 1964. These days he logs b/n 1-3k words a day. And he thinks his journal is roughly 10 million words long. Once a month, he'll print the last 30 entries and puts it in a 3-ring binder. The binders take up about 15 feet of shelf space. No one, including his wife, has read it. 

Now he posts some on facebook and [his website](http://www.thelifestoryinstitute.com/). He says he tends to pick  words more careful when writing for the world to see bc you dont want to be judged or hurt someone's feelings. 

Journaling helps him understand his life better and can be quite therapeutic. "Taking 15 or 20 minutes to write freely about emotions, secrets or upheaval can be a powerful tonic ... when you translate an emotional experience into words, it organizes them in ways not organized before. It makes them simpler and easier to get past." - James Pennebaker, author of Writing to Heal. 

One of Kempthorne's first entries was the following: 
I have decided to be a writer. I will it, thus: I am a writer. Now - by definition if for no other reason, writers are distinguised chiefly by the fact that they write. I must write - two hours a day until I finish school. 


Just sharing. Seems to be a theme I've encountered recently.  A friend swears by the 5 minute journal (I think that's a Tim Ferris thing). I've thumbed through The Artists Way by Julia Cameron. And I am currently reading Daily Rituals where the author recounts famous writers, composers, philosophers, etc daily routines. many of the routines include writing ... and drinking :D 

From the Wall Street article, here is a list of how to build a daily writing habit: 

- Write 500 words/day for 28 consecutive days, preferably at the same time and same place to create a routine
- Don't worry about grammar or punctuation. Be willing to write badly. Authenticity is more important than excellence. 
- Use prompts to get you going. Make a list of six of the stories you commonly tell. Get a photo and tell the story of that picture. 
- Keep it private. If you show it to others, you might worry about what they will say and never start. 
- If you can't think of what to write, describe the room you are in, what you are wearing, or a room from your childhood home, or what it felt like to brush your teeth
- Carry a notebook to jot down ideas or a recollection, conversation or image. 
(Taken from "narrative Journaling: 28 days to writing more or less happily for the rest of your life, by Charley Kempthorne). 

Do any of you have daily rituals or writing routines?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Generally speaking, are there common usages for rape/noncon in fanfic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 20:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I have a crap ton of questions about rape/non-con in fanfics. Answer all, answer some, or just throw out an opinion ...  

Typically, what is rape used for in a story? Does it move the plot forward or is it just another version of smut to read ?

Does the victim end up falling in love with their attacker? Or does the victim get revenge on the person? 

Is the person doing the raping the "hero" or the protagonist of the story? Or a villain?

Do all these answers change depending on the fandom? 

Does it change depending on the m/m, m/f, f/f?? 

Does violent sex get tagged as non-con? 

I"m not familiar with the tag, nor do I think I ever will be. But I am definitely curious of how this is used in fanfic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IFD Challenge: What does your favorite characteror your favorite pairingget fannish over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 18:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In honor of International Fanworks Day, ao3 has posted the challenge. 

Link: http://archiveofourown.org/admin_posts/4579

Let me hear what your fave character gets fannish over! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Save Yourself by Kelly Braffet - $1.99 [Kindle] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 22:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martyrs remake - thoughts going in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 18:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Martyrs Trailer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6dBZ1bCnS9Q feature=youtu.be)

Instead of shitting on it in the AMA, I thought we could "take it outside".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How likely is a brokered convention? (Or, how electable is Donald Trump in a general election?). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 19:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really really really am not a fan of Trump (Loved celebrity apprentice though!). 

I don't think he could win in a general election. 

If there was a brokered convention, would they just choose another candidate that was already running? Or can they choose from outside the pool (like a .... Mitt Romney - wishful thinking). 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Legally, does every crime have to have a motive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 20:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is a "motive" necessary to prosecute someone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite Snape fanfic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 17:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raise your wands o_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Becca Day (GRID athlete) was on Steve Austin's Broken Skull Challenge. Do any of you guys watch this show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 16:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can watch the current season on CMT

http://www.cmt.com/shows/steve-austins-broken-skull-challenge/

If you like America Ninja Warrior and Crossfit, then this show is probably right up your alley!  A lot of crossfitters and "crossfit physiques". I know a few better Crossfit athletes who have been asked to be on the show. They must farm contestants from crossfit gyms. 

The military one they have up right now was fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are panhandlers (or the homeless) going to do when we go cashless? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 00:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE worry about someone looking through the weird stuff you've googled to write stories for your fandom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 15:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to write a kind of descriptive scene for a death and I'm googling "What happens if you decapitate" "How hard decapitation" 

I hope no one shows up around me decapitated :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 23:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have sent two of my characters on a scavenging journey. And as a side piece they are going to do something important to the plot. But I had to get them out of their initial scenario first, so I sent them on a scavenge (which is common in the fandom). 

My question is I dont want to write out the act of scavenging - rummaging through people's houses to bring back supplies. It doesnt really add to the plot, honestly. 

Would it be bad form to just have one of the characters be like "Whew that scavenging sure was bullshit but  necesseary haha" and then move on with the story?  Or should I have a "scene" happen there? Like I could add some foreshadowing and character building ... because i think the fandom likes the interaction of the two characters ... but, at the end of the day, I think it's just a dead scene. And *I'm* the one writing it! So if I think it's going to be bad ... haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][MUSIC] super famous 80s song in a few soundtracks but not the "Don't you forget about me" song. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 02:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like "I am (something like 'beautiful') but I ...." and it seems like The Cure would sing it? Or maybe it was used in a movie starring John Cusack. 

 There's a guitar riff that sounds like "na Na naaarrrrr", then slower "I am ..... but I ....." and then the guy sings a little faster. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you submit your story if the fandom doesn't exist yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 21:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the book You by Caroline Kepnes. It's ALSO going to be a series on Showtime eventually. However, I dont see this fandom listed on ao3 or fanfic.net. 

If someone has already written a fanfic for this work, how would I go about searching for it? How would I go about writing a work under this fandom? 

The book is awesome, by the way. It's told from the viewpoint of a stalker (who is a snotty guy that works at a local bookstore). And he's mean and he ends up having more personality than the chick he's into.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best Investment You Will Ever Make (or Why some people shouldn't balk at the price tag of a Crossfit membership) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 16:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FYI - Miranda Oldroyd and Arnold Schwarzenegger have snapchats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 17:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arnold - arnoldschnitzel

Miranda - mirandaoldroyd

Let me know if you guys have other fitness snaps you follow (preferable weightlifting, crossfit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Love/hate with writing prompts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 17:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love browsing /r/WritingPrompts! The scenarios are so interesting! 

But I'm finding that, beyond that, I really don't like them. The last part of the prompt seems to "ruin" the story! It's like reading a book entitled "Snape Kills Dumbledore!" 

Someone has already done the outline for you, stolen the zinger, and then you have to do the hard part and fill in the less glamorous pieces. 

How do you view writing prompts? Are they an active part of your "writing life"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CrossFit: I want to dropkick a Chihuahua into an active volcano every time a photo of a beautiful woman is posted on the interweb and some needle-dicked, ass-hat says something stupid like, Whats his name? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 21:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crossovers: 2 questions on reader preferences (and a bonus question for TVD and True Blood fans!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 18:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just going to throw out fandoms I know, but you should get the idea. 

Say I had an idea for a True Blood/Vampire Diaries crossover (no, no, don't go anywhere, stay with me). 

FIRST QUESTION: There seems to be a general consensus that it's preferable for the characters of one story to end up in the "world" of the other. So you basically have ONE setting and you stay true to the rules of that particular universe. Is that a correct assumption? 

PIGGY BACK QUESTION: so in TVD, some vampires can walk in the day because of "magical" rings. But in True Blood, the vampires are toast; magic doesnt fix that (fairy blood does, but only for short moements). Suffice to say that "day walking" is a VERY big deal in True Blood universe but seems par for the course in TVD. 

Another note, the vampires as a whole in the True Blood universe seem to be stronger and more violent. 

If I set the story in the True Blood setting and brought over two of the TVD characters, I would expect the TVD vampires' day rings to still work. So I would like the day walking rings to NOT work on the True Blood vampires but still work with the TVD vampires. My thinking is that the vampires have different origination stories and, therefore, have different abilities. Plus, it gives TVD vampires an advantage over the True Blood vampires, even though the True Blood vampires seem a lot stronger. 

Does this make sense to treat the vampires as monkeys versus apes? Just different evolutionary chains off the same tree? (Note: I dont know the particulars of evolution so dont shoot me if monkeys and apes arent the best comparison). Or should I just have the day rings not work at all in the True Blood universe? 

LAST QUESTION: Those who have written crossovers, do your readers get "upset" with how you treat inconsistencies between the universes? Do you have tips on how to handle inconsistencies? Dont mention it in your work, pick one over the other, or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite "true crime" show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 21:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason, I LOVE true crime shows. I was introduced to the "genre" by watching 48 hours and Dateline. And ever since then, I've been hooked. 

My favorite true crime is, by far, A Crime to Remember (on ID channel). Most of the stories are set in periods before computers, forensics, and Miranda Rights being a "thing". In one of the episodes, the FBI had to fly a set of fingerprints to a jurisdiction so they could compare fingerprints found at a crime scene. 

I couldnt imagine what people used to get away with. 

So I choose A Crime to Remember.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
