<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9438</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it won't tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just take a look at /r/conservative if you want to ask us something.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No conservative can discuss issues here because they will get downvoted and silenced  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If government involvement in healthcare made it expensive in the first place: https://mises.org/blog/how-government-regulations-made-healthcare-so-expensive , why do people believe that heavier regulations will make it better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will the rule that reads: "Vote based on quality, not opinion." be enforced? I am sick of getting downvoted to oblivion when I try to discuss issues in conservative way. I know that sites like heritage or forbes are right-wing oriented but they are not wrong. Even then I get called out for posting "GOP propaganda" when it's clearly not that. I want to participate in discussion, I'm obeying all rules but I'm forced to delete my comments because I lose karma and then I can't answer comments because of cooldown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thoughts on this matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Government Regulations Made Healthcare So Expensive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks Obama! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay I wanted to talk with you but you seem toxic af so goodbye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.forbes.com/sites/timworstall/2015/01/04/solved-why-poor-states-are-red-and-rich-states-are-blue/#675abb021d60 read up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYC is blue because leftie policies work best when population density is high because you can use all public infrastructure you are funding with your taxes. People in red states vote R because they don't want to throw their tax money away for public hospitals and not use them because simply there aren't a lot of them. I think it's pretty common knowledge and saying they vote R because they are backwards shit holes is very offending and inaccurate to say at least.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/thathappened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If liberals are so keen on science, why do they claim that more than 2 gender exist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? There are more rich people who vote R  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will be good for them if they knew how to save up that money, find a better job and then stop taking welfare but as I linked, studies show something opposite. Poor people when they get welfare spend it all without saving for future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> French Right wing is very different that US right wing. People on the right in EU suport things like public schools or healthcare which is leftie policy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the hell are you talking about? If you give money to the poor they will spend this money and will become poor again. After 50 years of War on poverty self-sufficiency didn't become higher. Here are some articles to prove my point: https://www.forbes.com/sites/louiswoodhill/2014/03/19/the-war-on-poverty-wasnt-a-failure-it-was-a-catastrophe/#1a30ad096f49 

http://dailysignal.com/2016/03/15/self-sufficiency-not-government-spending-should-be-the-measure-of-antipoverty-progress/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
