<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1493</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decades of kegels can do incredible things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're nothing Feuerstein! You're garbage, you're garbage Feuerstein! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It most likely has to do with your location, mines the only one in town so you tend to get a little bit of everyone there. Maybe there's just no crazies in your area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Burger King in my city shut down. The Shawarma King is still going.

Shawarma: 1

The king: 0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean "seceded" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 12:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what you are talking about, this was obviously shot with a Red One. Filming in portrait mode is a stylistic choice on his part. His idiocy however, is not a stylistic choice... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When changing laws they don't generally repeal anything, they simply make a new law outlawing the previous one. So it could very easily be that since it's already federal law they haven't felt the need to make a new law for something thats already illegal . However, IANAL  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 01:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well light treason is generally for people who think high treason is too fattening  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 00:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High treason and petty treason originate from 14th century England. Petty treason was the murder of a superior by a subordinate. So a servant killing their master/mistress or a wife killing her husband. High treason was attempted (or planned) murder, murder, and levying war against the sovereignty. That included the king and his companions, and statesman (treasurer, justices). Most places don't have separate types of treason, as far as i know. England got rid of petty treason  a while ago. Canada has high treason and treason but the criteria for both historically falls under the former.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 18:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol "I can't post statements on public forums without being challenged, better get out of here before i might have to question my beliefs"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 00:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I go for a settlement, one day my child will question me for taking up his offer of money. If I agree to his offer, may be we will get something. But what will be her future being brought up as the daughter of a rapist. Even if her father is a rapist, she will realise one day that her mother struggled for her. She will learn it the hard way. That will make her a good woman, she said. 


This really hit me. She really is trying to make the best of it. Not only raising the daughter of her rapist but trying to make her the best she can be. The man who did this to her should be rotting in jail not harassing his victim. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 10:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, the lack of context leaves an air of mystery about it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 10:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your flair is something else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 10:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't it used in the second and third flags of the confederacy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 09:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could also arm "reverse suicide bombers" (journalists with c4 underwear) so that ISIS becomes weary of taking them hostage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Give ISIS an ICBM so they can launch it at someone and justify nuclear response from the rest of the world. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 08:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glass the sand  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 15:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That applies to Canadians as well, with red being the colour you really want to stay away from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 04:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pit: http://www.8muses.com/index/category/1772-the_pit

Pool Party (not sure if there's more): http://pipipimapi.tumblr.com/post/69392414043/pornosets-john-persons-pool-party </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 22:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the minion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 14:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She asks him not to "rope matt into this" so she at least doesn't want the brother asking him about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 04:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name is Madison Ivy, scene is from a brazzers video called  Big Tits at Work - Sell Me Your Sex. You'll probably have to torrent the full video, or buy a brazzers membership. 

http://www.newbrazzers.com/video/Sell%20Me%20Your%20Sex/14/

(longer set) http://vipergirls.to/threads/314621-Big-Tits-at-Work-Madison-Ivy-amp-Keiran-Lee-Sell-Me-Your-Sex-x1098?s=1b42a3c8dd5ea2166abf77f3a9e96b82 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 04:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tegan Mohr https://twitter.com/tabooddhist/status/528411337924550656

Xvideo page http://www.xvideos.com/profiles/tegan-mohr
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 05:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I could find

http://eye.swfchan.com/flash.asp?id=146499 n=Futashy+%28Apony%29.swf

http://eye.swfchan.com/flash.asp?id=136813 n=Futashy-0_2.swf

http://eye.swfchan.com/flash.asp?id=138859 n=FFFf.swf

http://eye.swfchan.com/flash.asp?id=136819 n=fluttershy.swf

http://rule34.paheal.net/post/view/1173162 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 23:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bam

http://www.comdotgame.com/play/angelas-quest-for-booty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 16:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I left that link alone. I'm going to /r/eyebleach now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 16:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so happy that you found the strength to get help. Keep moving forward buddy, we love you too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 18:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Provigil (modafinil) is an alertness agent so it will keep you awake but it doesn't really give you much in the way of energy. The upside is it doesn't work on the central nervous system so many of the classical side effects of standard stimulants aren't present. My fatigue isn't that bad any more and so I find it does what I need.  I personally don't notice much of a crash but you're mileage may vary. From what I've heard Nuvigil (armodafinil) has more of a cognitive effect than Provigil but I can't speak from experience.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hijacking the top comment to post some relevant info

National Suicide Prevention Hotline US - 1-800-273-8255

US Website - http://www.suicidepreventionlifeline.org/

Canadian Website - http://suicideprevention.ca/thinking-about-suicide/find-a-crisis-centre/

Suicide prevention resources and app that provides 24 hour hotline in Canada - http://www.thelifelinecanada.ca/

American Foundation For Suicide Prevention - https://www.afsp.org/

Please if you do anything access some of these services. I won't pretend to understand your situation but you don't have to be alone in this. Please just talk to someone.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 17:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of it, I think, Is what you said about education. My friends (and me) were all told that pot is just as impairing as alcohol. We all knew this to be untrue right away and add to that all the other lies we were told we ended up not taking it very seriously. We've grown up and realized how retarded of a justification it is but I can't help but wonder if we were told the truth about this stuff we might have given it the level of respect it deserves. Pot makes you sleepy, distracted, and slows reaction times. Saying that is far more effective than lying about it's effect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that if you brew it into a tea it acts as a hypnotic and can help you sleep. Never heard of hallucinations though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 15:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's too late... the ride never ends... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 06:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a wonderful person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 00:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case people don't want to look it up

20m = ~65ft  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Astarte sounds like the worst kind of dessert
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if ignorance is an accepted defense under the law... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 22:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So by commenting on the dogs lack of training people are somehow implicitly saying that the dog was justified in being there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he a white straight male? Obviously he was just handed the money, Minecraft is a product of his privilege.



Am I doing it right?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 23:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And since president is a lifelong title he would be President First Gentleman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 22:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair points all around. What do you think would be a more appropriate response? Or do you feel that the current way that it's handled is appropriate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 21:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that eh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 20:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess some people just don't give a shit about anyone else. Perhaps i'm more empathetic then most, i tend to feel for everyone. It just seems horribly myopic to not even attempt to humanize the people around you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you be empathetic if it were a family member? I'm curious, do you only feel for people close to you, or does this same callousness apply to everyone? I also get that a family member is different than a random stranger on the internet but I know i personally empathize with these people even though i get that it's largely their fault. It's a simple recognition that their human IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess if you're busy working outside and going hiking instead of learning, you're less likely to question the government. Makes sense if your goal is a strong fighting population who are not learned enough to question the leadership.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 19:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or at least be subject to a similar level of response when malpractice leads to a death. Doctors lose their licenses and are disgraced if they gamble with human lives. Cops seem to get paid vacations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 22:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But are they the type of people to be swayed by violence? Or will it just justify in their minds that black people are all violent thugs? I think I get the frustration (im white and Canadian so all i've got is empathy), and standing around while your friends and family are murdered sounds like no solution at all. Is it possible to sympathize with the situation and support the very real feelings and experiences of black people while also condemning the riots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rambling often stumbles upon truth believe it or not.

I get the sense that you're a very poetic and introspective person. I really didn't think your concern with appearance was a shallow one given how you write and the feelings you were describing. 


So let's accept that there is an aspect of you going unfulfilled. That aspect as you say is stuck and it's trying to manifest itself through your appearance. The issue being you don't feel confident or secure enough to fully explore that expression. Let's also accept that it's a part of who you are and that conflict arises when it can't express properly.  

I deal with a lot of social anxiety myself, largely stemming from my relationship with my father. So I'm not going to simply tell you to get over it. However, it is causing you to be unhappy and even self-loathe so we must concede that it is in fact an issue that needs to be addressed.


So what do you know about this aspect? Is it yearning for any kind of expression? Or only physical appearance? What are it's motivations and what do you think would sate it's desires?

Also let me know if I've gone astray in my reasoning, I only know what you've told me here so it's very likely I've missed something.

Edit: PM me if anything gets too personal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 07:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one in my area has a Tim Horton's, pretty unsurprising in Canada. They also have a cafeteria but it's not that great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 06:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think it matters to you? No judgement of course, I'm interested in your thoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 03:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it won't come easy...


Nothing worth having ever does </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you smell shit everywhere you go maybe you should check your shoes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 15:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the lesson here is always cut your own hair?


Learn something new everyday  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 18:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By 1938 he'd dragged Germany out of one of the worst economic depressions around. Though, he did it by building a large military, robbing Jews of their businesses, and annexing Austria and Czechoslovakia. Whether or not it was good he had a massive amount of influence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 23:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless its stipulated in the contract that your booth could be pulled for any reason the con-staff sees fit

That's what /u/jlitwinka is saying though, that a contract like that is too one sided and won't hold up in court. IANAL of course, but as far as I know you can stipulate whatever you want in contracts but those stipulations aren't legally binding just because they're in a contract. Something illegal is the obvious example, but really one sided contracts can also be struck down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 05:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mistake, don't know why i thought that. Still I don't think it's fair to say that reflects all of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 03:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? How is a CalgaryExpo security officer* calling the cops grounds to assume that Canada as a country dislikes protests and free assembly? We have it guaranteed in our charter of rights and freedoms and as you will note nothing came of the cops being called because they cant do anything about HBB going to a park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 07:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://g.e-hentai.org/g/316506/948a6fe69a/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 18:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the fact that i only know her name because of the incident pretty much proves that. Thank you for your responses and clarification. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair point, i guess that's why you said "could be argued" and not "should be argued". Also Clinton was impeached over this incident, so could you please clarify what you mean when you say Lewinksy came out  a lot worse? Do you mean public image? I was too young to follow whatever the media was saying at the time so i honestly don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 17:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about string theory? That's one of the most mystical things I've ever heard, but i think they're looking for a different kind of mysticism. The kind that's not predicated on chalkboard wide equations, and can be justified simply by "feeling" that its true. 

I'm actually not sure why it seems to attract house spouses more. My layman theory would be that household work isn't rewarding in a broad sense because one cannot see improvements or a finished project since there really is no great end goal to accomplish. You repeat the same things pretty much day-to-day without ever reaching a satisfying conclusion. Construction workers are supposedly the most happy workers for this reason, that at the end of a project they can stand back, look at it, and say "i did that". House spouses don't really have that, despite working hard. I can understand how someone in that position might feel unaccomplished, or useless to those around them, because they can't necessarily point to anything tangible to validate themselves.  


This is where Oz and his secret knowledge come in. He promises change, he promises health, he promises the world, and all it takes is a few pills, maybe some oils, maybe a book. A small price to pay for something bigger than yourself right? They can be a part of a movement that the majority of people reject, which i think would make it appealing to someone looking for validation. Now there's something they can use to try to help their friends and family, or themselves, and since the benefits are largely intangible they can easily justify that it's working. Instead of just doing mundane but necessary things like laundry and dishes, now they are helping to save everyone from the evils of modern medicine and to show them the light of Oz. 

Also some are probably just not that bright, i'm not sure we can discount that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe shes trans-regional?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious, how can it be argued that she held "less fault"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 16:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might as well jump on the armchair psychology wagon. I think it has to do with how the information is perceived in those around them. Something like quantum physics, or nanotechnology, doesn't contain the mysticism (purposefully so) that these other "alternatives" do.


I also think some are trying to find their new religion. Their actions just remind me of a certain brand of religious person, the gnostic who has secret knowledge and is willing to share it with you to save your soul. You get the same sort of defensive reaction if you try to argue with them. Perhaps its just a certain personality that's attracted to so called "secret knowledge" and if you peddle it, they will come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 00:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit allows any sub to link to anywhere, as far as i know, so im not sure what auhority the mods here have in that sub. Beyond that though, do you realistically think we can prevent people from linking to us? And what exactly are we doing wrong if they link to us? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 16:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a lot of words to say something the equivalent of "what about ME?!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 17:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, geographically you're closer to Germany so your Physical Sexism Ability Points (PSAP) are lower but because England and America do quite a lot of trading together your Capitalistic Sexism Ability Points (CSAP) are getting fairly high.* 




*Points only apply to straight white men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 22:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he also said that he played like a rank 600 player to keep it interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious but what would you do if the culture changes and yet women still choose not to enter STEM fields? Is parity as an end goal worth it if it means woman have to go into something they don't want to? Or would you contend that women only make that choice due to culture?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost funny in a way. They tried to make their insignificant issues into huge problems by conflating them with serious words/concepts and yet all it's done is remove the power behind those words/concepts. With this they've done far more harm to the perception of women's issues than they could possibly understand, and yet we're the bad guys :I  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 22:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also whats the difference between a "boys club" and a "safe space"? Aren't both just places where similar and like-minded individuals can intermingle without challenge? 

Oh i forgot , it's only bad when men do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 18:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But has that actually happened? Is there any case where someone has recieved a change in punishment by using the gay panic defense? I mean just because you could see it happening doesnt mean that it has, so im genuinely curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 18:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 21:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It changed to "sticks and stones may break my bones but words are free publicity" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasnt that interested before, certainly not interested now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out a broswer exstension called "hola!" It allows you access region locked content. Word of warning though, some places like Netflix hate this so use at your own discretion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldnt women starting their own league just further cement the stigma that women just arent as good as men at video games? Women arent physically disadvantaged like in tennis, so a womens league just looks like they cant handle the pressure. And the thing is that there probably is more pressure on women in e-sports. However, lowering the bar isnt going to make them look any more competent. 

I guess it comes down to whether you just want more women competing or if you want women to be more respected. I think that if the women currently in e-sports can prove that they have it what it takes to compete on the same level it would go a lot more towards fostering a competive scene where women are commonplace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 14:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts exactly, imo as long as hes open about the deal existing i dont feel he has an obligation to discuss the specifics. Now if he reviewed PC hardware i would want to know the exact nature of the deal but an alienware discount for some promotion doesnt really sound like a conflict of interest in this case.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 16:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two are joined pretty tightly at this point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 04:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow your eyes are mesmerizing, and honestly the rest of you is equally enchanting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 15:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's some Norman Bates level Psychopathy there, I can't even wrap my head around it. No remorse, no guilt, just calm disinterest in how long they suffered. Why'd she even do it? Just because she could?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 03:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right that's where the music analogy sort of breaks down. Isn't this DLC though, that's not exactly re-writting the cd with white supremacist bullshit, more like dropping the White Supremacist EP. The analogy isn't perfect though, and i could be wrong. Do we know to what degree this change will effect people who bought the base game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 03:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit he has a ton of [albums](http://www.discogs.com/artist/58562-Charles-Manson), I'm going to check them out. Thanks for the heads up, I guess he was a musician before the whole murder-cult thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 02:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you'd still wear the band tshirts you have? And keep the posters up? you would't care at all about the publics perception of you as a person when you wear such clothing
 
Yes, yes, and why should i care what the public's perception is? I don't think what an artist does now erases the merit of the art in the past, or my appreciation of said art. I still have (and wear) a Megadeth t-shirt even though i disagree with Dave Mustaine in general, i still rep a Metallica wallet even though they're total douchecanoes now, i still enjoy my favorite As I Lay Dying tracks even though Tim Lambesis tried to hire a hitman on his wife. I like what i consider good art and im not afraid to express my like for it. This is why i prefaced my statement with "I don't know if i'm alone in this" because i legitimately wasn't sure how mainstream this opinion of art is.

Sure, but would you display his artwork proudly for everyone to see with his name on it going "Yep, that's my Hitler painting, isn't it just lovely?".

Absolutely.
 
That being said, I do agree that Hitler drew some nice landscape pictures, he wasn't amazing at all, but they were decent.

Ya they're nothing really special, i think they're decent though. 

Although this is less relevant as Hitler is dead (hopefully!), A better analogy would be if Hitler was alive and well today and still making art, would you buy his new art, funding him and his opinions?

I will concede here, i can't justify supporting something that hurts another person. This is my own fault for escalating it to Hitler levels. I would still support a band i disagree with politically, socially, or personally because i feel an artist should be compensated for good art. So long as they aren't hurting anyone but that wasn't the original point made, so good show. However, if somebody, let's say Charles Manson (because why not), were to put out a good thrash metal album. I'd still like that album, i just wouldn't support it financially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 01:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skyrim taught me how to shout the corpses of my fallen enemies off the edge off a cliff so as to make it look like those stinking imperial bastards took a stumble while on patrol. Its quite the educational game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 01:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if i'm alone in this but i honestly wouldn't care. I might not buy this hypothetical bands new stuff if it gets changed to something i don't personally like but my opinion of their older work would remain unchanged. If it was good art before they changed their political views I just don't see how it somehow stops being good art after the fact. In other words I think Hitler can be a good painter regardless of his stance on Jews, and to like a painting by Hitler is not agreeing with Hitlers message. At least in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 22:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my new favourite expression </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 14:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They gave it an [87%](http://www.pcgamer.com/watch-dogs-review/)... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 06:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mods are having trouble keeping up with the sub at this moment. Theres been some disputes between some mods and they're actually looking for additional people. When this place is properly moderated theres very little sensationalism, or clickbait. 

If you want similar subs check the sidebar to the right, you can also find the rules of the sub there so you can read what we're about here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 17:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats your definition of treason and how does it supercede the accepted legal definition in Russia?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 16:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can it be treason if there is no precondition of loyalty involved?

Because under Russian law treason is defined as "espionage, disclosure of state secrets, or any other assistance rendered to a foreign State, a foreign organization, or their representatives in hostile activities to the detriment of the external security of theRussian Federation, committed by a citizen of the Russian Federation" "precondition of loyalty" doesnt seem to be a factor under Russian law, simply being a citizen obligates you not to disclose secrets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll come back someday... right...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 17:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean, its pretty surreal :( This is such a beautiful gesture though, all we can really do is show our solidarity, and this seems like a perfect way to do it. RT fans really are some wonderful people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 00:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya simply claiming neutrality doesn't make the stance well informed, it feels like hes forcing himself to neutrality, which i will give him credit for trying and for not just outright denouncing us. However a lot of the rant feels like him attacking GG but then saying it's not all bad and how that makes him neutral. He barely talks about Anti-GG and who they are, what they do etc, at least imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
