<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject16</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately clickbait works. Especially on reddit. 
Use of the downvote button may help. I guess.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I wonder if there are any plausible theories except the ones the MSM is pushing? Can not really come up with one yet. 

Why would they want to clean house now? 

The shooter is apparently only wounded. If he survives maybe some more info will come to light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Jewish Center Bomb Threat Suspect Is Arrested in Israel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Russian lawmaker shot dead in Ukraine. Somebody cleaning up here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The conspiracy lies in the question why he was shot dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me angry that the blogspam that OP posted gets more upvotes than the original article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have no real journalist employed. They just have writers who re-write stuff other people report. Such a business model should not be supported. Especially in times like this. 

We need investigative journalists. They need to be paid. So we should give our clicks to outlets who do employ those. And not those who rehost others original content. 

I started to sometimes down-vote the Independent, even though I like many of their headlines. Especially when they report on the work of other real journalists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I googled it. Seems to be legit. 
But in times of fake news I hate when outlets do not link to or at least describe the source of their claims. Especially when it is data that might be publicly available like here. 
There might be more interesting stuff there, but I'll never know because I do not know where the data came from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again do not give clicks to the Independent who do not employ a single investigative journalist who produces original content. 

Rather share the guys who found it out over at the AP:

https://www.apnews.com/d43ef4166da6400ab45140978854bbbb/AP-Exclusive:-US-probes-banking-of-ex-Trump-campaign-chief </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article is interesting. 
I just wondered. Who collected the data? There is no source given on the blog you linked. Do the cable companies publish those?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he is not getting much love for that:

[Hill Republicans say they're growing frustrated with Mattis](http://www.politico.com/story/2017/03/mattis-defense-hill-republicans-obama-236329) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is gossip. Stick to the issues people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article is interesting, but fuck your title change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think given that the things you mention are part of what lost her the election, I would argue that a lot of people truly had this reaction to Hillary? 
Especially Bernie Sanders supporters (and Trump supporters, obviously). 

There is this theory by many on the left that the Comey letter was the nail in the coffin for Hillary. She had bad luck, that this stuff about Trump just comes out now, but the reactions seemed to be similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Mattis is in a very powerful position because even Trump know he can not boot him. He would loose too much military support.
Mattis is just too respected by everyone. This makes him one of the most powerful members of the administration, because he does not have to be a yes-man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should rather get rid of handouts instead of promising more of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The National Review: Donald Trump Obama Wiretap Allegation: A Self-Inflicted Political Wound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Was sitting here and thinking about a name for the new 2017 account and the last R function I used was the first thing that came to mind  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Is Winning Where It Matters Most </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Tuesday, President Trump warned House Republicans that if they didn't vote for the GOP health care plan they could potentially face political problems. The warning was given a day after Republican leaders released amendments to try and sway critics and naysayers of the proposal.  


Regardless of the warning, Sen. Rand Paul (R-KY) said that he will vote no against the American Health Care Act because it does not fully repeal Obamacare. 

I have a lot in common with the president in that we both ran on repealing ObamacareWe [conservatives] ran on repealing it not replacing it with Obamacare Lite and I think Paul Ryans plan wont fix the problems. I think it will continue to allow the insurance premiums to skyrocket, he told FOX Businesses Lou Dobbs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rand Paul: I Will Vote No Against the GOP Health Care Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are so many issues of substances to care about. 

This is definitely not one of them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true. 

He could get rid of the perception that he is actually hiding something very easy that way. 
Although it would be the smart way, yielding is not his thing. 

Such a self-inflicted wound the bad publicity he gets here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hill Republicans say they're growing frustrated with Mattis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Defense Department veterans say the White House has put Mattis is in a nearly impossible position given that large swathe of the Republican foreign-policy establishment was openly critical of Trump during the campaign; Some say that has left Mattis with little choice but to turn to Democrats and to those without a political background to fill senior posts.

In picking Mattis, the president got someone who had bipartisan credibility and was seen as a tough national security official who wasnt going to toe the White House or the GOP line, said Jeremy Bash, a former Pentagon spokesman under Secretary Leon Panetta. Independence is an important attribute in a SecDef. But when you get that, you get frustration from the political folks. When youre not coming out of the establishment, you have the credibility to do bipartisan things. Youre just going to take incoming from Democrats and from Republicans from time to time.

The only guy who is not a Partisan Republican hack and Trump tries his best to obstruct him at every corner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washington Post uses data to show that some of the stories other MSM outlets about "Trumpgret" is wishful thinking instead of reality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New poll: only 3% of Trump voters regret their vote </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give clicks to clickbaity Indepent, but better share the AP who broke this story:

https://www.apnews.com/122ae0b5848345faa88108a03de40c5a/Manafort's-plan-to-'greatly-benefit-the-Putin-Government' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like Spicer knew this is about to come out, doesn't it?

That is why he ridiculously tried to paint Trump Campaign Manager Manafort as playing "a minor role". 

Could it be that the Trump administration spies on American journalists? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She does not say he will resign. The Independent is putting words in her mouth here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so this bots shows that I also post in The_Donald. 

Should rather increase confidence in my comment than decrease it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Donald Trump's former campaign chairman, Paul Manafort, secretly worked for a Russian billionaire to advance the interests of Russian President Vladimir Putin a decade ago and proposed an ambitious political strategy to undermine anti-Russian opposition across former Soviet republics, The Associated Press has learned. The work appears to contradict assertions by the Trump administration and Manafort himself that he never worked for Russian interests.

Okay so they lied about that. Again. 

I did not think too much of the Russian connection at the beginning. But more and more comes to light. And the constant cover-up by Trump and his affiliates makes it seem like there is not just smoke but also fire.

If there was nothing there, why not lay everything that could be construed as incriminating on the table in one go and get it over with?

When it constantly comes out that they lied and tried to cover it up, it makes the whole thing fare more damaging. 

The whole article is pretty interesting. Superb, unbiased reporting by AP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a good thing. Let him interact with some actual leaders. 

Maybe he can learn somethings about running a country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
