<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see that official spin story is ready, to bad that is miserable pile of shit just like everything else, coming form T_D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Few years ago NYC Council actually petitioned Google to reduce number of left turns when giving directions. 

Source: http://www.digitaltrends.com/cars/new-york-city-to-google-reduce-the-number-of-left-turns-in-maps-navigation-directions/

As far as mail delivery services UPS is claiming that it saves gas. A lot of gas 10 million gallons per year!!!

Source: http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/16/world/ups-trucks-no-left-turns/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That picture was taken in older European public transportation vehicle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 06:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story time!

My father and my uncle had same surgery about 10 years apart. Both of them operated Abdominal Aortic Aneurysm. 

Uncle who did surgery first had like 12 hour long surgery where they opened up his chest and he was in hospital for little over 30 days after the surgery. All together it took him close to one year to fully recover. 

My father had surgery less than 6 months ago and surgery lasted about two hours. They inserted everything through his inner thigh and he was out of the hospital after about 48h ... 10 days after the surgery Doctor give him clearance and he was back to work :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great info, thanks! 

Judging by what you are saying that means that my internet could be significantly slower, so in order to work properly and without any interruption I should probably need to upgrade my service to fastest possible option.

Also I found some "VPN routers" at the price of $130 for hardware plus yearly subscription. Do you think that adding router and just sending all data ( including stuff like Amazon Fire TV and Kodi ) would be good idea?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC Broadband Privacy Rules and /r/PCMasterRace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not entirely sure if this is the right place to ask this question, but I figured that you guys would be most qualified to give advice about this matter or at least point us to right direction. 

Anyway as you all probably know [House voted to repeal FCC privacy rules](http://www.multichannel.com/news/congress/house-votes-scrap-fcc-privacy-rules/411803) so I figured this would be a good time for average Redditors ( my self included ) to learn more about VPN service. 

It would be great if someone in this community would create the post that would provide more information as to how VPN works, how to use it, what to stay away form. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it is time to get VPN and I assume that majority of people, my self included have to idea how to go about picking the right option. 

Can someone knowledgeable about the matter make a post about what we need to know, how to use them and maybe even recommend company or two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is wrong with politicians, no seriously, why is this not a top story nationally?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your race? Buddy you are in the wrong century? Also "our race" was never majority in California, so with that said every morning when you wake up you should thank those damn Mexicans for allowing you to use land they occupied for as long as there is written history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know people who pay $1800 for a room in one bedroom apartment in Manhattan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wonder what tribe do your ancestors belong to?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to get rid of that cancer in next election cycle, no seriously both of them are bad for entire nation!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is that most of that stuff is in gray area and relies more on ethics and honor rather than law on books. 

Again someone needs to come up with physical evidence of wrong doing in order to get this spineless scum. They have army of lawyers and decades of experience of not being held responsible for their actions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People post videos of other people jumping on tables to destroy them because it is unusual and draws attention. 

As others have stated. I have yet to see person jump on the table with the intention of braking it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like Trump do not resign. Just remember as long as he is President he is more or less immune. 

Only way to get rid of him is to collect enough evidence to impeach him, and being that virtually everyone closest to him is neck deep to everything that is going on finding someone that will brake and start talking will be almost impossible especially while they are in power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When road constructions shuts down about 100 miles worth of highway in one of the largest metropolitan areas in United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha ... Good luck and have fun!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Santa Monica, much more to see and do in and around it especially in summer months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O yeah? 

Well, [this is what poorly planed construction projects look like](http://imgur.com/a/s7W1c). As the matter of fact probably about 100miles worth of douchebagiry planing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Over the years I known bunch of people that did this in Maryland and New York. It is not my intention to talk you out of it, or to say that you will have same experience. I just think that it is something that you should know before committing any money to it especially if you have to pay that money back. 

First I have yet to meet person that was actually able to "make money" by staying with the program. At best you will be able to break even if you stay on strict eggs for breakfast and McDonalds for lunch and dinner diet. 

Second, they were working in amusement park but they were also sent to local private residences and condos to work as lifeguards and nannies. One girl didn't even know how to swim, but management company didn't really care as long as there was somebody hanging around the pool. Most of them had to work overtime but for some reason they didn't get paid for it. 

Third, they were being charged for accommodations ( not much about $200-300 a person ) Problem was that they would squeeze up to 8 or 10 people in to 2 bedroom apartment that normally cost about $1200 per month. Also people in those apartments were changing all the time so they had to constantly worry about someone stealing their stuff.

Fourth, agency that was doing this was originally form Bulgaria. Owner of the agency was US citizen and he ended up with a long prison sentence for following. He was charging kids thousands of dollars to extend their work visas after 3 or 6 months long program. For the record he did not secure extended work visas. All he was doing was sending applications for tourist visas, and kids didn't know about it until it was to late. Also he send out couple of thousand bogus tax returns in the name of kids that were doing work. 

With that said I also know few people that signed contracts to do serious hard work like oil fields, Alaskan fishing industry and cruise ships. They did make money at the end of each contract. Depending on position up to $20000 clean.

Finally once you are on US soil **DO NOT GIVE ANYONE FOR ANY REASON YOUR PASSPORT!**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tuesday's Rant! Fellow Americans what are most irritating things in your home state? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That mofo didn't even blink, he just keeps on pushing that clunker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm sorry but that is on you. Who in their right mind would tell co-worker that they are definitely moving one year form now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know very well what DNC stands for. You seem to nitpick and act stupid for no apparent reason. All four people that I mentioned above were and still are part of Democratic Party establishment. Same establishment that failed miserably by pushing Clinton at all cost. 

Their time has passed with failure of Hillary Clinton it is time for them to let go of their personal interest and let this party advance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha 

OP left out Pelosi form title! Good move, that witch is more toxic Flint water. 

If DNC wants to get back on voters good side they need to purge Pelosi, Schumer, Wasserman Schultz, Brazil, and other establishment scum. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like nothing more than to have DeAndre on the team, but he is not a franchise player.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not professional PED popper that gets paid $30 million per year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good news Cavs fans! 

Now you have an excuse as to why this epic failure happened. LeBitch had to leave the game, due to flop injury </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like path to Finals is wide open   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will someone hit the fucking basket already!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the game I was hoping that Spurs would win, now I hope they win by 30 :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love KG, by far my favorite Celtic, but he needs to cut this shit show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope Kelly is watching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 04:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone make Cavs bench lowlights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lou is leader only on paper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lou - Donald Trump 

LeBron - Steve Bannon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at Pop they are up by 28 and he looks at LMA as if he fucked up last position in the close game ... Gotta love that guy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Denied ... for the 5 time tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhh
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go home you are drunk  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this Dedmon guy, where did he come from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree Cavs bench is really talented at getting BIG FAT ZERO at halftime!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record I usually don't up vote Lakers fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They came uninvited to block party  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is not playing against MVP candidate tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn Right He Is!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who allowed Brooklyn Team to wear Cleveland uniforms tonight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit Old Man Manu!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LeKawhi is kicking LeBricks ass tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be blast at parties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is because Lue is not a coach, he gets paid to look like one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought San Antonio is a Hipster town, didn't know they are in to block parties  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhh LMA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And their 8 players on the court team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ball don't lie!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit! I love clean blocks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LeBitch is upset! What did I miss?

Edit: LeBitches bitches are upset too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want to play Cavs in the second round?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solid like a brick  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that relevant to this discussion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traitor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lock Him Up! #MAGA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TrumpCare fail up vote party, anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 01:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA warning about Sony A7SII; A7SII; A6300; A6500; and RX10 Mark II </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do all my homework before making any purchases and none of the "independent reviewers online" even mention this issue, so I figured I should post here and warn everyone about this issue. I found out about following hard way, after purchasing my camera, that now I can't use it for filming in 4k on sunny days. 

First little background, I'm wedding videographer and part of my job is to film bride and groom photo session along with good percentage of ceremonies that are happening outside in bright sunlight. Reason why I added new Sony camera to my bag is so that I can film internally in 4k and be more mobile. 

Now imagine my surprise when I took my brand new tool for a spin and found out that LCD and EVF alike dim significantly when you go in to 4k mode even if I manually adjust settings to brightest option possible. In fact it is so dark that you can't even frame the shot properly especially when you are on gimbal. 

Official response form Sony is that it prevents overheating issue, but that is not entirely true, because A6500 for example will crap out in 4k ether way if you keep it running on room temperature ( 72F in my case ) 

Additionally if you do own or are planing to purchase A6500 get screen protector immediately! I literally brushed up my camera against gimbal while mounting it, and it left the mark on the screen.

For the record I have been doing this for years now and over the years I have owned close to dozen different cameras including two additional Sony mirrorless cameras and I have never had problems with scratching or shattering LCDs. 

Edit - Title correction, this is also true for A7RII ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't I adjust screen brightness on A6500 while in 4k? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just picked up A6500 and for some reason when I switch to 4k screen goes from Sunny Weather to not available for adjustment. Is there a way around it, because on the sunny day I can't see anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These are the 17 House Representatives that introduced a bill to let telecoms sell your personal internet history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FFRF wants religious flags removed from N.J. schools - Freedom From Religion Foundation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Israel's cyberattack unit arrests Israeli-American teen for 'hundreds' of bomb threats against Jewish institutions worldwide - Israel News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Promotional video for Ljubia Preletaevi Beli - Presidential Candidate in Serbia currently polling at 11% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nye/Ham: The Second Debate - March 13, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nye/Ham: The Second Debate - March 13, 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monsanto Has Lost $11 Million As Indian Cotton Farmers Begin To Use Indigenous Seed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 13:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was looking for Transcend Data Storage Company Website and this thing is first thing that pops up on google search! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit should ban sites like Washington Post because of the paywall. It is not fair that we are driving incredible amounts of traffic to their site and get rewarded by not being able to see what the article is about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico state has so many mass graves, lacks space for bodies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After more than 30 years, Newark gets new bookstore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 01:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would you take aliens to our leader? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fewer heavy Americans are trying to lose weight, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fewer heavy Americans are trying to lose weight, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BILL NYE AND BERNIE SANDERS DISCUSS CLIMATE CHANGE (FULL) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tattoo Artist Covers Up Racist Insignia For Free: 'Enough Hate In This World' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photographer gets sentenced to 30 days in jail for a drone incident that happened in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 04:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor Gives Advice On How To Wash Old Glory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 00:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona invites death row inmates to bring their own execution drugs to sidestep EU ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House approves bill to let people as young as 18 carry a concealed weapon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House approves bill to let people as young as 18 carry a concealed weapon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony release the SF-G series SD cards with 300MB/s read speeds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony release the SF-G series SD cards with 300MB/s read speeds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hugo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gypsy Roots - Lachto Drom - (1993) - The journey of the Romany people told through musicians and dancers of India, Egypt, Turkey, Romania, Hungary, Slovakia, France, and Spain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just wonder what we will learn about him soon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rutgers fashion police boot students from job fair for wrong color suit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superior Court in Paterson, question about juror parking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm summoned to do two day or one trial jury duty in Patterson and I could not find any information about parking. Does anyone know if they have free or at least validate parking for jurors?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Supreme Court rules against florist in same-sex wedding case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Washington Supreme Court rules against florist in same-sex wedding case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who designs your wedding albums? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 17:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texarkana fire captain, pastor arrested for sexual assault of 5-year-old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is Charles Darwin's Birthday! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 21:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Happy Birthday Mr. Darwin](http://imgur.com/a/kQdZK) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite smell that is unique to your state? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 06:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christie spikes bill requiring N.J. prosecutors disclose seized property </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 18:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC blocks 9 companies from providing low-income internet access </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitler's phone, 'which sent millions to their deaths,' to be sold at auction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giant iceberg poised to break off from Antarctic shelf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 03:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visited Iceland from Jan 16 to 25 ... Here is few things that I wish I knew in advance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *  Booking hotels last minute ( 24h or less ) is much cheaper than booking them months in advance. We were paying anywhere from $75 to $140 per night including free breakfast and WIFI at places that normally charge anywhere form $130 to $250 per night. 

* If your credit card charges exchange fees bring the cash and exchange it in the bank only. Banks in Iceland do not charge exchange rates. Always have credit card handy especially in remote areas if you need to stop by self service gas pump after hours. 

* Get a local SIM card form Siminn at the airport for $30 it will arguably be best purchase you made on entire trip. 

* You will not interact with locals much. Mainly you will talk to other tourists and immigrants who work in service industry. Locals are polite but really cold not friendly at all. 

* Do not book tours especially not Aurora Borealis. Instead rent a car and explore at your own pace. You will save a lot of money and you will enjoy and see more. In Iceland there is no access restrictions and you can go anywhere you please. Only time you truly need a local guide is if you are going on a glacier or in to lava/ice cave. 

* Go Aurora hunting every single night even if rain and snow is in the forecast. More often than not you will find the patch of open sky fairly early. 

Use following sites and apps on your phone with local data you purchased at the airport to find Aurora your self: 

Here you can search for open patches of clear sky: http://en.vedur.is/weather/forecasts/aurora/
Here you can find locations without light pollution (more or less entire island of Iceland minus (Reykjavik area) : http://darksitefinder.com/map/
Aurora cloud map: https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=eu.dziadosz.aurora hl=en 

* In Iceland there is very little variety. Those "hand made Icelandic wool sweaters" for example are on every single corner, they are all made in Lithuania or something and there is like 5 different options only. Same goes for hats, gloves, magnets, t-shirts etc ... 

* Go to Blue Lagoon as early as humanly possible. Later in the day it becomes absurdly crowded and you can find your self waiting in line for over an hour even if you have reservation. Also get preferred access ( whatever they call it ) it is defiantly worth extra money. 

Finally don't be afraid to explore. We found some amazing sites just by taking the turn on random unmarked road. Once you find and experience them don't go online and broadcast the fucking thing to everyone and their mother. 

P.S. Fuck every single person that tagged the wreckage of DC-3 airplane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father of Pac-Man Masaya Nakamura dies at 91 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 15:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father of Pac-Man Masaya Nakamura dies at 91 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father of Pac-Man Masaya Nakamura dies at 91 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father of Pac-Man Masaya Nakamura dies at 91 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Connors, 'Mannix' actor, dead at 91 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blind high school wrestler notches first win of career </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese factory selling giant inflatable Donald Trump roosters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 22:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Automatic Walking Reflex - 6 day old newborn walking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ft. Lauderdale Shooter Identified as Esteban Santiago born in New Jersey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Instagram views/likes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this is not the right sub, but I figured someone here might know what is going on. 

I recently started posting short 20-30sec clips on Instagram as the way to promote my self. Overall I'm getting positive reaction, but I noticed that for some reason I get more likes than views. 

As of this moment I have 3 views and 7 likes. How is that even possible?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 76 injured in Long Island Rail Road train derailment in Brooklyn, NY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 16:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa cabinet maker taking all 800 employees on week long Caribbean cruise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 03:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Viciously Attacked By Trump   Israeli PM; His Response Is Perfect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 01:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Four assholes vs one cyclist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 00:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vesna Vulovic, stewardess who survived 33,000ft fall, dies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Accused of Murdering 2 New Jersey Women Probed as Possible Serial Killer After Potential Link to Another Death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bodies Found at Home of Former Cop Cuffed in Drug Killings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 06:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers ignoring $7.4B boom in 'corporate welfare,' experts say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 18:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.J. actor won't serve prison over fake gun on movie set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawmakers ignoring $7.4B boom in 'corporate welfare,' experts say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.J. actor won't serve prison over fake gun on movie set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: Laws in Arkansas, Maryland, Mississippi, North Carolina, South Carolina, Tennessee, and Texas prohibit people who don't believe in God to hold the public office. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any tips on how to film Aurora Borealis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 20:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is many tutorials for photographing Aurora Borealis however I can't seem to find any technical tips as to how to actually film them. Stuff like camera setting, fps, should we use SLOG 2 or not, etc ... My goal is to capture Northern Lights as realistic as possible. 

We don't have much time only (9 days in second part of January) so I would like to learn as much as possible ahead of time so that we can hit the ground running once we land in Iceland. 

Here is the list of gear that is available to us, I would like to narrow down selection so that we don't have to take everything with us. I know that lenses could be better, but as of right now that is all we could gather/afford. 

Cameras: 

Sony A7S ( Original )
Sony A6300 x 2 

Lenses: 

Canon: 15 f2.8 fisheye
Canon: 16-35 f2.8 II
Canon: 24-70 f2.8 I

Sony: 16-50mm f/3.5-5.6 
Sony: 18-105mm f4
Sony: 30mm f/3.5 macro lens
Sony: 55mm f/1.8
Sony/Zeiss: 24-70 f4

Rokinon: 12mm f/2.0

Any advice or source would be much appreciated!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soldiers standing guard over John Glenn's casket at Ohio State Capitol Building </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 03:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryan Is Going Plastic Chair Crazy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 06:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 70 One Piece Traditional Style Plastic Chairs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 01:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to name Goldman executive Cohn to key economic post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon CEO Tillerson emerges as Trump's secretary of state favorite: transition official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exxon CEO Tillerson emerges as Trump's secretary of state favorite: transition official </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 02:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about dog sledding tour? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 01:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will be in Iceland form Jan 17 to Jan 26 and as of right now I only found one dog sledding company ( www.dogsledding.is ) Unfortunately they only have one spot available on 22nd of January. Problem is that there is 4 of us in total and we would all like to go. 

So with that said are there any other companies that offer dog sledding? 

Finally most important question, is it worth spending $200 per person for only up to one hour of dog sledding?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Can_Trump_Business/ - Here we discuss anything and everything related to Trumps private, public and political dealings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Can_Trump_Business/ - Here we discuss anything and everything related to Trumps private, public and political dealings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/Can_Trump_Business/ - Here we discuss anything and everything related to Trumps private, public and political dealings. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Faces Pressure on How to Handle Young Immigrants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Pick For Education: A Free Market Approach To School Choice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump picks Scott Pruitt to head EPA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't do this shit alone, post, talk and share. Lets see how good of the business man Trump really is! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Linda McMahon, Wife Of WWE Billionaire And Trump's Pick For Small Business Administrator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worried Auto Industry Braces for Change Under Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps Company-by-Company Industrial Policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump attacks union leader who called him a liar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> rumps Likely Labor Pick, Andrew Puzder, Is Critic of Minimum Wage Increases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT When rebooking the flight at the airport ask for the option that will get you to your destination fastest, not just for the first flight out of that particular airport. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happened to me in Vegas, my flight was oversold and people before me were demanding to be on the first flight out of there, so the girl at the gate complied and give them connecting flight that will get them home some 12 hours later.

Than it was my turn and I asked form my options to the same destination. She told me about the flight that was departing little over 2 hours later, but it was direct flight. I was home 5 hours before entitled couple ahead of me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Activist who filed complaint against Christie to run for governor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 16:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nancy Pelosi: I dont think Democrats want a new direction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 18:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Smear Campaign Against Keith Ellison Is Repugnant but Reveals Much About Washington </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 15:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grammy Museum exhibit of early Bob Dylan photographs by photographer Daniel Kramer at Monmouth University Center for the Arts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 14:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police Officer - Bismarck, ND </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:20:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Not everything is ON SALE today! Here is an example. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 18:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I purchased computer power supply less than two weeks ago for $99 plus $20 mail in rebate for $79 grand total! 

Fast forward to today. Same store, same power supply, " Original retail price $149", "instant discount $20" for the grand total of only $129" 

For the record other retailers were also selling same unit for anywhere form $99 to $119 prior to Black Friday!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suspended Wyckoff police chief to retire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook 'made China censorship tool' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic Rep. Gabbard meets with Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N.J. state employee used work computer to download child porn, AG says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will there be any deals for Sony cameras and lenses during black friday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mainly looking at higher end stuff like A7SII and few different lenses. This is my first year using Sony, so I'm not sure what can we expect. 

Also do they publish previews or is it a wait and see game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slavoj iek on Trump, Capitalism, and the Left's Global Crisis | 10th November 2016 | WNYC Radio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 04:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slavoj iek on Trump, Capitalism, and the Left's Global Crisis | 10th November 2016 | WNYC Radio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 19:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Interview: Bernie Sanders On Donald Trump Winning the Election - Nov 10th 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 17:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Entire DNC leadership should resign. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only way for current DNC leadership to save the honor and respect (or at least whatever is left of it) with us The People is to step down, and allow for new direction, entirely new leadership and fresh ideas. All this talk of being stunned, fighting back, not knowing, turning a new leaf, finding what the problem is, etc ... is pointless. They are the problem! All of them! No exceptions! 

America as a whole was screaming for help during entire elections including primaries, and they purposely chose to ignore it. We had candidate. A great candidate! Candidate with good ideas and most importantly support of the electorate! 

But no, they though it is business as usual ... Tell people what they want to hear, ignore the critics, throw few billion on media, marketing and pundits, bring few celebrities on rallies, and most importantly scare the living shit out of the electorate and they will eventually come around. Than they can just get back to business as usual braking campaign promises and looking out for special interest. 

Well, that did not happened this time around. On November 8 we The People did what we had to do in order to show them that business as usual in no longer acceptable way of doing things. 

Reforming DNC is not just changing narrative or sacrificing couple of DNC chairpersons (while making sure they get appointed to different positions within the system) but proactively changing the root of the problem. 

In my opinion platform and message overall are not the problem, besides changing any part of it is the easiest part. Problem lies with the messengers and the system they have created for them selfs and their Dynasties! 

**EDIT:** Sorry for the long read and my grammar, English in not my first language.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President-elect time to pardon this guy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you see Chris Christie? What role he will play in DJT White House? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As New Jerseyan this question is what we are currently talking about over at /r/newjersey. It is no secret that we are united about hating him (current approval rating in NJ is at 17%) form the bottom of our harts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man angry cops didn't have arrest warrant for him is jailed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 14:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA about Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 - If you have this Hard Drive Make Sure You Read This! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record I'm not member of this sub, so I don't know if this type of post is allowed. Reason why I'm posting here is because I believe that some of you might benefit form this information. 

Point of this post is not to shit on Seagate (even though they deserve it) but to inform everyone here and hopefully prevent it form happening to someone else.

**Important** If you use Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 and you don't have your stuff backed up on completely different HD do it as soon as humanly possible. I found out the hard way that these specific HDs have catastrophic failure rate! [Backblaze had to replace 4345 of these drives out of 4829 they deployed just three years earlier](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/). 

[Additionally there is a Class Action Law Suit against Seagate that is concentrating specifically on Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/)

**Story:** I'll try to keep in as short as possible.

I had three of these bad boys fail on me all at the same time and they were all purchased in December of 2014! All of my working files ( 5 wedding videos edits, all 5 almost completed! ) plus bunch of other personal stuff is gone! Two of them were in Raid 1 and third one was just a spare that I used to dump less important files. Luckily my cousin has few of these him self so we swapped few PBC boards and got them to spin but we were not able to retrieve the files because bios on each drive is unique to that particular drive so even if you have same exact board with the same PN and FW numbers you still need Bios from original board. Now this give me some hope to dig in to finding solution on my own. 

**Solution** First let me just say that I'm still in process of retrieving data so everything that you read may or may work actually work. If anyone is interested I can post an update once entire ordeal is over.

There is basically two possible ways of going about fixing the problem. 

**First option** is to test diodes and if you are lucky enough that you just had short and only one diode died you should be able to remove dead diode and get HD to work so that you can back up your files to different HD. Video below shows how to do it. 

Video for the first solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sfvwER9JwJc list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=2

**Second option** is to find exactly the same donor PBC board with matching PN and FW numbers (major pain in the ass, but I did manage to find two of them) and than remove Bios from your dead board and solder it to donor board. 

Video for second solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yn2eL4o-6Eo list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=1

**TL;DR** These specific Hard Drives are shit and if you are unfortunate enough to have one or more get rid of the cancer as soon as humanly possible. Additionally if you already had one die, you might be able to get some money out of Seagate trough Class Action Law Suit. 

**Edit** For the record all original files are safely backed up on two other locations. Only thing that was not backed up were my Adobe working files ( Premiere, After Effects, Audition, etc ... ) basically weeks and weeks of work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA about Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 - If you have this Hard Drive Make Sure You Read This! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 14:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point of this post is not to shit on Seagate (even though they deserve it) but to inform everyone here and hopefully prevent it form happening to someone else.

**Important** If you use Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 and you don't have your stuff backed up on completely different HD do it as soon as humanly possible. I found out the hard way that these specific HDs have catastrophic failure rate! [Backblaze had to replace 4345 of these drives out of 4829 they deployed just three years earlier](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/). 

[Additionally there is a Class Action Law Suit against Seagate that is concentrating specifically on Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/)

**Story:** I'll try to keep in as short as possible.

I had three of these bad boys fail on me all at the same time and they were all purchased in December of 2014! All of my working files ( 5 wedding video edits, all 5 almost completed! ) plus bunch of other personal stuff is gone! Two of them were in Raid 1 and third one was just a spare that I used to dump less important files. Luckily my cousin has few of these him self so we swapped few PBC boards and got them to spin but we were not able to retrieve the files because bios on each drive is unique to that particular drive so even if you have same exact board with the same PN and FW numbers you still need Bios from original board. Now this give me some hope to dig in to finding solution on my own. 

**Solution** First let me just say that I'm still in process of retrieving data so everything that you read may or may work actually work. If anyone is interested I can post an update once entire ordeal is over.

There is basically two possible ways of going about fixing the problem. 

**First option** is to test diodes and if you are lucky enough that you just had short and only one diode died you should be able to remove dead diode and get HD to work so that you can back up your files to different HD. Video below shows how to do it. 

Video for the first solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sfvwER9JwJc list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=2

**Second option** is to find exactly the same donor PBC board with matching PN and FW numbers (major pain in the ass, but I did manage to find two of them) and than remove Bios from your dead board and solder it to donor board. 

Video for second solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yn2eL4o-6Eo list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=1

**TL;DR** These specific Hard Drives are shit and if you are unfortunate enough to have one or more get rid of the cancer as soon as humanly possible. Additionally if you already had one die, you might be able to get some money out of Seagate trough Class Action Law Suit. 

**Edit** For the record all original files are safely backed up on two other locations. Only thing that was not backed up were my Adobe working files ( Premiere, After Effects, Audition, etc ... ) basically weeks and weeks of work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA about Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 - If you have this Hard Drive Make Sure You Read This! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 06:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point of this post is not to shit on Seagate (even though they deserve it) but to inform everyone here and hopefully prevent it form happening to someone else.

**Important** If you use Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 and you don't have your stuff backed up on completely different HD do it as soon as humanly possible. I found out the hard way that these specific HDs have catastrophic failure rate! [Backblaze had to replace 4345 of these drives out of 4829 they deployed just three years earlier](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/). 

[Additionally there is a Class Action Law Suit against Seagate that is concentrating specifically on Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/)

**Story:** I'll try to keep in as short as possible.

I had three of these bad boys fail on me all at the same time and they were all purchased in December of 2014! All of my working files ( 5 wedding videos edits, all 5 almost completed! ) plus bunch of other personal stuff is gone! Two of them were in Raid 1 and third one was just a spare that I used to dump less important files. Luckily my cousin has few of these him self so we swapped few PBC boards and got them to spin but we were not able to retrieve the files because bios on each drive is unique to that particular drive so even if you have same exact board with the same PN and FW numbers you still need Bios from original board. Now this give me some hope to dig in to finding solution on my own. 

**Solution** First let me just say that I'm still in process of retrieving data so everything that you read may or may work actually work. If anyone is interested I can post an update once entire ordeal is over.

There is basically two possible ways of going about fixing the problem. 

**First option** is to test diodes and if you are lucky enough that you just had short and only one diode died you should be able to remove dead diode and get HD to work so that you can back up your files to different HD. Video below shows how to do it. 

Video for the first solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sfvwER9JwJc list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=2

**Second option** is to find exactly the same donor PBC board with matching PN and FW numbers (major pain in the ass, but I did manage to find two of them) and than remove Bios from your dead board and solder it to donor board. 

Video for second solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yn2eL4o-6Eo list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=1

**TL;DR** These specific Hard Drives are shit and if you are unfortunate enough to have one or more get rid of the cancer as soon as humanly possible. Additionally if you already had one die, you might be able to get some money out of Seagate trough Class Action Law Suit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA about Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 - If you have this Hard Drive Make Sure You Read This! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 06:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point of this post is not to shit on Seagate (even though they deserve it) but to inform everyone here and hopefully prevent it form happening to someone else.

**Important** If you use Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 and you don't have your stuff backed up on completely different HD do it as soon as humanly possible. I found out the hard way that these specific HDs have catastrophic failure rate! [Backblaze had to replace 4345 of these drives out of 4829 they deployed just three years earlier](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/). 

[Additionally there is a Class Action Law Suit against Seagate that is concentrating specifically on Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/)

**Story:** I'll try to keep in as short as possible.

I had three of these bad boys fail on me all at the same time and they were all purchased in December of 2014! All of my working files ( 5 wedding videos edits, all 5 almost completed! ) plus bunch of other personal stuff is gone! Two of them were in Raid 1 and third one was just a spare that I used to dump less important files. Luckily my cousin has few of these him self so we swapped few PBC boards and got them to spin but we were not able to retrieve the files because bios on each drive is unique to that particular drive so even if you have same exact board with the same PN and FW numbers you still need Bios from original board. Now this give me some hope to dig in to finding solution on my own. 

**Solution** First let me just say that I'm still in process of retrieving data so everything that you read may or may work actually work. If anyone is interested I can post an update once entire ordeal is over.

There is basically two possible ways of going about fixing the problem. 

**First option** is to test diodes and if you are lucky enough that you just had short and only one diode died you should be able to remove dead diode and get HD to work so that you can back up your files to different HD. Video below shows how to do it. 

Video for the first solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sfvwER9JwJc list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=2

**Second option** is to find exactly the same donor PBC board with matching PN and FW numbers (major pain in the ass, but I did manage to find two of them) and than remove Bios from your dead board and solder it to donor board. 

Video for second solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yn2eL4o-6Eo list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=1

**TL;DR** These specific Hard Drives are shit and if you are unfortunate enough to have one or more get rid of the cancer as soon as humanly possible. Additionally if you already had one die, you might be able to get some money out of Seagate trough Class Action Law Suit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA about Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 - If you have this Hard Drive Make Sure You Read This! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 06:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point of this post is not to shit on Seagate (even though they deserve it) but to inform everyone here and hopefully prevent it form happening to someone else.

**Important** If you use Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 and you don't have your stuff backed up on completely different HD do it as soon as humanly possible. I found out the hard way that these specific HDs have catastrophic failure rate! [Backblaze had to replace 4345 of these drives out of 4829 they deployed just three years earlier](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/). 

[Additionally there is a Class Action Law Suit against Seagate that is concentrating specifically on Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/)

**Story:** I'll try to keep in as short as possible.

I had three of these bad boys fail on me all at the same time and they were all purchased in December of 2014! All of my working files ( 5 wedding videos edits, all 5 almost completed! ) plus bunch of other personal stuff is gone! Two of them were in Raid 1 and third one was just a spare that I used to dump less important files. Luckily my cousin has few of these him self so we swapped few PBC boards and got them to spin but we were not able to retrieve the files because bios on each drive is unique to that particular drive so even if you have same exact board with the same PN and FW numbers you still need Bios from original board. Now this give me some hope to dig in to finding solution on my own. 

**Solution** First let me just say that I'm still in process of retrieving data so everything that you read may or may work actually work. If anyone is interested I can post an update once entire ordeal is over.

There is basically two possible ways of going about fixing the problem. 

**First option** is to test diodes and if you are lucky enough that you just had short and only one diode died you should be able to remove dead diode and get HD to work so that you can back up your files to different HD. Video below shows how to do it. 

Video for the first solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sfvwER9JwJc list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=2

**Second option** is to find exactly the same donor PBC board with matching PN and FW numbers (major pain in the ass, but I did manage to find two of them) and than remove Bios from your dead board and solder it to donor board. 

Video for second solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yn2eL4o-6Eo list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=1

**TL;DR** These specific Hard Drives are shit and if you are unfortunate enough to have one or more get rid of the cancer as soon as humanly possible. Additionally if you already had one die, you might be able to get some money out of Seagate trough Class Action Law Suit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA about Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 - If you have this Hard Drive Make Sure You Read This! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 05:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point of this post is not to shit on Seagate (even though they deserve it) but to inform everyone here and hopefully prevent it form happening to someone else.

**Important** If you use Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 and you don't have your stuff backed up on completely different HD do it as soon as humanly possible. I found out the hard way that these specific HDs have catastrophic failure rate! [Backblaze had to replace 4345 of these drives out of 4829 they deployed just three years earlier](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/). 

[Additionally there is a Class Action Law Suit against Seagate that is concentrating specifically on Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/)

**Story:** I'll try to keep in as short as possible.

I had three of these bad boys fail on me all at the same time and they were all purchased in December of 2014! All of my working files ( 5 wedding videos edits, all 5 almost completed! ) plus bunch of other personal stuff is gone! Two of them were in Raid 1 and third one was just a spare that I used to dump less important files. Luckily my cousin has few of these him self so we swapped few PBC boards and got them to spin but we were not able to retrieve the files because bios on each drive is unique to that particular drive so even if you have same exact board with the same PN and FW numbers you still need Bios from original board. Now this give me some hope to dig in to finding solution on my own. 

**Solution** First let me just say that I'm still in process of retrieving data so everything that you read may or may work actually work. If anyone is interested I can post an update once entire ordeal is over.

There is basically two possible ways of going about fixing the problem. 

**First option** is to test diodes and if you are lucky enough that you just had short and only one diode died you should be able to remove dead diode and get HD to work so that you can back up your files to different HD. Video below shows how to do it. 

Video for the first solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sfvwER9JwJc list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=2

**Second option** is to find exactly the same donor PBC board with matching PN and FW numbers (major pain in the ass, but I did manage to find two of them) and than remove Bios from your dead board and solder it to donor board. 

Video for second solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yn2eL4o-6Eo list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=1

**TL;DR** These specific Hard Drives are shit and if you are unfortunate enough to have one or more get rid of the cancer as soon as humanly possible. Additionally if you already had one die, you might be able to get some money out of Seagate trough Class Action Law Suit. 

**Edit** For the record all original files are safely backed up on two other locations. Only thing that was not backed up were my Adobe working files ( Premiere, After Effects, Audition, etc ... ) basically weeks and weeks of work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA about Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 - If you have this Hard Drive Make Sure You Read This! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 05:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point of this post is not to shit on Seagate (even though they deserve it) but to inform everyone here and hopefully prevent it form happening to someone else.

**Important** If you use Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 and you don't have your stuff backed up on completely different HD do it as soon as humanly possible. I found out the hard way that these specific HDs have catastrophic failure rate! [Backblaze had to replace 4345 of these drives out of 4829 they deployed just three years earlier](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/). 

[Additionally there is a Class Action Law Suit against Seagate that is concentrating specifically on Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/)

**Story:** I'll try to keep in as short as possible.

I had three of these bad boys fail on me all at the same time and they were all purchased in December of 2014! All of my working files ( 5 wedding videos edits, all 5 almost completed! ) plus bunch of other personal stuff is gone! Two of them were in Raid 1 and third one was just a spare that I used to dump less important files. Luckily my cousin has few of these him self so we swapped few PBC boards and got them to spin but we were not able to retrieve the files because bios on each drive is unique to that particular drive and even if you have same exact board with the same PN and FW numbers you still need Bios from original board. Now this give me some hope to dig in to finding solution on my own. 

**Solution** First let me just say that I'm still in process of retrieving data so everything that you read may or may work actually work. If anyone is interested I can post an update once entire ordeal is over.

There is basically two possible ways of going about fixing the problem. 

**First option** is to test diodes and if you are lucky enough that you just had short and only one diode died you should be able to remove dead diode and get HD to work so that you can back up your files to different HD. Video below shows how to do it. 

Video for the first solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sfvwER9JwJc list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=2

**Second option** is to find exactly the same donor PBC board with matching PN and FW numbers (major pain in the ass, but I did manage to find two of them) and than remove Bios from your dead board and solder it to donor board. 

Video for second solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yn2eL4o-6Eo list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=1

**TL;DR** These specific Hard Drives are shit and if you are unfortunate enough to have one or more get rid of the cancer as soon as humanly possible. Additionally if you already had one die, you might be able to get some money out of Seagate trough Class Action Law Suit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA about Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 - If you have this Hard Drive Make Sure You Read This! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 05:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point of this post is not to shit on Seagate (even though they deserve it) but to inform everyone here and hopefully prevent it form happening to someone else.

**Important** If you use Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001 and you don't have your stuff backed up on completely different HD do it as soon as humanly possible. I found out the hard way that these specific HDs have catastrophic failure rate! [Backblaze had to replace 4345 of these drives out of 4829 they deployed just three years earlier](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/). 

[Additionally there is a Class Action Law Suit against Seagate that is concentrating specifically on Seagate Barracuda ST3000DM001](https://www.backblaze.com/blog/3tb-hard-drive-failure/)

**Story:** I'll try to keep in as short as possible.

I had three of these bad boys fail on me all at the same time and they were all purchased in December of 2014! All of my working files ( 5 wedding videos edits, all 5 almost completed! ) plus bunch of other personal stuff is gone! Two of them were in Raid 1 and third one was just a spare that I used to dump less important files. Luckily my cousin has few of these him self so we swapped few PBC boards and got them to spin but we were not able to retrieve the files because bios on each drive is unique to that particular drive so even if you have same exact board with the same PN and FW numbers you still need Bios from original board. Now this give me some hope to dig in to finding solution on my own. 

**Solution** First let me just say that I'm still in process of retrieving data so everything that you read may or may work actually work. If anyone is interested I can post an update once entire ordeal is over.

There is basically two possible ways of going about fixing the problem. 

**First option** is to test diodes and if you are lucky enough that you just had short and only one diode died you should be able to remove dead diode and get HD to work so that you can back up your files to different HD. Video below shows how to do it. 

Video for the first solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sfvwER9JwJc list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=2

**Second option** is to find exactly the same donor PBC board with matching PN and FW numbers (major pain in the ass, but I did manage to find two of them) and than remove Bios from your dead board and solder it to donor board. 

Video for second solution: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yn2eL4o-6Eo list=FLRdjTQrB1Re3FBk2OpfwvVg index=1

**TL;DR** These specific Hard Drives are shit and if you are unfortunate enough to have one or more get rid of the cancer as soon as humanly possible. Additionally if you already had one die, you might be able to get some money out of Seagate trough Class Action Law Suit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber's redesigned app wants to mine personal information on your phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best place to sell used camera gear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 20:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like eBay's and PayPal's high fees and Craigslist is sketchy from time to time. 

I was wondering how does it work with Amazon? Mainly are the fees high and is there a demand for used gear?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the bad weather rolling in I figured that is good time to remind everyone about following. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are not saving money by putting off to replace tires, brakes and windshield wipers!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside America's biggest prison strike: 'The 13th amendment didn't end slavery' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That in Croatia they gather stones out of sea covered in algae and small animals and than proceed to make the soup out of them. Once the stones are "cooked" they use them as garnish when soup is served. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report Highlights How Guns Flow Into New York From States With Weaker Laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Airbnb is now banned from listing short-term rentals in New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 15:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diplomat protected by immunity after punching his wife in NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 08:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hitler's house will be remodeled, not torn down: Austrian government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sony a7S III Specs Leaked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 02:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to check Canon shutter count? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 01:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I decided to sell few of my Canon bodes. I know that shutter count is low on all of them, and I would like to post exact number in description. I know that there is few applications, but I don't feel like testing few of them in order to find if they are accurate or not. 

So with that said what is your favorite way to check shutter count on Canon?

Edit: Cameras that I would like to find shutter count for are: Canon 5D, 5D Mark II, and 70D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some voting by mail in N.J. see their ballots returned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some voting by mail in N.J. see their ballots returned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 16:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy Note 7 Owners Sent Fire-Proof Boxes by Samsung </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glamour on the Gowanus: Pro Athletes Now Live in Brooklyn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 06:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to ask/petition federal prosecutors and judges why they are not enforcing following laws? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 03:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These three laws carry penalties anywhere from 3 to 20 year prison sentence and monetary fines anywhere from few thousand up to quarter million dollars for each offense. 

* [18 U.S. Code  1519 - Destruction, alteration, or falsification of records in Federal investigations and bankruptcy](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/18/1519)

* [1663. Protection Of Government Property -- Protection Of Public Records And Documents](https://www.justice.gov/usam/criminal-resource-manual-1663-protection-government-property-protection-public-records-and)

* [1666. Destruction Of Government Property -- 18 U.S.C.  1361](https://www.justice.gov/usam/criminal-resource-manual-1666-destruction-government-property-18-usc-1361) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $43 million in Superstorm Sandy funds unaccounted for, federal audit finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
