<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8335</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 21:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was shockingly underwhelming. Maybe it's just a joke episode - like when my mom hid fake lame Christmas gifts in her room knowing I'd be snooping - and the REAL season finale will air later. That is my best explanation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 15:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I largely agree with you. S1 and2 were amazing and completely captivating to me, and the psychological-thriller component was a massive part of that. The Brody-Carrie personal relationship story arc added a richness to the narrative that was also very compelling on many levels. Season 3 I found generally enjoyable, but the narrative felt a little unfocussed and messy and Brody's storyline minus the personal drama with Carrie just felt like dead weight. (Controversially, I liked the Dana storyline, but my main complaint would be that it wasn't a tighter narrative, not that it existed in the first place.) Season 4 is lacking the character study that made the first 2 seasons so amazing even beyond the psychological thriller angles, and now that it's shifted into more straight thriller territory, I'm enjoying it for what it is.. but really can't compare it as a complete and layered work the way S1 and S2 were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 20:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excruciating pain is bearable? Yikes!

I would recommend not rushing. Setting stringent timelines on yourself like this is not the best approach to progress, either for the spiritual or physical benefits. Why the hurry?

But as everyone's said, the issue is opening your hips. Encorporating hip openers throughout the day is the best way to keep your hips open. Do a few simpler hip openers when you wake up, and every couple of hours if possible. Make sure the body is thoroughly "warmed up" before attempting the more difficult ones. Some good ones are butterfly, happy baby (half and full), pigeon, rocking the baby / foot to head, cross-legged forward bends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 02:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did my teacher training at a [Sivananda](http://sivananda.org) Ashram, and would highly recommend it if you're interested in classical hatha yoga. It's an intense 4-week programme that gives a comprehensive, spiritual, classical approach, and is for most people a life-changing experience. Not sure where you're from, but there are teacher trainings worldwide. It's a bit expensive, but worth it. Best to do a short retreat at one of the Ashrams to see if the style is for you but if that's impossible you can get a pretty good feel for the teachings/experience from their website.  Good luck, wherever you end up :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-28 01:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this post is a bit old but thought I'd weigh in... I have had a few experiences with this. The two times similar to what you describe I'd been asleep, then was drifting in between wakefulness and sleep, with pulsating energy the first time travelling very slowly and methodically up my spine. The second time was more abstract, but involved the same pulsating energy only it didn't really move, just stayed in my solar plexus/heart chakra area. Some visions accompanied this as well, and a couple of times auditory visions too. I kept trying to wake myself up and then move, but it took too much energy and I kept falling back asleep (I guess... it was so fucked up it was hard to tell what was happening). Both times happened while I was doing a lot of meditation (I too have done vipassana courses, two actually, and served a lot too).

I realised that as absolutely difficult and terrifying as it was, the best thing to do was to just "let go", and let it happen without resisting or judging.. observing it as much as possible. And after speaking with my yoga teacher, a very experienced yogi, he told me that I had to practise more yoga asanas, as this releases the blockages that prevent your prana from flowing naturally. Kundalini should be able to flow uninhibited, but when there are "blocks" it can't travel properly, which leads to the more "negative" experiences with what should be positive and wonderful spiritual growth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 03:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do both: you need to convince her that she should stay up and watch it with you - BUT make sure she thinks it's actually HER idea, not yours. This is playing in Master Mode. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 02:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meditation is a huge part of my life. Now I meditate about an hour a day. I was drawn to yoga and meditation as a young adult, and they both became very strong anchors in my spiritual/mental/general life as of a few years ago. I think IN types are naturally drawn to practises like meditation as they help us tap into that intuitive and intrapersonal parts of our selves. And it is an extremely helpful way to deal with the monkey mind and anxiety that a lot of us have! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-16 14:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't really sound like a cult, more like a small and very conservative mini-church, her ties to which sound inextricably linked to her relationship with BF. You don't really mention any practises or beliefs that make it sound cultish per se, just insular. How healthy the church home is depends on factors you don't really address--if your daughter is feeling spiritually fulfilled, if she's happy, if her life has become more meaningful, etc. I don't know if "intervening" is exactly that right approach, but you should absolutely have an honest and open conversation where you thoroughly address your concerns in a loving and non-judgmental way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 03:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if it is a legitimate health concern, they will allow you a small meal at supper. This all has to be approved beforehand, of course, but is probably within the realm of possibility. At the 2 centres I've sat at, there were always several students who were allowed evening meals--usually pregnant women, diabetics, low blood sugar, etc... so you very well may qualify.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 17:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming to r/vipassana to ask this question may yield some kind of biased answers.. but yes, you should! The meals are not really an issue--most find that they are much less hungry, as not only are you very inactive physically, but the meditation kind of, well, lowers your appetite. The hours of meditation (which is 10.75, not 7, btw :) are difficult, but it's supposed to be! AND you will most likely find either some benefit, great benefit, or a life-changing experience if you surrender to the timetable and practise. Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 03:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was basically in this situation a few years ago. Very much wanted to do teacher training with the school of yoga of my choice, but couldn't afford it. Three years later, I can, and am doing it next month! I would say continue your practise, work on being the best yogi you can be (in philosophy, not just asana), and develop as much as you can as a student while saving money. You will then approach your training with more maturity and skill, which will help you. Also, programs under $2000 may not be as comprehensive and established as you'd want. When the time is right, you will be able to do it. And as controversial as this may sound, the fact that you "really, really want" it is in itself plausibly a stumbling block for you. You will learn patience, and perhaps to deal with that craving in a more helpful way. Best of luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 20:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like your girlfriend is clearly suffering on multiple levels. I would say your first step should be to treat her with compassion and understanding, and love, whenever you can. People who are treated with true kindness and love cannot help but respond positively to it, even if it's in a small or unseen way. When she says hateful or very negative things, you could gently point out the other sides of things, from a place of compassion as opposed to just criticism. 

If you believe that, by responding to injustice with hatred as opposed to compassion and peace, you end up exacerbating the "bad" in the world, it may be helpful to discuss that frankly with her as well to understand her perspective, and see if she can understand yours. It may be, though, that she is not in a place to shift her perspective just yet, which means that at root you may have to accept her negativity/hate as it is if you want to remain with her.  You can't help effect change in someone who isn't ready for it, and learning to accept her fully as she is may actually end up helping YOU grow spiritually in the process. If her attitude is something that is really negatively affecting you, however, perhaps remaining in the relationship is not something you should do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 16:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Vipassana centers are run somewhat like Buddhist monasteries. You observe monastic principles and adhere to a very strict code of conduct and schedule specifically in order to accelerate your spiritual growth.  Though many centers themselves use the term "retreat", that's pretty misleading, and it is absolutely for a certain kind of person who is serious about both meditation and spiritual growth. Because of the culture created at the centers, and the focus and intensity of the practise, it can be absolutely and completely transformative within just several days, which would be impossible to experience while living in regular society with a little bit of meditation each day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 03:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm really not sure.. I just know that a friend of a friend was told he was not allowed to come back on account of that. If I HAD to guess, I'd say it might have something to do with the idea that a yoga teacher presumedly teaches other students meditation techniques that are not (compatible with) the vipassana technique.. but apart from that I really have no clue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-05 03:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard of a couple of people being refused back at vipassana centers after revealing they've practised reiki on others (in general, not just at the retreats). It has something to do with having manipulated the energy of other people... honestly I don't know about the supposed rationale because they're really vague when telling people why they're not allowed back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 20:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, because during these courses you're meditating for about 11 hours a day, your meditation progress is very accelerated compared to a 1/2 hour sit each day. It's beyond "intense."  The end result is positive, yes, but the process is EXTREMELY difficult emotionally and spiritually. As part of that process, many deep-rooted issues rise to the surface, and if you're not in a state of stability or mental health I can see how things may be very difficult to deal with, which may exacerbate or reignite a more serious mental health problem. So running, for example, is a great exercise, but if you're not in great shape it'd be unhelpful and probably very harmful to run a marathon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 18:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really sorry to read about this. Vipassana centers can be very strict with these kinds of things, probably due to past experiences with people with certain mental health issues having very serious negative reactions during the courses... The course is very intense and many former issues can rise to the surface during such an intensive bout of meditation. After I sat my first course I heard of people being "banned" for previous mental health problems, practising reiki, and even being a yoga teacher. I definitely WOULDN'T recommend lying on the forms, if only because speaking untruths in order to engage in a meaningful spiritual experience is kind of oxymoronic, and goes against some of the core tenets of the vipassana philosophy in the first place.

I would recommend applying to the center in Montebello QC (it's an hour east of ottawa; i'm actually going to be there in a couple weeks! and they may have a different screening process) and kind of "watering down" your manic episodes.. perhaps emphasising that you were *de-diagnosed* with bi-polar and have been given a clean bill of health and have experienced no symptoms in years.. best of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 14:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Montebello, Quebec! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 04:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just today signed up to serve my first Vipassana course. What an amazing, beautiful man, who has transformed so many people's lives. Best wishes to whatever form he's taken now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 03:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching Spencer climb this ocean wall is going to be special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-14 18:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really a cliche, but the phrase "where [houseguest]'s head is at" is unbearably overused.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-06 03:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like many women in the summer, it's because of when she puts on foundation, which is the colour of her natural skin tone, as opposed to her current tanned skin tone over the rest of her body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 02:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I thought it was hilarious when it seemed GM was just being snarky...until it turned out that GM said what she said BECAUSE CANDICE WAS FUCKING PUT UP FOR ADOPTION. Horrific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 03:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 minutes of Jeff? Seriously, CBS, give us more show!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 03:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked it.
 America really dislikes you. How do you feel about that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 01:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to live in serious dread of nearly any social interaction with people who weren't family or close friends. A few years ago I began living in the moment as much as possible. What I mean by this isn't a carpe-diem-lameity, but simply focussing on whatever was happening at any given moment. For me, the majority of my social anxiety was in anticipation--*Who am I going to talk to? What will I say? How will that situation pan out?* I started very consciously trying *not* to do that anymore before and in social situations, and just to stay in the present moment, and focus on my breath. 

When I was with other people, I listened carefully, instead of worrying what I was going to say/do next. And almost every time, things ended up being fine. And if things get awkward? That's OK too. Accept it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 04:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rachel's on the left, Elissa's on the right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 20:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](http://www.bigbrotherbuzz.com/big-brother-15-elissa-reilly-slater/) is a picture of her looking almost completely real. Definitely some major, sad changes since then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 02:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like in an alternate reality, Aaryn, GinaMarie and Jeremy would all be tortoise poachers. Especially Aaryn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 02:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would find this infinitely more engaging if I weren't just waiting impatiently for BB to start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 03:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've never heard her with that tone in her voice. It was a little subtle, but still cutting. Sadly, Aaryn is probably still completely oblivious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 05:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually, that screenshot did make me want to try out bing. The bing side was pretty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 23:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the last 1/3 of the book yesterday. Now I'm trying to decide between jumping into A Feast for Crows or waiting... it's so *consuming* I can't tell if I want to wait or not! What do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 16:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been reading along with the show but after the season finale, I couldn't wait until next year to keep reading. I read the last 300 pages yesterday, almost unable to put it down except for those moments every 30 pages or so when my head would, again, explode. What an incredible read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 13:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that, and think it's largely true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 04:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in a different place than you (in Canada) but here, and most places that I know of, it is virtually UNHEARD OF to land a teaching job without "putting in your time" as a sub first. As great a teacher you may be or become, by looking at your resume you may be automatically unconsidered if an admin or HR person sees you don't have experience subbing, especially if there's a 2-year gap from when you graduated. Most teachers I know worked evening/weekend jobs which allowed them to supply teach whenever they could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 03:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to meditate first thing in the morning (when my mind is clearest, like you mention), though I also like to after doing yoga--definitely not the "exercise" you mean, but it is an AMAZING way to "prepare" for meditation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 13:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes: this is yet another piece of the Don Draper identity puzzle. Don is emotionally damaged in a million ways, including sex addiction, and every season we catch yet another glimpse into how his very unhealthy early encounters with sexuality have had an impact on his adult sexuality. The writers and actors knew exactly what they were doing with this scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-16 15:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title should be "Reading digital screens in the bathtub." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-14 02:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't check my work e-mail on my phone, ever. I do check my e-mails regularly while at work, and usually at home and every day on the week-ends at least once, though honestly, I'd like to get OUT of the habit of bringing my work home with me so often.  I try to be "present" as much as possible, and being glued to a cell phone, especially when around family or friends, is a real hindrance to that. I have never NEEDED to be connected on an constant basis. Probably 1/3 of the teachers at my school are generally the same way, and the rest not but mostly by choice. As for my principal calling...I've only been contacted at home by my principal twice, and I was able to answer. But if I wasn't able to get back until the next day? That'd be fine, I'm sure. I've run into real emergencies only a couple of times, and that was AT school, not on a weeknight or weekend. But it sounds like I live in a "slower" world than you, likely than most North Americans. I like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 23:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, sure, your particular job may require one, but of course there are lots of people (I'd guess most) have jobs that don't necessitate cell phones. I'm one of them. As a teacher, any phone correspondence related to work I do takes place either at school or at home. My boyfriend, on the other hand, is a reporter, and has his cell phone on him at all times out of necessity. Most of my friends have jobs where they have office phones and don't need cells for work.  But regardless, if I found out a guy who was interested in me didn't have a cell phone, I certainly wouldn't say "welp, must be unemployed, no thanks." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-13 16:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have no problem with that--in fact, I'd probably find it at least somewhat attractive because it shows a level of non-conformity and freethought. Facebook is useful but pretty lame, and I respect adults my age who choose not to use it. Cellphones FEEL necessary but really aren't if you have a house phone with voicemail. It's just another symptom of how everyone expects instant gratification these days and can't wait for anything, including communication. I can wait the 4 hours until he gets home to get my message. The world isn't going to implode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 03:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You definitely should read at least some Gogol! Unless you hate great literature, I suppose... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 03:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (I definitely can't pick just one favourite tv show atm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 03:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two meth dealers, a newly enlightened woman, and a 40-something comedian navigate their way through the New York advertising world of the 1960s, fighting for their right to sit on an iron throne. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 02:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super lame and boring and I don't get the appeal whatsoever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 02:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would listen to these guys all day, any day. Though I'd want Dali around too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 02:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommend that it doesn't really matter the style so long as it is neat, clean, and that you should avoid any hairstyle that looks overdone, or like you're trying too hard. If you have a super fancy updo that clearly took a lot of time and effort, for example, it just makes it seem like your priorities are a little off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 02:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then what's it for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 02:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After I read "The Overcoat" by Nikolai Gogol, I was inconsolable for hours. I was in public when reading, and when I finished I was openly weeping. While reading 'The Kite Runner' by Khaled Hosseini there was a huge section that had me crying so much I had to stop reading every few pages just to cry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 19:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> indecent images of children 

200 child abuse images on his computer

That literally means child porn, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 19:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be the worst analogy I've ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 19:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many adorably angry 19 year old boys! I really appreciate the new rules, as now r/atheism has become a hive of hilarious entertainment, as opposed to just a redundant shithole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 16:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sandobit makes the point I would have made... and still got downvoted. On r/feminism. 

re: how you've never seen a redditor who doesn't want equality... if you want, I can forward you comment examples of that, as I come across them in the redditsphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 04:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/noonereally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 04:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 04:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard of Thrice, and "alternative rock" is a massive genre... but I will say I just bought the new Vampire Weekend album (Modern Vampires of the City), and it is absolutely freaking amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 04:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If my clothes had pockets big enough for my keys, phone, and wallet, I think they'd likely be pretty hideous. And then where would I put my book and bottle of water? 3 3 purses 3 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 04:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you two should date 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 03:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually confession bear = "i'm edgy and secretly proud of my actions; upvotes plz" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 02:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should the civil rights movement have also fought for the rights for whites? Should the pride movement also fight for the rights of heterosexuals? The "feminist movement" (as if it's one thing, but OK) generally works toward *raising* the social, political, and economic status of women to that of equal footing with men. It's not just about blanket equality assurance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 02:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is teeming with very vocal anti-equality and narrow-minded users. Though they're not the majority, the fact that they are a VERY vocal minority can create a palpably toxic and unwelcoming environment for people who want to discuss "feminist" issues. Even mention terms like "feminism", "equality", "rape culture," "affirmative action", "wage gap" or "misogyny" in any popular sub and you will be bombarded, downvoted, and attacked. Mentioning that you're a feminist can easily incur as much negative attention as calling yourself a nazi, a racist, or a pedophile. It's a young (old) boys club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-02 00:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish someone in this thread could tell us what Seth's position is now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 03:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Checked wikipedia. Stopped reading at "multi-level marketing." Don't do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 03:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine a housewife as spending her days cooking, cleaning, possibly watching daytime TV while the pie is baking, and waiting for her husband to get home from work. No thank you. Though if/when I have children, I would absolutely prefer to not go back to work until they were all school-age. 

And with or without children, I wouldn't be opposed to working part-time if that was financially possible, but definitely not so I could simply be a housewife. There are far more interesting and rewarding things I'd prefer to be doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 01:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely see what you're saying--and that's why I said "can be" as opposed to "is." Most of the people I know who grew up on (or very near) small family farms have a similar outlook. 

Just out of curiosity, are you vegan now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 01:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, maybe I should qualify--I'd assess the Star as a usually-above-average-by-Canadian-standards source.

I just checked out [The Sun](http://www.torontosun.com/), which reminds me of one of those porn pop up ads and just screams TABLOID TABLOID. Sex store wallpaper? Nice. Plus their editorial today is on how greedy the CBC is. Gag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 00:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I find the Star to be a generally good news source, with a fairly progressive bent. The Sun I usually find panders to an overly simplistic conservative mindset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 00:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I like the (subtly different) question you answered far better than the question initially posed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 22:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol!!! At least s/he did give an answer eventually, after several very apparently important clarifications.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-27 16:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, I do have one unrelated question!  How do teachers deal with discipline issues (disrespect, defiance, disruptiveness, etc)--or is this not an issue? Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 20:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ages 16-18. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 20:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "upper secondary school" I think the term is lukio or gymnasium.  By "vocational school" I think the term is yrkesinstitut (?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hei Finland! I'm a teacher in Canada and have a few specific questions about your secondary school experience. I'd love to hear what you have to say! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 19:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hei Finland!

I am a high school English (Language Arts ) teacher in Canada and am interested in some of the particulars in Language Arts (idinkieli) classes in upper secondary school (or "lukio"). Please feel free to answer any of the below questions with as much or little detail as you'd like.

1. What are final exams like in these classes? Where I teach, usually a final examination would be worth about 30% of the term's final mark, and would consist mostly of multiple choice questions on reading comprehension and a writing section. What is it like in Finland?

2. How do teachers deal with deadlines for assignments? Is it a more permissive system, or are deadlines for assignments fixed and strict?

3. Are classes more lecture based (like university), group work-based, student-driven, or a variety?

4. Are students required to take Language Arts classes at vocational school? How are they different from at upper secondary school?

Thanks so much :)

EDIT: Thank you everyone for your answers! Very helpful and interesting. Upvotes for everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-26 04:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you remove the temporal/spatial degrees of separation like this, it shows just how disturbing eating animals can be. 

Interestingly, as horrific as the pig box seems, it ain't got nothin' on virtually any factory farm!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
