<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4121</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 03:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is only to make people feel better so they forget about it even though nothing is really being done. This is only on the federal level and not the State/local level where a little over 80% of people are incarcerated. The feds dont care about incarceration rates but the states sure the fuck do since they make tons of money off of cheap prison labor and fines off of things like possession of a plant. 
Look for private prisons to expand now at the state and local level. This is still a huge issue that should not be considered anywhere close to being fixed. It's symbolic gesture at best in order for get people to forget about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 04:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not taking anything away from his thought process but he ended up being a stooge for the DEA/FBI just like Leary and Hoffman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 00:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might think so but I'm pretty sure it all runs together. I want to play connect the dots, basically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need videos that you can't just easily google about symbolism, freemasons, the illuminati, child sacrifice and Hollywood that are legit and won't get me laughed out of the room when I try to share the information. Any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 17:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternate ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 17:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mrs. Doubtfire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 16:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. No. I'm guessing he likes them way younger. 

Edit: I got the "up to eleven" joke and upvoted it accordingly. I just decided to throw a paedophilia joke in there for shits and giggles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 16:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit! I can't believe the pastor's name is actually Dr. Marshall Stacks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 16:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is OP's mom.

Edit: Just to clarify, I'm implying op's mom is involved in a gangbang and is waiting for all the others to finish so she can get up.

Edit 2: So check it out....in this scenario op's mom is obviously in porn. She is involved in a scene with multiple "partners". They are all attempting to ejaculating on her and some of them have yet to finish doing so. So just like Ledecky, op's mom is waiting on others to finish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 16:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mrs. Doubtfire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 21:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're all obvious after the fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. He just looks the other way and continues to let the Clinton Foundation fund them by arming Syrian rebels via Saudi Arabia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is genius! Hillary is so fucking greedy she'll probably turn herself in for the reward money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 03:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'll show em! Oppression over! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 15:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome! I'm glad they decided to leave you alone. The amount of food that is wasted is sickening. It's crazy because you know like 90% of bands would encourage their leftovers to be eaten rather than thrown away. It's rediculous. All because people are scared to get sued by people that would never sue them and just be grateful for a full belly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. Saying that I ate the food scraps of a shitty band just to have a full stomach for free is definitely a humble "brag".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a stagehand. We always eat and/or split up what the band doesn't eat or drink when they are gone. Well, a couple of us went back to the green room and started chowing down because we thought they were all gone. Turns out they were not. They all walked in to us scarfing down their food. Our collective heads slowly looked up at once like a deer looking up from it's salt lick. We just kinda stared at each other for about 8 seconds. We then just nodded at 'em, mouth full of their tuna/burgers and walked passed them not making eye contact. 
The best part of this story is that one of them still ate half their burger that I didn't finish. So just for a little bit I felt the roles were reversed and it was glorious.


Edit: Words  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 13:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I feel bad for eating their ahi tuna and burgers in the green room a few years back. Getting caught was awkward but it was a small price to pay for a full stomach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 04:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who gives a fuck? Also, the Martian sucked soft dicks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 18:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have to catch anyone on foot when they can just shoot them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 04:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That letter is pretty heavy.  
One of the many things that brings to light that we're all pawns in a game we're not even playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's weird that his mom, who was a school administrator and his dad, a postal worker, would let him drop out of school in the 10th grade and start selling drugs. He made a shit load of money doing that. Then all of a sudden he disappeared for a few years only to come back and find Ruthless Records.  Then all of these rappers who turned out to be amazing and extremely influential joined his label and it was history. Makes me wonder if he wasn't helping the C.I.A. sell cocaine first. 

Edit: words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 21:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a heart attack gun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 20:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is just saying that so he can play good cop to Trump's bad cop when he picks Newt to be his VP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 19:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link! Yeah, it's such an evil and genius plan that worked to perfection. We are all pawns in a game we aren't even playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vanilla Thrice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they do anything?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ever think "Gangster Rap" was used as a weapon and Ice T, Ice Cube and Courtney Love were the "bullets"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most in this sub know that the gov't used gangster rap as a weapon but nobody really discusses the players in the scheme.

Rock/Grunge were going to be the staple of modern music in the mid 80's to mid 90's until they saw an opportunity to make white people scared of black youth, which were made angry and aggressive through gangster rap and living conditions in their forced and designated sections of cities, in order to divide us even more than we already are. It's the same time as the L.A. riots was going on as well.

Well, during this time Ice T(Body Count/Cop Killer), Ice Cube (N.W.A./Fuck the Police) and Courtney Love (Kurt Cobain) were all players in the game, in my opinion.

I was sitting around thinking about how Ice T went from clean cut, to 4 yrs in Army, to robbing, to famous rapper, to famous actor, and so on and so forth. Then I started thinking about how Ice Cube sold his first song to Ice T at 16 like he was being groomed or something. I mean, hell, his first rap group was even called C.I.A. ha. Anyways, he went from groomed by Ice T, to famous gangster rapper, to famous movie star and so on and so forth. Now, this is where Courtney comes in. She is the child of Linda, a renowned psychotherapist from San Francisco and Hank Harrison, who was the road manager and publicist of the C.I.A. project The Grateful Dead. She went from orphan, to stripper, to jailed for theft, to a musician/actress, to dating (Corgan) and marrying (Cobain) famous rock stars, then famous musician and famous actress. 

Obviously this is all speculation and me not being able to sleep but it seems that the gov't groomed Ice T and Ice Cube. They played ball and came out with a genre of music that would anger black youth and make them think it's cool to sell the drugs the C.I.A. was bringing in, as well as dividing the country w/ race. By doing this they were promised they'd be set for life. Millions of dollars, acting fame, musical fame, etc. Same for Courtney. They promised her millions of dollars, acting/musical fame and relevance. All she had to do was kill grunge...which she did when she had Kurt murdered. 

Anybody else out there ever think about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 07:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Polebearer" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bread and Circuses  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 15:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A swift kick to the back of the Achilles tendon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No, silly. That's his brother Keith. Keith Obama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 06:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and his drones are "damaging" innocent children overseas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 05:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!!  I'm gonna now go home and take an ore bath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 05:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. Well, you're in luck. I only collect Reddit silver.

Edit: Also, congratulations...assuming you give a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 05:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. You have to possess books in order to burn them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 05:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's long overdue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cleveland furniture stores need to start marking up their couches. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 05:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 14:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assange is just Russia's middle man in their "spat" with America. They are using him as a scapegoat to do their passive-aggressive taunting to the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 15:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, yes. The R. Kelly method. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We give them millions every month. Other than praying, it's the least they can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American citizens should form their own "Pirate Party" called the National Opposition Party or....the "NO Party" for short. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 22:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any suggestions for an exceptional father's rights lawyer in Louisville? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 02:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 13:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This shouldn't scare us.....this should piss us off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-30 07:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So who is this Frank Hugyournards dude that did the article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 06:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree and without needlessly going on and on, I'll just say that I do all of that and more. However, it still isn't enough. We can't get enough numbers to do anything.  As long as people continue to be a slave to technology and apathetic instead of angry it will continue. As long as the under qualified, trigger happy, militarized police force have their boots to our necks, most people aren't willing to risk getting their ass beat, losing their jobs, going to jail, etc for a war they think isn't winnable. Enough people don't realize their will to fight is being snuffed out by social media and technology. I mean, how bad does it have to get until people put down their laptops and pick up their "pitchforks"? Unfortunately, I believe we are going to find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 03:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No you are not. They want us to be distracted by this divisive dog and pony show that is the presidential race. The president is picked for us and our votes don't matter. Trump is only here to make sure The Dark Queen wins and Bernie is just here to give the illusion of hope and give the sjw's more migro-aggressions to waste their energy on. Unless we all start ignoring this pander pageant and get as passionate with who we put in local office as who we do in the oval one, then nothing will change. Personally, I don't think people are all of a sudden going to stop voting against their own self interest and just start educating themselves using the right avenues. We need to get out into the streets and I'm not talking about this Occupy bullshit where people just sing kumbaya and make people late for work. In order to make real change anger must replace apathy and convenience. I'm not very optimistic but I have a lot of popcorn and people in my bubble. Time to sit back, relax and watch the show. But make no mistake, in the rare instance that we actually do get fed up enough to take our country back then you'll be able to find me on the front lines. Change starts from the ground up not the top down.

Edit: Words and such
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 23:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honey, is that you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 00:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assassins Cred </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 03:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can this be an Olympic sport?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 03:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Louisville will crash the playoff party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 01:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because, isn't this Deja Vu... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 19:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And so I come out the closet 
And I step outside
And I take a deep breath as my weight subsides
And I scream from the top of my lungs
Let's all get along! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 16:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think he would be fair check out his part in the whole Waco fiasco. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 14:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She never left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's better than having banana split ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 23:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title Edit: "Someone's daughter's friend is having a normal hair day at home." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 22:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just floating the idea around but 
there's a "P" and what seems to be the start of an "S" on the door behind her. Is she in a psych ward? 

Edit: Sigh, root beer float joke Level 0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 14:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will the bigot beat the murderer? Stay tuned for more "Are You Smarter Than A Cheese Grater" to find out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 14:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they just made it to where you have to pay $2.99. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 12:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that and saying no to Rutgers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 02:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sigh, nope. Unfortunately, it's as simple as tribalism. People are just going to their corners, clinging onto whatever in their party it is that they lack or believe in their own life. It's about "I'm right and you're wrong" instead of really searching ones own mortality and making the right decisions to advance the species.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 02:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see everyone is giving into this divisive dog and pony show. The presidency was decided in 2008. Trump is here to ensure the Dark Queen gets the White House and Bernie is just here to give the illusion of hope. The whole system is broken and rigged against us yet we waste energy and time fighting against ourselves. That is what they want us to do. If we really want change it has to start from the ground up not from the top down. We have to get as riled up and excited about who we put in local office as we do who we put in the Oval Office. We are too distracted by surface and non-issues and our freedoms and voices are being suppressed as we sit idly by. Our responsibility doesn't end at the voting booth. That's where it begins. How bad does it have to get until anger finally replaces apathy and we decide to take OUR country back? If we ALL don't do some quick growing up and come together we will soon find out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 22:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The current Democratic Party needs to be dead to us. They only speak for their own corrupt agenda. We must look past the tribalism and break our ties to it.  We need a true Democratic Party, or 5, that doesn't try by any means possible to silence the voices of their own party.
It started way back in 1776, with the Constitution, when James Madison felt the country should be designed, and with his initiative, was designed for the power and control of America to be in the hands of the wealthy. He did this because he thought the wealthy were the more responsible citizen. So he ended up giving the power to the Senate, which at that time wasn't voted on but picked from the wealthiest of men. The system has been stacked against us since the beginning. I hate to say it but your vote doesn't matter right now. If voting mattered they wouldn't let us do it. The people that count the votes elect the politicians not the people who cast them. The change that you want to see happen won't happen until we stop being apathetic and scared and get out into the streets...And I'm not talking about this Occupy Wall St. shit where we all just sing Kumbaya and make it more difficult for our fellow man/woman to get to work. We have to stop being too apathetic and scared to try and take the power back from the ones who get ahead by making us powerless. Our freedoms are being taken away right in front of us and yet we sit and do nothing while the ones who destroy our country laugh at us with impunity. We are on the verge of losing OUR country and if we don't fight to get it back now then we might not have the chance again in our lifetimes. How bad is it going to have to get before we say "enough is enough"?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 15:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beyond the Thundersome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ......so personalized condoms it is! 

Just kidding. Good answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would you be able to actually achieve that and how would you use the surplus? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since change only starts from the ground up and not the top down....What are some unconventional methods, other than not getting your news from the mainstream media, we can use to get others as excited about who wins local and state elections as we do this divisive dog and pony show that is the presidential election?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares?! It's such an obvious divisive, surface issue. There are actual problems we have to address that's happening to our Commonwealth. There isn't any time to waste on giving any thoughts on where people piss and shit. There are better ways to focus your energy...unless you're some discriminatory dullard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 19:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How important is de-militarizing local police departments to you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 18:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet he gets traded to the Tampa Bay Ray Rices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 17:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! Very well said. We have to start regaining our country from the ground up, not from the top down. Too many people get left out that way.....and it makes no sense when you think about it. The presidential race is just there to distract us so the rich can continue to get richer through the current status quo. We HAVE to get just as excited about local and state elections no matter what state it is. Thanks for being part of the solution and not part of the problem :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 02:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laughing is better than crying so there's that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 01:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it :) You should submit some links about Sellus yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 23:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have to put away our screens and get out into our communities. We have to get as excited about who we put into local office as we do this divisive dog and pony show that is the presidential race. All that crap is just there to distract us. We must stop being apathetic and so comfortable in our own lives that we let our democracy and privacy be taken away from us, right in front of our face, while we sit idly by. It is up to us to make this country about it's citizens again. Sellus can absolutely win but not by just wishing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 22:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that endorsement was great!

Edit: He is doing an AMA tomorrow from 1pm to 2pm est. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Sellus Wilder, the Tim Canova of Kentucky. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 22:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 15:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Braddock: Missing in Action III </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 07:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he should give Trayvon's family 3/5ths of the money he receives from the auction as a sign of goodwill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 02:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you still think that nuclear power plants are bombs waiting to destroy us all? Also, why aren't you just the status quo of the non-status quo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 19:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..that came out of Kissinger's poisoned asshole  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 18:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other news....peanut butter is made from peanuts.

Edit: By this I mean, "What else is new?" in a "It's a shame nothing is going to be done about it." tone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 19:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 14:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very much so. Especially his wife. There was also pee and poop in it as well. Long story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 07:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boss's dishwasher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 17:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Barring no republican democracy theft or democratic indictment, he has the 4th best chance to become president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 15:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep...and he has the 4th best chance of anybody in the country to become the president of the "United" States and one of the most powerful men in the planet. 'Murica #1!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 15:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you hear that everybody? It's fine to come out now. The NSA doesn't "work" anymore because they have too much of your information to search through.  Oh, happy day!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 00:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aka  Mr. Littlepinky Bigthumb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 16:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are past the point of non-violent protest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a stagehand, working Prince shows were awful.  Him and his whole crew were dicks. He almost didn't play one time because we wouldn't black out the exit lights...since it was fucking illegal. His tour manager was some bitch who kept calling the white guys on the crew "boy" because she thought it was empowering. Fucking sucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 02:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice of him to drop by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 13:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boeings are weapons.  9/11 Eventually Forget! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 02:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thx. We are looking to park a 34' Airstream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 15:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who fucking cares </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 15:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably to keep other countries from suing America for all the innocent civilians they've killed in their respective homelands as well as trying to preserve the petrodollar for as long as possible, even though it's death is inevitable.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best RV park in the area or best place to rent land? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 23:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 01:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Genes, lips and tits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should all put down the laptops and pick up the pitchforks. "They" will not fear us until they start swinging from the gallows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 02:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should put down our computers and pick up our pitchforks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 05:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't they all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 05:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not on acid during a day when about 40 elementary schools are there on field trips </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 04:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 04:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ay Dios Mio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 03:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure I have. I ate some ice cream once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 02:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shoulda used her vag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
