<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 17:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could simply have that "pots not bad at all for you man" older cousin or brother to make you want to try it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Tag Posts Still a Safe Investment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't the Note 5 use only Exynos though? As in there wasn't a Snapdragon model released for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However you cannot even say that things do not exist because then you are implying that there is something which has the property of not existing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah you're right, I had the numbers switched </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except hemp isn't outlawed? There's still a lot of domestic products made from hemp, it's just not allowed to contain THC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samsung phones do perform better with the Exynos chips, however the Snapdragon variants yield higher benchmarks. 

EDIT: this is incorrect, Exynos yields higher benchmarks and performs better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're mentioned in about every other chapter but when I get home I'll try to find a specific quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Are the Philosophers in the Lankavatara Sutra? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 07:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this Sutra the Buddha denounces a lot of what the "philosophers" believe especially in regards to discrimination. Is he just referring to those that study philosophy and is saying that the Dharma in the Lankavatara transcends philosophy or is he referring to a specific group of scholars at that time like the Hinayana/Theravada which I know Mahayana sutras often argue against? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Monks, even if bandits were to carve you up savagely, limb by limb, with a two-handled saw, he among you who let his heart get angered even at that would not be doing my bidding"  
-Shakyamuni Buddha, Kakacupama Sutta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 17:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the album Dive by Tycho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 01:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleep well pupper : ( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always look into the other philosophies and religions and find that the Dharma has an answer for everything. It's different too than other religions or spiritualities like, let's say, New Age that have an answer for everything as the answers that the Dharma gives can be proven and can always successfully shut down all other ways of thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny because the same thing was actually said in the Gita haha.  
Anyway I have no interest in practicing Hinduism. I came to Buddhism from Advaita Vedanta so I'm already familiar with the superiority of the Dharma over other philosophies and faiths. Religion/spirituality/philosophy is just an interest of mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it to be more helpful towards understanding the Dharma by looking at other walks of life though. I feel it strengthens the Dharma by being able to see something that is seemingly contradictory still be subject to the Dharma. Also there's a sort of "you need to know what is wrong to know what is right" mentality towards it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of karma like this:  
A bad action means making the world worse. We live in the world. Therefore our world becomes worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. There's a reason why the Buddha didn't just kill himself after attaining enlightenment. Now we know the Dharma and we have this amazing opportunity to practice it and teach it.  
Being born in the human realm is supposedly extremely difficult. Sogyal Rinpoche explains it as imagining an ocean the size of the universe. A sea turtle swims throughout this ocean and pops his head up every 100 years. Also floating on this ocean is an inner tube with a 1 foot diameter hole. The chances of being born a human are less than the chances of that turtle poking his head up through the inner tube. Best to take advantage of this life as much as possible as enlightenment in the other realms is immensely more difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we can be compassionate to help others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that there is nothing to die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 18:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let go of the notion of self. Stop thinking "harming myself vs harming others". It is just harm. Suffering is being caused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Akshobhya in Hinduism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't sure if I should post this here or on r/hinduism, however I already frequent this sub so I figured I should ask here.  
I picked up a copy of the Bhagavad Gita: As it Is (the Hare Krishna interpretation of the Bhagavad Gita) and at the end of the introduction there's a list of the disciples of Krishna beginning with Brahm and ending with the author of the book, however number 9 says Akshobhya. I've always known that Hindus consider Shakyamuni Buddha as an avatar of Vishnu/incarnation of Krishna but I found it odd that a celestial buddha would be mentioned as a disciple here. I haven't been able to find anything out by googling it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 15:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's emptiness, there is no such thing as me, you, the computer/phone you're using. It's all a product of convention and illusion. Therefore Maitreya is also empty, void of a self. There isn't anything there that makes Maitreya "real". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 04:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember that in truth there is no such thing as Maitreya Buddha, so instead of saying that Maitreya will be the next Buddha, say that the next Buddha will be Maitreya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because in the early seasons she didn't have the acorn sticker.  
http://pm1.narvii.com/6102/74e5c120d5008213b1444fc234585a0a3e53816e_hq.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 05:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It proved itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It's the Walkway font </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wallpaper from Minimalist Wallpapers App  
Icon Pack: Lines free  
Widget: Kwgt base clock widget   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Start of an Adventure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you post the resources? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 18:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted because of The Cure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Digital Logic Design Project </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Verizon Note 4 didn't get MM until April </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no. Zen obviously picked up a lot of influence from Taoism but it also includes ideas and practices that aren't found in either Taoism nor other schools of Buddhism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? The apps on my gingerbread tablet don't even work anymore haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably a deal that the carriers make them. Like for example Verizon will tell Samsung "we'll stock your phone but only if you let us install some of our stuff on it." Apple on the other hand is big enough to tell the carriers "no" and the carriers have to comply or else they miss out on selling iPhones which makes them a lot of money. Google probably didn't let Verizon do anything with the Pixel since it was already very good for Verizon to be the only carrier stocking the phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cell phone carriers like to put their own apps and features on Android phones that I've never actually seen a person use in real life. Apple and Google however don't let the carriers do that on the iPhone/Pixel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Vimalakirti Sutra features a layman named Vimalakirti who actually outshines all the Buddha's head-disciples and is an extremely proficient Bodhisattva. On the Theravadan side however, Bhikku Bodhi states in his book "In the Buddha's Words" that one must go into homelessness if one wants to attain enlightenment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 23:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished reading the Vimalakirti Sutra and it's actually pretty hilarious how much it shits on non-Mahayanists. Half the lines of the disciples that aren't Manjushri are pretty much "We're Hinayana plebs so we'll never understand Vimalakirti's wisdom nor have his powers."  
  
That being said I absolutely loved the Vimalakirti Sutra and highly recommend it. Even with the unecessesary shitting on Theravadans (I lean mostly Theravadan myself) it's what made this sutra so fun to read. It may have actually been the most fun sutra I've read yet from when all the disciples each bringing up accounts of when they got shut down by Vimalakirti to when Vimalakirti brings all the celestial bodhisattvas and their Buddha to his house. It also had a lot of good insight on non-dualism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the statue as clinched fist on head. When I first saw the statue I thought of it as someone undergoing distressed thinking, but now it doesn't look distressed anymore with the hand under the chin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll start building the ship for the Viking funeral </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isis- Weight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's neither </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 04:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What everyone has been saying about Maitreya is correct, however the existence of Buddhas varies between Theravada and Mahayana. Theravada Buddhism believes that Gautama/Gotama (also often referred to as Shakyamuni) was the most recent buddha, and that the next will be Maitreya once the Dharma/Dhamma is forgotten. Mahayana Buddhism believes in celestial-buddhas which are buddhas that exist in other locations around the universe. The most popular of these is Amitabha Buddha, which is the central figure of Pure Land Buddhism. Others include Akshobhya, Vairocana, etc.  
  
The definition of a buddha differs between Mahayana and Theravada Buddhism. Theravada Buddhism claims that a buddha is one who attains enlightenment without learning the Dhamma from someone else. Someone who does learn the Dhamma from someone else is called an arahant. Both arahants and buddhas in Theravada Buddhism are considered to be on the same level of enlightenment, although buddhas possess more supernatural powers. A bodhisatta is a future buddha, so Maitreya is a bodhisatta and Shakyamuni used to be a bodhisatta. This paragraph purely refers to Theravada Buddhism.  
  
Mahayana Buddhism believes that a buddha is one who is on the highest level of enlightenment possible, and becomes so by living as a bodhisattva (the Sanskrit variant of bodhisatta). A bodhisattva is one who became enlightened, attained Nirvana, but continues to stay in Samsara for the wellbeing of others. During this stay in Samsara, the bodhisattva's buddha-nature continues to be nurtured until eventually they become a buddha. An arhat (Sanskrit variant of arahant) is a being who attained Nirvana and leaves Samsara, thus not attaining as much enlightenment as a bodhisattva. Maitreya is still believed to be a bodhisattva, and there are many others such as Avalokiteshvara and Manjushri. This paragraph purely refers to Mahayana Buddhism.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Dharma Explanation Made by a Meme Page on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 20:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Possibly, just try not to blow a lot of air into it because that might lodge the water further in there, maybe try a warm hairdryer for a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 19:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually how the phone waterproofs itself! If it tried to charge with water inside the charging port the phone would break. The galaxy s5's solution was to keep a flap covering the charging port. The s7 however is fine with you getting water inside the port, but just won't let you charge while there's water in there so the phone doesn't break. Wireless charging should work, and in the meantime just keep trying to dry out the port until it turns itself back on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 02:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same was with my galaxy note 4. I disabled Facebook and now it's back to normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
