<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1298</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 14:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know. John Goodman is up there with Anthony Hoskins, Michael Caine, Tom Hanks, and Jack Nicholson. He's one this era of cinema's best actors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 13:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand then. I had 2007 coins when literally all I did was one game of vs team death match, 1-50 horde at casual, and up to the first part of scene 2 act 1.

I didn't preorder or anything, so I don't know where the rest of the coins came from, but 700 coins for the best part of three hours play is terrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 07:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't add up. I played hardcore campaign until act1 scene 2, one game of versus, and one game 1-50 casual horde. 

I finished last night with 2000 credits in the bank. Do you start the game with credits already or something, as that just doesn't sound right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 08:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheech did warn Chong about coke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 07:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She Bear Glare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 07:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to London!! Here is your umbrella and swear book  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 08:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, if we get the game we we're shown 4 years ago with a fair chunk of content, I'll be totally happy with no graphical updates. 

Except one: 

Please change the warlock melee animation so it no longer looks like I'm throwing some dust from my pocket at folks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 23:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pretty certain that Eliskni or whatever the fallen are actually called will be a playable race in D2, much like the Elites were in halo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 12:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overwatch is a multiplatforn shooter, had I meant what you think I mean, I'd have said Shooter **on** console.  I'm sorry if my choice of words wasn't clear enough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 09:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'll check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MMORPGs with old style traditional RPG Menu battle systems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 08:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if there are any mmo's that have old fashioned traditional menu battle systems, that also utilise that in pvp? I appreciate that it isn't high octane thrills, but I would have thought it would lead to a much more strategic combat system than who can mash their hot bar quickest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 23:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a console exclusive shooter though is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PC

Edit: Destiny was made for consoles from the ground up making it a 'console shooter'. BF4, Overwatch etc were all made and released on PC meaning development was also made with PC in mind. It changes the way shooters are developed, as are some other games made with mouse control input in mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 17:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, Destiny is this generations best console shooter. Honestly, I think that says more about the games industry in general at the moment more than anything else. 

Destiny is not a bad game and has great shooting mechanics,  it is also the poster child of why too many publisher fingers can ruin an otherwise great game. I'm more interested to see if half of the cut content makes it back into Destiny 2 next year seeing as they now won't be supporting last gen consoles, and are in fact bringing it to PC (rumour).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 15:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes the game is not what it was supposed to be, it is still a great game though and honestly still is the best console shooter on this generation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 09:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I starting thinking as I was watching this that this could be a new Bond franchise with regular outfitters, intel folks, and some other re-occuring characters just with a different objective etc.

That actually would be really cool as long as they don't get crazy with the action scenes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 15:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That statement belongs on /r/WTF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can have a government organisation look at a business, what it does, the image of the company and who it has hired to deem if it is fair or not. 

If there is some kind of discrepancy, that business should be looked at in a case by case situation to assess if it's being unfair, or if the discrepancy is appropriate for the business itself, or its image. 

I.E. if you had business selling feminine hygiene products you'd think it'd be acceptable for there to be very few or any men at all to be working there. So if a man complained he was turned down for that job because he was a man, in this case it would sort of be acceptable, because some clientele may be uncomfortable with discussing their needs with a member of the opposite sex. 

I know what I'm going to say next is an unpopular opinion here as Reddit has a 'stick it to the man' attitude to business, but the needs of the business should be primary concern. When quotas cause a detriment to the business meaning it may earn less money because of it, people seem to forget that if the business fails, then more than the one person who wasn't hired will be out of a job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 12:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imposing quotas in general are a bad idea. The best candidate for the job should be chosen, irrespective of what they have betwix their legs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 18:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan Tudyk is my power animal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 17:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a completely bullshit way to fleece people who are *interested in cosmetics* out of more money. 

If you aren't interested in skins or cosmetics, you don't need to buy them. Sure they put a bigger carrot in front of you to try and get you to bite, but the more this stuff happens the. More consumer savvy people will become. It's just a shame it's going to take like ten years before people realise this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 12:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we have more artifact drops pleeeeaaaaaaase </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 18:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm amazed you got upvoted. Every time I argue this point I get shouted down by 'pro choicers'. 

Yes it's your body but if you didn't want the chance of a baby growing in you, use contraception. And before folks start shouting about rape babies, go look up what percentage of abortions are from rape cases and how many are aborted that are second thoughts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 17:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And brown... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 12:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I'd like *after* the final two ASOIAF books come out for there to be a single book story from one of the last hero / AA / stallion who mounted the world/ whatever for the original hero from the previous events with the others time period, only told from a companion of that heros perspective. I'd love to see how that legend spread to different parts of Planetos in different forms etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 08:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're in a firefight with a storm trooper asking yourself that exact question, you're off guard for just a split second giving the storm trooper the advantage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 20:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't that describe all hotbar mmo combat, which is like 80% the market share?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 09:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bardem is incredible in pretty much everything he has been in, in a pretty diverse set of roles.

My personal favourite scene with him though would have to be in The Councillor when telling Michael Fassbender about a previous nights shenanigans he spent with Cameron Diaz's character.

His face during the windscreen of the car part is priceless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 05:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original has the most appropriate score i've ever heard: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AK5jyVCdXwc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 12:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He ran down a Cephalopod. *on foot* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 12:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casino Royale was how you correctly modernise an ageing franchise. I just don't understand why they are now reverting to the older style bonds again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 13:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just gave me the idea that the traveller is actually  what is causing the darkness and that it is actually consuming all these civilisations. 

The darkness isn't chasing the traveller, it's what the traveller leaves behind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 12:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My money is on that Rasputin will be our new SIVA spliced ghost in destiny 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 12:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old school game but Ultima Online I think would fit that bill  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 12:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they had 2 heroic play lists.

1- All currently updated strikes are included, no strike specific gear, rep bonus remains as is. 

2- Themed playlist of a small selection of either classic, taken or SIVA or hive or cabal strikes, does have some strike specific loot, and also has better faction to vanguard rep reward ratios. Rotates weekly like the old Nightfalls did and there is a weekly challenge quest to do obscure objectives across the strikes in that weeks playlist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 12:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean there are *other* people who live near me on this sub?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 08:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was such a habit in classic UFO I ended up sabe scumming before landing so if I got ramp raped I could regenerate the mission and hopefully get a reasonable spawn. 

That was when I was eleven, but now I'm older I realise that it was just good tactics from the aliens. It was actually a pretty good reenactment of being dropped into a hot live fire zone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sucks because I think there is a great *great* boxer in there somewhere. His fight against Vlad proves that he has the control and discipline when needed, and he's not exactly an old man either meaning he still has time to grow as a fighter. 

I really hope that this doesn't end his career and he can come back and be the boxer he is but people seem to not want him to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 18:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good or bad, the guy has personality and to be frank here isn't anyone else remotely entertaining in the sport currently who is any good, and he fits that bill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 16:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a CD playing or MP3 it indicates the Album being played. That icon is a CD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 11:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legion is actually pretty damn good tbh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 07:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since we've been promised this kind of thing many, many times before i'm tempering my expectations for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 16:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A striking resemblance to Natalie Dormer in the facial department. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 14:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with what you're saying but that's the only book child I can think of that is likely to show up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 08:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My money is on Edric Dayne  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 19:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to define. 

This example is not helped by the way it's titled. It leads me to believe that I'm going to see lots of images of thighs, and while they all have thighs in them, nearly all the images have a sexual undertone it alters the theme of the gallery  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it is creepy to me. 

Art is subjective, and this discussion pertains to my belief that art is completely subjective to the viewer. *I* find it creepy. I don't find porn creepy. I find kissing children on the lips creepy but many seem to find it ok. It's subjective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not against sexually explicit images at all, I don't understand how you get that when I said how diverse the body is, all i'm saying is that nude art in the case of photography (IMHO) should be more about the composition of the image, the lines created by the body or absract creations using it. This gallery doesn't do that for me, particularly seeing as it's titled thighs and the focus on most of the images is the crotch. Fingers are lifting the edges of skirts etc, they are just way more erotic than the nature of the gallery leads us to beleive

To answer your question more directly, this is a gallery, not just one image </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 17:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porn isn't creepy because it's porn. It becomes creepy when it's trying to pass itself off as something that it isn't. This is the thing though, art is so subjective. I saw a clip of a woman who was putting paint up her vagina and squirting it out from like ten feet in the air and saying the mess was 'art'. Did she *need* to squirt it out of her vagina to make it art? To her it was, but to me she could have dropped the paint from her hand and produced the same result, making the sexual organ part irrelevant to the art.

You could argue the *Act* of doing it was art, but I wouldn't say that applies to photography, where the person admiring the art is not going to see how the image was taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I said, it's the fact that I do not see any art value in having your own face plastered over some girls nipples for a commercial image. It just strikes me as a bit letchy. I had no idea that he'd been accused of sexual crimes but I guess I can see that being probable, I hope for his and his models sakes though the impression I get from his work is wrong.

Generally I would say that nudity where it is not what makes the image interesting is art. You shouldn't need a nipple or an ass in an image to make someone look at it. The human body is an incredibly diverse, interesting thing. Many photographers can shoot an image where the focus is absolutely about the image and not the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence why a lot of folks here are saying this gallery is just a smidge creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 16:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider Terry Richardson to be an extremely creepy photographer, yet he will have had willing women to photograph in all his commercial shoots. Having a model put stickers of your face on their nipples for a shoot for instance is absolutely creepy in my book. (Emily Ratajkowski is the model i'm talking about if you want to google the images)

I'm not saying you're wrong (the majority of Yuria's images imho I would consider art, but there are some that do have a creepy vibe), but just putting it out there that it is no way an absolute statement of fact that having permission prevents creepy photos from being creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Flo!! Nice pic by the way

She's a lovely vixen, and i've been on one of their photography days which I can recommend if you want to get *really* up close and personal :)

Here is one of my shots of her: http://i.imgur.com/r6lCKH2.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bungie, if you're going to make it rain loot, but make everything good not go to our postmaster, for the love of Jolder, please let us bank our Gunsmith orders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 08:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 21:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you make drawings of the annoying dog annoying different characters? Or perhaps setting things up? I think that might make a good series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 12:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 10:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you hate Joe that you need to post a video with a derogatory title, why would you even come to this sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 09:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 76 year old mother is classed as mature, but she sure as shit doesn't accept my opinion on country and western music.

I get phone calls at work "Just listen to this song, you'll love it". No mum, I most likely won't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 09:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An ex friend of mine was run over by a taxi while he was drunk and messing around and was awarded 176,000 by the court afterwards (he had to have some major reconstructive surgery to his leg, but I think he was in the wrong).

3 years, 3 YEARS later he has signed on the dole again because he's spent it, then claimed all his friends had robbed him. Meanwhile all the things he should have bought for use getting around as he is essentially disabled now, us tax payers are now providing for him as he is now skint. What a cunt, excuse my language. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 09:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a video of a woman complaining to a police officer because she gave a 'redneck trump supporter' the finger and it was her god given right to do that, while it wasn't his given right to come after her afterwards.

I don't know how the police officer kept his cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 08:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  70%

Considering the state of the place this last couple of years, that's a pretty conservative estimate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 08:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only have a few minutes to look for it, but this link at least confirms the mangas publisher on it:

http://kotaku.com/ghost-in-the-shell-publisher-never-imagined-a-japanese-1771992584 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 08:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more Khorne Flakes but otherwise nice vid ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motoko is Japanese, but her shell is modelled on a westerner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I get that it seems white washed, iirc the explanation for the original anime was while Motoko *is* Japanese, as in her ghost, the shell is 100% western. 

Personally, I'd love it if they dubbed Scarlett with a Japanese voice actress just to emphasise what is actually going on, but that will never happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she asked that just as Motoko turned off her optic camo it would have probably been more intriguing for new comers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't just see why they don't do masterchef baker edition with the three GBBO judges with a back bone. 


Masterbaker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bakey McBakeface </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 11:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, while I wouldn't want to use this camera if I were shooting reportage or anything, honestly, I think i'd rather use this camera with the Foveon over my 5D Mk3 when it comes to product shoots, or anywhere I can control the amount of light properly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 11:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah exactly!

I get that there are some sacrifices for the price tag, but if this camera suits the style of photography you do it's going to do a hell of a good job for a fraction of the comparable price from the big boys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 10:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine had the same thing happen only they were married and had two teenage children. 

He said he doesn't feel bad about it, as technically he didn't do anything wrong. While he *did* feel a bit inadequate about it at first after he sat and digested it he just said that he wanted her to be happy after spending so long together, even if it meant her leaving him. 

I know this doesn't sound like a happy ending for him but this happened 4 years ago, and he moved in two years ago with his new girlfriend and has taken up cribbage and cocktail making. So yeah he seems pretty comfortable now hahahaha

It's going to feel pretty shit for a while but it will get better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 07:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It must be pretty depressing to be on that council and know the only reason you're there is because your father was in some movies and you're regarded as being pretty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still excerpts though the tracks are even titled 'excerpt of' but yeah I get your point. 

One thing I will at about Destinys music... I miss Marty O'Donnel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sigma SD Quattro Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 19:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think the final battle music in the Black Garden takes that accolade. Such a shame there are literally only snippets of it in the official soundtrack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 19:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that changed when Microsoft got involved. IIRC it's still pretty debatable who the forerunners were but it still seems likely that they are human. 

Halo 4 was where we started to see entirely new tech and met the Didact or whatever he was called. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was that perfect i'm sort of disappointed they are making a season two with the same cast following on from directly from season one.

I'd hoped they'd have each season as a self contained story, if only because a lot of the mystique is now gone from the characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 09:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first proper glimpse of the man inside the monster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 08:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I can't really give you a good answer to this.

Just over a year ago I would've said hands down Wlad, but after seeing Fury out box him (yes, people said it was boring, but it was a *boxing* match after all) i'm on the fence.

Fury has shown he's capable and deserves the current title of World Champ, but that still doesn't mean that he technically is as skilled a boxer generally speaking *right now*. He still has years left of his career though, and I have high hopes for him. If he can keep his ego in check while training and fighting, and use it to demoralize his competition, he has the potential to be legendary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 22:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 1 and 2 were amazing TV. It should have stayed as a bit of a mini series, but after *so many* tragedies it started to seem a bit soap opera </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 22:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you overthink any film, you're going to find holes (except Drive, that film is a masterpiece). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's in the opening scene, he's the scientist they rescue and later has his head blow up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I can't stand the fact that a *good* Star Wars movie came out and because it wasn't *the greatest film of all time* people shit on it. 

The only hole I can put in it is that Rey definitely comes off as a bit of a Mary Sue, but that may well be explained in a later movie.  The Force Awakens *is* Star Wars, done right. Disney and Abrahms did a great job bringing it back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 08:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a Crystal Ball too. Do people not say the child's full name before deciding on the name that the child will have the rest of its life?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 08:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a kid on the way now and we've obviously been looking at naming sites etc trying to think of names and I'm shocked to see in many that Khaleesi is in the top twenty of many of them. 

Really?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 22:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually when a big release comes out there are official /r/movies discussion threads.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the reason why i'm looking forward to the NES Classic.

I was going to splurge on a proper console after spending some money on the WiiU virtual console store, but to get those games and a working NES i'd be spending well over 600. I can now get the NES Classic which I can plug into my current TV set without having to either get an adapter or an old TV set and play all those games for a tenth of the price.

I really don't understand why more companies don't do this as a matter of routine with their older games consoles. I'd seriously pay 200 no problem for a working current TV compatible system and a batch of it's best games with a few rarities thrown in.

Imagine getting to play all those old N64 games again on holiday whenever you want and only need to carry around an item as big as a pint of milk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't 60% of the worlds population get those for free still right now?
Edit: Sorry for bringing politics into a thread about gaming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are insulting them by giving them a skinny 'k' in kurvy instead of embracing the buldge with a 'c'.

You *monster*.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] Can we get a discussion thread on 'Bridget Jones Baby'? I'm keen to see others opinion on this seeing as this threequel was actually pretty good </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 19:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 11:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it amazing the the Elemental Shamen, you know the one thats *supposed* to be tossing lightning bolts everywhere has the weakest lighting bolt of the three specs.

I mean I get that it's supposed to be a filler spell, but having the spell altered to perhaps have lightning rod be a spec bonus trait, and change the lightning rod Talent to be something like 'Overcharged Lightning': Targets affected by Lightning Rod have a 100% crit chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 11:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wha??

I can transmog my Scepter of the Sea to look like the Doomhammer?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 09:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like work though and not playing a game.

If I have to run in a circle for half an hour hoping I get enough mana spawns instead of playing the game, well, that just doesn't sound fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Nighy is promoting donations to Oxfam explaining the people's plight in Syria, and I cant help laughing because he keeps reminding me of his character in Love Actually </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 09:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 08:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she can have a type, but nobody else can if they prefer more athletic looking people?

Fucking Judas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 07:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's joking, surely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 12:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? When the original games were essentially Chibi through the majority of it? I think it hearkens back to the early half of the Final Fantasy franchise well.

It was only really since FF8 where they've attempted to get some realistic characters in there and maybe the battle graphics of FF7.

Edit: yes I know chibi is a particular art style, however they both look the same to me. If you think that the old sprites in the 8 and 16 bit games didn't have big heads and eyes, go back and look again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 12:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Devils Coach Horse Beetle?

Pretty gnarly looking European beetle which I'm sure it's bark is worse than its bite  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is a f***ing shame.

Not enough original style games coming out, let alone GOOD film license games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, it's exactly the kind of gameplay that wouldn't be crazy hard to develop it for either seeing as its technically a rail shooter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm,

I have worked on a project when she was there and while I never directly spoke with her, she seemed pretty amenable, even when other folks were dicking about on set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, Tyson Fury is English </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> original post by /u/itman290

https://www.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/52w74i/ill_just_poke_this_shark_with_a_stick_what_could/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why you probably shouldn't poke a shark with a stick. x-post from /r/wtf </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 17:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Warden (Rogue)
Morrigan 
Solas 
Alistair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last 6 games I've played I've lost to a Yogg. 

I get it isn't an instant win card, but I just can't counter it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 13:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now look at the place. Fucking immigrants  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 09:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the people that love Barb (like me) is for several reasons:

1) She wanted to help her friend stick to her morals.
2) She didn't really do anything bitchy to justify the way she died, making her tragic.
3) She really *really* reminds me of poindexter from the Revenge of the Nerds films.

Other than that though the nostalgia alone is enough. Shes a way over the top characture of everything I remember about the average teenage girl growing up in the eighties. THOSE JEANS. Omg. Nostalgia overload. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 08:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it how he calls the policeman an Uncle Tom. I'm glad to see the policeman remained professional at that point. I would have booked him there and then for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 08:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC there is a cool down on purchases per week from this guy. I don't know how many it is but folks won't be able to drop all their blood in one go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently, she has a similar look to Emma Watson with her short hair on the go which a LOT of fashion outlets will like. I'd be surprised if she grew it out if im honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 11:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always knew RDJ was a good actor, but even if it is supposed to be parody, he seriously does some of the best acting I've ever seen in that film </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 08:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My theory is that the demo gorgon and whatever planted those parasites are two different entities. The second one using the demo gorgon to get host creatures from our real dimension and bringing them to the upside down for impregnation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without sounding perverse, it's criminal the opening titles didn't have that shot last just that bit longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 08:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because everyone who lived in the eighties knew someone who looked like that. An exact characature of what 80's movies showed as the geeky kid. 

Seriously, check out Poindexter from Revenge of the Nerds 2. He's the male counterpart to Barb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 07:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those interested in this synth heavy music, here are some artists to look up that you might like:

- Kavinsky
- Vangelis
- MOON
- Carpenter Brut
- Mega Drive
- College
- Miami Nights
- Timecop 1983
- Perturbator


Lots more music, styling and 80's electric retro stuff can be found in /r/outrun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want an iPhone (they really aren't as bad as most of the android crew would have you believe, although there are drawbacks), right now isn't a bad time to get one over a two year contract. 

If you decide you want the new model when it comes out the contract will be up and then you can get another iphone and join the cult :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 11:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is less pressure on DPS classes to know mechanics for fights etc, and ranged DPS tend to take less damage so that makes Hunters and Mages your go to classes. Technically Druids can be ranged too, and also can Tank or Heal so if you're not sure how you want to play, whilst tricky to learn they might be a good bet long term. 

The other three way hybrid class would be Paladin but they are melee. 

Don't be afraid of rolling a known ranking or healing class though, they all have DPS specs for you to use, and also mean you can try other roles without having to refill another toon. Just remember if you do well as DPS and start doing Heroic and Mythic dungeons to start at the bottom teir normal dungeons if you decide to try a different role and that you have the relevant stat gear. IE: I play a Restoration Shamen as a healer, but when I get bored or want to chill because Elemental Shamen use Intellect as their primary stat as well as Restoration Shamen, I don't need to switch out so much gear. 

Another interesting feature is that you can now right click on your character portrait and select what kind of loot you want. So, you can quest and dungeon your heart out as a healer and then any loot you find can be selected to drop as tank gear for your class if you wish it. 

The best piece of advice for a new player though honestly would be just read through all the descriptions, and see what takes your fancy. If you live out your fantasy as a knight in shining armour you'll enjoy the game far more than you would playing a heretic Warlock you picked because it sounded easy to play for instance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 11:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably means levitation? I've never tried it but maybe it floats you over water which I guess would qualify for making canals less of an issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 09:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ghost wolf is faster than most mobs, just get out of range and cast it as you jump onto the water </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 08:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I'm from that phrase is used to describe muscular people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 08:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE these little touches blizz puts in. I remember when Zul Gurub released and I was mind blown with Hakkar kept whispering to my Rogue because she was a Troll. 

It's 10 minutes worth of coding but it really makes the world feel that much more alive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 08:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shaman and DK don't have that problem. 

Some tips:

If you haven't already do the early quest that gets you a disguise. Once complete you get to keep it and use it at any point. 

Also the inconspicuous baskets you see littered about? Mobs swagger if you're in one and you can reapply the disguise if you're inside one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 14:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean this sub is supposed to be tech advice and PC enthusiasm instead of the dankest of dank memes? 

You coulda fooled me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 12:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen several people say that there is a real focus in this game on melee combat, but so far it looks like a borderlands style looter shooter (it does look great though!). 

I guess we'll have to wait and see. I hope that it would be technically possible to melee your way through the game without getting bored. There is a real lack of melee centric first person games around. 

On a side note, if you like that kind of gameplay you should try Chivalry. It's multiplayer but has a really good melee system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 08:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn I miss my Dreamcast. Phantasy Star Online was the balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 01:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, I've been 110 for four days and never noticed this. I thought they were for when a patrol comes your way that can see through your disguise, you could hop in one while they walk past so you don't get detected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it amazing that in Guildford there are one bedroom flats going for over 1,000 a month. That's like 60% of my wages. So, by the time my PAYE and NI are paid, I'd be left with 280 a month to live on and otherwise exist. 

Take comfort in knowing it isn't just you mate who can't afford this shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand the government wanting to put in a charge for administration of the property register. But to charge someone the best part of 10,000 for an average price house where I live (Surrey), so someone in an office can spend about 6 minutes deleting and entering some names on a computer system and printing out a certificate is fucking bullshit...

100.00 would be too much but acceptable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a more serious note I think either previous divers have fed it (chasing other animals away so it can eat it all itself?) or it was checking you out trying to work out if you're predator or prey. 

Sorry bro but in either scenario it's looking at you thinking "FOOD!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice me Senpai! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 09:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 08:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not trying to be an asshole, but it wasn't a very funny one :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
