<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6310</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please read my post I never stated whether I wanted it or not, just the ramifications of what I think would happen if it was implemented  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're good man, i understood what you meant. A clear thought will get across a lot better and to a lot more people than a muddled one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or maybe i have the misconceptions, we don't have any proof i just base things off of what i see around me in the multiple servers i play on.  its all anecdotal, based on our own personal experiences.  Where you play you could be right and where i play i could be right. All in all good conversation with you. I'll take what you've said and see if i can find more concrete evidence of what im stating. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean it was a little ignorant of you to ask "why was raid towers removed from the game" it seems click baity and uneducated. Raid towers are still there just not in their full form.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it includes pvp of course, but is it the majority of the average players rust day? no. I would say the average rust players day is made up of mostly farming and pvping when either a) they're set up b) they are forced into the situation.  

You have to remember with this Bchillz is first and foremost an entertainer. Do you think anyone would watch his stream if he played the way the average player plays? he is on a schedule and he is there to entertain. His videos consist of going deep and wrecking whole crews. not of "watch me collect 23k sulfur from these stones." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Rifle bodies should come across (a little) more. "I dont loot the towns, because I cannot get guns from it"  spawn guns in boxes again.   
2. Recycler Needs to be louder, so you can contest the person recycling goods in PvP for the loot  
3. Fix stairs and glass windows in rad towns  
4. Bodies that are downed, You should be able to run through or over them  
5. Apply fog on heights to prevent roofcamping, Radiation or fog should prevent roofcamping 24/7  only allow short base defense  
6.  Syringes - Reduce the cloth cost on syringes  
7. Ladders  more expensive raiding ladders  
8. High external walls, Make them easier to jump over, remove the slow and nerf their damage  
9.  Tool cupboard radius, Lower the tool cupboard radius to promote raiding again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People would kill the same amount of nakeds (maybe more) if guns showed up on backs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO, i don't think having a gun show up on a nakeds back will make me kill them less. People are going to kill for killings sake. Its what makes up a huge part of the game.  

The 2 routes this could go is:  
1. See a gun on a nakeds back and deal with the threat.   
2. Not see a gun on the nakeds back and kill him for whatever loot he could have possibly picked up.  

My proposed solution is Xray Goggles with 6x zoom and night vision. possible heat signature detecting software can be added for 1 tech trash and 6 metal frags. EZ solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 18:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course its a valid way of playing, but the real question is "are the majority of rust players playing that way?". I don't believe they are. So his opinions or views are skewed just a little bit.  
 nbsp;  

A good analogy is a CEO wanting to change things according to his lifestyle and not his employees even though they are living a much different life than he is and there are much more of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what shit am i talking again? i didn't say anything against him, just that people give him stuff. Don't be so blind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spoiler](#s "when the unknown gentleman says the line "this will be a fine spot" later in the game its the spot that John Marsden is buried after he dies.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no that's not what he's saying, he always gets things handed to him by viewers or farmer friends. He doesn't have to farm because others just give things to him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
