<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8135</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 05:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 03:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Front seat of my truck after a football game. Started with a BJ and then she found out I was a virgin. She was so excited to take that away from me. 

I didn't mind lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 05:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 19:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does your daily routine consist of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 04:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow terrific answer. Thanks so much for the clarification.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why can't a nuclear reactor power the pumps that cool its reactors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a reactor core isn't cooled, it explodes I guess. Most (if not all) are cooled by cold water pumps powered by electricity. Why can't those pumps be powered by the reactor itself?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 03:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soap opera details unknown, so bear with me. 

In 1998-99 I was about 6-7 and there was a Days of Our Lives episode in the winter season. Part of the main premise was a beer can bring frozen in the pool that had iced over behind their house. I remember playing with my Christmas gifts while my dad watched intently, occasionally glancing up. 

The beer can was being held in place by a skeleton hand of one of the characters that was dumped in the pool after being murdered.

Scared the fuck out of me. 

I had to go to counseling at school, "drawing my fear" to help face it. I couldn't even look at snow or ice without breaking down and losing it. Eventually had some psychiatric therapy done in the nearest large town to help get over it. 

To this day I had zombie movies/shows/books, halloween, scary movies, anything that references dead people really. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 23:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 21:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Satan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 22:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure lol. It was up when I parked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McLaren P1 at Sunrise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 18:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 01:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SKLN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I've only begun to stretch my asshole enough for this type of action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to hit mine tomorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
