<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try guy-who-obviously-wants-to-see-my-equipment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a medicinal purpose for these things was discovered the price would increase by 7000 percent overnight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm totally using this for medicinal purposes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.amazon.com/Finger-Spies-Colors-May-Vary/dp/B003F2OP3S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.amazon.com/Finger-Spies-Colors-May-Vary/dp/B003F2OP3S </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best. Comment. Ever. Upvoted!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If those eyes could talk... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dong Eyes! That's hilarious!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a Project Fi Nexus and is in the case that Google sent along in the welcome pack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This came from the Dollar Tree. We live in southwest VA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THAT is awesome !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol....your brain is plenty dirty. Now that it's been mentioned I'm totally going to finger-blast the hell out of her with it.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hand is my wife. The other hand is her sister.  Good times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE using the term 'finger blast.' My wife despises it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good eye. Apologies to you and the entire reddit community. The middle finger was totally not meant for you ladies and gentlemen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, hey, hey..wait a minute..who said anything about putting this on my dick!?!? PERV!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll show you mine if you show me yo-.....uh this isn't a private message, is it? Shit! This always happens to me, but usually on Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife just used the word "sufficient" to describe my penis. So jokes on ya'll!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. Confirmed http://www.efedzone.com/forums/viewtopic.php?t=64 p=550

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's the one who took the 'after' pic. She muttered something about not being able to unsee it..or something like that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, reflections in the eyes of children's toys have never been kind to me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 00:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 23:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may do that also... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow....I really didn't think anyone would notice that! Good eye, Tusserte!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right, but I'm leaving them guessing on whether it's a toddlers finger or Andre the Giant's thumb. Fucker has HUGE hands! Also forget that part about a toddlers finger. That just shouldn't be used in the same sentence with my dick. Plus, I'm not allowed anywhere near children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a great idea...but no way my wife will let me use THIS one on the teapot....or anywhere in the kitchen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm forbidden from posting the update pic. Let's just say the paramedics were NOT amused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uncle Brynn? Is the you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 20:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grandma would have INSISTED.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 20:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TOTALLY left a mark! They're a lot...stiffer than the pack makes them look </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You know EXACTLY what I'm going to do with this, dont you?" I said as my wife handed me this. "Sadly, I do" she responded. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 20:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 16:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yoyo registration page seems to be getting the hug right now.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you see it..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 03:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 20:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good iron, an ironing board, some spray starch, and in about 5 minutes you can have a great-looking shirt with creased sleeves, straight collar, and no wrinkles. I'm sure there are YouTube videos to help you learn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 22:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's PVC why are there sparks when cutting it off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 14:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just moved into a place without cable TV, and this is literally the first thing I saw after installing a DIY antenna for ota channels... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So THIS just happened live on my local news station..(shooting) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 14:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It gets easier..." If you aren't watching Bojack Horseman you should give it a chance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 11:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very ambitious, 15-year-old laptop that hasn't been started in over 10 years, very ambitious indeed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 20:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 13:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. The next to last paragraph "When I wake up tomorrow..." shows you have the right attitude and disposition. I have no doubt you'll succeed at staying straight.  And if you can accomplish this, staying clean/straight, which can be impossible for some, then you can accomplish anything you decide to do. You have a bright future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 18:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try, Melanie! Nice. Try.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A transparent and sad attempt by SHENTEL to squeeze a few extra dollars from their lower-tier customers...and just as I was attempting to access reddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 13:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 14:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have narrowed it down to two possibilities:  A very pretty boy or an average-looking Charleston lesbian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who thinks the Dylann Roof video looks like a trailer for a new Matt Damon movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 14:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 20:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not personally do this, but I have seen it done and have overheard the perpetrators justifying it as 'payback' for the completely unreasonable and ridiculous movie ticket and refreshment prices.  

Reminds me of a quote that I am about to butcher, "A little power is everything to those who feel like they have none at all."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 00:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is perfect!  It was practically a reenactment!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 22:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats the funniest thing I feather written. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 22:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has a nest in the awning of the store where I work. The awning is made of cloth and is wearing. Somehow she got her foot wrapped up in a string from the awning. The more she struggled and twisted the tighter the string became.  I had to cut it loose and then hold her and unwrap the string from her ankle and toes with tweezers.  She spend this time rolling her eyes back in her head like Linda Blair in the Exorcist and shitting all over the place...also like Linda Blair in the Exorcist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont get your feathers all ruffled.  see what I did there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freed this little guy today.He thanked me by shitting on me and flying away...like it's MY fault he's HORRIBLE at being a bird. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 19:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wife's sister home alone this afternoon. Sees movement outside window. Photographs peeper staring into house. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 00:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 17:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rpicsanditsmodssucks, telling it like it is since way before my time. 
http://www.reddit.com/user/rpicsanditsmodssucks

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 16:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Our grab-and-go Sausage Breakfast Burrito is a combination of scrambled eggs, savory sausage, melted American cheese, and diced white onions and peppers all wrapped up in a soft white flour tortilla."

Scrambled eggs, check. Savory sausage, check. Onions and peppers, check. Melted American Cheese, che.....WHERE THE FUCK IS THE CHEESE?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A cold and inedible disaster-of-a-burrito from Burger King. Not to be racist, but they should have Cubans rolling these things..or ITS SHIT LIKE THIS, BK..I WANT MY MONEY BACK.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 16:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply. I have a Sprint Note 3 and just installed http://download.cyanogenmod.com/get/jenkins/106142/cm-12-20150407-NIGHTLY-hltespr.zip (latest nightly). Everything works great, but I have no mobile data and no access to APN settings.  If I find a fix I will let you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you found a fix for the APN yet.  I just installed the newest nightly and have no data...no APN settings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 17:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  flashed b

Have you found a fix for the APN yet.  I just installed the newest nightly and have no data...no APN settings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 00:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this woman sues these fucking cretins in civil court and bankrupts the county/city and each employee individually.  This is despicable.


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 15:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for the length. This really stuck with me...
"Apollonius of Tyana reads your future" from The Circus of Dr Lao

"Tomorrow will be like today, and day after tomorrow will be like the day before yesterday," said Apollonius. "I see your remaining days each as quiet, tedious collections of hours. You will not travel anywhere. You will think no new thoughts. You will experience no new passions. Older you will become but not wiser. Stiffer but not more dignified. Childless you are, and childless you shall remain. Of that suppleness you once commanded in your youth, of that strange simplicity which once attracted a few men to you, neither endures, nor shall you recapture any of them any more. People will talk to you and visit with you out of sentiment or pity, not because you have anything to offer them. Have you ever seen an old cornstalk turning brown, dying, but refusing to fall over, upon which stray birds alight now and then, hardly remarking what it is they perch on? That is you. I cannot fathom your place in life's economy. A living thing should either create or destroy according to its capacity and caprice, but you, you do neither. You only live on dreaming of the nice things you would like to have happen to you but which never happen; and you wonder vaguely why the young lives about you which you occasionally chide for a fancied impropriety never listen to you and seem to flee at your approach. When you die you will be buried and forgotton, and that is all. The morticians will enclose you in a worm-proof casket, thus sealing even unto eternity the clay of your uselessness. And for all the good or evil, creation or destruction, that your living might have accomplished, you might just as well have never lived at all. I cannot see the purpose in such a life. I can see in it only vulgar, shocking waste."

"I thought you said you didn't evaluate lives," snapped Mrs. Cassan.

"I'm not evaluating; I'm only wondering. Now you dream of an oil well to be found on twenty acres of land you own in New Mexico. There is no oil there. You dream of some tall, dark, handsome man to come wooing you. There is no man coming, dark, tall, or otherwise. And yet you will dream on in spite of all I tell you; dream on through your little round of hours, sewing and rocking and gossiping and dreaming; and the world spins and spins and spins. Children are born, grow up, accomplish, sicken, and die; you sit and rock and sew and gossip and live on. And you have a voice in the government, and enough people voting the same way you vote could change the face of the world. There is something terrible in that thought. But your individual opinion on any subject in the world is absolutely worthless. No, I cannot fathom the reason for your existence."

"I didn't pay you to fathom me. Just tell me my future and let it go at that."

I have been telling you your future! Why don't you listen? Do you want to know how many more times you will eat lettuce or boiled eggs? Shall I enumerate the instances you will yell good-morning to your neighbor across the fence? Must I tell you how many more times you will buy stockings, attend church, go to moving picture shows? Shall I make a list showing how many more gallons of water in the future you will boil making tea, how many more combinations of cards will fall to you at auction bridge, how often the telephone will ring in your remaining years? Do you want to know how many more times you will scold the paper-carrier for not leaving your copy in the spot that irks you the least? Must I tell you how many more times you will become annoyed at the weather because it rains of fails to rain according to your wishes? Shall I compute the pounds of pennies you will save shopping at bargain centers? Do you want to know all that? For that is your future, doing the same small futile things you have done for the last fifty-eight years. You face a repetition of your past, a recapitulation of the digits in the adding machine of your days. Save only one bright numeral, perhaps: there was love of a sort in your past; there is none in your future."

"Well, I must say, you are the strangest fortuneteller I ever visited."

"It is my misfortune only to be able to tell the truth." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 19:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides the power (we use 10x for almost everything) another difference in loupes is that some are made to view a piece held close to the eye and some are made to view a piece held at arms-length.  The ones we use are ordered from Stuller and are anywhere from $5 for everyday-use ones that are plastic on up to $50 for very nice ones.  The $5 ones suffice for nearly everything.  I have had the same plastic $5 loupe for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-11 13:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title should be changed to 'Mike Tyson puts piece-of-shit-reporter in his place."  This title makes it sound like Tyson was out of control, which he obviously wasnt.  The reporter is lucky that Tyson didnt "lose his shit"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know you're tired of these, but I talked my boss into taking the ALS IceBucket Challenge. Then talked my coworker into making it memorable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-23 05:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 18:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit!  I thought you might be kidding, but I posted that response like a jackass anyway.  My apologies, Sir or Madam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 23:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was an old and dusty photograph that I took a pic of with my phone.  I thought that was obvious. My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 15:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....then you're a good person.  Me, on the other hand, maybe I watch to much porn.  I saw this at McDonalds this morning and my immediate thought was "Peaches and Creampie?...I have to show this to the internet!"  Then I photographed it and proceeded to drive off in a rush...and I forgot to pickup my food.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats next, bacon and bukkake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 15:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-02 03:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG! Seriously...that brings back memories.  I totally forgot about that!  Thanks for the memory!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSFW Found in the street by our mailbox. I tossed it into my car so the kids wouldnt find it. They didnt, but my wife did. She doesnt believe my story.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 21:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 20:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, despite having a C64 with all the accessories, my family wasnt really financially well off.  I had never used a TI and so I really thought they were better machines with more potential. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 20:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not kidding, I was totally jealous of the TI guys.  At that time, in my area, there were two computers:  the C64 and the TI.  I ended up with 2 drives for that thing (1541CII) and I went through numerous modems.  I could connect to a chatroom in the nearest city, which was long distance so I couldnt stay "online" very long.  I would chat and trade pirated software by US Mail.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 20:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT, what else, lol.  Currently IT for a small business, and before that I was IT for local government for 7 years.  My grandfather bought me that machine, which was my first computer.  I remember his exact words as I opened the box, "if you learn how to use this you'll never be without a job."  This was in the early 80's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 20:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AWESOME! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 18:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I wish I still had it.  I saved it for years.  Then I moved a few years ago and it was lost.  It was all in a box with some software, including an unopened copy of GOES, which was a Windows-like OS environment for the C64. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taken sometime in the early 1980's. Me,my Commodore 64, 1541 Floppy Drive, MPS801 Printer,1200Baud Modem....and model rocket atop shitty black white TV/monitor. Boy was I cool... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 15:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 04:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope Google buys up every bit of this dark fiber and lights it up as a big fuck you to the telecoms and cable companies....yes you Verizon and Comcast  .. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 04:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think maybe promo was looking at the righthand side of the rat, which was insulated by the waffle.  The lefthand side is black.  Its really a nightmare.  I hope it was quick and painless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 03:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am upvoting this comment because you are a beautiful person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 03:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said the same thing.  This happened to the son of a friend of mine.  He came home after a long day, it was dark, dropped in the waffles, waited until they popped up, butter, syrup, eat, decide to check on smell, HOLY SHIT A DEAD RAT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toaster made a funny sound and a funny smell, but he ate the waffles anyway. Then decided to check the toaster...NSFL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 03:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 15:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he was caught red-handed.  There was no defense.  I called my supervisor and requested that he have someone else handle the call because of my relationship with the suspect and the awkwardness of the situation.  I still talk to the guy sometimes, still see him out with his family.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 14:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I set a static IP on my plex server, then on the router/modem enable the DMZ and input that IP address. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 12:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does your modem have a DMZ?  If so, configure it for your PLEX server.  That leaves it open to the outside world.  I have had mine like this for years and havent had any problems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 03:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who do not know, this is spray starter fluid, which contains ether.  Growing up in the country I have seen this in person more than once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 18:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True Story.  When I first started working for a local police department I was also a local volunteer firefighter in a neighboring town and was very close friends with the fire chief and other officers on that FD.  One of the first (police) calls I remember was: we received several calls from young ladies reporting that as they exited a local gym they observed a man, standing outside his vehicle, masturbating openly and watching them.  I immediately recognized the vehicle description and license tag as that of my good friend and fire chief from my local volunteer fire dept!  I couldnt believe it!  He was married with children, active in the community, great guy, etc.  It was a very awkward situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 01:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing- they line the straw or pre-rolled dollar bill with Vaseline.  That  minimizes the amount of powder that makes it to the body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 14:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sprint has turned against their customers.  There was a time when I could call in and easily have my issue resolved by a customer service rep, a time when dealing with Sprint wasn't a fucking nightmare.  But that time has passed.  True story: One of the phones on my account became inoperable.  So I purchased a used GS2 on craigslist.  I called to activate it, but was told I would have to activate it myself, online. I knew in advance that this would not work because I had tried it twice before.  I tried to explain it to customer service, but they insisted I do it online myself anyway.  So I tried.  And it failed. I called back.  I was told to go to a Sprint store and let the reps there do it.  So I did.  Only, the reps at the Sprint store had the same issue.  They called Sprint and were told to activate it online or take it to a Sprint store.  WHAT THE FUCK. THEY ARE THE SPRINT STORE.  Five hours of my time to activate a goddamn phone. This has happened to me 3 times over the course of two years..  I no longer recommend Sprint to my friends. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-06 14:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here.  I've been a Sprint customer for nearly 10 years.  I wonder if there is some sort of class action lawsuit potential over this extra ten bucks per month I've been paying for at least the last 7 years.  I was charged it and agreed to pay it because I was promised 4G.  Now, years later, no 4G...and I still have and use that same EVO.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 02:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What OS are you running on the server and can you ping its IP?  Does it have a static IP or does it get DHCP from the router?  Do you have easy physical access to the server or do you always remote to it (is there a monitor, keyboard attached or is it headless?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 01:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful....PLUS you have a siamese twin on your shoulder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-19 23:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.roanoke.com/news/virginia/article_50794e5a-7ff6-11e3-928d-0019bb30f31a.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 13:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Awards_and_decorations_of_the_United_States_Armed_Forces </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digg.com has made an awesome comeback! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 15:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tennessee Father Arrested For Insisting School Release His Children to Him </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 23:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 20:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its starter fluid....has ether in it.  Seen it done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life is precious. Fleeting. Then gone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 15:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 22:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is an old thread now, but I am answering anyway.  You speak of damaging the ring.  Most jewelers can take an unrecognizable ring and turn it back into better than before.  I have seen severely damaged and mangled rings be restored to excellent condition by the right jeweler.  I hope you got them removed in time and I hope you had them restored afterward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 21:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PR Sturgill in Radford, VA.  It isnt really local to you, but he's good.  He has customers all over the US.  The store has been there forever and has hosted 3 generations of jewelers.  PR can repair and make about anything.  I send all of my friends there...great guy to know even if you dont purchase jewelry or have a repair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who finds this handy? Remove the file extension from Imgur links to see the original, more detailed, page. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 12:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Example:
Before
http://i.imgur.com/T9mlFbB.png
After
http://i.imgur.com/T9mlFbB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-23 12:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two Bojangles within 15 miles of where I live.  They are both consistently filthy, hire disrespectful workers and their equipment is constantly out of order.  Every month, several times there is a handwritten sign on the drive thru that says "drive thru broken come inside" or " soda machine broken come inside if you want soda."  They have hired a young girl who acts like she has overdosed on xanax everyday.  I like their food and keep giving them another chance, only to be let down over and over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This beautiful dog came into the shop today. When you see it... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 02:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 13:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit, I was so hoping this guy would be black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 18:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ALWAYS get completely naked and I ALWAYS sit Indian-style on the toilet. I have done this for as long as I can remember. I can't poop any other way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 15:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are very thoughtful, and your father is lucky to have you as a son.  

Have you considered an Android device? Here's why...

1.  There are apps for the blind and for the seeing impaired (links below).
2.  You can play any audio book on an Android device
3.  Google Play Books will read aloud any downloaded ebook (and its easy)
4.  The storage is expandable
5.  AFFORDABLE

I dont know if your father is completely blind or can see just a little, but there are apps for the seeing impaired and for the blind.  This might be a great idea if you are comfortable setting these up.  If you arent and are in VA I can recommend someone who can or someone in the Reddit community can help.  

Links:
(apps)
http://mashable.com/2012/07/17/android-app-for-blind-smartphone-users/
http://www.androidaccess.net/
http://www.apps4android.org/?p=4107
(hardware: custom hardware is expensive..and may not be necessary)
http://www.tomshardware.com/news/Smartphone-Blind-Visually-Impaired-Project-Ray,18637.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 14:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> works for me...Eastern US.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 14:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck.  Goog Translate is working for me still.  I still havent read anything about the outage...usually they'll post status on their FB page  https://www.facebook.com/ThePirateBayWarMachine

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
