<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1861</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but I've no idea. There's a reddit post somewhere that compiles all the Indie titles onto one image - perhaps you could check it there! I just happened to glance at it quickly and saw the familiar logo of Duck Game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I (22/F) am obliged to turn up for a family friend's funeral but am finding it difficult to go due to several reasons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit, 


Sorry for the long post. 



Background: I come from an Asian household and am living abroad in the UK. I am not close to my godfather as I am to my immediate family. That being said, I don't talk to them on the phone regularly - I speak to my grandma on the phone maybe once a fortnight, and to my parents once every one or two months because I simply wasn't brought up to use the telephone as much. I don't even call my best friends (we just whatsapp and meet up when I'm back for the summer). In the UK I don't even get a phone plan, relying on top-ups for data instead.



2 years ago, I went for a short holiday stay with my godfather's friends X and Y (70s M,F) along with my cousin. They were nothing short of welcoming and I really enjoyed staying there. When I got back, I emailed them a few times but never called. I felt that this was going out of my way because I would never do that to my extended family (cousins etc - my family has never been close, maybe it's a cultural thing) but did it because my godfather said that he emails them a lot. My emails (to wish them well for the holidays, CNY, update them on my life etc) were never answered. 



The following year, my cousin told me over whatsapp that she was going to call to ask them if she could celebrate the holidays again with them. She invited me to join her and although I had other plans in mind, I didn't mind and said sure. My cousin had never called as well but after her talk with Y, she texted me to say that Y was extremely upset that I never called her, and said that I was ungrateful and that I was uninvited for Christmas. Thinking that it was not probably a good time to call, I emailed her to clarify, went on with my other plans and called after she had cooled down in a few months. 



This has led to a cooling between our relationships on both parts. We've talked on the phone once every two - three months but Y still remains cool. Throughout this time, X's health has been deteriorating due to cancer. I have not talked to X for the past 2 years because even if he did answer the phone, he would just pass it to his wife and did not seem to want to talk to me either. X is on his last days and my godfather has asked my cousin and/or I to be there at the funeral since he has a holiday planned (in SE Asia) and will not be able to make it during this period. Y has been distraught, and refuses to talk to me at all over the phone (I talked with her daughter instead to express my condolences).



I'm in a dilemma whether to go as I have to represent my family and my cousin may not be able to make it on some days. However: 


- I am nowhere as close to them as my cousin, have only met them once, and have been getting feelings of hostility from Y dragged over years.


- It clashes with the busiest time of the school year: this is my final year and I'm taking 7 modules in a block format, 6 hours per day with no rest days. If the funeral falls on a weekday, I'll have to miss at least 6 hours of the same module and won't be able to catch up with the rest of the module that's being taught the next day, not to mention upcoming group projects and assignments. Moreover it's a 5 hour round trip and train prices are around 100. I can try applying for college leave but doubt that will be of any use because they're not family or immediate family. 



I guess I'm confused as to what I should do but am afraid it will strain relationships once more. 



  ---   
  **tl;dr**: Family friend's funeral coming up soon, am expected to go, but his wife has been hostile to me and it's coming at an inconvenient time. What should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 20:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUCK GAME. This game is seriously underrated. My roommate back in college (2 years ago) got it on Steam and literally 6-8 of us would gather every night to play/spectate (it can host up to 4 players) and we would play from 11 pm - 5 am after exams. Every night. Our sleep cycle got so screwed up because of that game. I was upset that it doesn't support Mac and am eagerly anticipating the release on Switch. 

Highlights:

- you kill each other with weapons. Different weapons have different amounts of ammo. You can get creative with your weapons (will not say more to prevent spoilers)

- In the steam version, online play and creation of your own maps 

- There's a button dedicated to quacking.

There's some youtube videos of Duckgames if you'd like to check it out.

Edit: with regards to other games that I haven't tried out, I'm looking forward to Snake Pass, Yooka Laylee, Hollow Knight, ARMS, Splatoon 2 and the Indie game Flipping Death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 14:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boyfriend and I (in a house with roommates): 

"GET ON TOP OF ME."

"No it's too big it won't fit!!!!"

"GENTEEL BE GENTLEEEE!"

"Push harder"; "I can't; it's really hard to get into the corner" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
