<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3775</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 17:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably the "cosmic explosion" was a supernova. There are only a few candidates within our galaxy and closer than 7000 light years. Can you indicate which one of them is close enough to the Eagle Nebula to wipe it out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 23:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To many words for a haiku, but you're getting there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China does fabricate part of their claim, that Chinese fishermen made *exclusive* use of these islands going back hundreds of years. When you view other races, both asian and non-asian as subhuman, I guess it is easy to justify a claim of exclusive use to yourselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the original claim was laid out by the Republic of China--today known colloquially as Taiwan--**and was backed by the United States**  

Can you cite any specific actions the United States took to back the original claim. Everything I've ever seen claiming the US backed the claim was one of inaction --i.e. the fact that the US didn't fight the Chinese claim at the time is cited as US "support". China claims the US backed the claim in the past but has repudiated many US actions as the US attempting to be "the World's Policeman". If their position that US supported China's claim is based on the US not attacking it, then does that mean China recognizes the cases where the explicitly enforced international law?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a layman's terms I think you just said that a spaceship or observer traveling at light speed (or extremely near c) would measure the speed of light and would determine its speed  to be c; but this measurement would only hold for photons in a nearby "bubble" that is within their inertial frame. You imply though, that if there is a mechanism by which the observer can measure the speed of a distant light ray, they will not see its speed at c, but will instead measure a different value.   
Are you describing another way of viewing the time dilatation effect of relativity? Consider a light ray passing from point a to point b where a and b are connected by a line perpendicular to your velocity. Say for example Point A is a star that went supernova after you passed it and Point B is a nearby molecular cloud you also passed. The cloud lights up from the supernova. Are you saying that an observer seeing first the supernova, then the light of the supernova illuminating the molecular cloud would see an elapsed time between the two events suggesting a light speed different from c?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 13:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bald people keep politicians from speaking frankly? Ooh, that's so foliclist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When a reporter asked Giuliani why NYPD cops predominately targeted blacks for his "Stop and Frisk" policy, Giuliani, paraphrasing Willie Sutton,  replied "'cause that's who the criminals are."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 18:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the explosion part of the training? Or was this an accident that happened during training?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 18:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but was turned away after a **background check** 

So black power group blacklisted the guy based on some background information. What information did this group have that the ATF apparently didn't look at when he bought his guns? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 14:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked for many years developing systems for the US military. There is a US Mil Standard specification for almost anything you can think of. As proof, I present to you [ZZ-C-001597](http://everyspec.com/FED_SPECS/Z/download.php?spec=ZZ-C-001597A.024941.pdf), the Mil Standard for condoms, including standard sizes and puncture resistance testing requirements </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 20:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In male pattern baldness, head hair follicles that normally support 2-4 strands of hair per pore, begin losing strands before the follicle stops producing any hairs at all. I suggest that charlatans exploit this natural progression of baldness by claiming the follicles become blocked and sell products to offset a non-existent causation condition  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 20:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternate translation:  
Will Thee kiss me  
In The Dark, Baby  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 02:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the 1980s a lot of women's fashions look like what she's wearing ( shoulder pads, sheez  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 19:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an [infographic](http://www.compoundchem.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/The-Chemical-Composition-of-Insect-Venoms-v2.png) about the chemical content of bee, wasp, hornet and ant venoms. All of them are extremely complex mixtures of compounds, but there are components that are common to some or all of them as well as some that are unique I don't have information as to which compounds are actually the allergenic ones, but it could be a start if you are investigating your own allergy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 19:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much of AWS and Google electricity consumption is driven by services contracted to the Pentagon? While it probably only represents a fraction of those companies' business, it points out the fallacy of comparing Google or AWS to the Pentagon since the latter is a huge consumer of services from the former, either through direct contracts or through contracts with intermediaries who are themselves contracting the services from the major firms. Will also point out that many government contracts for cloud and/or IT services have clauses requiring a certain percentage of the power consumed to be renewable, much the same as there are requirements for percentage of subcontracted costs to be delivered by minority, or disabled veteran or native american or insert your special affirmative action interest group here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kremey filling. Twinkies are filled with Kreme (r), not cream </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  she should be administratively punished/reprimanded **for being incompetent**  

The last is your editorial. 
He is saying another person currently employed by the government would be subjected to administrative sanctions. As an example of other cases, recently the Admiral in charge of Naval Intelligence had his security clearance pulled. Congressmen have similarly had their access to classified data pulled after they were found to have intentionally disclosed classified information. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link and excellent explanation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you watch the video you can see the moons are "stuttering" all along their orbital paths, not just a specific location in orbit. There are cases where you can see them go into the shadow, but that's not the effect I'm asking about </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone comment on what is causing the flickering in brightness of the moons in this video? Clearly it is a sequence taken over time, but there isn't really enough stuff in orbit around Jupiter to have been caused by anything like dust or gas intervening between Juno and the planet/moons. Any thoughts would be appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 14:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there is a postulated moon of several hundred kilometers diameter that formed near its Roche limit and subsequently decayed back into the planet. Wouldn't such an impact "leave a mark"? Are there any physical features on Mars that can be correlated with this theory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Venus is the counter example that says a magnetic field in of itself is not a determining factor for whether a body will have an atmosphere. Venus is in fact much closer to the sun and more affected by solar radiation than Mars is. However Venus also has gravity that is 80% of Earth's. In addition there are signs of active volcanism on Venus: the planet's interior is still out gassing, even though it is unlikely to have a tectonic cycle like earth's where volatile components are recycled back into the mantle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't a simple matter of disagreement. It is a matter of claiming scientific statistics when there are in fact no real statistics because studying the topic has been suppressed by those who are afraid what actual statistics will show. If you want to make a claim of 500,000 to 3 million defensive uses of a gun per year in your argument for guns, you must certainly stand behind gathering actually statistics, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gary Kleck, a Florida State University criminologist who is the source of a debunked claim that critics say dramatically exaggerated the frequency of defensive gun use, recently served on a committee tasked by the federal government with creating a potential research agenda focusing on ways to minimize gun violence  

Kleck is best known for his 1995 study with Marc Gertz that claims that up to 2.5 million incidents of defensive gun use occur every year. ...Critics point to the study's "serious methodological difficulties" -- it extrapolates a very rare event, the slightly more than one percent of respondents to a survey that said they had used a gun in self-defense over the past year, to the entire population of 200 million adults. This means that even slight deficiencies in the accuracy of the survey, whether due to false positives or a sample that is not perfectly indicative of the overall population, can lead to large differences in the result. Harvard Injury Control Research Center Director David Hemenway has labeled Kleck's result "an enormous overestimate" and pointed out that the results require one to believe, for instance, that "burglary victims use their guns in self-defense more than 100% of the time."  

http://mediamatters.org/blog/2013/06/28/controversial-pro-gun-researcher-helped-write-f/194660

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 16:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malodorous concordance
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought I'd seen articles indicating corals were actually a symbiotic pair of a mollusk and algae organism; and bleaching occurs when the algae half of the symbiosis is killed. Is this accurate? Does the mollusk half also die?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do coral polyps ever re-take up residence on bleached coral so the reef is restored to life?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 19:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The possibility that the steerable treads under a piece of heavy equipment could rotate out from edge of  the machine and suck you under it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 17:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a giant chicken </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 03:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't get much worse for a functioning government than food riots and people dying from routine infections in hospitals. Venezuelan hospitals are being cited as worse than Gaza and Syria. Food production has basically stopped. Those Colombians in Venezuela are just one more destabilizing factor. Clearly they're certainly not making the place less fragile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 00:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those jokers in the corner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 22:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I  based my statement on the fact that corporate travel to Brazil in my company is restricted. Employees are not allowed to walk un-escorted on the streets and business facilities are behind gates with physical barriers, armed guards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad, guess I should have said Brasil too, even if I was complementing your country from emerging from its narcoterrorism past 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you dutch and 13 years old? Maybe you should get your wrists xrayed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 16:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While there is a multiple parameter methodology behind this, I'll have to say the end result appears to be highly biased. Looking at the graph, ~~Columbia~~ Colombia and Venezuela are ranked roughly equally. Looking at these countries "in real life", in Venezuela there are food riots ongoing in the country. The democratic process has been completely suborned by dictatorship and the country appears to be spiraling into an armed conflict, if not genocide. ~~Columbia~~ Colombia, while it has its share of problems has a rising economy and is considered in a transition from a developmental to industrialized economy. ~~Brazil~~ Brasil is rated higher (or lower in risk), yet their government is in turmoil with the president impeached, widespread lawlessness, and a collapsing economy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 14:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have acquaintances who are dutch, living in the US, both adhering to the Netherlands stereotype of above average height.  Their 13 year old son was near 6 feet tall, when he was injured at a ball game. Taken to an emergency room to determine whether his arm was broken, the radiologists all got very excited looking at his wrist bones. They called whatever they were looking at "Growth Plates" and based on what they say, concluded he had at least another 6 inches of height growth still to come. Saw the family a couple years ago, the son then 18, was heading off to college. He was 6'7'' tall </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 22:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Montreal Protocol did a good job and the ozone hole has begun to heal up, but it is still an occasional news item. Witness [this paper](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v478/n7370/full/nature10556.html) in Science regarding the unprecedented ozone loss over the Arctic in 2011 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 22:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a [coconut](http://laughterizer.weebly.com/uploads/5/0/9/8/5098219/7713172.jpg?617) that would really like to meet your carrot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 19:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That database, which is called the "Rap Back" system, is operated by the FBI and would notify police when a gun owner is arrested for a crime anywhere in the United States.  

Clearly though the problem is really mental illness.  How will the police know if a person who starts ranting about "the gov'mint gonna  take ma guns  if I get bulimia!" is mentally ill?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 18:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anybody explain what the magenta dots are? The ones that were already distribute all over the Indian Ocean when the simulation started? They also seem to pop in an out of existence throughout the simulation. Finally, it appears a portion of the red dots in that are actually simulated debris transition to a blue color over the life of simulation, with approximately half of the debris dots colored blue by the end. What does this signify? Is this related to the number/type of barnacles found on the recovered wreckage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 21:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was an experiment run at some recent major city marathons monitoring the blood electrolyte levels in runners as well as their water intake. The result of the study concluded marathon runners are induced to drink more water than is healthy for them by the prevelance of free water along the course. Many of them finished the race dangerously depleted and others dropped out due to effects caused by the same  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 16:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there smoke coming off her hands? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gulf coast native here - no longer live there but my family attempted to evacuate when one of the mid 1990's storms was bearing down on the coast near them. They spent 6 hours and got less than 20 miles from home in the horrendous traffic backup. Radio had the hurricane accelerating toward the coast and the first storm bands were less than two hours away. They figured it was better to be in their home than stuck out on the road when the storm came. Storm was pretty bad, lots of property damage, but they came through ok. House intact. In subsequent storms, they've evacuated 3 times, stayed 4 or 5 times. Major factor in evacuation is strength of the storm and consistency of predicted landfall. When prediction is jumping around, its hard to make the call. In at least one of the evacuations, they drove 8 hours inland only to have the storm hit 800 miles away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been years since I've had to do any of the math associated here, but am questioning the lack of discussion of wire resistance due to gauge vs induced impedance once the magnetic field establishes itself. I work in IT and sometime have to do peak and average power consumption for data center racks. Anything with motors in it (like disk drives and server fans) has an initially high power surge as the current runs  into the motor coils (ie solenoids) which initially has no magnetic field. Once the magnetic field is established, the resistance of the solenoid is going to go up, establishing higher resistance and power dissipation, and lower current.  I'm pretty sure there are a number of tertiary effects due to that peak to average current transition, including mechanical ad thermal shocks. I have to believe the wire gauge is going to have an effect on that transition  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes a lot less than 10cc for a small bubble to occlude a critical blood vessel in your brain. That's called a stroke. Some of small strokes (TIAs) are blood vessel the size of pinheads. The scuba diving danger "the bends" comes from small bubbles of nitrogen that come out of solution in your blood when you come up from depth too fast. Think of the bubbles in a glass of beer or soda after it is opened. Those bubbles tend to collect at your joints because the vessels flex and flatten where you bend your limbs, hence the name "bends". Similar to a stroke they can also catch in the small vessels of the lungs, blocking portions of the lung from working and causing shortness of breath, lowered blood oxygen levels  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait to see the people who cosplay this guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 03:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You see comrade, shirt is like plate of shrimp. It is part of cosmic knock on the door at 3 in the morning by computer dispatch kgb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 21:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend who drives a silver honda civic, 2010 or thereabouts. One day another silver honda civic drove by with a license plate number only two digits removed from his own. He was afraid to catch up for fear he'd see himself driving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 21:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The common wisdom one often sees is that the right side of the brain controls the left side of the body and vice versa. At a guess, I'd say OPs question was at least partially prompted by a belief that the only right/left connections of the sides of the brain to the opposite sides of the body run through the corpus callosum. Not an expert in the field but I believe motor control is primarily lower brain function and the brain side connections to motor nerves are in the cerebellum rather than the cerebrum region of the brain.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 21:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alan Furst's novel "Spies of the Balkans" is set in Greece during 1938-1940, and was a view of WWII I'd not previously seen including your discussion of the Italian/Greek war. Would be interested in the review of a Greek on the accuracy

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 21:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a good Italian friend, now residing and citizen of the USA.  He grew up in the 60s and 70s in Italy and was, as I like to joke "a card carrying communist". He acknowledges the atrocities of the fascists under Mussolini but doesn't feel their tactics were really very different from most European governments at the time. He feels similarly about the Americans and their liberation of Italy, pointing out a case of the American destruction of medieval monastery held by the Germans. Apparently there was an agreed non-combat status for the monastery during the stalemate in winter of 1944 lines. The Germans used it for an artillery observation post and the American's bombed it to smithereens. He views this as an American war crime, not the Germans abusing the argeed ceasefire terms.  

Bottomline is that he doesn't feel any particular national guilt for the actions of the fascists under Mussolini as he sees the Fascist part of his own society as much the enemy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 18:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marriage counselors also look at frequency of sex. People who don't fuck breakup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 17:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, did Tobacco Settlement Funds pay for this research? I know in Virgina a big chunk of money from the tobacco settlement funds went to research at VaTech looking into genetically modifying tobacco plants so they could be used to create pharmaceuticals. The scandal that got the last Va governor convicted of bribery was around a businessman who sold a diet supplement derived from tobacco. Those funds were supposed to go toward health treatments for afflictions caused by tobacco and for education to prevent/stop people from smoking. Before I give any credence to this study conclusion, I want to see the funding source and potential conflict of interest from the researchers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 17:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's going to know? I don't think every ranger station or park entrance station is going to have her photo pinned up in case she tries to come on federal property. They've got enough to do besides making sure banned people don't show up. She should have been sentenced to jail, even if it was suspended, with a condition of parole never to come onto federally managed land. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't recall ever being asked to show identity when entering a US National Park. National Forest and BLM Land are even less formal with Interstate, US and State level highways crossing many of them. This is a symbolic punishment at best. One could I suppose compare it to having a warrant out for your arrest. Nothing explicitly preventing her from going into one of these areas, but some severe ramifications if she is identified and arrested while in them. Kind of runs against the grain of the whole "not publishing private details of people on reddit" that is discussed in the article, but for the punishment to have any impact at all, it seems like having her picture well known. If if she did decide going into one of these parks again was a low risk proposition, having her face very well known and recognizable would make it less risky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 18:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In recent years several papers have discussed projects which have used data recorders on marine mammals like seals, sea lions, walruses and whales to get information about water temperature characteristics at depth where these animals dive. How is information recovered from these recorders? Do they upload directly to satellites or do these projects have to put data reception stations to recover them? Most of these programs have actually been directed at learning about the animals' behavior with the physical data being a side benefit. Do you see marine mammals being recruited directly as geophysical data collection platforms?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 15:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like the birds from Garth Nix's Sabriel/Lirial Triology: dead animal re-animated with a soul of the dead, spying and reporting back to the necromancer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 15:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Research from 1985](http://europepmc.org/abstract/med/3893385) showed low intensity direct current therapy at wound sites increased healing rate by 1.5x to 2X the healing rate of untreated wounds. Not sure why this wouldn't already be a known proven therapy for these cases </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 20:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this post and thought, "why is this limited to non-western?" visualizing in my head the TV preachers on the Faith Healing Hour. In the US South, revival tent services with faith healers are still a somewhat common sight. Think how many people there are who believe in "detox diets",  vaccination causing autism,  Jesus on Toast, Elvis sightings, Bigfoot and the Chupacabra  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I do like art and I think it has a place in a well rounded curriculum but I wonder at the actual motivation for making STEM into STEAM. To me it comes across as a way of making STEM less exclusive. A valid rationalization would be, I think adding aesthetics into technology design and improving communication. I've seen articles about teaching science grad students creative writing to help them "tell a better story" in their technical writing. I'd really like to see someone working in STEAM articulate the goals of including Art rather than it just being a form of non-nerd affirmative action.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noting the addition of Art into the traditional "hard" education subjects of science, technology, engineering and math, making STEM into STEAM  
Can you talk about the rationale for injecting Art in the mix and how it complements the overall educational content of the traditional STEM subjects? STEM was originally about encouraging students to learn skills that would enable them to become the inventors and business innovators of the future. Can you give some examples of how the STEM approach was less effective because it didn't include Art? Can you provide some examples where the inclusion of Art has improved the effective application of the more traditional technical subjects?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bacon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This caution is largely directed toward drinking stream/spring water from  "wild places" like national parks, national forests, state parks, etc. People think of them as pristine but in many cases they have been subjected to a lot of both human and domesticated animal traffic:   Think horses, cattle, sheep, dogs, mules, llamas. All of these animals can spread communicable diseases through their feces. In many cases it may not actually be in the parkland itself, but instead in streams flowing in from privately held or government lands subject to grazing leases. In National Parks there have been years of backpackers pooping in the woods. Dogs used to be frequent and still are present in some national parks. Giardia is going to be the most common concern, but cholera and e coli contamination are other possibilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 21:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a couple square miles of light sails with a robotic controller to furl or unfurl (or rotate them) reflect the sunlight at the appropriate time could put some velocity changes on its orbit enough to move it over to L5. It might take 50 years but you'd have the materials basis for an O'Neil once you got it there. Somebody want to simulate It in kerbal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 19:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point was though, if you were to accelerate a small asteroid say one that massed 100 million tonnes to a speed some gnats eyelash removed from c, its relativistic mass would be huge, perhaps rivaling the rest mass of the Earth. However, its gravitational field/attraction of other objects would still be the same as when it was at rest: 100 million tonnes. The relativistic mass, while present for the purposes of kinetic energy calculations in case of impact, would not distort space-time to create a gravity well equivalent to the Earth's. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [largest ship in the world](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prelude_FLNG) is being built in South Korea. It is destined to be a floating industrial plant to liquefy natural gas from the recently developed gas field off the Australian northern coast. Seems like a lot of investment building a whole industrial plant on a giant ship instead of just piping the gas back to Australia. So why are they doing that? Because, if they brought the gas back to the Australian shore, they'd be obligated to pay Australians, at Australian labor rates and benefits in the plant. The natural gas is Australian, the government gets some kind of royalty cut for the gas extraction, but that resource isn't otherwise serving Australia. They're building that ship so the plant can be worked by Chinese, or other very low cost labor. Welcome to the future where our governments have been bought by corporations and billionaires to serve their needs and not the needs of the country  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 17:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the faster you push the object (nucleus, person, planet, black hole, etc) the deeper it digs into the sheet and now the more space-time it is "displacing" (warping), or as the equations predict: the atom acts like a more and more massive object, displacing more and more space-time. Essentially, wouldn't this lead to a larger magnitude gravity wave? (I'm seriously asking.)   

Thought about this recently, may have even asked an AskScience question.  My question was something like "If a relativistic speed object passed through the solar system without hitting anything, wouldn't it still disrupt planetary orbits as its massive gravity well traversed across the solar system".  
It didn't get much traction but I googled some more and found the wikipedia article on [Mass in Special Relativity](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mass_in_special_relativity). Apparently the upshot is that space-time is distorted by the rest mass of an object, but does not create further distortions by the increased relativistic mass. If you think about, this makes sense because relativistic speed objects would tend to generate gravity waves as "wakes" when they moved through a vacuum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 16:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As more solar systems are catalogued and analyzed, it is becoming obvious the majority (70%) of exo-solar systems include a "super-Earth" whereas our solar system apparently lacks one.  A lot of systems also have very large planets in fairly close orbits around the star whereas our solar system has a pretty sparse, rocky planet only inner system.  We have have only seen a fraction of the systems and many stars may have planets that we can't see, but a statistical look at the ones we can see, show that we don't fit the most common patterns seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm not in the whole cosplay or fan convention thing so I'm kind of wondering at the rationale for dressing as an animated tv show character at a gaming convention. Wouldn't a gaming convention expect people cosplaying characters from video games? Is there an archer video game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 22:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually some models  do have something like a portcullis.
http://www.mannlakeltd.com/beekeeping-supplies/product/WW-176.html

Since there are multiple of them maybe we should say portculli ? The little metal tabs can be flipped over to open or shut the entrance gate. There's another one on the top edge you can open to force the 90 degree turn down, then another 90 turn into the hive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 22:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually it is the beekeepers who are doing it for the bees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A robbing situation is also pretty interesting to watch. The robbing bees will attempt a fast entry into the hive, often intercepted on the way in by a guard bee. When there is full blown robbing going on, you'll see pairs or triples of bees grappled onto each other struggling and rolling around like gang members in fight. Additional robbers can be seen streaking into the hive entrance, not bothering to land, but instead flying in and penetrating the crowd inside. It is for this reason, during robbing season people tend to put gates on their hives. Bees cant flight straight in or out. They have to go through a narrow gap or make a couple 90 degree turns. This prevents the "fly right in scenario", forcing them to crawl up and allowing guards time to respond. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 04:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They addressed that in the podcast. The one they announced was so strong it stood out clearly above the noise without any special processing. They're no using various signal processing techniques to look for other signals more obscure in the noise. There are also additional detectors coming online in Europe that can be used to cross correlate additional signals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 21:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why do they specifically call on Obama for this? The vast majority of the arctic is Russian and Canadian. The Russians literally dumped old nuclear reactors with their spent fuel into the arctic waters during the cold war. The Canadians have built the largest and third largest dams in the world in northern Alberta to hold the lakes of toxic waste produced from their oil sands workings. These are earthen dams which, if they fail (as earthen dams are want to do), they will dump millions or billions of tonnes of highly toxic wastes into the Arctic Ocean. Yeah, Obama should shut it down, but the Russians and Canadians have already indicated they intend to explore for oil in the region AND have demonstrated a pretty callous regard for the dangers of contaminating the Arctic Ocean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 21:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> could be, maybe that's what spontaneous combustion is. More likely they'd just run a fever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 21:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I heard about the cold packs on Science Mag or Nature Mag podcast. A quick google looking for the original research finds lots of people advertising cold packs for weight loss. I guess it didn't take long for people to try to commercialize it without proven protocols. How many people threw out their aluminum cook pans after the aluminum in alzheimer plaques research? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 21:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd read the brown fat activation would essentially come across as you running a fever all the time, which would happen if your body wasn't able to dissipate the heat, hence "sweating it off but probably more accurate to say the mass of the fat leaves the body as CO2 and H2O  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does space-time have an equivalent to "viscosity" that affects the propagation of gravitational waves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I listened to a podcast this morning on the "Sonification" of data. The podcast discussed the techniques to convert the LIGO gravitational wave detector data into sound which the research team used in their analyses. The podcast drew a lot of parallels between gravitational waves and sounds waves, prompting the thought that sound wave propagation and attenuation through a medium is affected by things like the density and viscosity of the medium. Are there equivalents to the properties for space-time -ie some property of space-time that we can derive based on how much the gravitational wave has attenuated over distance traveled? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's been research to show that brown fat can be activated just by cold temperatures, and not necessarily over the whole body. Most brown fat in humans is located in the back of the neck and shoulders. They've found that simply applying ice/cold packs to the neck/upper back can initiate the brown fat thermogenesis.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](http://www.cell.com/molecular-cell/abstract/S1097-2765%2814%2900954-X?_returnURL=http%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS109727651400954X%3Fshowall%3Dtrue cc=y=) is one of many research papers exploring the pathway to activate brown fat. Recognize this is like a holy grail money maker for the pharmaceutical industry if they can crack this. There's probably a lot of non-public research on the topic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There already are "commercially available EMPs". They're only sold to police and military but they can burn out a car engine at 100+ feet distance. [Here's another that apparently is temporary rather the permanent engine burnout ](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cuus8OtPY0w) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 19:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fat loss with a pill or prescription.  We all have "brown fat" tissues in varying degrees. Mostly we have it as babies but it deactivates as we get older. Brown fat metabolizes stored body fat (yellow fat) directly into body heat without having to be converted into sugars and consumed in muscle exertion. Chances are the skinny guy or girl you know who never wears a coat when it is cold outside and can eat like a pig without gaining weight has a mutation where their brown fat is turned on all the time. Scientists are decoding the metabolic pathways that can turn on brown fat. Eventually they will produce a drug that can turn on your brown fat.  

Sweat those extra pounds away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 17:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends - we have been doing weather forecasts for more than a century  using sparse data measurements from scattered stations to project temperatures across broad swaths of the continents. With the advent of more comprehensive satellite measurements, the accuracy of those models has been refined and confirmed. The comprehensive global temperature records uses those sparse records and modern models the project. They've also used other data sources like tree ring data and oxygen isotope ratios in glacier ice cores to validate and refine temperatures over a  broader areas; but when you get down to it, the older comprehensive dataset is going to be a projection based on weather models with sparse data points providing "ground truth". People with a preconceived notion that global warm is a lie will make the claim that unless you have validated ground truth for every point on the earth, it can't be trusted to be true. Many of these same people will also put extreme faith in things like "Tax cuts for the rich are good for everyone" - that are similarly based on models with limited "ground truth". In short, climate change deniers are like the accountant for the mafia - it is only trusted to the extent that it delivers the answers you want it to deliver </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are plenty of data sets that provide this information. The deniers, unable to argue with the trend will often argue against the validity of the dataset itself. One thing that is a valid criticism is what is baseline should be used as "the average" against which individual years are measured? The further back you go, the more scatter/diffuse the data points used to project the global average. A lot of this information comes from the logs of British Naval vessels from the 17th and 18th centuries. These sparse datasets then have to be used to model the temperature elsewhere on the globe based on measurements at various locations on the oceans and limited colonial stations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait for the charges to be dropped under the principle of "professional courtesy". The alternative will probably be a huge feud between MontCo and PW police departments targeting each others officers and their family members with malicious prosecutions and infractions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 02:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traditionally postal service jobs were awarded through political patronage and as 2nd career jobs for retired/discharged military. There was a bad mix of entitlement mentality and PTSD when the GOP decided they'd had enough with union mandated raises for an underperforming organization. A lot of the original sources of the attitudes in the USPS have been eliminated but much of it lives on in the corporate culture of the place. It is not just postal workers who actually shot people. There were many many events of postal worker tantrums and petty power plays that would get a retail worker fired. The label stuck because the stereotype fit many people's experiences in the post office </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 02:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sloth given 6 month sentence  after raping drunk Kate Upton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I should go bitch at Wikipedia, but seems like taking on this project, you shouldn't rely on single data  source.  
How about remakes where they didn't name it the same: Omega Man (Charlton Heston) / I Am Legend (Will Smith)

Off the top of my head I can think of at least two others where the titles did match up: "Four Weddings and Funeral" and "Look Who's Coming To Dinner", both remakes that seriously sucked compared to the originals
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roller coasters and other inner ear challenging amusement park rides. Loved going to the fair as a kid and riding the egg scrambler, etc midway rides. Same going to amusement parks for the really big stuff. Enjoyment continued into my 20s. After having kids and them getting old enough, took them to the fair. They loved the rides but I felt sick after riding. Second and third time over the next couple years, I tossed my cookies after some really tame ride. Aging I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 03:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In most countries police vehicles don't have inside door handles. What were these guys? A couple of meter maids making their first arrest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 18:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They write thank you notes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 16:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting how you relate a question about keeping guns out of the hands of inappropriate owners immediately to child molestation. A freudian slip perhaps?   

Clearly the answer the gun advocates had teed up, ready to state wasn't a suggestion for stringent gun registration. Yet, in the parallel you draw to gun ownership, child molesters are registered and must continue to be identified as such wherever they go, even after release from prison.  Some would say theres a very strong parallel, in terms of potential future  danger to society, between gun owners and sexual predators. Strict registration and monitoring is the answer in the latter case but somehow the parallel never seems to also be a viable solution for the former </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 16:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this accident, it was the worst I ever seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 12:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a night just like tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 22:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an acquaintance in high school who had a sort of dopey side kick friend. First time I went over to his house, he offered me a snack of something that looked like dry crunch pizza roll out of cut crystal container. He said "they're japanese meat flavored candy, my dad brings them home from business trips". I looked at them and declined. He looked over his shoulder and whispered, "they're really snacks for my mom's shitty little dog, but Danny thinks they're candy so don't tell him". His sidekick came in from the bathroom and saw the jar, pulled the lid, grabbed two or three, and started crunching them down. I was gagging thinking about it.  When asked, Danny said they were "kinda meaty, but like a cracker too" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 21:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a beautiful bird joining a distinguished flock. Let's name them  
 
**Compton Gamma Ray Observatory** named for American Physicist Arthur Holly Compton. Winner of 1927 Nobel Prize in Physics. Discovered the particle nature of electromagnetic Radiation.  

**Hubble Space Telescope** named for American Astronomer Edwin Hubble. Discovered the Milky Way is just one galaxy among countless billions. Discovered galactic redshifts and consequently realization the universe is expanding.  

**Fermi Gamma Ray Space Telescope** named for Italian Physicist Enrico Fermi, Winner of 1938 Nobel Prize in Physics, inventor of the nuclear reactor. Posed the Fermi Equation for the probability of extraterrestrial life. 

**Chandra Xray Observatory** named for Subrahmanyan Chandrasekhar Indian American astrophysicist, winner of 1983 Nobel Prize for Physics for studies in Stellar Evolution. The Chandrasekahr Limit which determines the mass above which a star will collapse into a Black Hole is also named for him. 

**Planck Telescope** named for German Physcist Max Planck, winner of the 1918 Nobel Prize in Physics for development of Quantum Theory. 

**ESA Herschel Space Observatory** Named for British Astronomer Sir William Herschel, discovered planet Uranus, studied and characterized nebulae as distinct objects from stars and planets

**Spitzer Infrared Telescope** named for Lyman Spitzer American Astronomer and Astrophysicist. Studied  the interstellar medium/dust and its formation into stars. Invented the concept of a large scale space based telescope that eventually became the Hubble. 

**James Webb Observatory** named for James Webb who  
1) executive assistant to O. Max Gardner, Under Secretary of the Treasury  
2) director of the Bureau of the Budget for Truman then  
3) Under Secretary of State, U.S. Department of State.   
4) Returned to Washington in 1961 for Kennedy as Administrator of NASA.  

For seven years after Kennedy's lunar landing announcement James Webb politicked, coaxed, cajoled, and maneuvered for NASA in Washington. As a longtime Washington insider he was a master at bureaucratic politics. In the end, through a variety of methods Administrator Webb built a seamless web of political liaisons that brought continued support for and resources to accomplish the Apollo Moon landing on the schedule President Kennedy had announced  

Has it really come to this? We are naming our next great telescope after a *bureaucrat*?  

Isn't there a science of great of the late 20th or early 21st who can be honored and inspirational to a new generation of the budding astronomers? Marc Aaronson,  Rychard Bouwens, Carolyn Porco? 

Come on people, do you really want kids looking at the beautiful images from this telescope for the next 20 years looking up James E Webb for their inspiration to get into science?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 20:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I accused of a crime officer?  
No sir, you're not accused of any crime. It's your money that has committed a crime. We're confiscating it because it is criminal.  
Oh? And what crime is my money being accused of?  
Why, being possessed by a brown-skinned scumbag like you of course
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 14:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait, what's all this about Muhammed "converting? It implies that someone else had founded Islam and convinced him to join their ranks. If you believe the Islam creation story, Muhammed "invented" Islam, largely based on his observations of the Jewish community in and around Jerusalem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 21:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a couple of top posts are marked "Not Really An Ad" where part of a business' signage is obscured by another object to make it funny. It can be argued that any business labeling, whether product packaging or signage on a building is in fact advertising. Partial obscuration is perhaps insufficient to be unfortunate placement, but two adjacent businesses with a humorous connection between the business signs would constitute unfortunate placement in my book 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trilateral Commission gonna disappear your ass stoner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You joke but most people don't realize in the "How Washington Really Works", most federal agencies have a parallel management structure similar to parliamentary democracies.  The US constitution says the president runs the executive branch and appoints/nominates leaders for agencies. In a parliamentary democracy, the party with the majority that "forms the government" appoints specific legislators to manage different agencies. However, in the US constitution, Congress must appropriate money for government spending. In effect this means the money to run the agencies. They're also given a loosely defined "oversight" authority. As a result, every federal agency has two or three congressional representatives who own oversight and budget authority for their agency. They meet regularly with the senior managers for the agency, and often put unpublished pressure on the agency "If you publish this report, I'll cut your budget so far you'll be mopping floors to make ends meet" etc. So, to answer the question, Paul Ryan is the prime minister of the US. However he shares some of that power with Mitch McConnell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 20:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cavitation is a result of the pressure drop over the "wing" --i.e. blade of the propeller dropping below the boiling point of water flowing across the blade. When the water starts to boil, the bubble disrupt the flow creating intense turbulence. The water then returning to the normal pressure after it has crossed the blade, causing the bubbles formed in the boiling to implode, which in turn creates shock waves. It is the shockwaves from those collapsing bubbles that carry sound so far underwater from cavitation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 19:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In reality the Japanese launched thousands of hydrogen balloons with suspended glass balls filled with incendiary materials. They were intended to set huge forest fires in the Pacific Northwest, crippling the economy of the US and tying up scarce manpower. An unseasonably wet summer prevented the vast majority of them from kindling any fires. The few that worked were rapidly extinguished before they could spread out of control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 14:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wind notices it. The differential in force across different latitudes causes it to curve rather than blowing in a straight line. As it curves and curls around itself, tropical cyclones are born. Sometimes they grow up to be big monster typhoons </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 14:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesh that country where women are routinely burned to death after their husbands have collected a dowry from the girls family </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 16:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's another Ramadan Miracle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 03:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're like me and your sunglasses are readers.  You wear the fucking things indoors so you can read the deposit slip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 23:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Governor Moonbeam is still in office! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 22:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She already has the cold eyes of the villain you know everyone is going to call her  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 21:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point of stealth aircraft is not being able to target or shoot them down with radar guided missiles. Very often their enemies know or suspect they're there. They just can't, in theory, determine their location with enough accuracy to target them
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 21:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes there is. It's called Transdniester - It is the Russian occupied strip along the Moldovan/Ukraine border, covering both sides of the Dniester river. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 20:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US JSF F-35 is noisy as all get out - louder than any of the planes I ever heard growing up on air force bases around the country. Unlike the stealth helicopters which have sound suppression, stealth fighters are pretty much all electronic stealth. As a result of that stealth, they're supposed to be flying up 10K or higher because they don't have to worry about radar. You might be able to tell they're in the area from the sound, but the area you can hear them over is 30 or 40 miles wide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 19:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering the Russian aggressive military aircraft maneuvers  against former soviet states and NATO countries in recent months, and  comments over the last month by [Putin regarding the planned deployment of anti-aircraft/anti-missile defense systems specifically in Romainia](http://www.cnn.com/2016/05/28/europe/putin-threatens-romania/), why are people thinking this a meteor? Do you people think the Russians don't have stealth aircraft too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 15:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the same goes for US citizens; but if you're issued a passport, it will be a US Passport indicating holder is a US Citizen. We do not class people moving between US states as "immigrants". Similarly, people moving the US States from US territories such a PR, US Virgin Islands, Guam and the Northern Marianas Islands are all US Citizens under law.  Only American Somoa is different, where the natives are considered US Nationals, but are not US Citizens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 15:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its funny, when I visited there, I thought "Cool, I can bring home fresh tropical fruit". Nope. Think again. There's no customs, but there is an USDA APHIS inspection station where you are questioned and have bags inspected. Bring out your fruit! Bring out your fruit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 01:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you could </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
