<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 15:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the effort all y'all put into the game. Happy Day 1 buyer here. But please can there be an official statements on memory leak and fps fix? There's a lot of people whose game doesn't work on consoles and PCs and what we don't want to hear is radio silence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 15:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Believe me, you can.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 15:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just Cause 3 and Battlefront Trial. Really tempted to buy battlefront if it's a bit cheaper after Christmas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 15:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've never gone as fast as the video? What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 12:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the game shouldn't have been released in the state it is. Xbox One player here, just a stuttery frame rate. The game went gold over a month before release to me the games state is unacceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 11:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's been reports of 5 - 10 minute loading screens even on ps4. Just because you've had no problems or haven't noticed them doesn't mean others haven't. Just look at this sub people have spent money on a product that some people can't even play without locking up, regardless of console or PC. Is that acceptable? The game went gold over a month before release, these things really shouldn't be an issue. It's made me lose a little hope in Avalanche a developer I've praised for years for making the best quality games out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 11:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with this one is that Just Cause went gold over a month before release, given that there really shouldn't be any of these problems especially ones that are so obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 01:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so, we've heard nothing off the developers yet which is dissapointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 23:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? The game went gold over a month ago? If a developer is saying yes the game is done and finished a month in advance then I don't get how it's acceptable to release it with a memory leak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 22:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fps drops here too on Xbox one. It is totally unacceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 22:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xbox One player here. I love this game, I really do. I haven't had this amount of fun in years. The load screens range from being a bit long to instantly loading. There are fps drops which for me is the worst sin. I've had the fps drop just from being in a fire fight with no explosions, it hasn't been the 17fps that has been reported but it's been noticeable. If you want the game it's fun even with these problems if you're not too bothered id wait until theirs a fix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 22:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The atrocious fps drops, memory leaks and long load screens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 22:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> System you playing on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any word from developers on the console versions getting a fix? It's nearly been 24 hours and it's unacceptable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 22:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 20:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it takes time for developers to make a game its best. Otherwise you get a pc arkham knight or Xbox just cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 20:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they bring a fix or it, since writing that post it happened, not during explosions but hen3 enemies were shooting at me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 20:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 18:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't experienced any of these problems with my copy. Is it really that bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 18:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me personally it's Witcher, Fallout 4 will probably get it but for me it's Witcher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 17:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have installed it offline still the whole 7 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 17:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and several friends own the game, all fine. All the people on my friends list says it's fine, the majority of reports on this here sub says it's fine. I don't see the problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the obscenely long install times on disk games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 17:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My just cause disk has taken about7 hours to install my friends took an hour, we have the exact same internet package and I've been disconnected while installing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 17:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is incorrect, owned the game since midnight. None of these problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no it doesnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Installing off disk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 hours later and just cause 3 still hasn't installed... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 14:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It must depend then, played for 10 hours no framerate problems or loading issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 14:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hype! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 13:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The exact same version, not sure why they had a problem a few friends and me are playing the game and none of us have had any problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never fear! Just cause 3 is fine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 12:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen the question asked a few times around here and after about 5 hours of play in one sitting it works fine. The frame rates solid, and the load times fine.  I think the day one patch solved all the problems. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 12:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem I have with it is that the game went gold over a month ago. Why does all this info about bad framerate come out the day before release? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have the framerate gone down during explosions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dropped money on an Xbox because my friends were on there and for Halo. I shouldn't have to fork over more money to play a properly optimised game. I get to buy maybe two games a year because of my finances and waited for this one. Why should I be punished for owning an Xbox  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 18:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will just have to wait until tommorow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure they will but I booked two days off work to play this game. If I drop money on a game I expect it to run properly on day one. That shouldn't be a big ask but that's the way it seems to be going now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's atrocious, utterly atrocious. This has made me think twice about buying the game. Awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just Cause 3: 1st Contact Technical   Performance analysis - Xbox One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 16:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Films and TV not updating episodes.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 12:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 00:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume he's staying up till midnight tommorow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 23:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hype for this game is unreal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 10:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fallout 4. The game is as vast as an ocean but as deep as a puddle. All of the main quest is uninteresting and boring and just flips the Fallout 3 story on its head. All the factions are so morally grey that it really doesn't matter who you choose, the voiced protagonist makes it a bad game to roleplay with and the lack of speech options or even skill speech options is annoying. All the new content they put in can't compensate for all the other stuff they took out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are missions working this time round? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 00:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is JC3 keeping the chaos system from the others? Only a certain amount of chaos unlocks the next missions? Are there factions this time round and you do missions for them? I hope this time there is more variety in missions, the story in jc2 could get a tad boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 14:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah sorry I made the post on my phone. I didn't mean to trash talk the game without proper reasons I wanted to evoke discussion as is the point of Reddit. Even things that are universally loved have flaws and as we talk and discuss them we can get better quality products in the future.

Edit: the factions never really explain what they want particularly well. All they do is trash talk each other making it hard to know who I'd want to align with. The only character I found interesting in the main quest is Nick Valentine , heck I constantly have him with me. Piper is just a journalist interested in getting people to wake up to the bigger truth. That's been done before and I don't find it particularly interesting. Father is just a bit of a dick and not that engaging and none of the other institute people are really memorable. As a game yeah it can be fun, exploring the wasteland? Great! It's the main reason I'm not selling it, I know I'll come back here and there to explore Boston but from an rpg stand point it just didn't excel. Fallout 3 made me in control of 99% of my character. I can give them a backstory, I empathise with having a dad more so than a child. I don't feel like I'm in the role of my character in Fallout 4. Which really should be the point of an rpg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 14:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly how I feel, Fallout 3 is my favourite game of all time and has tons of role playing elements. Heck you even have a hand at creating your backstory in this game, why they would take it out is a bit odd to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So here we are... 60 hours in and I'm done with Fallout 4. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 11:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main questline and characters are boring and uninspired, all of the factions are so morally Grey or uninteresting that it's not fun. My favourite bit of new Vegas was the factions and they just haven't implemented them well here. Settlements is fun for a bit but doesn't carry the game. Maybe one day I'll come back to it but Bethesda I'm sorry I'm just dissapointed.

Edit : I'm aware this isn't flesh out, let's try a bit harder..

the factions never really explain what they want particularly well. All they do is trash talk each other making it hard to know who I'd want to align with. The only character I found interesting in the main quest is Nick Valentine , heck I constantly have him with me. Piper is just a journalist interested in getting people to wake up to the bigger truth. That's been done before and I don't find it particularly interesting. Father is just a bit of a dick and not that engaging and none of the other institute people are really memorable. As a game yeah it can be fun, exploring the wasteland? Great! It's the main reason I'm not selling it, I know I'll come back here and there to explore Boston but from an rpg stand point it just didn't excel. Fallout 3 made me in control of 99% of my character. I can give them a backstory, I empathise with having a dad more so than a child. I don't feel like I'm in the role of my character in Fallout 4. Which really should be the point of an rpg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 23:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not exclusive to RPGs. The first experience I had with NG+ was with the Ratchet and Clank series on ps2, Arkham Knight and City also have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 23:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halo MCC, going through the games for the first time before buying 5 for Christmas. It's my fallout break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 23:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I want one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 23:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Brent, Brent Black?

Brentalfloss Brent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 23:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the same thing, a few people have tweeted the developers and they've reassured that the episode will be released before the end of the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 00:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of audio this episode is great feels very classic grumps, both parties enjoying the game and just shooting the shit. Looking forward to more of this!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 13:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super dissapointing, love skateboarding games just gotta wait for Skate 3 to hit backwards compatibility now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 00:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 16th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you down 360 games with Gold on Xbox One if your account isn't merged over from the 360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 13:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recreate the movie "Signs" with popular mascot and signage. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 17:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Give me some builds guys! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 17:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime I start a new game I always find it hard to not make myself or a generic all rounder to maximise fun, lost some builds here to go through fallout 3 and 4 with!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what's the point of doing it? If they all stand for something different I don't get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the point of joining all factions as one character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what my friends done. He only plays as one character and does everything. Will joining every faction screw him over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for stuffer31 Cutie and Kimberley Marvel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 00:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Big cutie Valery , Plump Princess and other videos. Holla at me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 09:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many factions are there in game? I was a bit worried because it seems to have less than new Vegas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 09:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's be investing into every perk and special in the game making it far less special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a 'Wrong' way to play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 08:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always want to see everything, and kinda make a genericish character over time but I feel that doesn't allow me to have other run throughs with other builds later on. Is there a right way to play? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 15:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, reset console. Deleted some things, heck even have it a break unplugged but still unplayable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been playing FO4 for nearly 5 hours, suffering from major frame rate issues on Xbox. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 15:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got to 5 hours game time and my game has slowed down to a crawl. It's unplayable at the moment, anyway I can make Bethesda aware of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 03:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good reference A +++ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To signify rebirth I'm going to start to play Fallout 4 naked and covered in my mothers blood. How are you guys going to play it for the first time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 23:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 23:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has the experience changed to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xbone User here - how do I know the download on my console is the game and not the stub file? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 17:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It says preordered on it, is that the game preloaded or will have to preload on the day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Fallout even that immersive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 13:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen people complain that Fallout 4 isn't as immersive as the other games of the series. But I've never really been immersed by any of them, each game has a plot and in the case of 3 you can't play the game after doing the main plot (without dlc). People want to play the game as themselves but the other games did have scripted events to which can take the player out of the immersion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for Stuffer31 Cutie. I have Bug Cutie Valery and Plump Princess videos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 15:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 12:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Their life is shitty enough as it is

uhhh... thanks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 12:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's on ps4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When does the new dashboard get released? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 10:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whose gone digital for Fallout 4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 10:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a lot of people saying they have the physical copy, I can't be bothered to install it after getting it on the day so I'm getting the digital copy and preloading it. Anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 00:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll pm you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for Miley, Jae, Britt Have : Vallery, Plump Princess </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 12:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either accounts or videos

I have videos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Birthday Arrested Development! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 11:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 09:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GT - subject1260nitt want to find a GTA buddy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Order is not on my order history but I have the email confirmation... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 09:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ordered Fallout 4 as you do and was going to check the scheduled delivery date but I can't find the product on my order list! I have the email confirmation saying I've ordered successfully. Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 19:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you look to see when somethings scheduled to ship? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 11:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry but the Pip Boy just looks really plasticy and cheap. I like the steel book and big Pip Boy carrier it comes in though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 15:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I should have specified yes I'm on preview. What's a hard reset sorry? Unplugging it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 14:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live alone with no dogs, it's a temporary fix until I get a new mic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Party Chat can't find my Microphone... But only when I'm playing games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 14:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 09:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The the same dude but I did the same thing, I just didn't find the game fun. The tower defence segments bored me and I didn't find the game funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 19:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a bit dissapointing I'm not the biggest co- op fan. I hope it's still good single player </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Kimberley Marvel, Have Vallerie Big Cutie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 19:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 16:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every year I hope for Ross and Danny to play it on Scream Train. Every year I'm dissapointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 01:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do we do that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 19:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's what you call a different opinion. For me CE's level design was boring and flat, grey corridor after grey corridor. Halo 2 actually had cities, alleyways and the spaceships had interesting places like gardens. I'm sorry but Halo 2 just pushed my buttons more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 18:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also playing through Halo for the first time, let's just say I wasn't impressed by CE at all... But Halo 2? Wow.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 17:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is the community? I own this game but have never played it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 16:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't followed AC since brotherhood. This is the first in a while I've been interested in, should u be playing catch up or is the outside the animus stuff gone now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 16:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> subject1260nitt's my name and games are my... Game.

Playing a lot of GTA and MCC at the minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MCC - can't find players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 15:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are people not playing even though 5 isn't even out yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 01:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GTA V, Rare Replay, Valiant Hearts and walking dead  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 10:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to be, with the new Freemode event update there has definitely been a noticeable inprovement to matchmaking  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 01:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And child murder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I backed out of the preview programme and didn't want new dashboard early but my Xbox installed anyway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 11:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you live in the UK... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 01:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rick and Morty was on Fox in the Uk this evening. I can only assume this is a regular occurance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 10:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very strange worked fine for me on Xbone. Did you sort it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 15:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with the game? I don't own the game but a massive fan of the series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 23:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes down all digital games if that game is digital </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 22:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here we go again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 22:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know but we had it 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 16:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah story is completed there are no informants on bleake  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 12:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK player here on Xbox and is not available  for me either... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are the Riddler informants for Panesaa Studios? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 12:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done all the bleake island riddles now have to do Panessa. Where can I find the informants that give me the locations there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Block cheddar and whipped cheese on 50/50 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 19:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 13:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try and read it before Sunday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [m] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 19:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 21:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry but I'm on mobile, could you type it out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 21:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 21:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added you Dec! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 21:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added you man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 18:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me about an hour and I'll have you over. Started today again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got back into Animal Crossing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 13:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started a new town today,

20 year old British male, plays at different times, will play at least once a day. I like nighttime 

5386-9773-1483 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 13:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a community site for new leaf? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 13:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subs a bit dead... And animal crossing community isn't really what I'm thinking. A site that discusses events, turnips etc would be cool. ACC just seems like a generic forum  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do events happen on the same day for everyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 13:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rebrought new leaf today, is it the bug off for everyone else? Or do events differ per game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 15:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Administration and communications </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 12:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has to be armpits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 12:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 12:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My employer is taking me out for a curry because of the last day. My phone is currently on my desk, with my ID card, a telephone, a notebook, stapler,and a box of paper clips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 12:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they're spending alot of time improving GTA 5 atm, however they did tease a new Red Dead so time will tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's my last day of work/apprenticeship today. I will spend my last day answering your questions. AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 11:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be on/off computer for the next 7 hours. With one hour for lunch, after the 7 hours I will be on/off Reddit blue as I go home.
As for right now, I'm on.

Yes this is a new thread I butchered the title of the other one.

AMA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 11:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FOCK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 17:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have issues of depression, apathy, self assteem and many many others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 17:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been there and done that countless times. I'll be praying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for an accountability partner online [Christians Only] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 16:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not too sure if this is okay or the right place for this but I'm looking for an accountability partner online. Someone who is of the faith and we can email back and forth about our lives, struggles etc. I think it's good and healthy to have someone distant praying for you and I'm very eager to do that for someone else.

This feels like a dating add but this is my basic information..

Names Tom, I'm 20, Ive been a Christian for 5 years, I'm from the UK and I was diagnosed with depression this year. (So you know a little of my circumstance)

Thanks all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 16:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats your plan man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 12:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the Pastor with no answer's podcast episodes that were uploaded. I think there's two and they uploaded on Saturdays? I really enjoyed the discussion, it felt like a natural progression and something that felt whole heartedly Bad Christian. I'm down with this being a full podcast with more episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 12:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm down for this, I will have the money for them on Saturday. What do you have in mind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 12:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He really jumped the carpe this time! That micey micey bastard I swear to God! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 23:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not wanting to dig up anything but can I ask what had the board/school your course is with saying to you/said throughout the year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 20:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xbone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Out of context Jake and Amir is best Jake and Amir </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 17:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I ask time and time again but I never get my wish, so I'll write down the name of these fish, you bish! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 17:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I speak to and only to... you! Jake and Amir's you silly old queers. I can see you are working hard, maybe you deserve a card? I know what I deserve though... Nah! Actually more then deserve.. what I *want*. I'll tell you what I want shall I? See my friend and I, we had a bet. How long will it take for me to receive a greasy sticky blu ray set.

[A thank you... poo!](http://i.imgur.com/PhkZzY9.jpeg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 16:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   eastern spiritual practices that can sometimes come along with Karate instruction.

This entered my mind too, I've already layed down my faith at them, saying I volunteer at a Church and want Sunday Mornings off. I'm going to go for the interview and ask questions there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doing a job for the sake of it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 15:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I applied for an Admin job at a Karate school. I had a phone interview today and was told that I would have to learn Karate and I will during work hours. This job now feels totally different then what I thought it was. I'm not passionate about Karate and have an interview on Thursday. I'd just be doing it for the paycheck, however I feel I have an administrative gift. Do I go for it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a crew that just wants to chill and have fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 15:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for people just to hang with and talk to while driving, no one who takes it too seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I failed my apprenticeship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 10:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got diagnosed with depression this year and just didnt do any of the college units. It's a crippling disease. Now it's time to find a job with the experience I do have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 10:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean Destineve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 20:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly reccomend Bad Christian. The idea is that they have real conversations about the faith and church without censor or much editing. It's an honest and raw look at life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 20:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R.I.P in piece Bonks Adventure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 15:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh absoloutley. I *could* have done alot more. Everytime I sat infront of a blank screen ready to work? Thought about killing myself. In those moments dying was better than doing any work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 11:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I would leave that church during the sermon unless he was talking about his life before the new birth.

I for one welcome honesty. The Pastor isnt a hero, he's as messed up as you and I. Why would you have this response? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've gotten to the point where I dont understand how God can be on my side. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 11:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am about to fail an apprenticeship, 2015 has been the worst year of my life. I've been diagnosed with depression and been generally apathetic. Because of this I am going to fail an apprenticeship I've been doing for a year. If God loves people who work hard and succeed. How can he love me? My mind is a mess and all over the place, help me. Pray. Please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My depression has made me apathetic, as a result of my apathy I am going to fail an apprenticeship I have spent the last year doing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 11:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like I didnt try to motivate myself, I *cant* and no body gets that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 09:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be surprised if it wasn't Fallout 3 or GTA IV on 360. Can't remember the exact game times though.

Don't get much time to play Xbox one so its Arkham Knight at 40 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 08:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can barely find any on the map, anymore! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 15:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Opinions are opinions and you're allowed to have them. But what exactly dont you like about the AC games? They're very similar to the Arkham games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a Riddler Trophy guide that uses the ingame chart? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 11:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found half using the riddlers informants but am going crazy trying to find them all. Every guide I've found would have me going through every one again seeing as I can't remember which ones I've done and not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 01:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been that long? Damn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This job for an Admin Assistant offer karate training </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 14:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on Toby's Church Structure? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 13:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few weeks ago now, but in episode 115, Toby did a little bit of reflecting and bought a way that church *could* look like for those who didnt hear the episode here's what he said...

Each sunday of the month, you'd have five different times together and five very different ways to do church..

1st Sunday = Do Sabbath for real - Cut yourself off from phone, technology etc and spend time with family and friends, having real discussion and real time together

2nd Sunday = Have a biblical teaching, that is actually teaching the Bible. Dont focus on me or the congregation and how we can apply it just teach the Bible and if the other stuff comes great!

3rd Sunday = Free for all in the Church Hall! People can bring and talk about whatever they want and what they believe to invoke discussion amongst the congregation

4th Sunday = A small talk on something relevant in the local community, the church or the world. Then split up into small groups and dicsuss.

5th Sunday = Music and food, a band just jams in the background as the congregation shares a meal and again real conversations open up.

And that's it. In the episode Matt did come up with some counter points but I was interested in what you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 13:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they're making Pastor with no answers it's own podcast! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] How do we get more people discussing here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 13:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the BC Pod having a subreddit! I feel that this space could be used more effectively however, for Christians to discuss issues brought up in the episodes or whatever. I dont want this sub to die like many others I've seen. What do we do?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 19:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup! 4 more chapters and an epilogue to go! I highly reccomend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It was dark for 8pm yesterday. This means my favourite season Autumn if finally here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 13:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont like Summer at all, much too hot for my liking. I love the cosiness and the colours of Autumn. Fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 13:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend named Jack. There are many stories I can tell about Jack but this is my favourite. I was chilling with a friend at his house when we saw Jack pass in a suit and tie carrying a briefcase. He normally wears shorts and a muscle tee, he's a gym geek, so we decided to phone him and ask why he was dressed so out of character. We phoned him and asked "Whats with the suit man?", he said that he had an interview. We were like "Cool man, where at?" he responded with "The Bank". Jacks never done accounting or had experience with money before so of course we asked why. "To open an account". We both were gobsmacked, this guy had dressed up in formal attire to set up a bank account and not only that but called it an interview. So curiously after laughing for a while we asked "What's in the briefcase then?" "Loads of heavy books, so that I appear smart if they ask questions"

We couldnt believe it, this is still probably the stupidest thing I've ever heard in my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 13:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's using a popular way of telling stories from the site 4chan. MFW normally has a picture of a face next to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 17:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you confirm that you are indeed 30 and flirty? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [UK] Gift card problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 14:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was given a gift card for a leaving present at work, went home put in the info. Great, I have 50 in my account. I didnt get a email confirmation however. Went to purchase something today and it says my balance is 0 and it wont let me put in the code again, I have no way to prove I put the code in and it wont work when putting it in again. What can I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 13:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's his murphday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 12:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy followed me on Twitter a while ago who has made exactly that. It's an Android app called [gamester](http://gamester.co) unfortunatley it's only for Android atm and as an iPhone user I'm not able to use it. If you have an Android device have a looksy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Such a damn shame that Ty never really took off... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 12:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there have been 4 games but it saddens me that no one knows Ty. The games were so unique with it's boomerang based combat and outback setting. I'd love for a Remaster so that people can pick them up and see what the fuss is about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 12:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, it's a shame that Ty didnt have that impact. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 11:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ty the Tasmanian Tiger has been forgot about, but dont worry.We still love you Ty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw an advert on Facebook for Sony giving away PS4's for 1 I thought it was fake, but my scepticism was confirmed when I saw this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 11:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 17:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright! Is there a recap that isnt 6 hours long? Damn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 17:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also remember to finish the main story in GZ since its leads up to MGSV. It should only take an hour of your time

Yeah I'm going to start tonight!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 17:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay cool! How about in terms of longevity? Hows the Multiplayer, will I be spending alot of time with this? Enough to hold me over till Fallout? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 17:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, I know the backstory is explained on the menu of GZ and I read and understood it mostly. Do you think I should just wait? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 17:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just play Far Cry 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I play MGSV without playing the others? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 17:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 21:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man probably gonna get this, will be the game to tide me over till Fallout. Do you think it's a game I could 100% how many hours do you think the game has? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 20:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a ton to do? How bigs the map? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've never seen a Mad Max movie, should I get mad max? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 20:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me! They're in my to view list. I was given an Amazon voucher as a leaving work gift and was wondering if I should watch the movies before bothering with the game? It's either that or wait to play catch up on MGS... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was Halo CE critically acclaimed when it came out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 17:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because I'm playing it in 2015, but the level design is atrocious. The level Attack on the Control Centre is just the same room repeated over and over and over again, I think back in 2001 people could understand when developers were just being lazy. The last half of the game has the same levels as the first half but backwards! I find the game fun but damn sometimes it's a slog. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 13:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just cant get my head around getting high scores in these. Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 13:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful of spoilers there kiddo.

Yeah I love City the most to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So does the Season Pass DLC end with Crimefighters pack 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 14:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's the case I won't be able to mask my disappointment. The only DLC I really enjoyed was the 1989 racetracks. But that's it. I hope there's more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 10:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I haven't played the game in a while, by special moves what do you mean?

Also any tips to perform critical strikes I barley get them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips for AR challenges? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 18:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get hit for the whole of the "Assault on GcPd" one And only just get 10000 points. I don't get it, any tips would be appreciated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this on Facebook with the caption "deep". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 13:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 13:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever game they want to play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here who doesnt cut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 13:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as in doesnt self harm but does other things. I stab myself with a blunt pencil in the leg so I bruise as I'm scared of blood. Found no one else who does something similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 11:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acknowledge Jon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help me!! What console buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 14:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 14:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much, the story Graham tells doesnt have a cliff hanger, but the thing with Gwendolyn will continue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 13:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *oooh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 13:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that the Chapters are unrelated as they all take place at different times in Grahams life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 13:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afa Nata! Afa Nata! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 13:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His videos make me laugh and entertain me. I have no reason to dislike the guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 10:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the Wii U! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
