<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6703</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 21:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm kinda lost here. Is he joking about strangling his kid to get laid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol you're one to talk about boring taste in film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I read the first sentence, saw what came after, and wasted my time writing a reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it just be the Multiverse? Apparently the MCU is part of the comic's multiverse (though I don't think they've interacted yet).

What if we started getting versions of the characters in the movies in the comics, and vice versa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than Hulk, who is arguably more powerful, Strange is definitely the most powerful hero in the MCU (Adam Warlock doesn't count yet). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you an idiot or something, why is this a reply to a comment about something else

Anyway if my film taste is so boring, give me your top 5.

inb4 exclusively French New Wave and German Expressionism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joke's on you, you took time out of your precious, fleeting life to shitpost something no one's ever going to read lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Engage with what? How I rank a movie against nazis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 06:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this is sooooooooo insightful and now I see the truth, I shouldn't vote!!!1! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 05:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much just stay away from Shadow Raid and Carshop (and other stealth only missions if there are more, can't think of any right now) until you get a better feel for the stealth. Otherwise, stick to what difficulty level you feel comfortable with and have fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *doofus

Who's the doofus now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilarious pasta. Truly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 03:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you don't think films should require more than what you see to enjoy them

I didn't say that. I meant if *that's all the movie is*, then its silly. Regardless, I'm done with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 01:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okey dokey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 01:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your version is much more extreme than mine.

I never said anything about wanting to instantly understand everything in one viewing. There's just not much more to the movie than the plot (visuals and so on) so when its as difficult to "get" as MD, that's a pretty big piece.

Going back to Eraserhead, did I understand everything (or really anything) about that the first time I saw it? Hell no, but it was still really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUCK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant read with comprehension. It seems pretty obvious it wasn't only the plot I took issue with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no u </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 00:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please just let me buy a shirt or something fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please be sarcastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see 2001 not being very surreal, but AN? Some scenes in that movie, were crazy surreal. Not that that really matters in this conversation.

I've seen some of his short films, like half of Dune, and a few episodes of Twin Peaks. I'll look into those other ones, thanks for the recommendation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree with that argument either. That wasn't what I'm saying, for the record. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I DON'T READ WHAT IS ACTUALLY SAID IN A POST DAE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddamn The Fox and the Hound.

Every. Single. Time.

The Iron Giant is up there too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm giggling at your username paired with this comment. Fits perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're half right.

;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  got me gud fucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man, didn't you know? Marvel movies are made for idiots and children, and if you don't like only the most acclaimed art house cinema, you must be an idiot or a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man everything about Eraserhead is awesome. The visuals, style, "plot", etc.

I know a lot of things are similar with these movies, so it would seem like if I like Eraserhead so much, I should like MD. But everything was so more more well done in Eraserhead and it went with what it is, a surreal, almost abstract mind fuck of a movie. MD kind of had that going, but it seemed like it went out of its way to add bizarre stuff that isn't connect with the rest, and then there was too much plot for it to be THAT abstract, and a lot of the plot didn't even go anywhere.

To address the last point, about explanation is secondary, I guess it just seemed like Eraserhead didn't need to make sense to be awesome. I can watch that and be satisfied. But Mulholland Dr. just seems like it's reading the viewer with not making any sense, while seeming like it should. I dunno, it's hard to articulate when talking about this stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do enjoy surrealism, though. Eraserhead, 2001: A Space Odyssey, and Apocalypse Now are some of my favorite movies. I appreciate you being nice though haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the solidarity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I purposely went in knowing nothing other than its a David Lynch film, there is a scary scene in a diner,  and a woman loses her memory. Pretty much no expectations, other than it would be good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2001 is slow but an incredible movie. I get why people say it's one of the best ever. This, however... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I acknowledged that in the post, yo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not too lazy to read into the movie itself, understood a lot of the themes and symbolism, but that's not really saying much, considering how obvious they are.

I just don't think movies should have to rely entirely on abstract symbolism and etc, to be enjoyable. Might as well just read an essay at that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 19:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know how to answer the first question.

Top five movies are, in no particular order, Seven Samurai, Star Wars OT, Hot Rod, Apocalypse Now, and The Thing. Off the top of my head. There are probably some others that I'd put ahead of some of these but I don't have a top 5 ready all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scratched Mulholland Dr. off my list. Biggest waste of 2 and a half hours of my life? Maybe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 08:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Eraserhead and from what I've seen, Twin Peaks is good. So I went into Mulholland Dr. pretty excited.

Then I watched two and a half hours of some scenes that kind of formed a story, in a boring way. I haven't looked up "explanations" or anything for the movie, because a) I don't think you should have to do that, a movie should be somewhat  enjoyable without having to resort to having someone explaining all the convoluted minutia, and b) I really don't want to waste any more of my time on this movie (the irony of that isn't lost on me, I know I'm spending even more time writing this shitty rant).

Also, the apparently infamous diner scene was more disappointing than a cum filled twinkie. So many people have told me about how scary it is. All it was was a guy telling about a really vague dream, and it isn't like there was very much about that itself that was creepy. I love horror, so its not because it isn't some James Wan jump scare, there was just nothing creepy about it. And to top that off, the two characters in the scene had pretty much nothing to do with the rest of the plot.

You're going to call me an idiot, or say I don't understand film or whatever the hell, but I'm pretty sure its just a case of a seriously overrated movie that people read way too much into. Maybe someone could explain why they personally like it, and then I can stew on that and probably still hate the movie a lot but with a bit less gusto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate non-Disney musicals but this looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not like the "introduction" movies really add to the plot. They introduce you to the characters. They're good if you like the characters, but you don't need to see them to understand the other movies.

Example: I never watched Ant Man. When he showed up in Civil War, I wasn't confused about who he was. Its not like his story is vital to the plot, its just additional info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 01:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is possibly the least interesting and informative movie poster I've ever seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 05:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait is this real? The camera angles and quality tell me **know**, but the reaction tells me yes.

Edit: I made that comment super late last night, I was tired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh great, a sequel to the most disappointing game I've ever played.

How fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Month of the month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the comments again. No it isn't doesn't make any sense in context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought Blood Dragon goddamn it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No it isn't at all.

Unless you're disagreeing with me over the soundtrack, what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize that, but I imagine that when self driving cars become the norm, it's gonna be basically mandatory to let them do their thing, for the most part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 05:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted a live action Fairly Off Parents movie just so Bruce Campbell could play the Crimson Chin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 05:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "me and muh buddy Keith took them pussy liberal computers out of our trucks so we can drive em ourselves, like real country boys huhuhuhuh"

-Idiots, in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 05:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened four fucking times a few days ago, in the spanse of like two hours.

Fucking Salem drivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 03:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What! The extra scenes flesh out the characters so much more, and barring Joy Division, the director's cut soundtrack is so much better.

Edit: Well fuck me for stating a fact (the extra scenes do give you more information, go fucking figure) and an opinion about the music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you watch it, you're going to be super underwhelmed because the amount of hype it has.

It is one of my personal favorites, but I wouldn't say it's one of the best horror movies ever made. It's definitely not for everyone, though, that's for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 21:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly it just depresses me. That's the only reason I don't like it. The whole "BRAAAAAAINS" is so underused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 20:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hail Hydra"

- Nick Spencer, writer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 07:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uuuuh, you're fucking stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 10:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AuPfTXBmiJ4

I had to look it up because I forgot how goddamn funny that part is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that movie is fucking hilarious, even if I do feel like a terrible person/13 year old for laughing at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washington Davis is a sick name tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the art is great but that's about it. I don't even get the concept. Like, why is Ulysses such a big deal? It's not like he's the first person in the MU who can see the future. Hell, his isn't even that reliable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 05:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is Hawkeye an old guy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about one that increases melee attack speed? If I remember correctly, there are a few scenes where Which hits guys to "stun" them, then shoots them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 10:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's an actor who does really crazy does shit with interesting people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 06:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 02:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lovecraft is my go-to, but if you're willing to read comics, Locke and Key, Severed, and especially Nocturnals are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 02:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only seen the first five and then Jason X-present, but  I'd have to say for me it goes:

Part 4

Part 2

Part 3

Friday the 13th (09) (I know, I know, I'm an idiot)

Part 5

Friday the 13th

Jason X

Freddy vs. Jason

If we include other media, Ash vs. Freddy vs. Jason gets the #1 spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 02:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, but that's the "character's" name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 08:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol

Everyone else is saying the opposite of you. Maybe you should stop being so overly dramatic. And stop trying to put hidden subtexts into other people's comments. He didn't say anything about the "flamer" being bad. In fact, he said it was a good thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 08:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck I wasn't ready for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 08:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, that destroyed me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 22:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People hate Jiro and Sydney? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 20:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been excited for a superhero movie since GotG but with GotG 2 and now this, I am fucking pumped. I don't even like the X-Men movies but this just looks really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 02:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...Duh?

Why does it matter if he was charged if he was acquitted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nate Parker was acquitted yo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this happens, I really hope it doesn't take place in present day. I feel like the technology will bog it down, like the Mission Impossible movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look at you you know his real name how clever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it depends on the type of the actors.

Vin Diesel vs the Rock is on par with Jackie Chan and Jet Li in Forbidden Kingdom, which is on par with DeNiro and Pacino in Heat. There are others but I totally spaced on what I had in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you little coward

lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 06:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is Jason sympathetic?

I get that he was bullied and had a hard life and stuff, but he's killed like hundreds of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 05:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 04:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hulu also has a ton of Criterion movies, and you can get a free week trial. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 04:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to sort by price? I wanna see if there's anything cheaper than the usual stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 04:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys please stop telling people Pontypool is about zombies. That takes so much fun out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I've been playing HW Jax wrong but that wouldn't hurt him too much for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, guess I shoulda clarified that but I figured it would be obvious enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> plz no

What did they change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How big was the XL update? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 20:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been gone for almost two weeks and I was excited to play with the new update, but its 30-something gigs for me. Is it really that big? I feel like that's almost the size of the full game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 07:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If its against the CPU, Ermac. Motherfuckin CPU is a cheap bastard with Ermac.

Don't really mind when it comes to playing against other people, but I hate D'Voorrah in general so her, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I watched Phantasm last night for the first time, and I have some questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 01:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so I got it right up until the end. Did everything happen or did it not? I know there are sequels, and I know Reggie's still alive in the new movie, but how does that work?

Do the sequels answer that, and furthermore, are the sequels good enough to watch? For the most part I don't watch horror sequels because they're almost never good, but I've heard Phantasm is an exception.

Also, were the sequels planned, or did they just make movie with a confusing ending and decide later to make sequels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second book? I count two already, *If Chins Could Kill* and *Make Love the Bruce Campbell Way*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 22:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know me responding to this isn't near as good as Ash himself responding, but he said Evil Dead 2 was his favorite somewhere else in the thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 22:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, man, Terminator Salvation's exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything about this movie (to me) is just about perfect. Strongly recommend going into it with as little knowledge as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You made me kill my friends."

Why the fuck would this be in the trailer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiend Without a Face is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Pinhead is put alongside Meyers, Freddy, and Jason because he's a slasher villain like them (I'd kind of hesitate to put Freddy in there to, because he's so much more supernatural how he gets his victims is way different), I think it probably has to do with him being nigh invincible, and/or the fact that he has such a signature look that he's instantly recognizable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks fucking awesome and I'm not even being ironic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 21:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying I agree or disagree, but this was an odd comment to read, considering the usual sentiment here seems to be that three of the best action movies released in the past 15+ years are Dredd, Fury Road, and John Wick, which don't take a lot of time holding the audience's hand and establishing stuff. People like them because they pretty much just go right into the action with minimal set up.

I don't know which I agree with (if either), but it's just kinda weird to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 06:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put them on something that resembles a wall and turn your camera sideways. Boom, million dollar picture right there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 04:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Favorite: Rogue or Black Canary

Least favorite: New Harley is pretty fuckin horrible, but Captain Marvel is coming in at a close second, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 04:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Daddy's grrrl

Someone kill me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 00:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would buy the Darkness issues and the Deadpool "Collector's pack" because I want to finish that run, unless you're trying to sell these in bulk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 20:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a record store in in 2014 with a few friends, and I was just starting to really get into music. I asked one friend, who seems to know pretty much everything about music, for a cheap recommendation. He brought me a Kid A CD from the $2 shelf and I got it, having only ever heard Radiohead's most popular songs (Creep, Karma Police, etc).

A few days later, I was sitting at home and I decided to try this new album (I wasn't optimistic for some reason). I expected some alt. rock or grunge, but when Everything in its Right Place came on, that sweet, sweet synth melted my brain. I listened for a minute or so, then jumped off my bed, turned the light off, and just sat and listened to the album two or three times.

Kid A is still one of my favorite albums of all time, and if you're ever looking for something to listen to on a long night drive, I wholly recommend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 09:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 09:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think the white high tops from HM would be cooler, but if you're going for the Payday 2 look, I think any brown shoes would work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
