<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4635</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 15:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just looked up the song. It actually has screaming in it...wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 20:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talon = Quinn's lost brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 06:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all have bad games. Nobody is perfect... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 22:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/fifthworldpics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 19:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep I play AP Sona mid too. Hilarious to play as because people don't see it coming. Just get Deathcap, Void Staff, CDR boots, RoA, and DFG. You can take down squishies really quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 03:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSFW link above. Just FYI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-15 15:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason this scares me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 04:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is basically what I'm going to do with my Surface Pro when I get one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 03:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knew this was going to be posted. Twas an epic "comeback". When I started watching it looked like they were losing but their team could 4 v 5 them without Chaox. Then at the end he got a pentakill. Was great. Would watch again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 23:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can play Karma though. What then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 04:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People will only abuse her once they can play her. Most people can't play her to her full potential yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 04:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should have believed you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 00:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the reason more to hate Teemo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 17:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/FifthWorldPics  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 08:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually saw this in a game once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 20:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to get the phone replaced twice. The first time the charging port on the phone broke. The second time the phone stopped booting up completely. It froze on the HTC logo. The third phone I got had overheating issues which caused the phone to reboot randomly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 18:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steam is pretty useless if you don't play games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 18:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amazing Nokia Lumia 920. Only wish I got it in cyan :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 06:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically yeah. I wanted to give the hardware a try. It was amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 06:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason I got the 920 was because my first Windows Phone was the HTC Surround. The hardware was terrible. I don't trust HTC anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 06:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been making a collection of backgrounds that I use. I currently use all the ones in the Mirror's Edge folder on rotate. Here they are:
http://sdrv.ms/RdZmwx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 06:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a Windows 8 mod? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 05:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the Surface RT for two weeks before I returned it. The build quality is amazing. Feels great in your hand. Looks great. Is solid and feels like it will last. None of the other OEM's could match it. Also since it's microsoft it wont have any of the random crapware OEM's install on machines now. I'm picking up a Surface Pro day 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 00:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I love Turbocross too. I would just rather play Super Crossfire. It's kind of silly how Uber said its fine that everything is unbalanced because it's supposed to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 20:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. I still love this game and play it all the time. 567 hours logged so far. It's a shame that almost nobody plays Super Crossfire anymore because I still think that is the best mode. Turbocross is fun but it just isn't as balanced as Crossfire. I just wish it took off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Troubleshooting] Headset Static Problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 18:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When using my headset sometimes people say that my voice turns completely roboticy and they can't hear me at all. I've tested my headset on another computer and it sounds completely fine. I also just sent my headset in for a repair so I'm sure that it is not the problem. Also the static problem does not happen all the time with my mic but it seems kind of random. I'm guessing there is a problem with my motherboard. Here are my specs:

[PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jdbH) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jdbH/by_merchant/) / [Benchmarks](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jdbH/benchmarks/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [AMD Phenom II X4 965 Black 3.4GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/amd-cpu-hdz965fbgmbox) | $89.99 @ Newegg 
**Motherboard** | [ASRock 970 EXTREME4 ATX  AM3+ Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-970extreme4) | $99.99 @ Amazon 
**Memory** | [G.Skill Ripjaws Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f312800cl9d8gbrl) | $34.99 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $69.99 @ NCIX US 
**Video Card** | [MSI GeForce GTX 660 Ti 2GB Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-video-card-n660tipe2gd5oc) | $299.99 @ Amazon 
**Case** | [Cooler Master HAF 912 ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-case-rc912kkn1) | $49.49 @ SuperBiiz 
**Power Supply** | [Corsair Builder 500W 80 PLUS Certified ATX12V Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-power-supply-cmpsu500cxv2) | $41.98 @ Newegg 
**Monitor** | [Acer G215HVAbd 21.5" Monitor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/acer-monitor-etwg5hpa07) | $119.99 @ Newegg 
**Keyboard** | [Microsoft 2VJ-00001 Wireless Standard Keyboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/microsoft-keyboard-2vj00001) | $19.86 @ Amazon 
 | | **Total**
 | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available. | $826.27

My headset is a Sennheiser PC 151. http://www.sennheiserusa.com/pc151

Also the front panel audio does not work either. When something is plugged in my computer turns the front panel on and off.

Here is a sample of what my mic sounds like: http://dl.dropbox.com/u/7912305/soundtest.mp3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 16:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you heard of Super Monday Night Combat? (Super MNC on steam). It's a third person MOBA but it has some different elements like tagging instead of last hitting. I think it's really fun even though the community is basically dead already and the people that are left are either really good or suck. Anyway here is a TotalBiscuit if you want to know more: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ixl6yOde-58 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 16:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think the 1.8 update was the best one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 15:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I build Vi I focus on getting as much attack speed as possible. I start in the jungle and build Triforce first. If they don't have much magic damage on their team I get Berserker's. Then I build Zephyr, Frozen Mallet,  Phantom Dancer, and Infinity Edge to replace Wriggle's Lantern if the game gets that far. She gets about 270 damage and 2.3 attack speed (with her passive) with that build. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Looks Like A Great Way To Build Vi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 11:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 23:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep Warchamp and friends have a bad reputation from their Minecraft griefing. Wouldn't touch this client with a ten foot pole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 01:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  #3232;\_ #3232; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 03:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh...not so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 20:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DIS I LIKE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 19:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the new keyboard in WP8 is awesome. I once typed out a whole sentence by just using suggestions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 18:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Surface Pro will be your friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-01 22:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> InstantAction was so fun back in the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 07:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made a WP7 game a couple weeks after it launched and my app launched from the same place you left it no matter how you launched it. I programmed it all in. What I did was save the entire game state before it got tombstoned. Whenever it got launched again, if there was a saved state, it would launch from that state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anybody tried playing Battlefield 3 multiplayer for PC recently? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 08:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried connecting to Battlefield servers today and I actually got it to connect to servers repeatedly today. This is how I got it to work.

1. Try to join a game with a ping of 25 or over.
2. Once the game icon appears on the taskbar click on it.
3. The game windows will pop up and will flash loading in the bottom right corner and then disappear. The game window will be completely black now.
4. After a couple of seconds the game window should close and you should get the error no reply from server. This was the error that was happening before and should only happen the first time you try to connect to a server this way.
5. Repeat steps 1-3 again with a different server except this time after the game window flashes loading it will stay black for a couple of seconds then the map loading screen should come up. This means you are actually in the server.

These steps seem to work most of the time. Sometimes you don't need to click on the game icon on your taskbar for it to work. However sometimes the game does not connect if you do not click on the icon. I've tried connecting to the same server with out clicking on the icon and it doesn't connect but if I try connecting to that server again and do click on the icon it does connect so you should just click on the icon every time. I also have Go to game when ready checked but that should make no difference.

If anybody else has the game for PC and is having issues try the steps I listed above. It you do get the game to work please post back here. Also if you still cannot get the game to work please still post here with what error(s) you are getting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 01:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys it's Microsoft Word/Office 2010 for Macs. You should probably xpost this to /r/apple to get more help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 05:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **BUTTHOLE GUY BELOW** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 20:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has the Intel HD Graphics 4000 in it. Apparently they don't suck as bad as they used to.  
http://www.notebookcheck.net/Intel-HD-Graphics-4000.69168.0.html  
http://www.notebookcheck.net/Intel-HD-Graphics-4000-Benchmarked.73567.0.html  
You can run any Source game fine on it probably. Any of the COD games except maybe BL2 fine. BF3 will probably be a no go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 23:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Order Time**: Wednesday, November 7th, 1:10 AM

**Order Method**: Online (Business Premiere)

**Color**: Matte Cyan

**Shipping Status**: Unknown (Preprocessing)

**Shipping Method**: Unknown  
____________________________________________________________
So I ordered the phone as soon as it went up online. It was a little weird for me because I have a University discount applied to my account so I had to order through Premier. I ordered Cyan and they said it should arrive on the Friday of the official launch. On Friday I called AT T and they said that it was still processing and to wait. On Monday it still had not arrived and I called them again and they said my phone was on backorder and could take anywhere from 2 days to 2 weeks to get to me.

After I heard that I basically said fuck that, cancelled the pre-order, walked down to the Microsoft Store near my dorm to try to get the 920 in Cyan. They were also out of stock so I settled for the Matte Black instead. I love the phone but I still wish I could get it in cyan.

Another thing AT T messed up on was my phone transfer. Apparently I lost messaging when I switched devices so I had to contact them again and they had to reactivate messaging for my phone even though I didn't change my plan at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 09:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When ordering the phone a box popped up saying that to get the wireless charging plate you had to select the Black Wireless Charging Plate as an accessory. In the final checkout the cost of the charging plate was subtracted completely so that it was free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 07:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldnt preorder the 920 earlier tonight so I called Customer Service and they said I could not order the phone until Friday. Contacted Live Chat and they said to wait a couple minutes and then it started working. Preordered the 920 in cyan with the free charging plate for $99! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 19:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just called Best Buy to see if they would do the price match and they will not so cancel your Best Buy orders and pre-order through AT T! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 19:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure they will only be showing off Microsoft Surfaces at Microsoft Stores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 22:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI: The Google Search app does not support Windows RT. I was trying to download it onto my Surface but it wouldn't show up. I found a direct link to link to the store and it said this app does not support your device. Kind of annoying, hopefully Google supports it in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-27 22:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got to the Microsoft Store in Boston right as it opened at 8 and i was number 54 in line. I think there were a max of maybe 60 before I got my Surface. I think some people got there at midnight thinking the store would open then and had been waiting there all night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 21:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked one up at the Microsoft Store today. I love it already. However I need a real laptop replacement so I'm going to return this and get the Surface Pro when it comes out. The build quality is one of the best I've seen on any device. No OEM will probably be able to match the Surface Pro. It will definitely be a day one purchase for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 21:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked one up at the Microsoft Store today. I love it already. However I need a real laptop replacement so I'm going to return this and get the Surface Pro when it comes out. The build quality is one of the best I've seen on any device. No OEM will probably be able to match the Surface Pro. It will definitely be a day one purchase for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 06:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18 Male

Go to college in Boston so that makes me kind of interesting! Also I like talking to people! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 22:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's because OEM's didn't want the Surface Pro to compete with their subpar hardware at launch. Why get a shitter OEM tablet at $1000 when you can get a well designed and manufactured Surface Pro for the same price? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 01:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. Better than other phones. Weren't anything too spectacular. I did like the built in kickstand. However the build quality sucks and I had it replaced 3 times. Can't wait to get the 920. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 01:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been waiting a long time for this. Bought a HTC Surround a week after launch and now pre-ordered the 920 in cyan for the WP8 launch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Complete] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 04:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jdbH) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jdbH/by_merchant/) / [Benchmarks](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jdbH/benchmarks/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [AMD Phenom II X4 965 Black 3.4GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/amd-cpu-hdz965fbgmbox) | $89.99 @ Newegg 
**Motherboard** | [ASRock 970 EXTREME4 ATX  AM3+ Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-970extreme4) | $99.99 @ Amazon 
**Memory** | [G.Skill Ripjaws Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f312800cl9d8gbrl) | $34.99 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $69.99 @ NCIX US 
**Video Card** | [MSI GeForce GTX 660 Ti 2GB Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-video-card-n660tipe2gd5oc) | $299.99 @ Amazon 
**Case** | [Cooler Master HAF 912 ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-case-rc912kkn1) | $49.49 @ SuperBiiz 
**Power Supply** | [Corsair Builder 500W 80 PLUS Certified ATX12V Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-power-supply-cmpsu500cxv2) | $41.98 @ Newegg 
**Monitor** | [Acer G215HVAbd 21.5" Monitor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/acer-monitor-etwg5hpa07) | $119.99 @ Newegg 
**Keyboard** | [Microsoft 2VJ-00001 Wireless Standard Keyboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/microsoft-keyboard-2vj00001) | $19.86 @ Amazon 
 | | **Total**
 | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available. | $826.27

After about 2 and a half hours I built my first [computer](http://imgur.com/a/uQ9NF#0)! I bought the [parts](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/comments/10upe0/build_help_900_gaming_build/) this Wednesday and everything arrived today. I got a little help from people in my dorm but the best feeling was when it started up with no problems. I'm still installing Windows but hopefully no issues come up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Help] $900 Gaming Build </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 04:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [PCPartPicker part list](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jdbH) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jdbH/by_merchant/) / [Benchmarks](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jdbH/benchmarks/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [AMD Phenom II X4 965 Black 3.4GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/amd-cpu-hdz965fbgmbox) | $89.99 @ Newegg 
**Motherboard** | [ASRock 970 EXTREME4 ATX  AM3+ Motherboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/asrock-motherboard-970extreme4) | $99.99 @ Amazon 
**Memory** | [G.Skill Ripjaws Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f312800cl9d8gbrl) | $34.99 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 1TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st1000dm003) | $69.99 @ NCIX US 
**Video Card** | [MSI GeForce GTX 660 Ti 2GB Video Card](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/msi-video-card-n660tipe2gd5oc) | $299.99 @ Amazon 
**Case** | [Cooler Master HAF 912 ATX Mid Tower Case](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/cooler-master-case-rc912kkn1) | $49.49 @ SuperBiiz 
**Power Supply** | [Corsair Builder 500W 80 PLUS Certified ATX12V Power Supply](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/corsair-power-supply-cmpsu500cxv2) | $41.98 @ Newegg 
**Monitor** | [Acer G215HVAbd 21.5" Monitor](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/acer-monitor-etwg5hpa07) | $119.99 @ Newegg 
**Keyboard** | [Microsoft 2VJ-00001 Wireless Standard Keyboard](http://pcpartpicker.com/part/microsoft-keyboard-2vj00001) | $19.86 @ Amazon 
 | | **Total**
 | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available. | $826.27

Hi! I have been thinking about building a PC for a little while now because I have a really old laptop and would like something better to use while at my desk in my dorm. I started with this basic build from [here](http://www.choosemypc.net/build/?budget=650 usage=gaming form=microatx oc=false) and adjusted it where I though I should. Some thoughts:

CPU: I wanted a quad-core CPU instead of a dual core because I also want to do some in game recording (Dxtory).
EDIT: Moved to an AMD CPU because it is cheaper

Storage: Only a regular HDD instead of adding a SSD also because I don't really feel like I need an SSD. [Here](http://pcpartpicker.com/p/jcw7) is another look at this list with an SSD.

Video Card: Went for the 7950 instead of the 7850 and took out the SSD option. See link above.
EDIT: Changed to the GTX 660 Ti after some recommendations. Also I heard you get Borderlands 2 for free with it.

Optical Drive: I don't even really want to buy this because I only have 1 game I need to install by CD which is Flight Simulator X.
EDIT: I don't really need a CD drive anymore.

Monitor: I need a monitor. I almost have no preference besides the bigger the better.

Keyboard: I would prefer a wireless keyboard.

This list will probably be updated soon after getting a couple more people to look over it. Thanks for all the help!

EDIT: Some changes. Also went with a ATX Mid Tower instead of a mATX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 13:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still waiting to hear about a tablet that comes with a dedicated graphics card inside its dock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 22:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nokia Lumia 920 all the way. I currently have the HTC Surround and that phone let me down a lot. WP7 OS was amazing but HTC made a really bad phone. I'm not taking my chances again and I'm going straight for Nokia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 19:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  #3232;\_ #3232;

NSFW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 22:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boxers or briefs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 03:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSFW: Penis dipped in Nutella. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It seems like you guys focus on babies way too much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 05:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah babies can be annoying but not having kids also means you don't have teenagers! I'm 18 and I'm 95% sure I'm not going to have kids. Not because I hate babies but I don't want to raise another me. I really don't want to deal with a teenage version of me. I don't hate teenagers, I just wouldn't want to raise one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 06:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disney: Gravity Falls, Nick: The Legend of Korra, Cartoon Network: Adventure Time, Regular Show, The Amazing World of Gumball.

I never stopped watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 06:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I just bought Anamanaguchi's album Dawn Metropolis. It's awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 01:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HTC Surround with Windows Phone 7. Awesome OS, the phone hardware is shit. Going to buy a Nokia Windows Phone 8 when they come out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 00:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need a cell phone for my job...I need a cellphone for contacting my parents, my brothers, other people. It's probably because you are 13 that you don't really need one. You stay close to home and there is always somebody else with a phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 02:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All these people are good because most of them if not all of them use massive air. Without it they would still be really good...but still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 04:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HTC phones don't feel like they came out of cereal box but they certainly have the insides of one. My HTC Surround has way too many issues. I had to get 2 warranty replaces just because something broke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 01:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should only stop if you feel like it...yeah it's kind of weird. Personally I wouldn't do that at all because that's just me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 04:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The HTC Surround is a really terrible piece of shit too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 04:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a 4 on AP Calc AB and a 3 on AP Stats. Unfortunately my school only takes 4's and 5's and I was planning on taking Calc 1 in college anyway and wanted to skip Stats...sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 05:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked earlier and I didn't see it I guess. I checked again when I saw this post and it was there. I applied on a Windows 8 Release Preview machine and it still went though. I am so excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-04 17:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assault is just on sale right now. He will probably go up to the 6750 price soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 04:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Rhode Island and we have this exact system. Does it really change anything...not really. Once you get your limited drivers licence people treat it like a full license anyway. Drive all their friends, drive while distracted, drive while drunk. Parents don't care about the times when their child can drive at all.

What this law is really doing is basically trying to make up for shitty parents and kids who don't follow the rules. If a child knew driving while texting is idiotic and that driving while drunk should never ever ever be done we would be fine but that doesn't happen. Peer pressure doesn't help with this either.

It also doesn't change the fact that older drivers suck at driving too and how easy it is to get a license once you turn 18. In Rhode island once you turn 18 you can go to the DMV take the computerized test (it's really easy, most of it is just what sign is this). Get your learners permit. Take the road test 2 months later. Pass the ridiculous road test (apparently one of my friends passed even though he did a rolling stop at 3 stop signs and that is supposed to be an instant fail). Then you are perfectly good to drive. Why is it when I turn 18 I'm magically better than my 17 years, 11 months, and 30 days former self? This act sounds like a good idea but doesn't really fix the issue. It's like putting a small band-aid on a gash wound. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 04:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from the Incredibles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 00:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost...if they didn't rename windows explorer to file explorer. The Metro side of Windows 8 still lets users see files. They are just trying to make it less confusing for basic users (grandmothers). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 04:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Fuck wasps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 05:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have scoliosis too but I only found out when i was like 16 but I probably had it since 15 or 14. I wore a brace for like 1.5 years (16 hours a day, every day) then stopped wearing it because 1. it sucks and 2. it was getting too small for me so it hurt really fucking bad. I just went to the doctor again like 2 weeks ago and its about 49 degrees which is really bad but they don't want to do surgery and since I'm basically done growing they said I'm probably good. Also I'm a guy and guys get it like never so that was fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 05:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of. It was the iD Gaming Camp at Harvard University for Programming for the Xbox 360 (C#/XNA). I'm guessing it would be a little different than a regular tech camp cause we stayed overnight for 2 weeks.

Anyway it was fun. It really would depend on what you are doing also. For mine we started slow by learning basic programming and progressed from there. I already knew a lot about C# and XNA so I helped other students during that time. We also had a final project and the Friday of the first week I got to start my final project early because I basically knew everything they were teaching. Everybody in the class made a final project but they were all very similar because the teacher was stepping though the project and students could make art changes or code changes they were comfortable with.

Since it also was a gaming camp we played lots of games. Basically our day was wake up at Emmanuel College (that's where we were staying), walk to the T, ride the T to Harvard, eat breakfast, work for like 2 hours, have an outside break for like an hour, eat lunch, work for about 3 hours, then have gaming time for like 2 hours. Then we took the T back to Emmanuel and hung out there till lights out.

It was fun. We made friends quickly. There were 3 other sections besides mine, Level Building with UDK, Map Making with Starcraft 2, and Model Making with Maya. There were about 50 kids (13-18) in total. Also I was 17 so I was older than basically everybody. Our counselors were pretty cool and they were all either in college or just out of college but they knew their stuff.

**TL;DR It was fun. I had fun. I did get to work on something I enjoy. And you will have fun!**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 20:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my third year working at a state park as a ranger. However my mom did work at the main office for the department and that's how I got my job there.

I did also land a job as technical support at my college for the school year. They sent me a letter saying they were looking to hire freshmen. I was like what the heck doesn't hurt to apply. I did really well on the phone interview and I did pretty well on the in person interview and I got hired.

Just look around and apply wherever you can because it doesn't hurt to try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 02:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I main Sin and it is extremely annoying how her most powerful skill (grapple) makes her completely exposed. She loses cloak and her grapple times are extremely long. Spark was basically fine because his skill was being able to deal a lot of main fire damage. Sin and Wascot should have been buffed up to his level instead of Spark being brought down to their level. They can still dominate if played effectively but any class can do that. If a team has even a shred of intelligence they will stick together and commandos can't do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 01:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only annoying when I am like 8 and 1 and have the most bot kills on the team (100-150) and my bottom 1 or 2 are like 0/6 and 50 bot kills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 03:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a magician and a ninja: http://www.youtube.com/user/azoazotube </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Senior Tile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 23:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 03:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's only $5! That's not a lot" 30 games later... "Oh god what have I done?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-07 03:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toodaloo eachotherfuckers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 22:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with 1.5 margins as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 02:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch Dogs was played on the next gen console called the PC. [True story.](https://twitter.com/miladesn/status/209795736479604737) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 04:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard this many times from my college counselors this year. It isn't all about your GPA. Why would a school accept all really smart kids. The school wouldn't be diverse at all (not just the race way). Colleges want a whole range of kids, really smart kids, kids who play sports, theater kids, tech people. This does include people with lesser grades.

Hell, I got into NEU (Northeastern) with a pretty good scholarship and a 3.07 GPA but I have lots of game programming experience I showed them. I guess that helped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-25 20:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many 12 year old can afford a server. Very few due to their parents. I assume many more abusive admins are the "fat stash" adults than kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-25 19:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It would seem, from a natural point of view, that baby animals would be seen as an easy source of food.. yet for some reason all we want to do is hug them.

We want to hug them to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-20 15:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got this phone originally a week after Windows Phone launched launch so my contact is almost up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 20:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah mine freezes and reboots randomly sometimes too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else have huge problems with the HTC Surround? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 01:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently on my 3th phone because of numerous problems. First time my charging port stopped working. Second time my phone would not boot past the HTC loading screen. Now on this phone the screen gets random phantom touches near the bottom of the screen which can hit the start button. I can't replace it this time because my warranty ran out. The OS is great, but the phone hardware is not as good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 16:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ #3232;\_ #3232;](http://i.imgur.com/yGLdC.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 00:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have over 600 hours on BF3. I stopped playing though after a patch gone wrong. It was fun however and well worth the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 23:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cranston, Rhode Island </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 23:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you dropped your phone it would break the concrete on the sidewalk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 22:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Push one lane while the other team is distracted with the other lane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-12 16:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also forgot. Don't die, don't die, don't ever die. Dying feeds the other team and late into the game it take a very long time to respawn so don't die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
