<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7383</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rolling for the Bioshock Infinite season pass.

[Steam profile as proof I don't have anywhere near 250 games] (http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198101335103/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy birthday!

I'm unoriginal so my ID is [subject7383] (http://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198101335103/) (you'll have to click the link because I'm so unoriginal that someone else has the same name as me on Steam)  
I'd like the [season pass for Bioshock Infinite.] (http://store.steampowered.com/app/214933/)

Also on the off chance I win I'd like to request you pick another person with a game $40 since you seem to be willing to spend $60. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 04:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're interested in more (kinda) like this there's [.baxter.] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SbOCTl8J6uo) which is another band Tim McIlrath (vocals for The Killing Tree and Rise Against) was involved with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 00:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I start grad school (and get a salary) in about 6 months, so it seems like a bit of a waste to buy a stereo amp then have to buy a 5.1/7.1 amp in just 6 months; I was thinking the same speakers for FR and FL, and the smaller Covo-S for the rears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Working in a terminal-esque environment is a big reason I upgraded too.

If you're willing to risk doing some damage I've seen some people mod their monitors to be VESA mountable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually familiar with him; I can't quite justify the audiophile setup with an amp, sub, and 5 speakers yet, even if I listen to the Zelda Symphony and SotC soundtracks all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 06:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I just did the same thing,] (http://www.reddit.com/r/AverageBattlestations/comments/302w4f/added_2_monitors/) huge difference! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 14:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a bit awkward at times having to look up to see the upper third of documents/webpages. But if I'm running a math program or processing data on it it's less noticable.

I may upgrade the central monitor to 27-32" down the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 04:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MOBO: MSI X99S SLI Plus ATX LGA2011-3 Motherboard  
CPU: Intel Xeon E5-2603 V3 1.6GHz 6-Core Processor  
RAM: Crucial Ballistix Sport 4GB (1 x 4GB) DDR4-2400 Memory  
Storage: 3TB Seagate HDD, and a 120GB Samsung 840EVO SSD  
GPU: EVGA GTX 760 4GB  
PSU: EVGA SuperNOVA NEX 750W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX  
Case: Corsair Air 540  ATX Mid  
Keyboard: Logitech K120 (not into mechanical)  
Mouse: Gigabyte GM-M6800 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 02:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Wallpapers] (http://imgur.com/a/3S1pF)

Getting an L desk, chair, and speakers when I move in August; if anyone can suggest anything I'd be grateful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Added 2 Monitors! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 01:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 05:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the extra input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 04:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The speakers are actually integrated into the monitors, I suppose I should've placed the circles within the monitors. There's only 1 3.5mm audio in port for each monitor.  
I already have 2 male-male 3.5mm cables, so if I were to get the cable you linked I'd be able to do it, right?

I'm no audiophile, but would a pair of [$10 USB speakers] (http://www.amazon.com/Logitech-S150-Speakers-Digital-Sound/dp/B000ZH98LU) be *that* much of an improvement over integrated monitor sound? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 02:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actually planning on upgrading to [a cheap-ish 5.1 system] (http://www.amazon.com/dp/B003VAK1FA/ref=wl_it_dp_o_pC_nS_ttl?_encoding=UTF8 colid=26CXL2VK9HMW coliid=I12DLQ5W2WPTIT), but I'm moving for grad school soon and wanted to wait until then, hence the PS in OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 00:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I scoured the internet and came up with a handful of similar solutions using cable splitters and 3.5mm/RCA converters, but I figured that since I already have sound data being sent to each monitor there may be some way to split it via software. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using two monitors with built in speakers as independent left/right stereo speakers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 00:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I just got 2 new monitors which have built in speakers, they're flanking a central monitor and I'd like to set each one to output left/right sound only, I figured this may be confusing, so here's [this diagram to help out a bit.] (http://imgur.com/GnRqiSD) What I want is for the left and right monitors to act as separate stereo speakers, "left" sound would play through LL and LR, and "right" sound would play through RL and RR.  
I have a general idea of how I could do this using cables and splitters, but I'd rather just use what I have.

* Windows 8.1  
* MOBO integrated sound (X99 chipset)
* Monitors connected digitally to graphics card (GTX 760)
* One monitor connected via HDMI, other via DisplayPort (both to graphics card)

I tried using Virtual Audio Cable; although I could get both monitors to output audio simultaneously, I couldn't get it to separate properly.

Thanks for any help!

PS: I'm aware buying separate speakers would produce better sound quality, but I can't justify the cost of an entertainment-only buy.

EDIT: Added diagram to ease understanding

EDIT2: To anyone with the same question, it looks like it's not possible via software alone; /u/Feltz- offered an easy physical alternative below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 20:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something along the lines of Stockholm Syndrome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 06:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just excited that my learning and teaching really interesting things isn't gonna indebt me anymore.  
That might not be a good thing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 04:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense I suppose. I would be too distracted to even manage a spreadsheet on the bus let alone my usual work so I didn't think of it out of the scope of email and reading documents.  

Thanks for the input! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ...have been used in **behavioral science** for quite some time. They are pretty *useful when you want to talk about the sexual orientation of people whose gender is unknown or irrelevant*.

In the context of a journal publication I'd rather see "a sample set of gynephilic individuals were evaluated under..." than "a sample set including heterosexual males, homosexual females, bisexual ... [three pages of academic jargon for people who like women]." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 18:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you (or anyone else) explain the reasoning behind using expensive subnotebooks (not just Apple) for these sort of situations rather than just a tablet?

I'm genuinely curious as to how people utilize these sorts of laptops designed solely for travel use; it seems to be a pretty popular choice but I can't wrap my head around it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 18:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obsession with a minimalist aesthetic I guess.  
On the upside, USB C is pretty cool (and open!). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you end up utilizing all of that space? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 22:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what was used; [This video] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AgWDMPfvXSg) uses [TCCA](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trichloroisocyanuric_acid) and has a minimal description of what happens.  
It seems it could also be calcium hypochlorate tablets, in which case it reacts with the water to form calcium ions, chlorine gas, and oxygen gas (as well as some side reactins oxidizing the alcohol/producing chloroalkanes).

This is a pretty stupid idea in either case, as the fumes are dangerous. A half-as-stupid option would be dry ice, where you still get the desired boom without the noxious fumes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 01:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit's Markdown automatically assigns ordering so if you're making a list and delete some parts it doesn't ruin everything. Check my source on this, it's kinda neat:

2. 
7. 
7. 
945. 
42.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 23:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anyone has any extra monitors sitting around I could use the extra screen(s). Also if anyone is getting rid of single arm VESA mounts I'd be more than willing to take that too.  
I'd regift after my thesis is done in August. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buying Advice: Acer V236HL or Asus vS238H-P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 10:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone,

I'm in the market to buy 2 1080p monitors to flank my Acer H236HL. I needed them to be 23 inches, VESA mountable, and $150 each; I have it narrowed down to 2 monitors:

Acer V236HL  
or  
Asus VS238H-P


Use:  
I'll be doing a bit of document/infographic design with InDesign (not professionally, so I don't need 99% Adobe color space), viewing multiple scientific articles (double column format), writing word docs and plotting data, but most importantly, triple monitor gaming (GTX 760 w/ 4G VRAM, mostly RPGs); I imagine I'll be switching them between portrait and landscape regularly while procrastinating on my thesis.


Does anyone have any advice on which of these two (or any others) I should go with, or suggestions for easily pivotable VESA mount arms?

Edit: On the off chance anyone stumbles across this and is curious, I ended up not getting either since I didn't realize they were both TN panels.  
I went with an Asus PB238Q. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 06:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/buildmeapc would be very helpful if you have a general idea.

Things seem to be on the cusp of a change for hardware.  
Someone else mentioned monitors and waiting on buying 4K, I agree with him; I'd buy a 1080 or 1440 screen for now and plunge for 4K when DisplayPort 1.3 and HDMI 2.0 hit and G-Sync/FreeSync are more common and there are more with IPS $800 (which would mean maybe saving a bit of money on a GPU, getting a 780 or 970 now and spending the extra money on more monitors).

NVidia's Pascal architecture will be coming out sometime next year and I suppose 4K gaming will be commonplace then, you could possibly even do multi-4K displays on just one card ([right now it takes 3 980s](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jt5oE0gpnnk)). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 05:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shadow of Mordor was really well optimized.  
Bioshock Infinite was as well, and I thought it had the best story out of any of that series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 05:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on a *really* tight budget this time last year and got a Lenovo U510 refurbished for a bit under $400. The screen is 768 but it has a 1TB HDD and a 24GB SSD (they don't put the OS on the SSD though).

I was able to play stuff like Portal 1   2 and Skyrim on it in my down time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 21:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if these answer your question as to a brewing process, but here are a couple interesting links.  

[Computational chemistry paper on cations in coffee.] (http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/jf501687c)  
[ACS Undergrad web post, which has a bit of info about roasting (and decaffeination if you're a masochist).] (https://acsundergrad.wordpress.com/2013/02/27/a-cup-of-coffee-for-the-chemists/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 19:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm not; don't be condescending.

What I was building to was an example where two viewpoints could be represented. Take this case where [an artist had a disagreement with the record company publishing their album,] (http://www.billboard.com/biz/articles/news/1083961/streetlight-manifesto-flips-off-victory-records-to-release-acoustic) there are three parties to consider: a fan who pirates the album, the band themselves, and the record company.

1. The fans' act of pirating the data (the album), according to your guidelines is morally reprehensible as it takes away *their* money. "Them" is ill-defined, but since the counter-argument often defines "them" as the artists, we'll look at their case next.
2. The band members themselves, the creators of the data: in this instance, the producers of the data are at odds with the publishers regarding the withholding of revenue (whether they are entitled to revenue from this data, and how much, is an entirely separate argument). They *advocated* fans pirating their album or buy it directly from them. From their standpoint, fans pirating is a positive, as it lessens the hold that the publisher held on them; the fan would be stealing from thieves. Regardless of the reason for the fans' piracy and the dispute itself, no loss of revenue would be incurred due to the creators of the data, this is morally neutral to the creators, as per your rules. 
3. The record company: the publishing corporation obviously considers fans pirating as a negative, as it "takes away" their capital.

Shades of grey don't only apply to the well-used example of "a man's wife is dying, money is sparse, does he steal the medicine?"

Different parties are affected in different ways, and view the act in different lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 18:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a post on the GradCafe concerning this topic.] (http://forum.thegradcafe.com/blog/53/entry-452-all-about-interviews-experiences-for-the-gc-minions/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 07:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So disregarding the aspect of theft - be it infinitesimal or zero - the basis of the argument is justification of the action?   
Wouldn't you agree that varies with the frame of reference (even for things that obviously aren't necessities)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 06:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're arguing moral absolutism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
