<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4555</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't see anything in the future new things happen every day that take us by surprise and completely change our perspectives. Even if you don't see it, do you want it? There are endless options out there, if being a pilot doesn't work out there are still so many opportunities to travel. You see yourself as a loner, so put yourself out there! Talk to people, we all fail at conversations or mess up with women occasionally but being able to brush it off is something that you need to learn to do. You can find people your compatible with no matter what, look for groups who are interested in the same kind of things you are.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write out a list of things you want to do. Do them one at time and check them off the list. Enjoy yourself, go out talk to random people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just how expensive groceries were.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to be much more specific. Start asking yourself big questions. Would you just be happy as a pilot? Do you want to settle down have any sort of family? Would you be willing to give up family to be a pilot? My uncle used to be a pilot in the air force and moved on to be a commercial pilot, he has a family but he only sees them a few months out of the year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hit the books. Random walk down Wallstreet is a great intro. Also the first book I read on investing and I loved it. http://www.amazon.com/Random-Walk-Down-Wall-Street/dp/0393340740/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1367820864 sr=8-1 keywords=random+walk+down+wall+street </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-06 08:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't go wrong with simplicity. A close friend of mine got simply the word hope tattooed on her wrist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
