<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1535</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 09:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderfalls
Middleman
Pushing Daisies
Carnivale
Hannibal
Bella and the Bulldogs
Utopia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably my all-time favourite Gaiman book. You should check out his earlier graphic novel, 'The Tragical Comedy or Comical Tragedy of Mr. Punch,' as it strikes a similar chord. 

As for other authors, Anna-Marie McLemore is good at creating that same lilting, dreamlike quality. Especially in her latest book, 'When the Moon Was Ours.' Erin Morgenstern and Stephanie Garber channeled similar tones in both 'The Night Circus' and 'Caraval,' respectively. Also great is Diane Setterfield's 'The Thirteenth Tale.'  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Cosby makes ALA history as the first person to have books challenged because of authorship and not content </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually really like the Cormoran Strike books, they're a good reminder that Rowling actually writes a well-plotted mystery. (Though I thought the third book was a bit too long even though I liked that Robin was getting more of a showcase.) 

But in terms of more contemporary authors I think Jasper Fforde is doing interesting stuff with the genre and his approach to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://ew.com/article/2016/06/20/penny-dreadful-series-finale-john-logan/

Showtime didn't cancel it as much as John Logan, the creator, decided he wanted season 3 to be the last. Probably because he was tired of writing the whole series and getting very little recognition for how good the performances and writing was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this one's better than her previous trilogy, so definitely get to it a fast as you can. I've been stretching out my read of it because I don't want it to end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
