<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7496</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 22:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right that progression may be slower after basic upgrades but even with them it is possible to get good score like 15k diamonds also I didn't want ppl to end game (maybe not end but satisfactory score and all achievements) too fast ;)

Thank you for nice words </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 09:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. I wasn't sure how to categorize it ;)

Thanks for commenting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 00:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Game is free.

I've made it with help of my girlfriend and CC0 graphics from Kenney.nl
It took me almost 2 months. It is a mix of RTS   Tower Defense games. 

The iOS version is coming next week.

Video with gameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hIdypOh4AR0

Feedback appreciated.
Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DEV] Aliens vs Bugs: our new RTS / Tower Defense indie game. We hope you like it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 00:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-22 11:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Q1 - rand() % 100 gives you form 0 to 99

Q2 - just store time at start and take difference from now

Q3 - it depends on IDE, but usually 'release' builds work this way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-21 23:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on type of minigame, few of them I may easily play with 1 hand. Anyway I have in mind few tricks that will make playing with 1 hand easier. Thank you for the review. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 17:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I've crossed them out. I've send you code. Sorry for problems and thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 14:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Honest review.

* I may add it, at all it make sense to allow everybody name the pet however he/she wants.

* Sound can be disabled/enabled in settings. I used http://www.bfxr.net/ it looks almost the same.

* I personally like fullscreen games, but I'll try to solve it by adding option in settings to enable/disable fullscreen.

* I did it 'by design' to all games that have arrows. I thought that it is better. I'll review all games and reconsider it.

* Good point. It may be nice to blink 1 or 2 times.

Thank you for all these notes! They are really helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
