<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8089</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm.  My top 3 steakhouse salads:  Wedge salad with tomatoes, bleu cheese and bacon; spinach salad with hard boiled eggs, mushrooms, and bacon; Caesar salad with homemade dressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People call me lazy, tell me I'm faking it, say it's all in my head, tell me to "just sleep more", etc. I try to explain it to people, but almost nobody will listen. To them, I look fine, and thus must be fine.

There's an ugly idea that's held by far too many people.  They believe that somehow, because they once knew (or heard a story about) a malingerer or drama queen, that all people with disabilities, mental illnesses, and other chronic and "invisible" conditions are contemptible loafers who are taking advantage of privileges and accommodations they neither need nor deserve.

Worse, it seems that individuals who feel this way also seem to have appointed themselves as judge and jury on the matter and they feel that every person who has such a condition must **prove** or affirmatively legitimize their conditions in order to be accorded the appropriate levels of respect, compassion, and accommodation.

It's one of the nastier common manifestations of the [just-world hypothesis (or fallacy)](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Just-world_hypothesis), and it's a really shitty way to treat people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that's known as "early Spring in the northern hemisphere." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but they *do* appear to be an accurate representation of the typical inferior quality product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your relevant username is much improved by the fact that the account is over 5 years old.  Way to play the long game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't ***remember*** commenting in this thread already... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A combination of weed, focusing on other more interesting things, and 3:30 a.m. existential crises.

Beef jerky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. What do you predict will be the bottom-line outcome for people such as myself who are Medicaid eligible only due to its expansion under the ACA?  IOW, what do you think will my coverage options and costs will look like when this is all said and done?

2. Assuming, based on what I've read so far, that I should expect to be among those hardest hit by the repeal of ACA and enactment of AHCA, *when* should I expect that my son and I will lose coverage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not 100%, no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 07:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Some*, sure.  They are a distinct minority, comprising fewer than 25-30% of all women, and by some estimates, much fewer than that.  Because what many researchers now believe is that even women who can have orgasms "solely" from vaginal penetration are *actually* achieving the orgasm from indirect clitoral stimulation of the very long nerve endings that extend down and away from the clitoris, reaching behind the vaginal wall and not from the mythical and wildly popular, but wholly unproveable, "G spot."

The reality is that very, very few women can have an orgasm without any clitoral stimulation at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's get the easy one out of the way.  Yes, you used who/whom correctly there.

As to your real question, I can definitely see the ambiguity you're referring to.  All I can say is, if you had been in the room with this guy, there wouldn't have been any doubt in your mind about who was the perpetrator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is suggesting to suppress or hold in a sneeze, merely to refrain from screaming as the sneeze is expelled.

Some people have a (very correctable) habit of "voicing" their sneezes.  It's extremely jarring and extremely preventable with no ill effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was *literally* the bill of goods he was attempting to sell us.  How do you know Vince? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 05:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  God I hate people.

Basically.

My stepmother was an ER nurse and I worked for my state's department of motor vehicles for 8 years.

Between the tragic stories I heard from my stepmother over the dinner table as I was growing up about young people dying in vain, and the breathtakingly ignorant comments I have heard from people renewing their driver's licenses when they have to answer the organ donor question, it makes me want to punch people in the throat when I hear them start in with their uninformed, harmful bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 04:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no longer a young person, and it's clear my opinion is an unpopular one in this thread, but maybe it's exactly because of my older age and, therefore, different historical perspective, that I feel compelled to chime in.

To be clear, I don't use it as an umbrella term for gender and sexual minority individuals as a collective....I use it to refer to my individual sexuality, and I believe that for that purpose, the words that sound and feel most right to me are the words I should be able to use.

I wholeheartedly understand the myriad reasons why "queer" is (and long has been) controversial within the LGBTQ community.  I also have come to understand that younger generations of non-heterosexual people sometimes use the term differently from how I would.  Nevertheless, I am a 41 year-old woman who has identified as queer for a rather long time despite understanding how fraught with complications the term may be, and I would like to share my reasons for this choice.

Many of you probably know, but maybe some don't, that [the movement to reclaim "queer" away from being a slur began in the late 80s. It was a somewhat militant reaction to the AIDS crisis among a certain segment of young LGBT people at the time.](http://www.uapress.ua.edu/product/Reclaiming-Queer,5850.aspx)

I am a product of those times, and the notion of reclaiming a term that resonates with me on many levels has always been appealing.  "Queer," for me, has had other added benefits, not the least of which is accuracy and authenticity.

I am a woman who has been involved in more relationships with women than with men over the course of my life.  I have known I was sexually and romantically attracted to other women since before puberty.

OTOH, at age 17, I entered into a what ended up being a 19-year relationship-turned-marriage to a man. During the course of the marriage, we raised a child together.  During the course of the marriage, I also continued to have romantic and sexual relationships with women.

My marriage ended in divorce when I was 37. Since then, I have been not been romantically or sexually involved with any men, and I don't plan to be in the foreseeable future.

However, it would be inaccurate, inauthentic, and dishonest of me to call myself a lesbian for a variety of reasons, my past and my potential (unknown) future being 2 of them.  A third is that, truthfully, there's a lot about me *and* my sexuality -- apart from my orientation toward women -- that *is* queer in the most mundane sense of that word, and I'm perfectly OK with letting people know that.

With that said, as a kinky/non-monogamous person myself, I don't know how I feel about the idea of kinky or poly, yet **heterosexual** people, also identifying as queer.  While I understand that being a kinkster or committed to polyamory can feel very much like an orientation, my gut reaction (even if it is gatekeeping) is that there is a qualitative difference between a person's preferred relationship structure/dynamic and one's sexual orientation.  So, if I had to take a stand today, I'd say that I agree about not liking the word being used by straight people.

Ultimately, I choose to proudly, consciously, identify as queer because it still resonates to me as political affiliation and also because it is the label that I believe most accurately describes me and my sexuality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex-husband did this every time he sneezed too, and also consistently denied doing it.

Like, how do you not **hear** that?  Between being rid of the scream-sneezing and the spitting everywhere, divorce has brought some unexpected, yet very welcome, benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack White and pretty much everything he's done, regardless of which project it's from, with the Raconteurs stuff being the biggest exception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here.  I think I might miss George Carlin even more, though. Even if his material had turned somewhat one-note and bitter as he approached the end of his life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not an organ donor because if you're in an accident and they see the organ donor symbol on your driver's license, they won't work as hard to save your life."

That's a lie that should be offensive to every first responder,  medical professional, or person who cares for one.  No EMT, nurse, or physician is looking through your wallet to see if they can *let you die based on your organ donor status* instead of trying to save you.  If your emergency team fails to save you, only after they've done absolutely 
everything they can, then they call in **a completely separate team of doctors to handle the organ harvesting and donation process**.

 
There are [tons of other harmful myths about organ donation](https://www.organdonor.gov/about/facts-terms/donation-myths-facts.html) that also make me want to scream, but none quite so much as this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that socioeconomic status is an important factor, but I'd be *very* curious to see how abstinence-only sex education curricula and the predominance of certain religious denominations correlates with this map's information.

As to Utah, the Mormons are exceptions to many demographic "rules"/trends; their low teen birth rate is undoubtedly attributable to numerous factors other than the type of sex education offered that are unique to their (unusually homogeneous) community and way of life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems completely predictable to me, since it actually appears to have less to do with urban vs. rural than it does with southern vs. eastern or western and/or locations where the available sex education curriculum is "abstinence only." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on an interview panel for some entry level positions with our state's department of motor vehicles.

One applicant, on his application under "reason for leaving" a particular former employer, wrote:  "Assault charge against supervisor." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 01:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, my poor first boyfriend.

We were both 16-year-old virgins; I wasn't really expecting all *that* much better than it actually was (*i.e.*, **very** brief and slightly painful), but then he couldn't help himself from asking:

"So, did you...ya know...um..."

"Orgasm?  You mean, did I have an orgasm?"

I paused for a minute so that I **didn't** say out loud the words in my head which were, "Yeah, sure I came in under 45 seconds without you so much as *looking at*, let alone touching, my clit.  You mean you missed the earth-shattering multiple orgasms?"

Instead, what I said was, "No, baby.  Not this time.  We can have fun trying again next time." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is just a shower thought, but here's the pedantic actual answer you probably weren't looking for:

The biggest difference is actually that in Mario, the stress is on the first syllable, and in Maria, the stress is on the middle syllable (the long 'ee' sound).

What I think you are referring to, though, is the fact that most English speakers have a tendency to use a schwa ("") in place of the "correct" vowel when pronouncing the *unstressed* syllable(s) of words.  The "" makes a neutral vowel sound that we, as native English speakers, perceive as corresponding to each of our 5 written vowels, depending on context.  This is why "Maria" sounds like "**Muh**-ree-ah" instead of "**Mah**-ree-ah."

EDIT: added final sentence to clarify. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My parents both have pretty significant mental health issues that affect their functioning in different ways.  They also had a chaotic, high-conflict separation and divorce that began when I was 7 months old and from which the ugliness lasted through my entire childhood, so there was **a lot** they both did wrong.

But, one thing that my mother, in particular, really did right was they way she approached sexuality and "body stuff" in general.  From an extremely young age, I knew that Mom wasn't going to freak out, no matter what question I asked her.  When my grandmother caught me halfheartedly masturbating at age 3 and started to have kittens about it, my mother rushed her out of the room, saying, "Nope.  You are not going to give my daughter a reason to think there is anything wrong with *any* part of her body."

There were always good books in the house that had answers to questions I might not be comfortable asking her -- and she would just silently make sure they ended up in my room, on my bookshelf.

All in all, she prepared me remarkably well for a happy, healthy sex life.

She consistently sent the message that as long as everyone involved wants to be doing it and is taking steps to prevent disease and pregnancy that sex is really fucking fantastic, and no one should make anyone feel bad about wanting to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  It's the same reason that on DUI stops, they use field sobriety tests that have time and again been disproven as unreliable. (The one-legged stand, finger-to-nose, horizontal gaze nystagmus, and walk-and-turn are the 4 most commonly used field sobriety tests and they all have serious validity/reliability issues.)

If the officer can make you nervous, you're more likely to utter some statement that could be construed as a confession to operating under the influence, which is all he needs for an arrest and search.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The belief in "happily ever after" or more fundamentally, the idea that somehow, someday, in some way, everything is going to be OK.

I've just been through too much to buy that anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a reasonable point.

But I'd also argue that the artists I named made a greater contribution to music in their dramatically cut-short lives than many artists make in an entire lifetime of normal span. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A wholehearted "yes" to everything you said, plus, **OP really needs another party -- who she would trust to act as a witness in any future proceeding -- to be present at tomorrow's meeting so that the trainer and her apparently clueless boss are not able to collude about what was said or done during the meeting.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having not practiced/observed the Sabbath since roughly 1991, I really can't comment on how the internet/technology in general has impacted Sabbath observance.  Jewish families have been dealing with not being able to cook, per se, on the Sabbath for approximately 6,000 years. I guarantee you that, in that time, far more Jewish housewives have prayed for a magical oven above a magical pizza delivery.

You might be right...the rabbis might approve of this one as an acceptable loophole in the rules, again, I can't say for sure.  But who wants to eat nothing but pizza every Saturday? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That *technically*, yes, that first 'r' "should" be pronounced, buuut...that should you choose to do this, you should also expect people to want to punch you in the throat for being such a pretentious fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given your boss's totally unacceptable response when you reported the harassment to him in the first place, I would **strongly** caution you against meeting with the 2 of them unless someone else you really trust is there.

You have every right to decline, or insist that a colleague/friend/HR rep (although remember that HR is there to protect your company, not you) also be present during the meeting.  If they won't agree to that, *please* do not attend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are 100% right.  People who abuse the protections in place for people with disabilities for the benefit of their own stupid, self-indulgent bullshit make my blood boil.  And they do exist.

But unfortunately, there's no way to make the system perfect in terms of weeding out all the liars/assholes without catching some people with legitimate need in the net. So, we end up erring, legally, on the side of caution and tend to give people the benefit of the doubt (although I think the effectiveness of the system overall could probably be improved).  This is similar to the idea that our justice system knowingly is designed to allow guilty individuals to be acquitted rather than allowing innocent individuals to be convicted.

Thanks, btw, for taking the protections seriously even though a lot of guests make a mockery of them.  The people who really need their service animals appreciate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hmmm?](http://www2.pictures.zimbio.com/mp/g9NuzTvkfoAl.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Tamacn](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vyOSXRCJlIg) (or anything else by Rodrigo y Gabriela, really). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be.  Someone receiving a report of sexual harassment is never supposed to offer their opinion about the severity of the event while the report is being made.  That's indicative of a lack of training/concern about what is potentially an issue that could cost him his job (as the person responsible for taking your report).

This is now straight to HR, and if you don't like the vibe you get from them, I'd make your next step a quick call to your state EEO or Civil Rights Commission.  It's not that the dude raped you in the bathroom, but when less severe yet still unacceptable shit like this goes unchallenged, guys like him just keep doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phones are (by and large) electronic these days, so no, you can't, and even when they were landlines, IIRC, Orthodox Jews were not permitted to make phone calls.

Also, transacting any business (such as paying for pizza) is prohibited on the Sabbath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are in the U.S., your employer has an obligation to prevent sexual harassment of its employees not only by its own employees, but also by its customers, vendors, and contractors.

This is absolutely something that can and should be reported to HR.  Please consider doing this so that if your company chooses to continue distributing for sleezebag's company, then there is a paper trail putting them on notice about his unacceptable behavior.  For future trainings, if his company sends him to instruct and your employer permits that, then they are responsible for his actions.

Your choosing to report this could have a significant effect on future women who are exposed to this behavior from him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always struck me as fitting that she entered "the 27 club" of great artists who died at age 27 and whose flame burned with too much intensity to last:

Jimi Hendrix, Janis Joplin, Jim Morrison, Ron "Pigpen" McKernan, and Kurt Cobain, among others.  It feels like she belongs with this group...tragically sad, but fitting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was raised observant Jewish, but I haven't practiced in many years, so I'm not familiar with this particular technology, but:

/u/wahlburgerz is correct. Orthodox Jews are prohibited from working, which explicitly includes igniting any flame/electricity from sundown on Friday through sundown on Saturday.

One way to overcome this prohibition is to have another (non-Jewish) person handle this, or, in the alternative, to turn the oven on and leave it on for the duration of the Sabbath.

I would imagine that this setting allows some custom pre-programming, so that the oven is set to turn off overnight on Friday night, perhaps turning back on Saturday morning so breakfast can be made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, but "chaputa" is what sent me over the edge.  I speak Spanish, and I can think of *a lot* of ways that could be interpreted as a slang term...all of them are hilariously offensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is is actually mine, too, but English is, well, funny like that. It's super non-phonetic; sometimes random letters are silent or make unusual sounds.  So, OP is right and so are you.  The 'l' in wolf *should* be pronounced, and the 'l' in salmon *should not*.

It gets even trickier when you look at words like "almond."  Most Americans now pronounce the "l," but at one time, the proper pronunciation was much like that of "salmon," with the letter being silent, and only uneducated, lower-class individuals would pronounce the word with the "l" sound.  Over time, this "uneducated" pronunciation became the accepted one.

Phew.  Sorry.  That was probably a lot more than you bargained for, but I'm currently taking a phonology and phonetics class, and these issues are fascinating to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work in a call center providing inbound customer service; one of the only technically-related issues we dealt with was resetting passwords by phone.  This is a story about what happens when people who don't know how keyboards work call in for a password reset.

One day, as I was about an hour into what ended up being an 88 minute call with Mr. Bless-His-Heart (Mr. BHH), I was going over the password requirements for like the four-hundredth and seventy-third time, when he asked me one of the most beautifully stupid questions I have ever heard:

Me: "Your new password needs to have a minimum of 10 characters, and at least one uppercase letter, one lowercase letter, one number, and one special character."

Mr. BHH: **"Wait. Does it need to have an *upper case number*, too, or just a regular one?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it.  My tuxedo cat is "tiny panther" and my white w/orange tabby is "tiny lion."

Although, in the mornings when they are nibbling at my face and batting items off my nightstand in an effort to accelerate the delivery of their breakfast, they are, collectively, "tiny assholes." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 17:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, but we *definitely* don't need these sorts of protections to be codified in the law...that's just catering to special snowflakes who want to have their pets with them. Besides, people don't *actually* discriminate against individuals with disabilities...**/s** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1965, a tractor trailer lost control and dumped its load of 30,000 pounds of bananas onto the roadway in Scranton, PA.  Harry Chapin wrote a song about it appropriately titled, ["30,000 Pounds of Bananas."](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/30,000_Pounds_of_Bananas)

That shit was bananas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that some outlets engage in manipulation has literally no bearing whatsoever on my point.

Regardless of how biased you believe media to be, journalism is essential to preserving human liberty.  If you think the sources available to you are inadequate, all that means is that you have an even greater responsibility to A) educate yourself so that you are able to distinguish good information from bad and B) support good journalism so that it can again thrive.

If you genuinely don't understand why supporting and maintaining a strong, free, adversarial press is in the best interests of everyone but tyrants, I don't have the time or the patience to explain it to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [According to the AMA they did on r/books awhile back, it *could* be that gal.](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/3aungz/hi_im_sam_garland_aka_upoem_for_your_sprog_ive/csg4z6u/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Falling asleep while listening to my huge, ridiculously affectionate orange tabby's deep rumbling purr with my face pressed into his fuzzy tummy.

* Floating on my back in my favorite swimming hole in my favorite campground.

* Couldn't agree more with OP about a campfire on a beautiful night.  I'll add to that the scent of pine trees, someone playing acoustic guitar we can all sing along to, and joints passed around the circle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DPRK troll level: nuclear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What "it" are you referring to?

What monolithic "media" are you referring to?

*Some* media outlets are blatantly and egregiously feeding bullshit to the public, yes.  Such has been the case for the entire history of journalism.  That is an argument for people to be consume more news, not less, and to demand that good journalism be available.  It is the responsibility of every adult citizen to be educated enough to assess the credibility of sources and to put in the effort required to do so.

There is a reason the free press is part of our **First** Amendment; its vigorous existence is essential to preserving democracy.  If the state of the American media is unacceptable to you, attempting to to destroy it is not the appropriate course of action.  Instead, the response should be to invest in journalistic efforts that meet the desired standard, no matter who is engaging in those efforts.  Isn't that the "free market" solution most Americans cream their pants over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The internet is useless to you without journalism.  Some 14 year-old  in Syria can upload a video of his village getting bombed, but what does that mean without the reporting that explains the hopelessly intricate context of the conflict?

The principles that Aristotle (and other political philosophers) laid out regarding the fundamental nature of people, our governance, and the cities we live in has nothing to do with internet access or lack thereof, or any other details of modern life.  Some characteristics of humanity are timeless and predictable.  It is the height of arrogance and lack of historical perspective to think that we have outgrown the lessons left to us by the giants of western thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just factually incorrect, unless you consider an earnest effort at disseminating nothing other than facts in order for the public to have access to them to be a narrative.

While it's certainly true that a great many -- I'll even concede most for the sake of argument -- media outlets are **intentionally** pushing a narrative, it's a rejection of reality to suggest that every single one is doing so, and doing so consciously, to boot.

Even if you were right, it still wouldn't alleviate you of the responsibility to filter through the bias and analyze the information to the best of your ability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If I don't want to take part in the politics, that's fine.

It's **not** fine, and that's wholeheartedly not the purpose of the electoral college.

Democracy, by its very nature, is a type of political regime that is highly susceptible to devolving into tyranny (see Aristotle's *the Politics*, not me, I didn't make this shit up, I just bothered to read it).  The most important way to ensure that it does not do this is by having a well-educated, involved, politically informed public.

Along with rights come responsibilities.  Staying informed and participating in the process are some of the most basic among them.  The fact that I have to spell this out is *heartbreaking*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The people writing the headlines are smarter or more invested in the story than I am, but their objective is to push a point of view without any regard for truth or objectivity, not to objectively disseminate information.

It's just as naive to assert that every news source is intentionally pushing a narrative than it is to be unaware that news sources have a bias at all.

The solution is not to avoid news and current events; the solution is to put in the effort required to be an critical consumer of information.  That is, you pay attention and always skeptically assess the potential biases at play, fact-checking when necessary.

I simply don't accept the notion that it's OK to abdicate that responsibility.  Obviously, I can't stop you from choosing to do so, but as far as I'm concerned, it's definitely not something a person should brag about.

No one is better off ignoring current events.  It might be easier and less emotionally turbulent, but it's not better for you in terms of being a functional, informed, contributing member of society.  More importantly, on a larger scale, society as a whole is not better off when its citizenry is willfully ignorant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said this in another reply, but maybe I should've been more specific.  I'm not talking about watching TV news; I'm talking about intentionally ignoring current events.

How bad/toxic it might be is not really relevant.  As a (theoretically) functioning adult member of society, a person has a responsibility to pay attention to what's going on around them.  You certainly don't need to watch TV news to do that -- I don't.

Further, there's a difference between merely not paying attention and *bragging* about not paying attention.

To answer your question, Comey just hates the Patriots, as any self-respecting American should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you. I don't even *have* TV, so I certainly don't consume my news that way.

But that's really not what I'm talking about.  I definitely didn't mean "watch TV news." Maybe I should have said, "pay attention to current events," because I don't care what conduit you use to access the information, but wearing blinders and deciding not to notice or care is not pulling your weight as an adult citizen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FML. I don't know how I did it, but I accidentally deleted my original comment, which said:

I think it would *have* to be /u/poem_for_your_sprog  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 00:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how I did it, but I accidentally deleted my original comment.

It said:

I think it would have to be /u/poem_for_your_sprog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's the sketch I'm thinking of...lol, indeed.

But what Chris Rock doesn't mention in that sketch is that this hatred of knowledge is a phenomenon that is absolutely not confined to black people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teenagers, *especially* when it comes to having agency and the ability to make independent, autonomous choices about their sexual and reproductive health and activity.

Obviously, they need unfettered access to comprehensive, unbiased information in order to do so, but they are far more capable of it than they are often given credit for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How they "don't read" or "don't pay attention to the news."

Your intellectual laziness and refusal to engage with the world around you *really* isn't something to be proud of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 23:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Always leave it to the punks and poets to tell it like it is. They feel all gone now, damn shame.

I know how you feel; it's all too easy to despair.  Here's something I think you'll like, though:

[Yell Fire!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7dYojHK7cu0)  ~Michael Franti   Spearhead (you may remember Franti from his days in the early '90s with [the Disposable Heroes of the Hiphoprisy.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Disposable_Heroes_of_Hiphoprisy) 

Apologies if you're already familiar.  If you're not, turn the volume **UP**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Danny Trejo.](https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/ae/b2/06/aeb206d56fdfc804dd7f26bfd992e199.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 22:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're lucky if it's Fox he's quoting; these days it's just as likely to be Breitbart or InfoWars.  Fox has incurred his disfavor at this point for being part of the "extremely dishonest" media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yiddish for "cozy" or "homey" but also slang for another Jewish person, in the sense of "not-Goy." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haymish in the house? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Maryland Medicaid recipient.  I am eligible for Medicaid due to its expansion in my state under the Affordable Care Act.

Real talk:  As someone whose income is near the upper limit for coverage under Medicaid, how soon should I expect that my son and I will lose health coverage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the relevant username, btw.

My understanding is that the alpha-release latke was nothing more than unseasoned, coarsely shredded potato fried in schmaltz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Dancing is a perpendicular expression of a horizontal desire."  

~George Bernard Shaw

It's really not weird at all, when you look at it in this light...it's just a socially acceptable metaphor for what you'd like to be doing with your dance partner in the bedroom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to argue this technically true point.  However, the style of latke perfected and popularized by Ashkenazi Jews and turned into a traditional Chanukah food (adding eggs, onions, and *specifically*, matzoh meal) is unarguably a specifically Jewish iteration of an originally Russian dish.

And I'm sure you know the saying about 2 Jews in a single room holding a minimum of 3 opinions...so I'm equally sure you know there was no way to make that comment *without* starting a war.  ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not my ethnicity, but if we make those some tacos de barbacoa (de chivo, preferably) with cebollitas, can I request to be adopted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any day of the week, yes.  Tzimmes is waaay too sweet for my taste.  There are tons of Jewish foods I love, but I'm not super fond of the stews. As I mentioned elsewhere, I'm not a big fan of cholent, either.

I love blintzes, brisket, kugel, even gefilte fish...but I'll gladly pass the tzimmes straight to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And this is why I love reddit.  I was coming here with, "And if you touch the Queen of England in the right places, she will arrive in her own bedchamber."

But I think I might like yours even better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
