<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8423</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 03:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That guy in the red shirt has shit stains on the back of his pants."  Look and see who looks at the guy in the red shirt's ass.  Bonus points if the guy in the red shirt is the mind reader and gets red in the face from embarrassment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's as if they seem to forget we're the third largest country in the world and our diversity is world rebound.  With all the food and holidays also comes political and moral beliefs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 13:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bisexuality is an extension of the binary sexualities of homosexuality and heterosexuality.  Pan sexuality is a broader term with subsections like gynosexuality(attraction to feminine body types, women, traps, cross dressers, lithe men, etc) and androsexuality (attraction to masculine body types, men, bull dykes, cross dressers, body-building women, etc) as well as the usual homo and heterosexualities thrown in there.  Most people have more than one sexual preference when you get into what they like.  The woman up higher who is heterosexual and gynosexual, likes penis and women's bodies but not vagina; the guy up higher who likes traps and women, and laments not finding one who wants to use a strap on, also hetero and gynosexual.  Liking dick in your ass doesn't change your sexual preference  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 21:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been listening to NPR less and less over this election cycle but I did get to hear Terry Gross grill a Clinton and Trump rep equally.  The satisfying part came in that the Trump rep was used to it and could counter her claims in varying degrees.  The poor Clinton rep was so blind-sides and just couldn't keep up beyond denying.  Terry seemed so upset.  I feel so bad for the folks at NPR who hate Hillary as much as we do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When you're wearing rose colored glasses, all the red flags just look like flags" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neighbors parking in gravel patch in the back of my house bordering an ally. I gave them permission but plan on using the land next year. How do I keep it from becoming an easement? (OH) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 17:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 04:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21h of possible cut scenes, if I remember.  Naturally, you won't see all 21 in one play through, but you will see roughly the length of the Lotr trilogy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 17:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I showed this to my wife, response:

"I don't get it, is it something about the vacuum?  Is she crying about cleaning?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Craigslist and friends who also participate in the hobby are good places to snag second-hand gear.  I have just about everything he did (at home because it was a paved hiking trail ffs) and haven't spent more than 200$.  This guy easily dropped 1k on everything he had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was Hocking Hill's family trails.  Like, designed for children and the handicapped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guys gear was name brands and probably close to 1k.  That's more than I've spent on this hobby in 6 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, some people just like trail food.  I have a friend who hikes, he'll break into his trail food while doing house work or or mowing the grass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly?  I can believe it was partly that.  Hocking Hills has a set of family and handicapped trails, which he was on, and some pretty advanced trails.  He may have read about the place and thought he was getting into some serious Man Vs Wild shit.  However, his polo, dress khakis, and hair loaded with styling product sure didn't fit that theme, especially when it was 85 degrees with decent humidity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You probably weren't also wearing dress khakis, a polo, and had greased up hair in ~85 degrees weather with ~70% humidity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/hiking has good information on the sidebar but /r/ultralight is good for beginners.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy was in dress khakis and a polo shirt, too.  When it was ~85 degrees out and decently humid.  Maybe he was trying to pack enough to offset stupid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy was hiking family trails at Hocking Hills.  I think you need it more than him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, but with his dress khakis, polo, and greased hair I think he just liked new toys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're missing the point.  I said they're out of shape to show they're a novice.  He was also wearing business casual clothes with his gear.  The point is that he went out and spent close to 1,000$ on gear to go hike a family trail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened in Hocking Hills, in central Ohio.  There's always someone within 100 yards there due to its popularity.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 14:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nature is beautiful.  Most hiking trails have very good sight-seeing potential.  You have easy trails for dates or family outings.  You have more difficult trails for the kid inside of you that misses jungle gyms.  It also keeps you in shape.  I can see why it's not for everyone, so I won't blame you if you just don't like it because you'd be in the majority.  But I enjoy it and so does my kids, so it's a win-win to tire them out without going to a McDonald's play place, and I enjoy myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 06:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not one thing, but seeing an out of shape person hiking with hundreds of dollars worth of clearly brand new gear, most of them aren't even necessary for the hikes they're on.  I saw an honest to god satellite phone sitting in a side pocket of a backpack with a hydration hose on a 3 mile light trail.  Good thing it was a light trail because his boots were fresh out of the box.  

Just wear something comfy that isn't flip flops and carry a water bottle if you're trying hiking for the first time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 04:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find pregnant women attractive.  It's nothing I actively think about or something I fetishize in a perverted way, it's just an attractive feature on a woman for me, like if she has long, beautiful hair or an ass you could bounce quarters off of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine, I've shopped in worse than cargo shorts.  But I was replying to why people find them unattractive.  I'm right there with you in still wearing them, they are pretty useful when doing errands or house work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small breasts.  Sorry, it's shallow as hell, I know, but I just don't find small breasted women attractive at all.  But if your on your second vowel, we can talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it bad I find pig noses really hot on the round face of a chubby woman?  Did I watch too much muppets as a kid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they look ill fitting due to all the pockets and  fact they usually hang below the knee.  So it makes the person look childish and therefore immature.  It's like seeing someone in a too-large suit, to give a reference.  I still wear the fuck out of cargo pants.  I'm married with kids, I don't give a damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 02:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure you're lying a competitive wage?  I worked at Walmart in the back unloading trucks.  We made less than half of what the guys loading them make at the DCs and no one stayed longer than two years.  Why?  You got fork lift and other powered equipment experience and OSHA license and then got a job at a DC or warehouse.  I moved to a lowes DC that paid 1.5x my pay at Walmart and the work isn't as hard.  My manager friend still complains that the unloaders are terrible and they can't keep anyone.  It's like they turn daft when I tell them to pay the back room guys more than cashiers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 23:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely, with a crowd that small, they have signs to show people when to applaud and when to stop.  Just as bad, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 15:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of two things could be happening when Anakin runs into Palpatine's chambers.  1: The scene looks just like the movie but on the ground lies a dead/dying Obi Wan.  2: on the ground lies several dead masters and a dead Palpatine, with a victorious Obi Wan and Windu over the corpse.  In both scenarios, Anakin would not attack the Jedi, but in the first scenario, while he and Windu easily defeat the emperor, Anakin goes far too deep into the dark side when killing the man that killed Obi Wan.  He will blame the Jedi for his dead for some reason and keep digging into the teachings of the Sith.  Without an Obi Wan to temper him he will, without a doubt, fall.  Interestingly enough, he will most likely join the council and attain the title master after the fact in both scenarios thanks to killing a powerful Sith Lord and all the seats that just opened up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 01:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On mobile or I would.  Just sort but top of all time.  The story is number 1, titled Prey.  Number 2 is the sequel, Prey II. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 23:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remind me of one of the top stories in /r/hfy humanity joined a confederation of sentient creatures  about a hundred years back and has been relatively isolated, and for good reason.  All of the species are prey animals.  Not a single one is a predator.  An intelligent predator is pretty much their version of the boogeyman.  Humans always wear suits that cover our forward facing eyes when interacting with other species.  It's a pretty good story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seoul has a population of roughly 10 million people.  The thing about soul is that it's very close to the border.  So close, in fact, that not only can short range missiles hit the city, but NK artillery is within range of the city.  At most, the city would have minutes to react before decades of installations let loose on Seoul.  So yes, millions will die in less than 24 hours.  If NK ever releases its payload on Seoul, the event will go down in history along side other wartime massacres like the siege of St. Petersburg  and Pearl Harbor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/me_irl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 03:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well then.  I'm sorry your relationship has bit a bit rocky and has lead your bedroom where it is now.  A few questions:

You said you told him you liked defined bodies and he started working out.  Is he still obese?

You said he cheated on you with a hooker ~2 years into the relationship and God a happy ending from an old woman n Vegas:  has he had any other extra-marital sex?  Have you?

It isn't very clear to me, was the hooker the point of the DB's start or was your first child?  How close was your first child and the hooker incident?

Have you or your husband ever gotten your hormone levels checked?

This seems more like a post for /r/relationships The DB here looks like a symptom of a much deeper problem in your relationship and individual lives.  But we're more than willing do to what we can here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would imagine there's definitely AC and plumbing thanks to the water benders!  I would imagine it would be a lot like the Roman style of AC plumbing.  The Romans often had running water going through their homes to keep them slightly cooler.  Add water benders making chunks of ice and you have a very efficient AC system.  Similarly, when it's cold, have fire benders heat the water until it's steaming hot. Plumbing would be simple as well, let the brown water drain out.  Now I can see water benders doing one of two things: pushing the poop water waaaay out into the ocean, or evaporate all the water, leaving behind foul sand-like waste to be buried by the earth benders (can they bend it now?  It's mostly minerals with all the liquid gone.)  with LoK's large pro-environment world, I imagine something like the second one would be more likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 02:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your first mistake was assuming DOCTOR DOOM was a bad guy at all.  Has he done morally reprehensible things in the eyes of many?  Yes.  But has he ever done harm for harms sake?  Has he ever acted out of malice and hatred?  While I admit he has enacted revenge in the past, revenge was simply a satisfying byproduct in the grand scheme of DOOM.  DOCTOR DOOM is a hero and never forget it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This, sadly, boils down to semantics.  It is said that Faenor is "the mightiest of all elves" but it is also said  that Fingolfin is "unmatched in physical combat."  I would give the match to Fingolfin for two reasons.  The first, the only feat that Faenor has on Fongolfin is him vs the Balrogs.  At this time, the Balrogs were standing between Faenor and his silmarils, making him Silmaril-lusted.  Fingolfin, on the other hand, is consistently in combat and comes out unscathed.  When Fingolfin fights Morgoth, it isn't a outlier feat like with Faenor and the Balrogs.

Second, the Morgoth feat puts Fongolfin's fighting ability as the fourth strongest being on middle earth ever.  It goes Tulkas, Morgoth, and fingolfin ties Manwe, as it is said Morgoth is stronger than him even when trapped in his human form.  This makes Fingolfin stronger than Orome in physical combat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you managed to transport all that gold out without it all getting stolen by bandits or losing it to the desert, that gold would be worth a lot but wouldn't make you the richest man in Agrabah.  You would have more gold than the sultan, but most of his wealth is tied up in land and commodities.  You and your grandsons will live like kings but, as a sultan once said "my grandfather rode a camel, I drive a Mercedes, my sons and grandsons drive landrovers, their grandsons will ride camels." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brock is a much better trainer than Ash in all aspects but one (will touch on that).  Brock would train Charmander at a pace he and Charmander were comfortable with.  He would also show Charmander an unconditional love and not use him nearly as much as Ash did.  This would cause Charmander to evolve slower than he did in the OT.  But, given time, Charmander would still evolve into his final form of Charizard though most likely not until after the Indigo league.  Charizard also wouldn't have learned to push himself as hard as he did with as and would not likely become powerful enough to go toe-to-toe with legendaries.  I think the other Pokemon would pick up the slack with no Charizard but what your left with is a very powerful Pokemon that Brock never uses because he's too sporting to utterly dominate any Pokemon battle.  But you'll know shit got real when he does send Charizard out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 14:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike current demon hunters, Illidan's transformation took place in stages.  The first stage of his transformation was back during the War of the Ancients.  Illidan's was trying to play double agent and did something to Sargeras's benefit.  For his service, and sensing great magic and potential, Sargeras himself granted Illidan his magic sight and adorned his body with the fel tattoos, marking him as Sargeras's agent (many believe Sargeras also sensed his treachery and marked him for that as well). With his new power and abilities he fought and killed a pit lord named Azinoth and took his twin blades for himself.  Marked as a servant of Sargeras everyone mistrusted him.  Luckily his brother and best friend were the duel leaders of the night elf people following the sundering so, even after recreating the Nightwell, he was only imprisoned instead of killed.  

At the time of his imprisonment, it's arguable he was already a demonhunter.  He has the tattoos, the magic sight, the magic and martial ability, and he has the title Betrayer.  But it isn't until he absorbs the skull of Gul'dan that he takes on his current appearance and gains his immense power.  Thanks to Sargeras's fel infusion from before, the mass amount of fel energy turned him into a half-demon-thing and tied his soul to the twisting nether.  It's at this point we get Illidan who begins to train the Illidari after the events of WCIII. He's so demonic that Tyrande, his childhood friend, and his own brother hardly recognize him.  He is exiled.  After his exile is when Illidan forms the Illidari (a.k.a Azerothian Super Friend).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 05:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Elder Scrolls are all legends!  Surely you don't believe that, every few hundred years, one being, who's race and gender change depending on the story teller, comes into great physical and magical power as well as leads one or more guilds, and then vanishes from memory?  If the story of how Emperor Martin fought and banished a Deadra Lord with the help of a ever-changing partner who is a male Nord in Bruma and a female Argonian in Leyawiin is of no concern than worrying about where the South gate lets out relative to Bravil isn't much worry.  Focus on the moral of the legends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 17:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step one: be attractive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see why that would help it be easier for some groups, but I think the feel of sieging a Titan fortress would be lost if it were organized differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outside of the MCU everyone knows he's Thor.  Thor hears prayers to him and has caused a small resurgence of traditional Scandinavian/Germanic polytheism.  His most powerful move is focusing his divine energy into a godblast, which he used to repel a starving Galactus.  Thor is stupid strong in Marvel comics and very much a public God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 15:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he translated the Beowulf that many scholars refer to to this day!  

Tolkien was a brilliant man with many interests.  He was also deeply saddened at the loss of culture of the Anglo-Saxons.  He even lamented the story of King Arthur being so romanticized to the point of the original name being in French ( La Muerte De Arturo) I think it's very fitting that Tolkien manages to revive so much Anglo-Saxon-esque mythology and make it so prevalent today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 06:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More likely Tolkien and Denham's tracts drew from the same well as earlier works as far as stylistic choices go.  You're probably right in that Tolkien had read the book, but his main focus was on Anglo-saxon literature written around or before the Norman conquest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 22:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had sex with a teacher at my school, but not my teacher.  I was a senior and she was a fresh-ish English teacher in her mid-twenties.  We just sort of got along in a personal level.  I would visit her classroom any chance I got to talk to her and she actually seemed happy to see me too.  I was kind of nerdy in school and the local comic-con was coming up.  We went together and got home super late.  And I decided to stay the night on her couch.  Nothing happened that night.  The next day was also spent with her but things were much more flirty.  I spent the night again but not on the couch.

We're married now, have two kids.  We just tell people we met while she was teaching at my school but we met the year after I graduated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like a real virus! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 00:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the Yakuza, for as much as Reddit likes to circle jerk around how "good" of a criminal organization they are, regularly forces women to do porn, including extreme porn like this, due to the high demand of niche markets and loads of money people will pay for it, being so he's to come by.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, cucumber snatch would be able to tell Light was Kira by the replacing all writing utensils within 50 miles with exact replica writing utensils with each one bearing a unique chemical composition that would then be present on Light's hand and the Death Note! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like in the OOtP during the battle at the ministry.  Everyone is just lobbing around curses and hexes.  But when Voldemort and Dumbledore fight, it's like the difference between PeeWee football and the NFL.  Look it up on YouTube but suffice to say that no one will be half as powerful as those two without both natural ability and constant studying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 02:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Batman is the most--no, fuck it.  Go to /r/whowouldwin and just search batman.  You'll lose 5 hours of your life and see why Batman is the most OP plot-armored Mary Sue ever imagined. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 02:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  Look up Drew CareyHe wears military issue glasses most of the time from when he was in the military.  Just liked that you can beat them with a hammer and still wear them, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 02:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saitama for OPM is a brute 6 (invulnerability) and a strike 12 (wins with WAAAN PAAAANCH) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 05:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no sources and am sure this is inaccurate but:

https://img.ifcdn.com/images/b79cd487e1c710592678a69ee4a978631bf990f4742ee55ce0c3f90f960f68b9_1.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 05:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need a hug, man? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just Flash get dangerously close to melding into the speed force.  Flash's speed depends on how much of himself goes into and becomes part of the speed force.  It's also how many iterations slowly become faster and faster--practice going deeper and deeper into the speed force while still able to pull back out of it.  This dimensional splicing is also how he can run outside of time without undoing our four dimensional universe and how he can run around the world at the speed of light without leaving behind a solid line of nuclear explosions, he isn't wholly in our dimension.  And the more he leaves our dimension the faster he can go and the more hax he gets.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, characters that can warp reality to a significant degree could feasible beat Saitama.  But, like I said in a thread about worm, Saitama's power is to win with one punch.  That means he wins against anyone he punches.  The only way to win against him is to not get punched while defeating Saitama which is impossible through brute strength.  So someone like Vision or Zatana could possibly beat him with magic or reality bending but even that would be hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 04:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Detectives Victor Von Doom and Arthur Dent are an unlikely pair.  While I think Doom will carry the duo, Dent would make a perfect straight man between all the weird stuff going on around him and the extremely strained relationship between Doom and commissioner Richards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 04:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to elaborate?  No tinfoil, just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean?  So you mean to say, what if the cut had merely caused a flesh wound?  That humans can treat the loss of limbs as flesh wounds?  That Arthur was mistaken in his judgement of how much damage his strikes had inflicted?  Either way, Arthur was a better swordsman than the black knight so the outcome would have always been the same: Arthur was going to cross that damn bridge and the Black Knight was going to lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 07:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's, like, his birthday and she was all reassuring she wouldn't forget the beer because she forgot on two previous consecutive shopping trips?

Maybe his dad is dying and is in hospice care at the house and that's his favorite beer and wants it before he goes?

I mean, he's probably an abusive dick but let me have my fantasy, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 07:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.  I found out my uncle had Brugata Syndrome (sudden death syndrome) and it most likely killed my grandfather, his father.  I knew I would never have children if I tested positive for it.  Boy that was a scary test but luckily it came back negative.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 05:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yoda foresaw this battle decades in advance during  his meditations.  Yoda will drag out the battle, challenging Deathstroke's morals as the two fight into a stalemate.  Eventually, when Deathstroke begins to question his way of life and his focus wanes, Yoda lowers his guard and takes a fatal hit, killing him instantly.  But the encounter has left an imprint on the bounty hunter.  He meditates on the encounter and is visited by none other than Yoda's force ghost.  Through mental, physical, and spiritual training, Slade Wilson becomes a grey Jedi master.

But really though, Yoda's feats are second to only Palps and not by much.  He nearly won their encounter.  Deathstroke physically outclasses Yoda but would lose the mental game fast between Yoda bettering himself (precog, force enhancement) and hindering Wade(mental clouding, frying his electronics).  If Wade doesn't get Yoda down fast, the geriatric will fight a fight of attrition and quickly gain the upper hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 20:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least she'll do things for you and not treat every single kink like I've asked her to have sex over a murdered corpse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 02:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting a five is fairly rare, I doubt they saw more than a few fives per hundred as tests.  I could see them having a short meeting with every student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 15:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it's not like the heroes aren't some of the best their respected classes have ever had anyway.  I think Kil'jaden would fit in well with Herod like Thrall, Garrosh, and Uther.  Yeah KJ is stronger than them but, really, not by as much as you'd think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 20:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see Jack triggering with a power similar to Null's in the yangban.  You could even argue that those two might have the same shard.  Other than that he could be a trump of any kind; nullify, project, etc.  with the ability to communicate with shards Jack is always bound to be powerful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure being drunk had a lot to do with both of those claims he made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 17:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multitasking.  Ever switch back and worth between two tabs or Windows?  Ever want to watch Netflix or YouTube in the background while doing something else?  Dual monitors are for you!  Have Pandora or Spotify on the side while you work are Reddit.  Espouse information into a Reddit comment quicker by glancing between screens rather than click, type, click, type back and forth.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 15:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, a large bloc of the Republican Party is racist, so I can see where they would be disenfranchised.  But a large bloc of the Democratic Party is racist but in a different way.  It's just the Republican racists are more publicized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 20:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I was speaking in WoW's timeline.  High elves have been the Allince's version of the Horde's Ogres: they're there in cannon but aren't in game as playable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High elves have been part of the alliance since vanilla.  And have been residing in Dalaran and Stormwind since vanilla.  Blizz said they didn't want to make them an option to confuse them with blood elves but they threw that out the window with Pandas already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 01:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've thought the customization overhaul through a lot and have thought of several

Humans: vrykul, high elves

Dwarves: dark iron, wild hammer

Elves: highborn, saytr/ fawns?

Gnomes: mechagnomes, diseased gnomes?

Draenai: broken, illidari

Worgen: different wolf appearances?

Orcs: brown orcs, felorcs

Trolls: buff trolls, sand trolls

Undead: high elves, monstrous?

Tauron: Tonka, something?

Blood elves: blue eyes, broken

Goblins: fat, more color options for skin

Pandas: they already have red panda, what more do you want?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice tits though

http://i.imgur.com/MOMQggb.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 07:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to CGI dat bootie, son!

CGI DAY BOOTIE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 07:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good casting choice.  Brie has a strong jawline, decent build, and doesn't look like a fridge.  Shame we can't say the same about DC's  borderline hebefiliac choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well their being assholes to a corrupt political machine who is passing Hitler and shooting toward Dr. Evil levels of evil.  It's like a bad fanfic is trying to make them look evil "is there a fuck you emoji lol" I mean, come on, it doesn't even seem real.

That's who they're being assholes too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, I don't k ow more than the FBI.  I did watch Comey speak to the house, and it was painfully clear by how explicit he was in detailing Clinton's crimes that they know she's guilty.  But Comey also knows the justice system (duh) and knows he won't be able to get a conviction with the evidence he has managed to get.  He can not prove beyond a reasonable doubt.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 12:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't k ow more than the FBI, I never even brought up their investigations.  But since you did; she's guilty and the FBI knows it.  But they also know they can't prove it beyond a reasonable doubt against the greatest team of lawyers in the world that Clinton will have for the trail.  Comey doesn't want to put some DOJ lawyer on that snake den. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eehhh.  Maybe if the opposing candidate wasn't Hillary.  Her list of wrong doings would be just as long and would have a lot more felonies.  Like, a lot more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good god, imagine the memes.  The mass suicides in late November from the meme-withdraw would be catastrophic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost as if one of the candidates should be in prison instead of the White House.  Trump is an asshole but he never wiped his ass with the constitution and gave the American people the middle finger while pounding away at Blind Justice's ass with a big black strap on... Metaphorically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 05:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course no one should use terrorist attacks to further their political agenda

[LUISE CK PICTURE]

But maybe if someone else acknowledged the increasing number of terrorist attacks often having roots in radical Islam then people would stop seeking out Trump for the safety he makes them feel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 17:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind that this is Goku at the weakest we will see him in DBZ.  He can fly but it takes energy.  On the way to fight Raditz he even rides the Flying Nimbus.  He knows that he won't be able to eat or rest much with the time constraints and being dead so he has to save his energy for the whole trip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 16:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fundamentalist Islam is now the dominant form of Islam.  So when he says Islam that's what he's talking about.  Progressive Islamists exist in large numbers but so do Mormons and I never refer to them as simply Christians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 04:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gandalf's relationship with the Eagles( who are also servants of Manwe), his use of lightening magic, and there's arguable feats like enthralling Bjorne and commanding Sauron to remove his corruption of Theodin.  Sauron was the most knowledgeable Maiar when it came to the rings of power, which is why he was given the position of White.  

And, to the best of my knowledge, the only major retcon Tolkien ever did was in the Hobbit, which came out before any of the other books.  TLotR was written with the whole world thought out already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 00:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/tolkienfans and /r/asksciencefiction are the two best places I know of!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 22:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 22:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elune confirmed world soul, more like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 21:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mfw meme magic exists in DC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 21:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Partly true, but the magic Gandalf could do would have been an extension of his Patron ainur, Manwe, would be able to do.  Manwe was the lord of the skies and air, and the master of authority.  You see this in the battle with the Balrog where Gandalf commands him to not pass.  The world bends around his will to make his command so, the Balrog dos not pass.  Saruman, on the other hand, serves Aule, the crafter.  With his magic, he is able to create a new, stronger breed of Orc.  

During their fight, they were simply throwing raw, weak magic at the other.  It's on their specialties that a Maiar really shines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 07:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The current alignment system has evolved to include inherently good and evil things, but the 1/2e systems were closer to height and skin color as far as characterization goes.  With that in mind, I am saying the whole alignment system as a strict set of morals able to characterize entire people on are inherently flawed.  The batman chart is a good example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 05:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes he sweats.  The flash is still human with a very high metabolism.  I'm guessing his suit wicks the sweat away and, once in the outside of his suit, his sweat loses the power of the speed force and trails off of him.  Keep in mind the Flash isn't leaving raindrops behind him, he's an incredibly fit man going for a leisurely jog as far as his body is concerned.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 05:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem with this is the alignment system was originally thought up as a fluid system that most characters self identify as.  For instance, both Captain America and Punisher would call themselves lawful good.  For every argument that crops up for defining each sector of the the 9x9 char, another refutes it.  Captain America can't me LG because he gives too much mercy, mercy is the opposite of lawful.  Darth Sidious isn't evil because he was unifying the galaxy for the greater good--like ripping off a bandaid, it was necessary.  The alignment system has no defining character because people change, and the lines between assignment change, or at least aren't straight and possibly take up 4 dimensions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 04:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they did go over a bump, and this did cause poor Marvin to get shot in the face.  The reason why this happened is because, when they went over the bump, Vincent had his hand holding the gun while resting it on the back of his seat.  When his balance was suddenly shifted, he tensed and tried to brace against the seat, his finger (which should NOT have been resting on the trigger) squeezed to grip the backseat and pulled the trigger instead of grabbing the seat.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 02:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To understand what the good doctor meant, you have to understand Loki's relationship with the other gods.  Loki's role was to humiliate the other gods in order to remind them of humility.  This job could be anything from cutting off all of Sif's hair to birthing the wolf Fenrir and then getting it to bite off Tyr's hand.  This job was important to the gods as humility was easy to lose when you are worshipped and deified.  Now, from a Christian outlook of black and white, Loki would look evil.  I mean, he did a lot of dickish things and would bring about ragnorok.  So it is easy to see that, when you go around looking at other religions with the notion of good vs evil (a bad idea in Nordic myths as everyone is a dick) the guy who is going to end the world is the one who you call evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 03:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you aren't a *strong* reality warped, once Hulk has you in any sort of grapple, it's over.  Hulk's strength is infinite.  If there is an amount of force needed for someone to be nuggied to death, Hulk will reach it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
