<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2004</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No fuck that. I never use ketchup in my BBQ sauce. Molasses son! Edit: in not on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was probably at least $30. Typically ribs are $14.99lb, brisket $18.99lb, cake $2.49, sausage $3.50 per link, drink $2.49. Pickles, onions and bread are "free". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people feel like homeless people contribute nothing to society, so why should the rest of society have to pay to support them? With the military it soothes the panic within them from the red scare.... They know if Russia tries to invade us, Uncle Sam is gonna retaliate. It's mostly people over age 60. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My branch of the family(mom, dad, sister and brother) are the only ones who have left. Everyone else (4 aunt's and uncles, grandparents, 30 cousins) all work for the family business. We were all taken out of my grandfather's will at that point and my dad was the oldest son. Literally disowned us just for moving to a different state. My grandmother just died Thursday and we hadn't talked since I left in 05. I'd call her on her birthday, leave a voice mail and never got a call back. And that's the norm there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that relevant at all?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then Magic and the Lakers would be hit with tampering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure if he was to stoop to those lows, Magic wouldn't want anything to do with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "force" him. There's nothing he could do other than say "please take my son." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I'm from you're basically considered a traitor if you leave. The families there have lived there for a hundred or more years in most cases so family is all they know. None of my friends from high school talk to me anymore because I left and they all felt betrayed. I have offered my best friend a good paying job on multiple occasions in Dallas and he turns it down every time "because he can't leave his mom". He's 30, she's in good health and married. He works in a potato processing plant making $13.85 an hour and he's been there for 10 years. It pisses me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the most realistic situation is to end up trading Wes and the Mavs pick for a higher pick, and trying to draft Monk, Fultz or Fox. The great thing with this draft is that it's heavy on guards, which Dallas is in desperate need of. If the starting lineup could be Curry, Fultz, Barnes, Dirk and Noel, I think that puts them right back into contention. Optimally they'd sign another big like Griffin or Ibaka and bring Dirk off as a 6th man but that's not going to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it is. I've gotten a few unexpected "me too" comments in the grocery store or places like the dentist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one with a homeless person holding up a sign that says "I just want my childhood back." That usually gets a few good ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Young kid on the team was trying to impress us with hard passes, I wasn't ready since he was like 6 feet away. It also broke the tip of my thumb and pushed the bone out of the skin which sent blood squirting. Good times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good God, you're right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had a mud room(room where you take off your dirty clothes when you come in from playing) growing up. It was carpeted and my brother dumped his tackle box. He forgot to pick up one of the fish hooks, we were wrestling and it went all the way to the eyelet into my buttcheek. My grandfather tried to pull it out with pliers to no avail since it was barbed. So I had to ride to the hospital with no bottoms on. Oddly enough the doctor that delivered me as a baby also removed said fish hook and performed two surgeries on my leg after I broke it. His famous line which I'm sure all kinds of doctors use was "You're all set kid, I hope I never see you again." I feel like I disappointed him many times growing up. Thanks Dr. Hershey!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother in law was actually recruited by them and chose to work for the NSA instead. Now he and my sister live off the grid in Western Kentucky with no cell phones or internet. He's seen some shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
