<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1121</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it will likely have to increase commercials, which defeats the purpose of PBS to begin with  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> except it literally isnt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how have republicans actually shrinked government, except for wanting to cut PBS and environmental agencies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the difference being that refugees in real life are human beings.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> our country is at stake here, we dont have to "give him a chance". He should have thought about this sort of thing before running for office </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The nazis having socialism isnt what made them fascists though, so your comparison is pretty weak sauce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvel movies are fun, at the very least. I haven't seen the new DC movies, but by the sounds of it they are pretty serious and drab.

Marvel movies are generic and pulpy, but the good kind of generic pulpiness  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so we should let him off the hook if he takes action to create more wars?

okay
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is the top three aren't denying services to anyone, the Christian one is. How do people not see the difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do people like General Mattis? I mean, he just seems reasonable by virtue of not being a crazy as the rest of them.  He still [brought us to the brink of a potential war with Iran](https://theintercept.com/2017/03/01/trumps-moderate-defense-secretary-has-already-brought-us-to-the-brink-of-war/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanders did way better than anyone expected, and he did well in states clinton lost.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> openly worked to undercut the security of the state of Israel


do you have a source on this?  As a politician he has had a fairly status quo stance towards israel

if its just him condemning israel building settlements, than good on him :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 23:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no systems specific control (ie, setting police precints and school districts)

no way to easily tell where the demand is for, or even what exactly the demand is for

traffic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanders campaigned for Trump

wot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secret life of pets was really good when it was about the life of pets. it was really bad when dealing with things that are not actual things pets do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> meesa too, thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dwight's siblings were mentioned a few times, just not by name. 


I think a funnier show than the farm would have been a Fawlty towers esque  show about Dwight running a bed and breakfast with Angela and mose  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9/11 was over a decade ago, and does not reflect modern crime statistics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tk-421, do you copy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad this really happened, good to know our youth are out there protecting our values -_-

disregarding, of course, that was book was anti racist for its time, written by an abolitionist, and is considered a very humane portrait of African Americans (again, for its time). Disregarding that it is continually upheld by most everyone as a classic of American literature, and is still taught in school, regardless. 

it has been a few years. I know they use the N word a lot and dont exactly show the horrors of slavery, but in which ways was it xenophobic or sexist (for its time) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it totally has an ending. a bummer ending, with a cliffhanger, but the film feels complete at its end. 

ROTJ has ewoks, the worst acting of the OT, is visually uninspired, and a scene where han solo distracts a storm trooper by tapping him on the shoulder and running the other way. Its the stupidest movie of the OT, redeemed by Luke's fight and the death star assault (and general good editing in the final bits) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it more than hot fuzz, but less than shaun of the dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 20:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a liberal, which of his policies appeal?  Because they all look like shit from where I am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the difference being amy shumer isnt all that bad, and is mostly hated for being fat and a feminist 

(stealing jokes is bad, but she was hated before that came out) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh look, hating amy schumer. thats original </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats just about the least relevant quote, delivered in the least relevant way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> using youtube as a news source </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edgy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a proud American. I despise Mr trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lobbying ban is okay. I disagree with him keeping promises, because his promises sucked. I have no opinion on TPP, it seemed that economists were split on the issue. 

As for creating jobs, I am genuinely concerned about his ability to do so consistently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 14:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has the gop indicated that they are willing to meet us halfway?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/PrequelMemes/comments/5sbrfe/medieval_sheev/

Its been posted at least once before, twice if you count it once appearing as a non gif
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, most upvoted comments I see about moonlight are positive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trump makes me remember his administration fondly. However, yeah, Bush was not a good president </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'll try reposting, thats a good trick" - /u/imperialxwarlord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess, popular in the mid terms, unpopular once all sorts of people have been dropped for a few years and insurance rates dont come back down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why link to Fox news when you could link to the actual study, or an article going into more depth?  Why not up what the actual author of the report had to say? https://www.wired.com/2017/01/author-trumps-favorite-voter-fraud-study-says-everyones-wrong/

Heres what the math should look like (that is, if Richmans initial study was accuratewhich many researchers doubt). If 6.4 percent of the estimated 20.3 million noncitizens in the US voted, and if just 81.8 percent of them voted for Clinton (the percentage who voted for Obama in his 2008 study), thats an added margin of a little more than 835,000 votes. In other words: Even with all of those supposedly fraudulent ballots, Clinton still would have won the popular vote by more than 2 million votes.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, well very cool then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fantastic!  that said, its a bit built up for York County, ME (i'm from Buxton). Hard to tell exactly, but some of the buildings look more in line with Portland in terms if density. Maybe look at downtown Saco for reference. http://www.amtrakdowneaster.com/sites/default/files/imagecache/sc_815x310/Saco_image002.jpg

Overall, you capture the feel and its very cool. I will check your story out

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nah. La La Land is good, but Moonlight was far better. If it had come down to, say, Manchester by the Sea versus Moonlight, then maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so a lot of diversity in the answers, then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHUP TEE DO!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with the expanded membership programs, maybe not. However, in years past, films about LGBT people and independent black films were particularly unpopular with the academy. The expanded membership would have helped this, plus the ranked voting may have as well (people voting for fences or hidden figures may have been likely to put moonlight as their #2 film) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> downvoted for your edit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The norse and celtic portraits are awesome, for sure. These are an improvement, but yeah the norse and celtic are still better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O'Keefe does have a history of heavily distorting facts. 

The O'keefe video (which I watched) was likely heavily edited. The camera rarely showed mouths moving, frequently had faces out of the picture for long periods of time. Did he ever release the raw footage, for an independent source to review? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> known liar okeefe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didnt the democunts get caught committing voter fraud in multi-able states

no, they did not

Some states are so lax on voting laws you could be a north Korean strait off the boat and vote with out any form of ID

you still typically need an ID, or at least a valid ssn, to register

Im highly suspicious that Hillary won the popular vote fairly

virtually every city voted her way, and 60% of the population lives in an urban environment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> has their been a "minor character of the month" yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the problem comes when we have an administration actively lying about terror attacks by immigrants, while ignoring what is done by white americans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the PT, quite a bit.  That being said, I know the films have a lot of weaknesses when compared to other films.

1). episodes 2 and 3 are all talk, little showing. 

2). The plot requires supplementary material to make a ton of sense. I like the story, because I am a fan, but it isnt right for a movie to rely on other works heavily. 

3). Anakin's character is never quite right. Compare him in the movies to him in the animated clone wars. In the movies, he is whiny. Like a teenager as intended, but hard to root for. In the show, he is goofy, powerful, cocky, and loyal. the seeds of the darkside are evident in him, but he seems like a brave warrior, the best starpilot in the galaxy, and a good friend

4). building on that, there isnt a strong POV for the audience to identify with. This isnt inherently bad, but these particular films could have used it

5). Ahead of their time SFX?  you betcha. still not up to where they need to be based on how much they were used? also correct

6). Episode 3 especially feels like it was directed by a tired person.  The 100% cgi sequences are great, because lucas could sit down and direct them at his own pace. You can feel that he lacks the patience for live action. Compare the yoda vs palpatine fight to Anakin vs Obi wan. Compare obi vs obi wan to obi wan vs Maul in episode one. Maul's death fight is fantastic. The one in ROTS is shot like a conversation, and way too close. 

7). the actors never feel immersed in their environments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a 50 state strategy would hopefully have people who reflect the progressive ideals by the measure of their districts. A liberal/progressive in texas will have different opinions than one from new england.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heartbreaking and beautiful. Loved it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's fantastic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did we watch the same la la land?

Moonlight is a more personal story. Written better. Less clichd characters. Beyond that, it has a distinct visual look (lala land borrowed from old movies), and great acting. Lala land had fine acting, but nothing really rising above that. Plus Ryan gosling isn't exactly a world class singer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an ass and no one likes you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LLL was good, but I'm shocked it's getting so much love. I found the story pretty shallow, and the musical sequences weren't enough to elevate it above the shallowness (except for the few big numbers) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 01:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found it to be a beautiful movie. Heartbreaking and very human. The social issues are great as well, but the movie didn't lean on them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have age classificstions really worked for much? I mean, little kids still end up seeing r rated movies, and violent TV

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now THIS is reposting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one needs nazi fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Noise Addict - I Wish I Was Him (acoustic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait until they are on sale. a lot of them are cosmetic, so ignore those for now. TOG ads the most content, imho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you not see a difference between eating cereal and stealing a car?

the equivalant would be saying that putting sweet baby rays on all foods is the blackest thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its a terrible place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there isnt, too my knowledge, a mechanic to have empire/kingdom titles be destroyed. Itd be cool if there was, but there would have to be some other mechanic determining kingdom stability and ruler influence over vassals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its good, quite good. Not folk punk though. Everything up until christmas island at least somewhat fits the mold, their two albums since (christmas island and the bible 2) are more indie punk/garage rock.  So its good, but not in like with the genre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idiot bubbles

thats why so many big, successful, and innovative companies choose to operate out of these areas, right?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...you mean a band no longer sounds the same as they did when they were in high school, 10+ years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pat the Bunny is (was?) pretty big in the scene, as were his various bands (ramshackle glory is the most recent). AJJ's early 3 or 4 albums as well. Defiance Ohio is good. Days n Daze, blackbird raum if you want something more "punk". Ghost Mice are on the softer side  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the best defence is a good offense. We must siege their holdings and end this war </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you expect?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is what, his fourth final film? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can assure you, it's the gop pushing for some forms of religious law, not dems  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He endorsed her at the end of the election, same as most primary opponents do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for starters, i didn't insult you personally, while you did insult me personally

Secondly, this is an american movie, made by americans, about americans, for americans. I was pointing out that your insinuation that slavery is not the literal worst thing to have ever happened (it wasnt literal genocide in the same way of the holocaust i suppose), it is still incredibly vile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everyone is overly sensitive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes fellow kids i too partake in narcotics EDIT i am not a member of the police </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *citation needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if someone is complaining about PC culture, SJWs, or snowflakes, there is a 100% chance that they are overly sensitive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> brainwashed into thinkig that slavery in the south was the worst thing that ever happened

I mean, slavery is *the* darkest part of American history. Seeing how many bad things we have done, thats really saying something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> single payer was not popular then, and is only gaining popularity now. Healthcare is getting expensive for some, though prices have always been rising, so some of this is exaggerated. people who would have once been uninsured are now covered through various programs, which is great. Pre existing conditions are protected, which is great. Is it perfect? no, lots of room for improvements. but it is an improvement.

LGB marriage was dictated by courts, but by Obama appointed judges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7/10 people are trump supporters

maybe, but perhaps...

trump got crushed in the popular vote and only wins in rural areas, which is favored by the EC

ahh thats right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> comprehensive healthcare reform: check

de escalating US involvement in iraq: check

significantly improved economy: check

LGB marriage: check

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where do I go to get money 2 protest. I love getting paid to do things id do anyways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serf City, pirated, with no instructions. Playing splitscreen with my brother, one of us using a joystick, which was super hard if I recall. 

Other contenders, AoE1, Space Quest 4,  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if john kerry had spent a lot of time on 9/11 truther websites, thatd be the comparison.

I cant think of any left leaning conspiracy theories that are notable and current, except that 9/11 was an inside job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> without mods, you can make this by making avenues using two sets of one way roads (which is what I do) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> errday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People from Maine just have good taste ;)


Joking aside, having been raised in southern maine, there are a number of theaters playing these sorts of movies, where as a lot of other states lack movie theaters playing independent movies until they've been nominated. But I know moonlight was shown in Portland on release, same with Manchester by the sea  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> only true stories are allowed here it cant be false </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats ur favorite miller </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 min? Of ALADDIN? lock this lad up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 20:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've def seen them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hate speech had nothing to do with hitler

blaming a racial "other" to gain power and solidarity among the majority was one of his tactics  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I oppose legal thought police. Thats not to stop any individuals from combatting dangerous viewpoints, but I worry about legal santions against words of any kind. The exception, in my opinion, would be schools. Schools should be allowed, under narrow guidelines, discipline against racism and sexism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't, but I worked with a business development manager who had worked with some trump brands (casinos, perhaps?). said he pays well, and its good comparatively to similar establishments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> meirl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the actor is playing him in this movie is 27, harrison ford was 34. So he is 6 years younger, but you're right, thats not super significant when we call it a "young" han solo movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PP already has a lot of donations funding them. That said, its expensive and a lot of users of PP are poor and cant afford to give much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planned parenthood will give you free condoms, im fairly certain. They also do STD screens for men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 22:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Palpatine exploited existing failings of the republic. He didnt cause them to get too big to fail, he didnt make valorum wishy washy.  He made the trade federation invade naboo, but he alone  didnt create the situation that allowed for that ploy to work in giving him  more power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the leading contender this year is a fluff film about LA, so you aren't exactly right about anything

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this post is not as good as other posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> por que no los dos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> from my point of view, you're forced garbage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you underestimate my high personal combat score </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, casterfo is a great character. I liked (didnt love) the book, but hope they do more with his character in the future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh for sure

in real life politics, I am skeptical of overly centralized control, but this would be the pro empire argument.

the republic was dying due to infighting and the slow moving political process. A private company invaded a planet, and the corruption was so high it would have taken months through the courts to change it. Sheev was the alternative. With emergency powers, he could make quick decisions over a number of issues that, under a huge republic, would have taken too long in deliberation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
