<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8546</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giraffes are not a single species as previously thought, but rather four distinct species, DNA analysis reveals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 18:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alien Interpreters: How Linguists Would Talk to Extraterrestrials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Laura Kipnis reviews Jessica Bennett's Feminist Fight Club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 17:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original research: http://archpedi.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=2548440  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children born by C-section have higher risk of obesity, even after adjusting for other factors, Harvard study finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 17:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is beautiful. Be like Maine. Don't let others force you to be a flower if, deep down, you're a pinecone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Maine's state flower is a pinecone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 22:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like this guy is pretty optimistic this research will lead to that: 
It could also tell us who needs to be treated aggressively and early with restoration therapieswe call it resodding the lawn. We could tell individually, patient to patient, what bacteria need to be given back based on a sample collected at admission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 18:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems good in theory, but surely what's holding most people back from big life changes is money, not "permission" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hesitant to Make That Big Life Change? Permission Granted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 18:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans in the intensive care units of hospitals experience a change in the microbiome, but antibiotics probably play a role there. A study on the gut microbiomes of prisoners would be very interesting. Though probably difficult to fund and complicated in terms of consent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 18:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To tide you over, [here's a great and funny account](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/the-martian-scientist) the crew's astrobiologist wrote of the experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 22:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably the human brain is hardwired this way because that's how babies work. When they come out, they're fragile and you're afraid of breaking them. By the time they can walk, you've dropped them a few times and they're fine, so you don't sweat it any more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 14:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true you'd have options if they pull their financial support, but I know the burden of student loan debt can also be huge. If the nutritionist option doesn't work, you might decide that sticking it out as a "flexitarian" (heating a healthy vegetarian diet at school and whatever they eat when you go home) for four years is worth it. Either decision is legitimately and totally justifiable. 

Regardless, I'll second what others have said about talking to a counselor once you get to college. This kind of issue with controlling parents is one mental health counselors on college campuses probably have a ton of experience with, and they can help guide you through it from both a logistical and mental health standpoint. Good luck and enjoy the first week of college! Trust me, this will get easier once you're there and not under your parents' roof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 13:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I make a really easy quinoa dish inspired by exactly the recipe for cheesy broccoli quinoa /u/elara829 recommended. I sent the recipe to my parents, because my dad's trying to eat more fiber, but doesn't like quinoa. Well, he loves this:

2/3 cup dry quinoa, 2/3 cup frozen spinach, Butter or olive oil, 2 cloves garlic (I like a lot, but use small cloves if you don't), 1/2 cup shredded gouda cheese, Lemon juice, Salt and pepper to taste

1. Rinse quinoa in mesh strainer under cold water. 
2. Put rinsed quinoa and 1 1/4 cup water in small pot on high. 
3. Once it starts boiling, turn heat to low and set timer for 15 minutes. 
4. After timer goes off, remove from burner and set aside with lid still on for 5 minutes. 

5. While quinoa is cooking, mince garlic and saut in butter or olive oil on medium heat. 
6. Before garlic browns, add frozen spinach (I think I used about 2/3 cup). Cook with lid on, stirring frequently, until it thaws and heats up.
7. Add lemon juice, salt, and pepper to taste. 
8. Stir in cooked quinoa and 1/2 cup shredded gouda cheese. 

Whenever I visit my parents, we make a double recipe. I eat half as my main, and they each eat a quarter as a side with some chicken or whatever. Now, quinoa's not the cheapest thing out there and is harder to find in some areas than others, but this might be good to try as an occasional thing if your local store has it (you can also usually get it cheaper online than in a store).

Oh, and since she likes black beans, here's another super easy, one-pan [quinoa dish](http://damndelicious.net/2014/04/09/one-pan-mexican-quinoa/) I love. It might be a good one for you to try out spices with her with. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you do need to be careful about not getting your money stolen by scammers. Don't wire anyone money until you've seen the flat, have a good gut feeling about the people in it, and have a signed contract. Definitely never wire money to somebody who says they're not in Berlin at the moment, etc. 

But I've never heard of anyone being robbed in person at a WG viewing. Way too risky for the crooks. With a physical location involved, the police here would be all over shutting that kind of operation down. 

Edit: When I was looking, I saw the "wg.whateverstrasse" emails all the time. Germans are weird about privacy. I'd actually say that would give me more of a sense of trusts, since scammers try to sound legit by having "real" email addresses with "real" names.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use the Living Earth app. While not 100% reliable, I've found it better than other things I've tried.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Individuals with more muscle mass do not need more protein after resistance exercise. Recent study contradicts standard sports nutrition recommendations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Science Can Help Get Out the Vote: several proven strategies for boosting turnout on Election Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 17:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 08:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! This is very reassuring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 23:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for weighing in. I'm seeing them in the kitchen too, and my roommate has a lot of old food in the pantry. I'll have him go through it and will do the same with mine. 

Do I need to worry about bringing eggs with me to my new apartment in clothes, books, or bedding?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 Scientist Predictions About the Future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 13:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 10:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course. [Here are some pictures](https://imgur.com/a/77Keu). I live in Germany, which is probably also relevant for identification. 

Edit: I did some googling. Am I correct that these are Indian Meal Moths? If so, why are they in my bedroom?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to avoid bringing moths with me to new apartment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 23:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The apartment I'm subletting seems to have a bit of a moth infestation. I see/kill 3-5 a day, and the next day there are more.  Anyway, I'm moving to my own place in a bit over a month, and would like to avoid taking the problem with me. I don't have any furniture, but clothes, books, lamps, and large framed pictures. What should I do when packing to be sure the problem doesn't follow me? 

Also, once the room's empty, anything I can do besides vacuuming to take care of the issue for the person after me? 

Update: [Here are some pictures of the culprits.](https://imgur.com/a/77Keu)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the study](http://nature.com/articles/doi:10.1038/ncomms12452) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because "sneaker" male fish ejaculate in other males' nests and swim away, female ovarian fluid evolved to favor sperm of more attentive mates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 18:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what they mean by "evidence piles up." Scientific consensus is a cumulative effect. In the case of the rapeseed study, this kind of pesticide had been shown to make three species of domestic bees sick (the only three species that can be bred in lab conditions) over the short-term. But they didn't know:

1. If it contributed to long-term population decline. The new study spans 18 years (9 years before they started using the pesticide in the UK and 9 years after), so now they know it does. 

2. If it had the same effect on wild bees. The new study looks at 62 species' populations over that period, so they can see that bees that pollinate crops with that pesticide suffer drastically more population decline. 

Edit: This [interview with the lead author](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/increased-bee-extinction-associated-with-neonicotinoid-pesticide-use) is a nice read on the new bee study.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think of people who are really wary of genetic testing, because they're worried about discrimination on some level? For example, people in the US can't be denied health insurance because of preexisting conditions right now, but that's fairly recent, and laws can change. Do you think it's fair for patients (especially those with hereditary diseases in their families) to be worried about the implications of genetic tests?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that views of swing voters do not matter much to presidential candidates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the paper](https://www.researchgate.net/publication/303541868_Spatial_Processing_in_Infancy_Predicts_Both_Spatial_and_Mathematical_Aptitude_in_Childhood).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Babies' spatial reasoning predicts later math skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 12:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neonicotinoids were licensed for use in the UK only in 2002. Since the data in this study spans 1994-2011, they would be able to see a decline associated with their use starting in (or shortly after) 2002.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 12:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the alternatives have other, more immediate consequences for the environment: 

"The reality is that a crop like oilseed rape cannot be grown without the use of pesticides. One option is to just not grow this crop anymore, which is probably not very realistic. If you continue growing it, but stop using neonicotinoids, youre going to have to switch over to something else to control pests. Because neonicotinoids are systemic, they're quite targeted. If you start applying pyrethroids as a spray, then you've got issues of drift and water contamination." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much for doing this AMA. What do you think of the [recent study](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/apollo-astronauts-at-greater-risk-of-death-from-cardiovascular-disease) suggesting that deep space radiation may have been harmful to Apollo astronauts? Have you had any cardiovascular issues yourself? (I hope this isn't too personal a question. Apologies if it is!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 12:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually like the Mller out of focus in the background posters. He's aware of his reputation as a faceless technocrat and is embracing it (or rather his PR person is) with the "not in this for the glory--just competently getting things done behind the scenes" message.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 10:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your relationship with the surgeons and other nurses like? Is it possible to have work friendships in such a high-stakes environment?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This article](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/suicide-survivors-tell-their-stories-on-reddit) talks about how anonymous spaces like Reddit can help people with mental health issues who might not otherwise seek support because of stigma. Do you think that they can also contribute to decreased stigma over time, as people with less exposure to mental health problems come across threads like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To support female academics, data and accountability are needed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 10:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> former US team doctor (who's also a swimmer) explains what makes Michael Phelps so good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 17:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 16:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has the spread so far meshed with your predictions early in the outbreak, or has it surprised you in some way?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 16:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [original research](http://jac.oxfordjournals.org/content/early/2016/07/27/jac.dkw283.abstract?sid=cd52ccef-1890-4336-830c-95c4c3654e8a) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HIV Medication Protects Mother-to-Child Transmission in Mouse Models </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 16:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 10:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say the difference in tone comes from the fact that Trump doesn't really have a science or education platform. The Clinton stuff seems to be straight from her website, because that's where candidates publish their platforms. Trump doesn't address science or education issues anywhere official (except healthcare and immigration, where I was surprised to see the thing about unemployed STEM graduates is [actually in his platform](https://www.donaldjtrump.com/positions/immigration-reform)) I guess the article isn't neutral in the sense that it's an attempt to highlight that discrepancy, but trump doesn't really have enough of a science policy where it would be possible to make a column like the Clinton one for him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does mention she has a good senate record on stem cell research, but yeah, the NIH mention would have been good there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I like is that you can really see support for science across her platforms. Grow the economy? Invest in STEM education. Healthcare policy? Invest in scientific research. Tax policy? Tax incentives to companies addressing climate change and disincentives to those contributing to it. 

To me, this platform really shows recognition that scientific progress and innovation is key to the long-term well-being of the country in nearly every respect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 14:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, anyone who wants more of a challenge just look at the first hint.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Hillary Clinton and Donald Trump stand on science and research: the 2016 science platforms at a glance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 14:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 14:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Maybe this is more obvious than I thought. It's actually just research on each citys' Olympic Games overall.](/answer) 

For more cool charts about this, see the interesting article in [Scientific American](http://www.scientificamerican.com/article/scholarly-olympics-how-the-games-have-shaped-research/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 14:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. [Look at the years](/hint)
2. [Specifically, look at the intervals of the years](/hint)
3. [Red line is Atlanta](/hint)
4. [Blue line is Sydney](/hint)
5. Big hint: [Green line is Beijing](/hint) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graph shows amount of academic research done on what topic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 14:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scholarly Olympics: A graphical guide to the impact of the Olympics on research (or vice versa?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 12:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 11:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This manufacturer is already getting ready for TTIP.

Note for Americans: [TTIP](https://www.theguardian.com/business/2015/jul/03/what-is-ttip-controversial-trade-deal-explained) is like TPP, but with Europe. In my experience, Americans have never heard of it, but people over here (Europe) are very much freaking out about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Although the researchers caution that their study does not suggest cause and effect, they note that it does suggest that an infection, use of antibiotics or other factors that change the bodys natural collection of gut and other bacteria may individually or collectively contribute to behavioral changes in some people with mental disorders."

Here's the paper: http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/bdi.12416/abstract

And the abstract on ResearchGate for those without journal access: https://www.researchgate.net/publication/305393794_Individuals_hospitalized_with_acute_mania_have_increased_exposure_to_antimicrobial_medications </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infections/antibiotic use correlate with manic episodes in people with severe mental illness, Johns Hopkins study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 17:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sample size is such an issue with space medicine research. Interesting that they combined this cause of death data analysis with the mouse study to confirm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live outside the US, and anecdotally food allergies seem less common here in Western Europe than in the US. Is that really the case, and if so, any idea why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 12:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is of great importance as, to date, no bacteria from the human body has been able to produce such compounds

I wonder if this is due to lack of looking at human sources of bacteria from which to produce antibiotics (since using bacteria from soil is apparently more common) or whether there are just so many bacteria in the human body and so much variety from human to human.

Seems to me looking at humans for the right microbes to develop antibiotics for human diseases makes a lot of sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flooding from yesterday's storm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 10:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 15:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Six scientists and engineers live and work in an 11-meter-diameter dome in perfect isolation on the slopes of the Mauna Loa volcano, in Hawaii. Everything they do emulates future crews on Mars to test psychological factors involved in, and technologies developed for, such missions." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL there's a team of NASA scientists who've been pretending they're on Mars for nearly a year. They live and work in a dome on the side of a Hawaiian volcano and only go out in spacesuits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 15:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
