<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2622</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 03:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a new boyfriend. You need someone who will help you grow as a person and will accept your help to grow as a person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 03:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with boners? I've always had fun with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 03:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe she likes you and didn't want you to know. Maybe she thought you already knew... Man the fuck up and talk to her about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 03:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEVER! I saw you kissing pavement... I hate that guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 03:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like "beercules". It's not original, but people will dig it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 03:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sit him down, like a man. Talk to him, also like a man.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 03:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is going on  with the guy with the whip and the girl(?) doing a handstand?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 03:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because you're right across the table... And you're boring either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 02:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or... Close enough, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 02:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try, Chris Brown! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 02:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. It's all good. Try again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we know who did it... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 02:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 01:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you're describing is a deeper concept than free will. By definition, free will is simply "the power of acting without the constraint of necessity or fate; the ability to act at one's own discretion"

Free will has nothing to do with what you know or what is scientifically possible in the world. My examples of overeating or suicide are perfect in that I wasn't doing them out of hunger or depression. I was just doing it for the hell of it.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 01:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also wrong meme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 01:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a... Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 20:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do have control over your thoughts thoughts though.  Right now I'm on Reddit. I think I'll go catch a plane to Nebraska. That was pretty fucking random. I literally have no connection to Nebraska nor has it been mentioned at any point recently. I pulled it out of my.

Even if your thoughts do control your actions, how is that not free will?

You are your brain. Free will would be any idea that happens in your head that aren't orders from someone else.  It's impossible to do anything completely without thought, conscious or subconscious. 

The only way I would accept that free will doesn't exist is with proof that everything is predestined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 13:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I could walk into my room and kill myself even though I want to live. I could.  If I wanted to, I could kill someone else right now. I could go eat a whole pizza. I could eat until I'm full and then keep on eating for no particular reason. Or I could stop.

There is  usually at least one reason that we do things, but the fact that we make a choices IS free will.  Or the fact that we would make a decision to take the long way home. Why would our brain send us the longer route? Wouldn't it want to be as efficient as possible? If free will didn't exist, wouldn't we make the same decisions over and over again?  There would be more consistency to our lives.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 13:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Russia, meteor sell pieces of you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 13:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be more specific. I cited an example. What didn't you understand about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 07:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs a different fucking title! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 07:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide provides the best evidence of free will.

Unless you want to tell me that in "God's ultimate Plan" he was just like  "aaaand subject2622 is going to blow his brains out March 1st at 1:37 AM" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 07:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scar in the center of my bottom lip from falling down with a bottle in my mouth when I was three. My teeth went through it. 

I had a bottle at the age of three because the sucking helped relieve ear pain. Because someone will eventually ask.

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 06:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cue pussy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 06:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most important thing you should always remember if you get shut down is that you've literally lost nothing by approaching her. You have gained experience. She's the one that's missing out. You can't just TELL yourself that. You have to KNOW it and wholeheartedly believe it to be true.

Good luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 06:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With great content comes great responsibility.

You must choose between making the world laugh and keeping your friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 06:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 06:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok. Listen (read) very carefully...

1) Pick out girl

2) Commit to approaching her. Don't bitch out or I'll punch you in the cock.

3)Walk up to her (keeping your body angled away from her) and playfully say "I just wanted to let you know that I saw you checking me out" smile and walk away.  

Practice and master this and then come back for more information.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 06:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cute if you're a girl. If you're a dude, it's just sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 05:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Any of these?](http://www.nudevista.com/?q=diana+doll+massage s=t) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 05:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a picture from her facebook and reverse google image search it.  Add some words like "amateur" and "fuck"  

That's what I'd do. That seems like the best way you'll get results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 05:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Is THIS your card?](http://motherless.com/AC157D8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 05:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Album](http://forum.phun.org/showthread.php?t=593851) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 05:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name is Tessa Taylor. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 04:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Horny Holly?](http://www.teenporntube.com/gallery/horny-holly-full-body-shot-SrPVHNcoEXl.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 04:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like her paw print tattoos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 04:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Adrenalynn](http://www.nudevista.com/?q=adrenalynn s=t) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acted like a bitch and gave women everything I thought they wanted.  I'm glad those days are over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a mailman, I sincerely apologize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Future moments are the BEST! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at Warped Tour with this girl. It was almost the end of the day. "We the Kings" were playing and they brought out Cassidee Pope to sing "We'll Be a Dream" with them. Halfway through the song, time just slowed way down. I looked over at her. It was like she was the only person there.  So beautiful. Things didn't work out but that moment will stick with me forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It blows my mind how many people actually DO follow through with this kind of promise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mom told me an interesting story today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my classmates great-grandfather died recently. The funeral was held today and If you've ever been to a funeral, you know that there are usually two viewings hours apart and the family goes home between them.  

Apparently someone stuck around after the early viewing and stealthily stole the wedding ring off the corpse and took a shit on the floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no place for you here, you murderer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing, when they heard about the Polars... I hope you're happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you started with 10 Link Karma and 50 Comment karma, and links and comments costed Karma to post, would there be less crap on Reddit? or more reposts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 03:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 02:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Polar Bears committed mass suicide after you killed Grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 02:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably volunteer to be slaughtered for food because I have no valuable skills. Especially in an apocalypse situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 02:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things are worse but people are also candy-asses. They have this "zero-tolerance" policy now that if you're caught fighting, both parties get in trouble. You're not allowed to whoop the bully's ass for him anymore because you need to be the "stronger" person and tell a teacher instead, so they can in turn say "Well, there isn't really anything I can do bout it unless I see it, so why don't you just try to steer clear of him from now on?" 

Society created this problem by punishing victims. Much like the gun debate, bullies aren't going to stop bullying because it's all of a sudden "illegal (so to speak) yet you've effectively stopped victims from defending themselves. Now the victims think they're protected when they actually aren't but they also know that they can't put an end to it through violence or they're going down for it too even though they were only defending themselves. 

*EDIT:* Grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 02:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "repost" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 02:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tap everyone on the shoulder first and let them know you're about to do it so they have a chance to leave. Also compliment their penis size so they don't get offended that you touched them while they're urinating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 02:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Internet Russians are immediately and completely trustworthy... Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 01:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll be DMing though. That should be one hell of a campaign! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 01:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KILL IT WITH FIRE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 01:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you talking about? It's the same picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 01:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After viewing the images, his soul was absorbed by Nick Cage. That's why he has the capability of playing such a diverse range of characters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 01:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that little thing on the right is the transmission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 15:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Teeth" was a better description than "horn"... Tusks trumped teeth. Sweet progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 14:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. All my original comment said was "They're teeth"

Then I noticed I had -7 points and I was like "WTF!?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 09:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start inbreeding some horses and maybe one day a horse will grow a tooth out through it''s skull. Keep me updated with the results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 08:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't mind if we "light up" then!

because they spin tires also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 08:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. The tusks are enlarged incisors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 07:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She should dye your hair too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 07:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's an album... No name though](http://fapdu.com/horny-busty-amateur-girl.pics) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 07:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like her name IS Barbie Brilliant... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 06:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing she fixed that mistake... Bad grammar can be really embarrassing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every. Single. Day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 06:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 06:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, these are the kind of guys that get girls... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 06:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could we call it a curb? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 06:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes... I'm going to spend my Saturday with ANAL_SLICER... Nice try.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 05:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, good sir.  All subjects should be resolved so succinctly. 

*EDIT:* Wow... That went south REAL quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 04:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. But "Most religious" doesn't say a lot from my family... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tusks are teeth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, but you really don't have to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about it?

It's designed so you slip it halfway under something so that someone thinks they've found five dollars. When they pull it out, they're supposed to see that its not real and become disappointed and flip it over to see that it has a christian message and... BAM... Now the finder is supposed to want to go to church to find christ and give his/her life meaning...   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that too. I even considered making another post elsewhere dedicated to that. Feel free to try it for yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... If you've actually lost respect for him and you're not a good actor, then you're boned.

Otherwise, just say "Hey, I was looking for some candy in your room and I found your stash. Is it cool if I start smoking again?"

Now, in this situation, you don't have to start smoking again if you don't want to but this will let him know that you're cool with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right!

This could solve so many of the worlds problems! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't think it's as bad as you think it will be. 

I used to get in trouble all the time for porn that my dad had watched but he wouldn't man up and admit. I didn't figure this out until I was old/savvy enough to remember what I watched and delete my own browser history.   

My parents have always been ok about everything. Even when they found out I smoked weed and when they found out I drank underage.  I've always talked it out with them.

No matter what approach you take, the end result is the same. You HAVE to talk about it.  Just make sure he knows that you're not going to hold it against him or respect him any less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 03:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could do that.
or you could make something up like "Why does it smell like weed in here?" even if it doesn't.
or "Hey, I found some weed on the floor and I just wanna let you know it wasn't mine in case you happen to see it in the trash"  then wait for him to start rifling through the trash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once used a pink pen to draw some sweet shades on Andrew Jackson and made him look like Elton John.  My waitress from that day still laughs about it when she sees me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assalone

I one saw a package adressed to a woman named "Lurethria" also... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if the wrong side of the cookie comes off??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You win. 

No one gives a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're teeth.

*EDIT:* Holy fuck. They are. I still upvoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Products have warnings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to him about it, like an adult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nick Cage, Nick Cage, Nick Cage, Nick Cage, and Nick Cage

John Wayne, Liam Neeson, Al Pacino, Robert DeNiro, and Jason Statham </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have they fucked yet? Perhaps they should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know exactly what you mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was my sister's tip. She was pissed until I told her that I'd buy it from her for $2.  

I ripped her off so bad!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 02:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took a picture of a Ford F-150 Raptor one day because I had never seen one before but my cousin talked about them all the time...

The guy slams his brakes, throws it in park, jumps out and starts running toward my shitty old truck yelling about me taking a picture of his "license plate". I damn near pissed my pants.  After explaining the situation, he felt like an asshole. I've never taken another picture of anyone else's car though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 01:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister works at a pizza shop. She got this, and only this, as a "tip". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 01:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how much time someone put into designing this bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you si... Hey fuck you! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 01:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 21:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You want me to cite a specific case? 

You're definitely one to be throwing around the word childish.  I can't figure out if I should hate you or feel bad for you. You're obviously not that smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 09:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 403 Forbidden? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 09:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lindsey Meadows! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 09:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I've seen her... I'm just not sure where. I'm actually still looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 08:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just did... 

Seriously, piss off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 08:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Big Tits At Work](http://www.porn-star.com/nikki/index.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 08:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Brooke Scott?](http://www.yobt.com/content/750757/brooke-scott.html?wmid=611 sid=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 08:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best guess is Riley Reid... Probably not her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 08:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats Rikki Six!

Good taste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 08:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
