<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4116</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GGG did not intend for Frost Wall to be used to one shot bosses. Sometimes the way things are designed have unintended consequences, but those consequences are not glitches or bugs. That is not what those words mean. A glitch or bug is a fault in the way something was coded. This is coded perfectly fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this a bug? Izaro is killed before he starts any attack phases, so he instantly goes down. Everything is working as intended. It's like calling the Frost Wall shenanigans a bug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've provided my evidence, a trusted source. If that's not enough I suggest you do some research. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've provided my evidence, a fairly well respected newspaper making the claim, what's yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to be equating "not completely bankrupt" with "completely unaffected". Yes they still exist, but with a considerably lower valuation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for, ya know, that time they lost 180 million because they [broke some guys guitar](http://www.economist.com/blogs/gulliver/2009/07/did_dave_carroll_cost_united_1). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd be surprised actually. It's not entirely uncommon that people get run over by them, fairly uncommon but less so than you might expect, people sleeping in fields usually. I remember a story about a couple sleeping in a field back where I used to live, got run over by one. But I digress, my point is that you don't usually die from it. There are occasions where people do, but normally you survive. Though I suppose in some respect, considering your motive, that might actually be better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is complete bullshit. Paying out on legitimate cases of wrongdoing on their part does not mean anyone can throw any claim at them and they'd have to pay up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well first off, after reading the other comments along this thread it would appear we disagree on what qualifies as CoC discharge. The build I'm talking about would be what you would call Cospri's Discharge. I call it CoC discharge because it still uses the CoC setup, and Cospri's casts on crit, and the name CoC Discharge has a history.

Secondly, your request is ridiculously nebulous. Show you a video of what? A video of the build killing guardians? Doing strands in less than a certain amount of time? Killing Uber Atziri/Shaper deathless?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your standard for "very good"? Name some things it can't do that preclude it from coming under that category. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ever play some soggy biscuit? Sometimes you're risking it in hopes to not get the biscuit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CoC Discharge is still very good. BV is better than it was last league, if you don't factor in the multiple stacks bug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said that it would only be interesting enough if it *did* happen, so I interpreted that as you questioning the plausibility of it happening since if it's definitely going to happen, whether it has or hasn't happened already is irrelevant. Could you point out where I went wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just letting you know that there's a much more realistic offer on the table than "18 million retweets for a lifetime supply of nuggets". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but is too emotional to access it.

I think that's mostly true, but I'd put it differently. I'd say that while his problem is emotions, it's not that he's too emotional per sey, but rather that he was taught to bottle up his emotions and power through them and so has never learned to cope with the feelings he's had since childhood surrounding his parents death.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ones murder the other is terrorism

That is incorrect sir. The definition of terrorism is not "murder committed for religious reasons", or any variation thereof. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A guy being offered free nugs for life by not only Wendy's if he hits 18 million retweets, but Tmobile straight up offering him the nugs "and more" if he switches from AT T isn't awesome to you? Is your bar that high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Tmobile has already offered him free Wendy's nugs for life "and more" if he switches from AT T. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amount Ziz payed per mirrior: ~1800chaos

Price of mirrors in LSC: ~11872c

But yeah, totally the same thing.

Not saying the guy is a cheater or w/e, but your comparison is ridiculous. Mirrors are alot cheaper in HC, this is the case every league as far as I'm aware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying that if you "free up the market" prices will become the same as they are in other countries? In other words, insurance companies will, for no reason, make far less money in America by paying more for the healthcare they need to provide but charging the same amount for the insurance? And you think this will happen if you just "free up the market"? Does "free up the market" mean " sprinkle magical pixie dust" in American? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also far more expensive than it needs to be because the healthcare it pays for is far more expensive than it needs to be. But I get the feeling you'd prefer to ignore that aspect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're leaving the price of insurance out of that equation you couldn't be more wrong, if you are leaving insurance out of that equation then you're just plain intellectually dishonest.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You aren't serious, right? The supreme court made their decision on same sex marriage in 2015, while countries like Spain, the Netherlands, Canada, and Belgium legalized it as early as 2000, and as late as 2005.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think that gun ownership costs 0 tax dollars?

Also, great job you've analogized two ridiculously different things in a reductionist manner so as to make it seem like their point is dumb. Does that make you feel better about your shitty healthcare system? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  that is the most expensive in the world by a huge margin, even when accounting for the quality of the care

FTFY
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Experiment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he has been a redditor for 11 years, so 40k karma is only ~10 karma a day on average. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://np.reddit.com/r/funny/comments/35fyl8/my_favorite_jackie_chan_story/cr47urw/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, hate the things actually. My hobby is sticking them into boxes with vials of poison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saffron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely agree. Something reminiscent of Darkshrines would be amazing, but with a more competitive aspect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't bothered to do shaper yet, but I've got all Guardians down on my Cospri's Discharge build with not too much trouble outside of some annoyance with Chimera and a few one-shots from Minotaur. Feel free to have a look if you want, character is MuzeCock.

https://www.pathofexile.com/account/view-profile/Muzebreak/characters  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
