<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 22:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops, wrong play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations to Jay Ajayi for forcing the fumble! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 12:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This ain't no Mudd Club.  Or CBGB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This season's NFL playoffs are beginning with three games, in order, featuring teams from Houston, Detroit, and Pittsburgh P-A. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 12:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This ain't no party.    
This ain't no disco.    
This ain't no foolin' around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 12:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely the appropriate theme music for this wild-card weekend is the verse of ["Life During Wartime", by Talking Heads,](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DblvhECdws0) that begins:    
*Heard about Houston*    
*Heard about Detroit*    
*Heard about Pittsburgh P-A...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I root against certain teams after the Steelers are eliminated, and generally cheer for the AFC in the Super Bowl, but changing my flair would feel disloyal to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 20:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'd never jump on another team's bandwagon.  That also means I understand why I haven't yet seen a comment from anyone on the Steelers bandwagon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 14:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've been here for years    
Rockin' your peers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 13:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, the Steelers had 0 playoff wins in 39 years.  Then they won 4 Super Bowls in the next 8 years.  So don't give up, Lions, you have the NFL right where you want it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe because [when the going gets tough, the tough get going.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m1DxjjUrZhw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strawberry Switchblade - Since Yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 12:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting /r/onehitwonders. Only moderator inactive for three years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 11:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 11:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their big hit was ["Since Yesterday."](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x7QPBzAJ_io) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 04:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Green's practice on Thursday didn't go well, and he didn't practice today.  So don't count on him Sunday.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep an eye in WR Sammie Coates against the Dolphins.  He may finally be fully healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Steelers defenders received not only zero selections, but in fact *zero votes*?!

Thanks for the bulletin board material, AP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 00:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me more about this fried ravioli. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only they'd bring back *NFL Primetime*, then I could handle Berman's shtick forever.

NBC, I don't know what you're doing with the rights to NFL highlights, but it ain't *NFL Primetime*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 22:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool.

The Pass Charts visualization struggles with Antonio Brown, and presumably anyone else with 100 or more targets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Ninite help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... you put MRW in links frequently, and have been texting about both a recent purchase and some sort of game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you, or rather they, begin by updating Adobe Acrobat before printing the price list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scoring defense is a stat *heavily* influenced by the Patriots' high-powered, low-turnover offense.  [Opponents started on their own 24.87-yard line, on average, against the Patriots' defense this year!](http://www.footballoutsiders.com/stats/drivestatsdef)  That was the worst opponents' field position, on average, in the league.

Advanced stats that [take into account the Patriots' weak strength of schedule](http://www.footballoutsiders.com/stats/teamdef) point to a solid defense against the run, but also to a vulnerable defense against the pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what is the real weakness of the Patriots?  Their mediocre defense, especially their decidedly mediocre pass defense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Steelers' "weakness" is that they twice let players score touchdowns... **in two situations in which the best strategic move, once the opponents got the first down, was to let them score.**

I agree that our defense can be inconsistent, but the justification is absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd tell him that I'll make a great attach when he becomes ambassador to Ireland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ross Cockrell and Justin Gilbert could both definitely improve their CB play.  Ross Cockrell has played 98% of snaps and has 0 interceptions.  Justin Gilbert was originally drafted eighth overall by the Cleveland Browns; he was a bust there, and the Steelers traded a sixth-round pick to get him.  He needs to start pushing for playing time on defense.

Jarvis Jones has been a bit disappointing at LB.  Ryan Shazier has been a great LB, but needs to stay consistently healthy.  Vince Williams was a good find in the sixth round, but it would be great to see him step up from "career backup" level.

Daniel McCullers has been slowly coming along at DT.  No complaints for a sixth-round pick, but if I were greedy, I'd ask for him to push for playing time as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first two of those head coaches retired, and the third is still coaching, so the Steelers haven't *fired* a head coach since Bill Austin at the end of 1968. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 17:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about a coach that starts off hot, and then has a couple of losing seasons?  Say...

* 11-5, lose first playoff game

* 9-7, lose first playoff game

* 12-4, win first playoff game, lose second playoff game

* 11-5, win first two playoff games, lose Super Bowl

* 10-6, win first playoff game, lose second playoff game

* 11-5, win first playoff game, lose second playoff game

* 7-9, no playoffs

* 6-10, no playoffs

Is it time to let this coach go now?  How about if the next season is:

* 9-7, no playoffs?

Of course, this is Bill Cowher, and after that 9-7 season, the next five seasons are:

* 13-3, win first playoff game, lose second playoff game

* 10-5-1, win first playoff game, lose second playoff game

* 6-10

* 15-1, win first playoff game, lose second playoff game

* 11-5, win three straight playoff games on the road, then win Super Bowl XL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 16:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the hilarious thing.  It's a Dolphins fan on Twitter... reposting [a picture from 2011... taken by **RAVENS** fans.](http://www.freedomcardboard.com/forum/showthread.php/75267-i-hate-the-steelers-and-am-soooo-happy-they-lost?p=1166833 viewfull=1#post1166833) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please elaborate on "computational evolution".  Do you mean what computer scientists refer to by the term of art "genetic algorithms"?  What function do you use to evaluate the fitness of your evolved population?  How do you generate new candidates in the population?  If fitness is based on actual results with human subjects, what ethical concerns arise with testing your candidate solutions?  Does an ethical requirement to discard poor candidates quickly tend to restrict you to a strict hill-climbing approach? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU THINK 25F WAS COLD?  THAT'S CUTE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe threeish years after this year?  And my hopes are for one more Super Bowl win in that timeframe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert Golden didn't participate in practice yesterday, but had limited participation today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 22:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [YOU'D BE SURPRISED](http://pfref.com/tiny/YghKs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah.

Maybe the Patriots will get to six Super Bowl wins after LII.  In that case, at least the AFC would finally catch up to the NFC again.

But if that doesn't happen, you're making a pretty big assumption that by the time the Patriots win six Super Bowls, the Steelers will still have only won six. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 20:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh?  The Patriots are equally as successful as the Steelers when it comes to Super Bowl wins over the last ten years.

The only two-time Super Bowl champion over the last ten years: the New York Giants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 19:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I wish you had a healthy Tannehill -- always better to face teams at their best -- but Moore is a perfectly fine backup, and "next man up" is ever the watchword. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears that you're echoing both this phrase from the article...

New England has been the NFL's best team over the past decade, and no one else even comes close.

... and the obvious caveat: "as long as you don't care about Super Bowl wins." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JUST WAIT TILL YOU ENCOUNTER THE COLD

Y'ALL ARE DOLPHINS, NOT NARWHALS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any cool algorithms, parallel or otherwise, behind the tech? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, [there are only six players with at least 1,000 total *career* passing yards and 1,000 total *career* receiving yards.](http://pfref.com/tiny/XUHXN) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot, in fact, see that we were fairly "iffy" when it came to predicting the outcomes of games.  I cannot see where we predicted the outcomes of these games at all.

If you're arguing that we should have anticipated matchups between two playoff teams more than other matchups, I suppose that's generally true, but not universally.  For example, we'd have anticipated Steelers at Bengals regardless of the teams' records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see the problem.  The Evil League of Evil advanced to the postseason at a ratio of 5/7.  That's a perfect score. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 13:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **CHEEZ-ITS! CHEEZ-ITS! CHEEZ-ITS!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be that the headline was inspired by the reddit story, though: believable, if unsubstantiated, reddit story inspires fake news writer to create fake news story with similar plot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's neat to see this original version of a famous song by the same artist that made it famous.

For anyone interested in original versions of famous songs by *different* artists than those that made them famous, there's /r/woahthatsacover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They literally didn't have an offense that could stop throwing the ball.  **Their roster had no TEs.**  They were using the "run and shoot offense". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 00:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The demise of NFL Primetime was a huge loss for NFL fans.  Closest substitute I've found so far is the NFL channel on YouTube.  Yes, commentary on NFL highlights is **so bad** these days that just showing the key plays with the original commentators is superior to anything else I've seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case anyone was confused, Tony Dorsett's team, on offense, was the one with only ten men when he scored his 99-yard touchdown run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Courtesy of /u/Twentington1 on /r/ObscureMedia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruce Woolley - Video Killed the Radio Star [Made famous by The Buggles] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're looking for /r/woahthatsacover, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 05:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've actually completed four years on reddit, and are on your fifth year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 00:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 2 games had EVEN lines all season?  Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, no one was too surprised when the 15-1 Steelers lost to the Patriots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming the Chiefs even get a chance to face the Patriots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still poking around for an answer to the question.  Eric Dickerson and Curt Warner went #1 and #3 in 1983, their rookie season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Where to find SIX NAPOLEONS.](/Watch the end credits of S4E1 carefully.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SIX NAPOLEONS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just posting here for anyone else who saw SIX NAPOLEONS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 16:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's another Easter egg not mentioned in this article, a reference to:

**SIX NAPOLEONS** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 00:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't the LA Rams concede a touchdown like this at one point in the 1980s?  /u/JaguarGator9 and /u/ChiBears85, what say you?

Of course, the Chargers started a playoff game against the Steelers after the 1982 season by conceding a touchdown on a kickoff they were receiving, but the Chargers went on to win that game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Raiders, Chargers, or both: please stop being pathetic, at least for this week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 00:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 15:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Chargers may have let some good coaches go too early.  Disclaimer: I haven't followed the Chargers too closely, and I agree with the conventional wisdom that a coach who "loses the locker room" has to be let go.  So if any of these coaches lost the locker room, my mistake; they did need to be let go.

It seems as if the Chargers didn't want to let Bobby Ross go.  But I consider the firings of Marty Schottenheimer and Norv Turner to be mistakes.

Schottenheimer's playoff record was understandably a concern... but two games is such a small sample size in a league where a bad bounce can change everything.

Norv Turner's last three years: 9-7, 8-8, 7-9.  Compare Bill Cowher, 1998-2000: 7-9, 6-10, 9-7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 14:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There might be a few other teams who tend to hang onto their coaches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a side effect of 2048 looking very neat in base 2: 100000000000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 13:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If, however, the Bucs somehow don't make it to the playoffs this year, then this post should be supplemented with at least one other season in which a team needed four games to go their way: 1989.

That year, the Steelers won their last game and made the playoffs by getting the necessary results from three other games that week, the last of which was on Monday night (thanks Vikings).  In contrast to 2006, though, the Steelers and all three of the other teams they needed to win were all favored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Terry Bradshaw called all his own plays, so things are a bit murkier when trying to separate his personal success from the success of the Steelers offense in his days.

On the other hand, he obviously benefited from the Steel Curtain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mentioned NE win Oakland win, and NE win KC loss.  The other win-loss scenario (ignoring ties) that gives Miami the 6 seed and Oak the 2 seed is NE loss Oakland win KC win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emmanuel Sanders, etc.

The Steelers have also made a few mistakes by failing to appreciate the players they had.  Certainly Rod Woodson; arguably Mike Vrabel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 16:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Steelers have a history of paying well to retain absolute best-in-class talent, but of letting go a lot of first-class talent just a half-step below best-in-class.

Bell appears to qualify to get paid by the Steelers, but we'll see how it works out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 14:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when Mike Vrabel had the game-clinching interception to *defeat* the Patriots 7-6 in a playoff game?  Good times, good times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 20:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This is what the game would look like if you were in the worst seat in the house." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 13:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like [Italy "realistically" controlled its destiny against Bulgaria in Euro 2004.](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/UEFA_Euro_2004_Group_C) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 12:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An analogous situation was 1982, when with one game left to play in a strike-shortened season, Cleveland had clinched a playoff spot... *unless Cleveland lost and Buffalo and New England tied*.

Cleveland lost to Pittsburgh and Buffalo and New England were all tied up in the fourth quarter, but eventually New England won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was sat at home eating Christmas desserts when Poe throw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naw, Dontari's team is making it to the playoffs.  That other Poe's team's season... is nevermore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, you know, most of the NFL used to play both offense and defense, although the last of those players retired in 1962: Chuck Bednarik. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Dontari Poe is still in the playoffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 06:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay.

By that point, we might even have enough players healthy to play more than two down linemen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 06:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 346... for Dontari Poe...might have the right digits for his weight, but seemingly not in the right order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 05:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listed... *listed* at 346 pounds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 05:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're OB Jesus, yes you're the real Jesus    
All you other B Jesuses are just tryna tease us    
So won't the real OB Jesus, please stand up    
Please stand up    
Please stand up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 05:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I've woken up from a really long coma!  I must send a telegram about professional football immediately!  Please convey me to the closest telegraph office with all due haste!"

"Uh, here's a web browser pointing to /r/nfl on reddit.  Good luck." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trust me, I watched it on TV at the time.  The ball is on Aaron Bailey's chest, but clearly, clearly hit the ground after.  This was not a controversial ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 23:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS Harbaugh threw that pass, and the last few of that drive, with a **dislocated finger on his throwing hand**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 09:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also the 1993 film entitled [*The Nightmare Before Christmas*.](http://movies.disney.com/the-nightmare-before-christmas) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 01:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colts still have a slim chance against the Raiders as of this writing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pittsburgh will clinch at least the #3 Seed with a win over Baltimore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 00:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washington's and Cleveland's victories will enable Pittsburgh to clinch the strength-of-victory tiebreaker over Houston, should Pittsburgh defeat Baltimore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pittsburgh will clinch at least the #3 seed with a win over Baltimore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 00:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Internet suggests that the Blue Palms Brewhouse on Hollywood Boulevard is a Steelers bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the price of a dime, you can always talk to her.

In 1981, when a pay phone call cost a dime.

And when there were still pay phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But "no penalty" would have been the wrong decision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing to keep in mind is that the Strength of Victory tiebreaker can come into play when teams decide whether to play their starters, even if the final standings don't use the tiebreaker.

For example, this season, suppose that Pittsburgh were to defeat Baltimore, Houston were to defeat Cincinnati, and Oakland were to defeat Indianapolis.  Suppose further that Pittsburgh were to get the combination of other results necessary to clinch the Strength of Victory tiebreaker over Houston: for example, assuming that Oakland were to defeat Indianapolis, Washington defeating Chicago would suffice.

In this scenario, Pittsburgh is locked into the #3 seed.  The Strength of Victory tiebreaker has come into play with one game left in the season.

Now suppose Pittsburgh rests Roethlisberger, Brown, and Bell against Cleveland... but Landry Jones, Fitzgerald Toussaint, and Eli Rogers lead Pittsburgh to victory anyway.  Well, Pittsburgh is then the only 11-5 team in the AFC, so they're not involved in any tiebreakers at the end of the season.  But Strength of Victory nevertheless made a big difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 15:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the reasons that replay doesn't work as well in the beautiful game is that sometimes replay actually doesn't show the foul.  [Esse Baharmast's penalty call for Norway against Brazil](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7-lNODXuA6k) is a famous example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 21:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, Coach, I would have made the point after, but the goalposts kept moving backwards! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks -- the reminder about the NFL app for Verizon customers will be extremely useful if I get temporarily stuck at somebody else's house on Sunday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your original video has been taken down, but NFL.com has this one: http://www.nfl.com/videos/pittsburgh-steelers/0ap2000000146413/The-Immaculate-Reception </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seem to recall on the 25th anniversary, in 1997, NBC showing for the first time an alternate camera angle that made it extremely clear that the ball bounced off the shoulder pads of Jack Tatum (legal), not off Frenchy Fuqua (illegal back then).

Edit: [found it.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YMksKd9Jjho)  Let's pretend I didn't say anything about shoulder pads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Bowl XVIII was in 1984, not 1884. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *If that guy speaks*    
*With five stressed beats*    
*Then you can bet*    
*That that gent*    
*Is a classy bloke*    

*The guys in hose*   
*Who talk in prose*     
*Are prob'ly low-class*     
*Or servants*    
*Who make the jokes...*

[Source.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aHWhswbRZA0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Pittsburgh defeats Baltimore, Pittsburgh hasn't yet clinched the strength-of-victory tiebreaker on Houston, but could do so on Saturday, possibly with help from tonight's result.  If Pittsburgh defeats Baltimore, Pittsburgh would need two and a half good results from the following list to clinch the strength-of-victory tiebreaker over Houston, with a tie counting as half a good result.

Week 16:

* New York Giants defeat Philadelphia.

* Buffalo defeats Miami.

* Washington defeats Chicago.

* Chicago loses to Washington.  Yes, that means that a Washington victory over Chicago counts as two good results for Pittsburgh, not just one; a Washington-Chicago tie counts as one good result, not just one-half; and a Chicago victory over Washington is still zero.

* Cleveland defeats San Diego.

* Jets defeat New England.

* Oakland defeats Indianapolis (which would, however, be fatal to Pittsburgh's outside shot at a #2 seed.)

* Dallas defeats Detroit.


(Obviously, if Houston loses to or ties Cincinnati in Week 16, then Pittsburgh can clinch a better record than Houston by defeating Baltimore.)

If Pittsburgh defeats Baltimore, but hasn't quite received all two and a half or more good results from other games in week 16, and Houston defeats Cincinnati, then even if Pittsburgh loses to Cleveland in week 17 and Houston defeats Tennessee in week 17... Pittsburgh still can add good results from the following list to the previous list to add up to two and a half:

* Green Bay defeats Detroit.

* Indianapolis defeats Jacksonville.

* Minnesota defeats Chicago.

If I made a mistake, /u/NFLPlayoffScenarios can probably catch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 21:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll cheer for any AFC team in the Super Bowl.  It's been my wish since Super Bowl XXV to have the AFC catch up to the NFC in Super Bowl victories.  Right now, it's NFC 26, AFC 24.

Of course, the Patriots are far from my preferred AFC Super Bowl representative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Buffalo_Bill_Cody

"Bills" won a 1947 contest for the nickname, because it was an allusion to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 19:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if [Guy on a Buffalo](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iJ4T9CQA0UM) taught me anything, it's that a bison is still regularly referred to as a buffalo.  We don't have any other wild buffalo in North America, and precious little water buffalo livestock, so there's rarely any confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 19:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Steelers are more likely to lose to the Browns if the Steelers have already clinched the AFC North, so I'm not sure you want to cheer for this result already, with Bayesian inference and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 18:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Steelers could end up with absolutely nothing to play for against the Browns, being already locked into the #3 seed.  Could Landry Jones and a cast of backups lose to the Browns even more easily than the starters could?  Yes, yes they could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEH, FAN OF THE PURPLE BROWNS WHO THINKS HE KNOWS SOMETHING ABOUT STEEL... GETS TOLD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, was at a block party for that game, hosted by a Wolverine friend.  Was not watching, heard the dismay, caught the highlight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The voiceover is why the album version is clearly better than the song in OP's linked video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 17:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a business meeting in a restaurant's private room with the door closed, nowhere near the state of Alabama, when this play happened.  I'll always remember hearing the roar through the closed door, realizing that it was from the Iron Bowl watchers, and wondering whether the highlight I'd see later would be worth it.

Obviously, it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 16:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neuroscientist Jim Fallon famously discovered through neuroimaging that his own brain had the low activity in the orbital cortex associated with psychopaths.  Therefore, a two-part question:

1) How do you handle the privacy concerns in your work?  One can imagine neuroimaging bringing unwelcome attention to a patient with certain brain characteristics.

2) Have you looked at neuroimaging results on your own brains, and what did you discover? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, for Steelers fans this is a highlight burned into their nightmares.  If he had made the field goal (and the Chargers had then not come back to score in the last four seconds), the Steelers would have advanced to the playoffs after the 2013 season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/notapantsday just made this video [for this comment.](https://np.reddit.com/r/Unexpected/comments/5jjpo9/opening_a_beer/dbgv9mb/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opening a beer with a sheet of paper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 22:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Steeler in the running for NFL MVP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody at the NFL is twisting the knife in the Steelers.  This is [Ryan Succop we're talking about.](http://www.nfl.com/videos/nfl-game-highlights/0ap2000000305995/Succop-misses-game-winning-field-goal) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wholeheartedly agree!

It's only a partial repayment on the debt, though, because the Steelers are already self-motivated to win, whereas the Bills won in Week 17 last year after having already been eliminated from playoff contention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 17:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this Steelers dream scenario, can we throw in an OAK loss as well?

*Baby bye bye bye*... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 14:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a layperson in this field, is the following summary of my understanding correct?

* Most of the time, *C. trachomatis* divides into two cells similar in spatial dimensions, but differentiated by one being MOMP-heavy and the other being Hsp60-heavy.

* Sometimes, however, two or more smaller MOMP-heavy cells bud from the original larger Hsp60-heavy cell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 10:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hall of Fame is also a marketing gimmick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 02:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extremely clever, accounting for the two Super Bowls won by AFL teams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough.  I'm always looking to improve my understanding of English dialectical differences, so thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes... but do you ever use the phrase: "In college, ..."?  Or is it all "At uni, ..."? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washing our produce also prevents consumption of foodborne pathogens.  So keep washing produce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 23:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still use it for my avatar on a couple of forums.  No problems there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or even someone who missed 18.75% of the season, otherwise known as "this comment is the first mention of Le'Veon Bell in this thread." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pro Football Reference has [a list that appears to be reliable going all the way back to 1946,](http://pfref.com/tiny/bccKR) on which this season's Bills currently rank sixth.  There are indeed no teams between the 1963 Chargers and the 2016 Bills, so the 2016 Bills would rank fourth on the since-1954 list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... you'd bet nineteen months of reddit gold against one month of reddit gold that the Packers will defeat the Vikings?  Because I'll take that bet right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will surely be the best story set in 2049 since *Miner 2049er*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right.  The Eagles have still scored more points than their opponents this season.  They have fallen prey to the randomness of close games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 15:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's as crazy as any East Coast teams, college or pro, naming themselves the Hurricanes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 13:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a cursory search of charities accepting Bitcoin, the best fit I've found so far is tunapanda.org.  In an attempt to assess their legitimacy, I tried to quickly locate their Form 990, but was unsuccessful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Early favorite for AFC Special Teams Player of the Week.  6/6 FGs plus that tackle to save four points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 00:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From basic astronomical record keeping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 22:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the mayor of Phoenix, wasn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 22:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disrespecting the Terrible Towel has frequently been bad juju. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 17:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2015, the then-St. Louis Rams had to switch to a silent count on offense at home, because of traveling Steelers fans.

[Source.](https://mobile.twitter.com/jthom1/status/648247786840821761) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 14:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you really want the Patriots to meet the Steelers in the playoffs, right?  The Patriots have dominated that postseason match-up ever since Mike Vrabel stopped being a Steeler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 11:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I told him, "Listen, buddy, I don't take my clothes off for anybody, even if it **is** artistic!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can confirm that the flair process is so easy that you can go out drinking and playing cards, walk home slightly inebriated, get on reddit and decide to finally get your /r/science flair, take a pic of your diploma, send it to the mods with the required details, and just like that, you have flair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 20:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Computer science counts like this: 0, 1, 2, 3, ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 13:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  [Reuters reports:](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-papua-quake-idUSKBN1460CF)
The PTWC said tsunami waves were possible in the next three hours along some coasts of not only Papua New Guinea but also Indonesia, the Solomon Islands, Pohnpei, Chuuk, Nauru, Kosrae and Vanuatu.

Just in case you are in the danger zone and reading reddit, here are NOAA's tsunami safety rules.

* A strong earthquake felt in a low-lying coastal area is a natural warning of possible, immediate danger. Keep calm and quickly move to higher ground away from the coast.

*	 Not all large earthquakes cause tsunamis, but many do. If the quake is located near or directly under the ocean, the probability of a tsunami increases. When you hear that an earthquake has occurred under the ocean or coastline regions, prepare for a tsunami emergency.

*	 Tsunamis can occur at any time, day or night. They can travel up rivers and streams that lead to the ocean.

*	 A tsunami is not a single wave, but a series of waves. The largest wave may occur several hours after arrival. Stay out of danger until an "ALL CLEAR" is issued by a competent authority.

*	 Approaching tsunamis are sometimes heralded by noticeable rise or fall of coastal waters. This is nature's tsunami warning and should be heeded.

*	 Approaching large tsunamis are usually accompanied by a loud roar that sounds like a train or aircraft. If a tsunami arrives at night when you can not see the ocean, this is also nature's tsunami warning and should be heeded.

*	 A small tsunami at one beach can be a giant a few miles away. Don't let the modest size of one make you lose respect for all.

*	 Never go down to the beach to watch for a tsunami!
WHEN YOU CAN SEE THE WAVE YOU ARE TOO CLOSE TO ESCAPE.
Tsunamis can move faster than a person can run!

*	 During a tsunami emergency, your local emergency management office, police, fire and other emergency organizations will try to save your life. Give them your fullest cooperation.

*	 Homes and other buildings located in low lying coastal areas are not safe. Do NOT stay in such buildings if there is a tsunami warning.

*	 The upper floors of high, multi-story, reinforced concrete hotels can provide refuge if there is no time to quickly move inland or to higher ground.

*	 If you are on a boat or ship, weather and time-permitting, move your vessel to deeper water (at least 150 feet). If it is the case that there is concurrent severe weather, it may may safer to leave the boat at the pier and physically move to higher ground.

*	 Damaging wave activity and unpredictable currents can effect harbor conditions for a period of time after the tsunami's initial impact. Be sure conditions are safe before you return your boat or ship to the harbor.

*	 Stay tuned to your local radio, marine radio, NOAA Weather Radio, or television stations during a tsunami emergency - bulletins issued through your local emergency management office and National Weather Service offices can save your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magnitude 8.0 quake hits east of Papua New Guinea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 13:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 13:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edited to add this paragraph.  [Reuters reports:](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-papua-quake-idUSKBN1460CF)
The PTWC said tsunami waves were possible in the next three hours along some coasts of not only Papua New Guinea but also Indonesia, the Solomon Islands, Pohnpei, Chuuk, Nauru, Kosrae and Vanuatu.

Just in case you are in the danger zone and reading reddit, here are NOAA's tsunami safety rules.

* A strong earthquake felt in a low-lying coastal area is a natural warning of possible, immediate danger. Keep calm and quickly move to higher ground away from the coast.

*	 Not all large earthquakes cause tsunamis, but many do. If the quake is located near or directly under the ocean, the probability of a tsunami increases. When you hear that an earthquake has occurred under the ocean or coastline regions, prepare for a tsunami emergency.

*	 Tsunamis can occur at any time, day or night. They can travel up rivers and streams that lead to the ocean.

*	 A tsunami is not a single wave, but a series of waves. The largest wave may occur several hours after arrival. Stay out of danger until an "ALL CLEAR" is issued by a competent authority.

*	 Approaching tsunamis are sometimes heralded by noticeable rise or fall of coastal waters. This is nature's tsunami warning and should be heeded.

*	 Approaching large tsunamis are usually accompanied by a loud roar that sounds like a train or aircraft. If a tsunami arrives at night when you can not see the ocean, this is also nature's tsunami warning and should be heeded.

*	 A small tsunami at one beach can be a giant a few miles away. Don't let the modest size of one make you lose respect for all.

*	 Never go down to the beach to watch for a tsunami!
WHEN YOU CAN SEE THE WAVE YOU ARE TOO CLOSE TO ESCAPE.
Tsunamis can move faster than a person can run!

*	 During a tsunami emergency, your local emergency management office, police, fire and other emergency organizations will try to save your life. Give them your fullest cooperation.

*	 Homes and other buildings located in low lying coastal areas are not safe. Do NOT stay in such buildings if there is a tsunami warning.

*	 The upper floors of high, multi-story, reinforced concrete hotels can provide refuge if there is no time to quickly move inland or to higher ground.

*	 If you are on a boat or ship, weather and time-permitting, move your vessel to deeper water (at least 150 feet). If it is the case that there is concurrent severe weather, it may may safer to leave the boat at the pier and physically move to higher ground.

*	 Damaging wave activity and unpredictable currents can effect harbor conditions for a period of time after the tsunami's initial impact. Be sure conditions are safe before you return your boat or ship to the harbor.

*	 Stay tuned to your local radio, marine radio, NOAA Weather Radio, or television stations during a tsunami emergency - bulletins issued through your local emergency management office and National Weather Service offices can save your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 12:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for upvoting the thread so I saw it, everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 21:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the Colts play in a dome.  They don't have any horrific weather.  There's some weird thing about it they makes everyone I.  The stadium babe together more than normal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
