<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3931</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you please explain who "leeches off the hard work of authors"? Are you possibly referring to, among others, editors? Because editors are what make print books immeasurably more professional than self-published ebooks. You can tell within an instant when something is self-published and has had no real work put into it other than simply writing out the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I get your logic. I've had my Kindle now for a month, and I do get that overwhelming sense of choice that comes from pirating retro games. And I'm not even pirating the books, I'm using an Overdrive library. I wishlisted 800 books immediately upon buying my Kindle, so excited to have access to all of these books that were before too expensive to buy all at once... and then a day or two later, the choice paralysis hit me. 

So I'm already rationalizing to myself, "well I'll use ebooks as a way to sample books, and any of them I like enough to finish, I'll buy a physical copy." The downside to this is I'm really impatient and will quit a book within 20 pages or something, telling myself it's not worth it and that I have hundreds more books to try out.

I've got mixed feelings about the whole thing, I guess you could say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a Facebook? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about an option to flair posts? Based on discussion, news articles, and any other options you deem suitable? There needs to be some way to filter out the constant "lol guyz do u think real books are better than ebooks? I DO HAHAHA" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, this idea that "long and dense" is automatically a good book, I feel it's a dangerous one. If that's your preference, then that's totally fine. But don't give people the wrong idea, there are absolutely shorter classics as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to /u/pithyretort, this thread is [against the rules](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/5yuwdk/why_does_this_sub_circlejerk_over_demonizing/det2iw7). Waiting for him to lock it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this sub circlejerk about how books are better than ebooks? (self.books) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey /u/pithyretort

Thought you said threads such as these weren't allowed on /r/books. [Or did you lie to us?](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/5yuwdk/why_does_this_sub_circlejerk_over_demonizing/det2iw7) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 06:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely the former. What's the point of the latter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually he's in better shape by default because Uncle Phil is now dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean not that I give a shit, we're powerless to stop this kinda thing - but I'm curious, how can a microphone be recording if the OS is powered down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't aware anyone considered Jack or River as companions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh I prefer the idea of writing piece by piece, that just makes sense. But the way people take about TV, it's always seemed like that's not the case. So TV really is more loose and improvised than they make it sound? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to replace the text above heroes with hero names instead of usernames? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 00:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm incredibly stupid, but sometimes when things get crowded, I find it difficult to tell who I'm healing/boosting as Mercy. When the center of the screen says I'm healing "xXx420ProGramerxXx", that doesn't really tell me much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure that isn't referring to season 11? How could they add him to every episode on such short notice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Writing is like music - it's a sign of good taste to be able to recognise the merit in lots of different styles.


I know this sounds reasonable in theory, but I can't really abide by it in practice. With music, I can listen to pop music that is simply "enjoyable" instead of "amazing" because it's only 3 or 4 minutes long per song. With books, even an easy read is going to take hours of my time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skipped around the first 15 minutes and it's so choppy. Things begin with the scene where Walt and Skyler are buying their house, years ago, interspersed with a couple shots of Walt from season 5 looking at his vandalized house. I'll admit that was interesting and got my hopes up.

But the chronology is so strange. Immediately following is the "chemistry is the study of change" scene. Then you get Walt's cancer diagnosis, then the 50th birthday breakfast, then all of a sudden Gretchen and Elliott's party. And then a little after that, you get to see Walt on his trip with Hank to watch them bust a meth lab.

It just feels very disjointed, and not in an interesting Tarantino-esque way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skipped around the first 15 minutes and it's so choppy. Things begin with the scene where Walt and Skyler are buying their house, years ago, interspersed with a couple shots of Walt from season 5 looking at his vandalized house. I'll admit that was interesting and got my hopes up.

But the chronology is so strange. Immediately following is the "chemistry is the study of change" scene. Then you get Walt's cancer diagnosis, then the 50th birthday breakfast, then all of a sudden Gretchen and Elliott's party. And then a little after that, you get to see Walt on his trip with Hank to watch them bust a meth lab.

It just feels very disjointed, and not in an interesting Tarantino-esque way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not a companion, at least according to the press releases. He's not someone we'll see in every episode.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not a companion, at least according to the press releases. He's not someone we'll see in every episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna have to say no. Skipped around the first 15 minutes and it's so choppy. Things begin with the scene where Walt and Skyler are buying their house, years ago, interspersed with a couple shots of Walt from season 5 looking at his vandalized house. I'll admit that was interesting and got my hopes up.

But the chronology is so strange. Immediately following is the "chemistry is the study of change" scene. Then you get Walt's cancer diagnosis, then the 50th birthday breakfast, then all of a sudden Gretchen and Elliott's party. And then a little after that, you get to see Walt on his trip with Hank to watch them bust a meth lab.

It just feels very disjointed, and not in an interesting Tarantino-esque way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt the type of smart individual the doctor takes on would be that dull. They may ask what is a computer, yes, but then they'd say something like "Ah yes, so this must be the logical conclusion to my abacus!" A bad example, but I don't see how it couldn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why aren't we allowed to have companions from the past or the future? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can have ANYONE because, you know, time travel, and it's always someone from the modern day. Why? They even teased us with the idea of a Victorian Clara before they said "lol no let's go with the boring option again."

Is it primarily because of the silly idea that the companion needs to be an audience surrogate? Because I'm certain that a character from a different time period could serve the same purpose. If anything, maybe someone from the past would be BETTER for that purpose. The doctor would have to find simpler analogies to explain what's happening to someone with a less technologically advanced understanding of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only theory is that most fans (judging by lists ranking the companions) don't seem to like Kamelion, so maybe that one misstep was enough on its own to scare Doctor Who writers from ever again trying something "different." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bad acting and writing was intentional? ... what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sick of modern day companions. Why can't we get anyone from the past or future? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can have ANYONE because, you know, time travel, and it's always someone from the modern day. Why? They even teased us with the idea of a Victorian Clara before they said "lol no let's go with the boring option again." 

Is it primarily because of the silly idea that the companion needs to be an audience surrogate? Because I'm certain that a character from a different time period could serve the same purpose. If anything, maybe someone from the past would be BETTER for that purpose. The doctor would have to find simpler analogies to explain what's happening to someone with a less technologically advanced understanding of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually is terrible news. The acting in the first season was wooden and the dialogue was unbelievable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see how anyone says DBZ is better than Dragon Ball aside from the nostalgia of Toonami. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know of any screenshots of the inside the books? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  However, maybe try to focus on one book at the time, because sometimes the issue isn't the book itself but your attention span. Juggling several novels at the time could certainly reduce the pleasure and investment you can have in either of them.


I think this is probably the biggest thing. I need to stop trying to read four books at the same time. 

And as for exhausting great books and then starting on good books, I've always more enjoyed the idea of just re-reading the great ones. If they're good enough for me to finish, it's almost always because they had to depth to them that I can appreciate even more on a second or third reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSA, CIA, any other three lettered government agency you care to name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the quality of these books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, so I've had a Kindle for about a month now. I'm loving that I don't have to buy books and can just borrow from thousands of books from my library. 

But... I can't bring myself to buy an ebook. There's something weird about it to me, partly due to paranoia of what would happen to my books 10 or 20 years in the future. So for my absolute favorites, I'll keep buying physical books.

A lot of the more interesting books I've noticed lately happen to be from NYRB Classics. So I want to ask, does the binding or the pages feel cheap? I got a few newer books shortly before I got my Kindle, namely Bradbury's The Martian Chronicles and Camus' The Plague, and both of them honestly felt like they'd fall apart if I sneezed on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mentioning those two in the same breath is intriguing... now I want to hear a band that combines the two haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which band or musician do you feel would write a great video game soundtrack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First one that comes immediately to my mind is Dream Theater. I'm not really a fan of their music anymore, seems like they're trying way too hard to impress, but I can't deny that something like [The Dance of Eternity](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Ik9qECIWgc) gets my blood pumping and would be fantastic in an action game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which band or musician do you feel would write a great video game soundtrack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First one that comes immediately to my mind is Dream Theater. I'm not really a fan of their music anymore, seems like they're trying way too hard to impress, but I can't deny that something like [The Dance of Eternity](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Ik9qECIWgc) gets my blood pumping and would be fantastic in an action game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do what I did as a support: uninstall and quit playing the game. If you are at the trench and trying to support four carries, you are fucked. And if you try to say "cant beat em join em" by choosing a 5th core, you're also fucked because of limited farm.

So honestly, if you're not already high MMR, I'd say it's unfortunately a lost cause. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 05:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 27 :x why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do the babies whining about this even mean? Either you take the point or you don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One thing I love about competitive in this game is the refusal to waste your time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the second team caps more points or has their payload travel a greater distance, victory is declared immediately. This is a feature that continues to impress me. I've always hated in multiplayer games when I have to keep playing even when it's clear I've already won or lost. Overwatch treats your time with respect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I'm such a stubborn asshole that I have an issue with nonfiction, too. In theory, I love a lot of nonfiction. It's fascinating stuff. The problem is they'll be like 600 to 800 page long books and seem to repeat themselves over and over to justify that length. Might just be reading the wrong books. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 02:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I find exactly what I think I'd like and then just buy them used. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that actually stated somewhere or just a cute plausible explanation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the problem, high school teachers tend to phrase their interpreations in such a way that they're the objectively correct ones. They don't even hint at the possibility that there are two, five, twenty, hundreds of other interpretations. I realize this is partially to simplify things, but I don't think they understand the damage this does for students. An opportunity to reignite (or begin) a love for reading is lost.

A little story. My junior year teacher had us read one book a month for Accelerated Reader (idk if you've heard of it, it's pretty stupid, you can only read certain books that have a comprehension quiz attached to them.) I read Faulkner's The Sound and the Fury and Woolf's To the Lighthouse back-to-back. Understandably, I would think, I was a little bit mentally exhausted. So after that, I decided I'd try McCullers' The Heart is a Lonely Hunter. But my teacher was like "You know you're smarter than that, why don't you pick something else?" Bitch, are you serious? If I didn't already love reading, I'd have probably been turned off from it for a long at that moment.

I understand reading can and should be used for learning/enlightenment - and this is still my favorite use for it, part of why I'm so A.D.D. about what I read, can't easily find something that suits me - but it's also for entertainment. To put down the McCullers just because it's not as deep as Faulkner or Woolf seems a little absurd to me, especially because it's still more substantial than plenty of other things I could be reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I've always been the type of nerd who loves to think about the meaning of novels but NOT when forced to do so by teachers. When they ask something like "Why was this piece of clothing/furniture red or blue or green", I'm always thinking who gives a fuck? On the other hand, I read literary criticism of my favorite authors like Salinger or Woolf just for fun. I feel like they always had more interesting and surprising insights than my teachers. 

edit: On that note, what's the most interesting lit crit available to read online? Do you have to be a university student to access it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I'm sure it's happened, I can't recall putting down a book due to the story. It's when the writing steers towards the extremes, either too simple or too flashy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, it's funny you mentioned Harry Potter- I reread Sorcerer's Stone a couple days ago and I was honestly pretty frustrated how different it is now that I'm older. Now that I'm more critical of what I read, I was constantly asking "why is he special? why do adults fawn over him? what has he DONE?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arrested Development is soon leaving Netflix, so they probably felt no reason to do such a thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched White Christmas first just because I love Jon Hamm - but I don't see what's wrong with the first episode. I would have absolutely watched that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf is with opinions like these where you need to take a sci-fi show seriously, especially when it's clear that it's trying to be occasionally funny?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ALTHOUGH "Witch" is one of those episodes that becomes a bit more important the later the series goes on (it's where you first meet Amy) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I guess more than other writers, his themes are very apparently repeated from book to book. Within ten pages of Sebastian Knight I was like.. wait.. this just seems like a retelling of Pale Fire, without the cute poem and commentary. And the synopses of a few of his other books just seem like exercises in perfecting the Lolita story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His writing screams "look at me! look at me! I am incredibly witty!" He's not at all transparent and it's annoying as fuck.

[And look at this list where Nabokov trashes basically every well-respected author.](http://wmjas.wikidot.com/nabokov-s-recommendations) Hemingway, Faulkner, Conrad, Balzac, Camus, Cervantes, Dostoevsky, Henry James, Mann, Maupassant, Poe, Sartre, Wilde - nothing is sacred to Nabokov. He doesn't say this, but it seems to imply "My work is FAR superior to these fools." Who does this asshole think he is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never seen this show, was a bit too old at that point, but damn this is kinda funny "That's the D in prindle"

I'd probably watch this but I've never been a huge fan of child actors, I feel like Boy Meets World is a rare exception </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here I was thinking "thank god finally someone sped up this obnoxiously long video" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 21:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like three star reviews are the best to look at because of that, though sometimes I'm looking at them and thinking "Wait, this review is absolutely glowing..  did you forget to click 5 stars?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason I give up, typically, is bad writing. I'll come across a book that's highly regarded... and there are simple, boring sentences everywhere. Or a bit of the opposite, where you can tell the writer is trying REALLY hard to show off. Writing that is either too simple or too grandiose really pulls me out of the experience, so Vladimir Nabokov and John Green are equally annoying to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, right I forgot what this thread was about. Well, I wouldn't doubt Rowling writing more Potter novels eventually, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think there will be a sequel? Harry Potter makes a shit ton of money, there's gonna be a sequel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie was better. The writing of the book was laughable. What kind of scientist is going to write "Yay!" multiple times, even in a journal?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes I wonder if I like reading, or if I have high standards, or what. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All my life, basically, I've been the kind of person who has a short temper with books. If I'm not enjoying it within 20 pages or less, I'll put it down. This is part of the reason I bought used books, because I know I'm hard to please and I'm not about to buy a new book that might bore me.

Now that I have a Kindle and access to thousands of titles through Overdrive, this habit hasn't changed. I'll check out four or five books at a time and usually return all but one of them. 

It's rare that I finish books. I'm the polar opposite of the kind of person who will stubbornly finish a book no matter how much they hate it. I don't necessarily see anything wrong with this, though I do sometimes wonder... do I really enjoy reading as a whole, or just certain particular stories? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad I'm not the only one who's feeling this way. Had my Kindle for a month now and while I love it for reading books from the library that I don't plan on reading more than once, I can't bring myself to buy an ebook. So I think what's going to happen is my absolute favorite books, I'm going to buy physical copies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They come across Konoha being completely destroyed, hundreds of thousands dead and..break into a joke? The dude threw a rock earlier and he jokes about that rock accidentally smashing Konoha. Like, what? Haha genocide lol.

Wow, now I kinda want to watch Naurto just because this sounds like a train wreck. Is the comedy "so bad it's good" or is it just outright terrible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dragon Ball has two things going for it, the charming 80s art style and the fact that it doesn't take itself too seriously. By contrast, Naruto's art style looks too slick and its characters (from what little I've seen) kinda seem brooding and angsty. 

I might just go with your final suggestion of Ruroni Kenshin, since a couple others have also mentioned that one, not to mention it's one of those shows where I watched a little bit of it on Toonami as a kid and never finished it. Definitely going to watch more of Yu Yu Hakusho, too. After that, I'll dig deeper into the more obscure series mentioned here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I thought it was red no matter what. So it does turn yellow if you're safe? I'll have to check that next time I see a D.va ult :x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any visual indicator for the radius of D.va's ult? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost a game just now because of this. I was Mercy, healing everyone up, then a D.Va comes and ults.. no big deal.. I back away to res them, but I wasn't far enough away and I died along with them. I've been playing for a couple months now and I'm still confused how far the blast radius is. Surely there is some way to tell visually how far it extends? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like I'd love it. I've always been curious about the first Hunter x Hunter, and you specifying the 2011 series is further intriguing. Is the older series not as good or just simply not matching my criteria? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL ARE YOU KIDDING

there are constant threads on the front page about the superiority of physical over digital. Biased mods, much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this sub circlejerk over demonizing ebooks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK so for someone who's never watched Naruto - partly because it looks more like a kids show, partly because it's so damn long with filler - should I watch it or not? Is there a list of not-filler episodes or is it just simply not something I should pick up if I want something more manageable? YYH has a reasonable 112 episodes whereas Naruto has an insane 600+ episodes.

(Same reason I've avoided One Piece, too - I love the idea of a an elastic pirate, it's so silly and original, but goddamn I do not want to watch 800 episodes.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fighting anime that doesn't use power beams, just well choreographed moves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit I've still not seen a whole lot of anime outside of Dragon Ball, Death Note, Cowboy Bebop, and Madoka Magicka. But I can tell you I'm not a huge fan of DBZ now that I'm older. Sure, it looked badass when I was a kid, all those flashy lights... but now it seems incredibly lazy compared to something like Goku vs Krillin.

Cowboy Bebop has interesting fights, though I've got a different problem with that series in that there's little to no story. I know there are pieces here and there, but it's largely episodic, which I don't think works outside of like a mystery show.

I've been meaning to watch more of Yu Yu Hakusho. How do the fights in that show play out? Are they more interesting than DBZ's Kamehameha waves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 06:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the only episode of season 5 I'd say was really good is 6781 or whatever it's called. Might be my second favorite episode after If-Then-Else. Actually, I've noticed I have this unintentional bias towards Shaw episodes because my third favorite is probably the one in which she is introduced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 03:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question is so pointless, yet gamers ask it all the time. The solution is simple: take a break. Whether you're getting bored of gaming as a whole or one game in particular, take a break. Focus on your other hobbies for a while. You are not obligated to play video games.

This is such an oddly gamer mentality, too. I've never seen anyone say "I'm burnt out on movies, how do I bring back the passion?" Because I imagine most people can reason to themselves, "let's focus on other hobbies for a while." Gaming is the only hobby I know of where people ask this bizarre question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When does your party reunite permanently or does that never happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the better question is "which spells SHOULDN'T be in quickcast", because 95% of the time, quickcast is just plain better. One of the only exceptions that comes to mind is Void's Chronosphere. I've not played Dota in a few months so I can't recall what else would be similar to Chrono, but surely you can work it out based on that assumption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dubbing live action movies is still a thing? ... why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ELI5 why was Vine ever a thing

If for some reason you want 7 second videos... why not upload a 7 second video to YouTube/DailyMotion/Vimeo/whatever else is around these days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My biggest problem with John Oliver is his total lack of respect for his viewers' intelligence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is perplexing to me considering his show is on HBO, a network that prides itself on smart writing, and yet that's the feeling I get from his jokes. The subjects he chooses to report are almost always fascinating on their own merit, and his urgent tone keeps me captivated, yet it's like clockwork where he'll say "oh shit, not had a joke in a minute or two... should say something funny so I don't bore them!"

I know you can say, "that's the point... it's a comedy show..." but the problem is he's just not funny in this environment. He's much better at the serious stuff, ironically enough. I think they should either toss out the jokes or get better joke writers, though again the very inclusion of jokes seems to imply HBO doesn't respect the intelligence of their viewers to watch the news on its own merit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd love to read more interesting personal documents from common people in history, i.e. Howard Zinn's A People's History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 18:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't necessarily appreciate the idea that this is the "real history" or whatever - but it's certainly more interesting. I love reading how normal people centuries ago lived their lives, from their own words. So much of traditional history in school is about kings and presidents, and while that's obviously important, it's also a little hard to relate to the dry politics without knowing how the people felt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people are misrepresenting their interest in Zinn when they say shit like "the real truth" - for me, the reason he's so fascinating is the focus on showing personal documents of common people, those that were affected by the big political decisions we read about in history books. It's not "the real truth" - it's a different side to the same truth. I get bored of reading about kings and queens, presidents and whatever. I want to know how people like you and me reacted to history as it happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't most history based on "hindsight bias"? Otherwise it would be "current events." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard Bradbury is an asshole. I guess this is one more piece of supporting evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK I love ebooks but let's look at that "5million per year" figure - how much of that is self-published shit from someone writing My First Novel that has barely had any editing? For as convenient as ebooks are, there are also downsides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a way to borrow ebooks from a public library. As an example, here is the [Brooklyn Public Library Overdrive](https://brooklyn.overdrive.com/). If you're out-of-state, you do need to pay a yearly fee of $50, however I'd say that's a great deal for their collection of 120,000+ books when you consider Netflix is almost twice that amount per year. And of course, your own public library also has an Overdrive, more than likely. I paid for an out-of-state library card because my local library didn't have nearly enough of what I wanted to read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Through Overdrive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is gonna make reading longer books like Infinite Jest *infinitely* less stressful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not played DQ9 since release. Are there any fun challenge runs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something manageable. For example, which one is easier for a newbie to challenge runs, a low level run or a solo hero run? Or is there some other more unique run to try out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Diamond Age * </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love long dungeons. They're the primary reason I play JRPGs, much more than story. You can imagine my dislike for most RPGs made after FF7 based on that preference. 

I'll have to give 4 Heroes of Light another try and actually finish it this time, no idea why I quit it. Probably because of the complaint I've seen a few people make in this thread that the party is split up quite often, that did get annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 05:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's not like Wind Waker where you're like "Great I came all the way here to get a ... butterfly necklace.. yay.." ? Because that's probably why I can't bring myself to replay Wind Waker these days, I feel like I'm slapped in the face for exploring its world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [no spoilers] So... now that people have the game, how large is the world of BotW? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even have a Wii U or Switch, but I'm still eager to play this game asap, however I can. For me, I've still never played a game that equaled the magic of exploring Dragon Quest VIII's overworld. Does the new Zelda come close to that sense of wonder? Is it fun just to explore what's out there for treasures? (I assume it's worthless trinkets like in WW or SS, but it's more the journey than the reward in Zelda games) And how large is the world compared to other games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The human race is gonna be gone by then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh I've still not played Bravely Default, largely due to what I've heard about it. A game that forces you to replay the same part like five times in a row just to pad out its length can't be that great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was sarcasm. Notice how I said he inspires many different opinions on his work due to his popularity. For anyone to think they have a unique opinion on someone as popular as King is entirely delusional. 
Just as many people hate him, as they love him, as they like him, as they dislike him, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if doing this is the reason he's disabled in the first place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the opinion on Final Fantasy: The 4 Heroes of Light these days? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never did finish this game. One of those silly moments where I was enjoying something a lot, read a review and saw some flaws mentioned, and just decided I'd quit. Sold my DS around then, too, coincidentally, was kinda getting bored of gaming at the time. Now I'm thinking about trying it out again because I really liked the art and music.

Is it a hidden gem or best forgotten? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People seem to think $9 a month should get you a ton of access to shows.

The only reason I think this is because *it's the way it used to be*. If such a service as Netflix were introduced today at that price, I'd be thrilled. But we know what Netflix used to have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably a stupid question, but what happens if I keep my Kindle on airplane mode and keep an Overdrive book past its due date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 22:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there some kind of DRM that will delete it from my device regardless of wi-fi connectivity? Or will only wi-fi trigger returning the book automatically? So in theory, could I check out the full 15 books, turn on airplane mode, return all of them so others could read them, and still have them on my Kindle until I decide to turn on wifi again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never did watch that, but such praise has me curious. I'll try to watch it tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copy and pasting what I just said to someone else: The thing is you need the emotion to be subtle. You need it to be a sleight of hand, not to let your audience know what's happening. Putting up VERY obvious indications that say "this scene is sad, please cry!" is insulting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is you need the emotion to be subtle. You need it to be a sleight of hand, not to let your audience know what's happening. Putting up VERY obvious indications that say "this scene is sad, please cry!" is insulting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't mean it's not funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even less of a reason to keep a subscription. Cool.

You think they'd AT LEAST make a deal to keep the first three seasons of AD, considering the fourth season makes no goddamned sense without what comes before it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Pixar's storytelling too manipulative, i.e. is it too obvious they want you to cry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Toy Story 3, I began to suspect they were manipulating their audience's heartstrings too transparently. With Inside Out, I confirmed my suspicion. When I felt sad near the end because of her emotions shutting down, also I felt insulted. They weren't even trying to hide anymore what they were doing.

When I caught up and finally saw The Good Dinosaur recently, this is dialed up to 11. There is barely a story to all of this. It's just "crushingly emotional scene" after "crushingly emotional scene." I'm not saying a family/children's movie isn't allowed to be sad - but this one in particular took it too far. There didn't appear to be any reason or motive beyond "Hey we're Pixar, this is what we do!"

Their animation is still the best in the business. It's just too bad their storytelling is so manipulative and formulaic. The one glimmer of hope for me is The Incredibles 2, because I'm HOPING it's going to be more about a good story instead of obvious tearjerking moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After watching The Good Dinosaur, I think I'm done with Pixar for good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Toy Story 3, I began to suspect they were manipulating their audience's heartstrings too transparently. With Inside Out, I confirmed my suspicion. When I felt sad near the end because of her emotions shutting down, also I felt insulted. They weren't even trying to hide anymore what they were doing.

When I caught up and finally saw The Good Dinosaur recently, this is dialed up to 11. There is barely a story to all of this. It's just "crushingly emotional scene" after "crushingly emotional scene." I'm not saying a family/children's movie isn't allowed to be sad - but this one in particular took it too far. There didn't appear to be any reason or motive beyond "Hey we're Pixar, this is what we do!"

Their animation is still the best in the business. It's just too bad their storytelling is so manipulative and formulaic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK... then where is this content? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see all four seasons. Which region do you live? Or is this removal something they plan to do in the future? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 19:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, Netflix has a ton of b-movie trash that no one wants to watch. That doesn't make them "decent pieces of content." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thousands?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I get it. I know they're trying to push their original programming. But someone needs to step in and do what they once did by offering a streaming service for excellent movies. Maybe the rights to stream are simply too expensive. All I know is Netflix used to be easier than pirating, while these days it's looking like the opposite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say the driving force for that decision, subconsciously, (unless you've never liked them) is that Netflix doesn't really have many movies these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Netflix broken or is there even less content than we thought? [US] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they play all these tricks to hide their lack of content, but I'm starting to suspect that's even more true than we realized. I go to the Western subgenre and there are only 22 titles. Of these, there are five that I think anyone would want to watch. Once Upon a Time in the West, El Dorado, The Sons of Katie Elder, Blazing Saddles, and The Good the Bad and the Weird.

The first is what I'd say is the one true selling point. The following two are included only by virtue of starring John Wayne, however they're not his most famous. Blazing Saddles is a comedy more than anything. The Good the Bad and the Weird is a Korean action movie that is influenced somewhat by Westerns, but I'd hardly call it a Western.

And similarly shocking small numbers are found on other genres. Is the subscription cost of Netflix now basically a way to fund their original programming? Because unless there's something wrong with the sorting and there's something more (and I'm not expecting HUNDREDS UPON HUNDREDS, but damn), they're not really delivering much of anything in the way of good movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 08:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Things you're doing wrong every day: everything.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KlA_YXDm9bg)

[Things I hate about modern gaming: stories](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Utk2k8Z4bJE)

[How to watch a movie in a theater.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9BDi3rkBV7s)

These are my favorite videos. Always loved his website as a kid, but the vocal delivery makes his shit 10 times funnier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the actual fuck did this receive gold? You get someone who was a hero on the front page, then someone makes a joke about it like the internet always does. No one takes anything seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I've always found it funny how they begin each episode with "please support the official release." My thought is always the same: dudes, I don't LIKE the official release anymore and haven't since I was a kid. DBZ is pretty bad, when you set aside nostalgia. Not only does TFS make fun of this, they'll also occasionally make cheesy moments into something badass just like they should be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah I mean like a redditwide thing. "Is this post super popular on one reddit? Then we ban that link from all of reddit for a set amount of time in an attempt to prevent reposting." Maybe that would get messy in the case that people don't visit a specific subreddit, I dunno. Maybe the real solution is to make it so you can post whatever you want, but that the same news article/video can only reach the front page from one sub at a time. I hate when something important has happened, like a celeb death or a shooting, and /r/all is littered with the same thing in different wordings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... oh. I didn't even know that's a thing. I might have to try Hyper Metroid again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 01:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, there's absolutely nothing wrong with reposting if some time has passed in between them. But this really is posted all the time. Certain videos need a reddit-wide "age check" or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video is posted weekly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is one of the most popular writers of the past century, a fact which is sure to inspire many different opinions on his work.

Yes, you are the only one who doesn't like him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people still call him Ron Swanson? He's pretty famous, pretty sure people know his real name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a long way to the top when you do this repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, yeah. It's a millenia old cliche. The problem is this time it's right. Any other idiot president was at least a politician. This guy has literally no political background. His only reason for winning the election was his celebrity status.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cute. You think Trump knows a word with more than two syllables.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't the very first. I know Wilkie Collins' The Woman in White did the same thing, not sure if there was also one before that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand this is a silly reason to put down a book, but I couldn't make it very far because of the journal style. Not that I don't enjoy such a technique, the thing is the entries were SO elaborate that I couldn't suspend my disbelief. I was constantly asking myself, "would anyone really make a journal with such perfect grammar?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bit of a Mercy/Zen main who's really thinking of adding Sombra to my roster as a backup support. Maybe that doesn't actually work, but in my head she's so good at it. Especially now that the health kits will be saying "look at me!!!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Action films (probably Asian) that have amazing choreography and don't have frantic jump cuts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Watching this video on Jackie Chan's movies](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z1PCtIaM_GQ) really gets me in the mood to watch some martial arts. The video really highlights why I don't like a lot of action movies: there are so many cuts that you can't really see the fight. Not only that, it makes me dizzy. 

I say "probably Asian" in the title because I'm not sure if any American (or other country) films have this type of fighting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I live in a small town so no such thing like that exists for me. But that sounds pretty awesome and I'm jealous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, the worst part about this song is ... it's not catchy. I've just listened to it and can't even remember anything about it. It's clearly trying to be poppy and catchy, yet her first album had much stronger melodies to the point I can reconstruct most of its songs in my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh god... now I know I'm going to hate the whole album. thanks.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 00:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [SPOILER](#s "I didn't mind Greer's death because, like you said, he was ultimately a pawn for Samaritan. I don't consider it to be sudden, either, due to his immediate servitude to Samaritan as soon as it was booted up at the end of season 3.")

[SPOILER](#s "For me, what really annoyed me was the fact that Finch reunited with his wife, that  the Machine ended up living, and that Shaw got to continue the mission. Were it up to me, the Machine and Samaritan would have both survived. It's a bit twisted and dark, but it's the whole idea that ideas cannot be destroyed. I refuse to believe Samaritan could have ever been truly destroyed, same as the Machine. Once one of these super AIs is launched into the world, its intelligence would be so massive that there would be trillions of escape plans.")

edit: finally got the spoiler tags to work wooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, right. I forget about that. This makes me sad, I'd love his regeneration story to be with the Cybermen. I doubt it, but I hope the Christmas special is a non-canon cute little thing instead of a regen story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this book any good? For stories where the movie is more remembered than the book, I tend to assume the movie is superior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I knew the answer to this. Threads like these are why I seldom visit any respective fandom's subreddit. There were multiple theories about Gus after that episode initially aired - and, as is evident through this thread's existence, they're still occasionally a thing - and all I could ever think is "He's a teriary character meant to the serve the plot of this one episode. That's all." The way fans are compelled to attach undue importance to any new character is baffling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you say second last? Pretty sure they're also in the last episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too, found the ending disappointing - and considering we're a rare bunch, I want to ask what you found disappointing about it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, too, found the ending disappointing - and considering we're a rare bunch, I want to ask what you found disappointing about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally. Hard to find anyone who agrees with me the ending wasn't entirely perfect. I feel like maybe I'd have enjoyed it more, even unchanged in its current form, if that season were longer or if less of the episodes were "number of the week" - I'm someone who enjoyed season 1 and 2 when it was more episodic, but once the Machine/Samaritian battle was underway, going back to that felt awkward.

As for the ending itself... I felt there were too many happy endings. If any one of them were to have happened in isolation, then that's fine - but all in one episode felt cheap to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no difference between unranked and ranked. If you don't get tilted playing unranked while you do get tilted in ranked, you're placing a stupid importance on "the ladder" and "needing to climb." Just treat it like your unranked games, ignore your MMR, and you'll climb eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those who don't use Goodreads, how do you keep track of what you've read and where do you get your recommendations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a Kindle for about a month now and I've been reading a lot more thanks to Overdrive libraries. But there's a small problem with this, which is cataloging which books I've finished, which I've started and put down (a lot of them, but this isn't at all a new habit), and then which books to read next.

I tried Goodreads and I don't know... not only does it feel clunky, I'm wary of receiving recommendations from a website that focuses so much on young adult fiction. Not that I don't enjoy a good YA novel every now and then, but they're such a small part of what I read.

So for anyone who doesn't use something like Goodreads to generate recommendations for you - where do you usually find them and how do you keep track of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you know what the Dunning-Kruger effect is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just put your kid(s) up for adoption and divorce your wife. You'll have a lot more time for reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although if you were to base Ringo's worth to the Beatles based on those two songs, I'd almost forgive you for it. Don't Pass Me By is decent but Octopus's Garden is stupid. Well.. it's better than Yellow Submarine, at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol all I get in CD is a waste of my time.. it's like they forgot they had CD queued up, so after everyone chooses their hero, they all abandon the gam. No one at 1k mmr wants to do this, sadly, but I think it's fun as hell. Random Draft is the best option for "I want to play Dota with a limited and random pool of heroes" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fire mixtape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to think this, but it's not at all true. Ringo is more creative than you'd think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is pointless, so I'll link one of my favorite videos on the internet

[Hal Holbrook as Mark Twain](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_rTMNnxwSE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 04:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole idea of what is and is not "high art" can change with the times. To my understanding, Dickens was considered like a soap opera when his work was fresh, and now it's regarded as a classic with literary merit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By this logic, I wonder if IMAX cameras will become the standard in a decade or two, or if they'll always remain a bit niche. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 01:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate this kinda shit, reminds me of people who are very militant about drawing a line between "literature" and "genre fiction" - a good book is a good book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After the introduction of color film, why were some movies still black-and-white? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not being negative here, quite a few of my favorite movies are black-and-white, and something about the cinematography of a b w film is captivating, the way the shadows look. So, I'm asking simply out of curiosity. Was color film significantly more expensive? Was it an artistic choice? Perhaps it was a mix of the two? Or maybe there's some other reason that doesn't come to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Download Starcraft 2 Starter Edition
* Play vs AI for a week or two
* Come back to Dota and feel like a badass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 22:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level design seems fine to me, but might as well wait until next week like you said. Thanks for the tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I could wait to make much more progress until then. What's set to change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, definitely. I've played both games on the MSX through the ports that came with MGS3. They're both surprisingly intuitive, I don't think I used a walkthrough more than once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To my understanding, CDDA isn't really a roguelike because there is no end game. Stuff like CDDA and Unreal World remind me more of a precursor to today's survival gaming trend, except they happen to be turn-based and look a bit like a roguelike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a super big fan of Hyper, but that's down to the bosses being absurdly quick - not the reason I play Metroid at all. However, I'm sure there are people out there who do enjoy a more action-based Metroid, and if that's the case, I don't see a problem with Hyper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I highly recommend Metroid Rogue Dawn to everyone interested in the series. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a hack of the original NES, which as far as I can see, isn't as popular to hack as Super Metroid. I can understand this, since Super is arguably the more classic of the two. I gotta say, though, what I've played of this game so far is stellar, to the point I'd gladly donate some money to the developer. He's turned a game that I've never enjoyed as much as its sequel into something magical. 

It's this quirky blend of Cave Story-esque platforming with exploration - the kind that I've not really felt since I played Super Metroid as a kid. There are all these hidden passages and, even with the mini-map, you'll probably get lost. But it's the enjoyable kind of lost. Also, the music and art are both stellar. There are also occasional health recharge spots, which is such a rewarding feeling, seeing them really tells you that you're headed in the right direction. Also you can save by pressing select+A+B at the start menu, so that's pretty awesome.

Honestly, between AM2R, Hyper Metroid, and this, we're kinda spoiled by top-tier fan projects lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For anyone who knows about SMW hacks - is there a hack that focuses on platforming, i.e. takes out the feather? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 18:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never really enjoyed SMW and part of it is that damn cape - I know you can say "Well, just don't use it", but the temptation is always too strong. But despite using it, I'm not enjoying myself. I'm simply using the easiest way to beat the game. I'd love to play SMW as a platformer instead of a hang glider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 17:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're talking about modernism as in the literary movement, yes. But comparing him to McCarthy seems to imply he's contemporary when he wrote his stuff like 50 years before him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the whole idea of "death metal drumming in children's music" compelled me to look up death metal in other genres.. and well..

[Death Metal Country Classics](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZRIkRKzGRUk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much of your reading consists of re-reading favorite books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 08:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this something you consider a waste of time, too busy with thousands of other good books that you don't want to re-read something? Or do you make a habit of re-reading your favorites, whether it's yearly or what?

And a little related, how many of you re-read something IMMEDIATELY after you read it for the first time, just because you liked it that much and now you want to view it in a different light since you know what happens in the end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nabokov and Joyce aren't exactly modern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 23:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played FF3 on PSP and while I liked it for the most part, the lack of a save point in that long final dungeon was nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, really good homebrew games sound like a good time, too. Might try that first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is a mysterious character in the starting are that gives you your first quests and he offers some teaching points

Yeah, I noticed this in the E3 videos which is exactly why I think they're lying to us. So this character only shows up in the starting area and then leaves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because this is Nintendo, where we've had varying degrees of handholding since Ocarina of Time. Twenty years of this. Saying they're suddenly going to stop treating their customers like idiots makes me suspicious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, did they lie to us? Does Breath of the Wild have an obnoxious intro or a helper buddy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, did they lie to us? Is there an obnoxious intro or a helper buddy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NES games that hold up today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 19:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure the only NES games I've finished are Dragon Quest 3 and 4, Super Mario Bros 3, and most of Mega Man 2. It's not necessarily that I can't play NES games, rather that I grew up on the SNES and Genesis so I have no special attachment to the NES. I'd like to fix that, though. 

Any genre, which ones still have smooth controls and level design in 2017? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 07:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen you around this sub a bit and trust your opinion so I'll ask - in those four hours, was there any hand holding? I know Nintendo SAID there wouldn't be any, but I'm paranoid (especially after Fi in Skyward Sword treating me like a goddamned idiot) that they lied and there's still going to be hand holding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 06:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skyward Sword is the game that made me switch to PC gaming and I'm only now starting to recover from that. There is so much hand holding in that game and it's goddamned insulting. That game scarred me to the point I don't trust Nintendo when they say Breath of the Wild doesn't have hand holding. I'm sure there's some stupid sidekick telling you where to go and what to do that they "forgot" to mention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean as bad as I want it, it's like the only game I want on Wii U except maybe Super Mario 3D World. One or two games doesn't really justify a console to me, no matter how good they are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kaiser mentioned in a recent interview that episode 6 is his least favorite, and I'd actually rewatched the first season a few days before the interview - and I can absolutely agree with him. That episode is quite boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a Wii U or Switch but I want Breath of the Wild so bad :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 06:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brogue looks like a mess, even if you use the disable colors menu option. If you want graceful ASCII, Sil pulls that off much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [All you need to know about keys](http://zelda.wikia.com/wiki/Small_Key) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
