<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7478</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think broom man without rug boy would be a clean sweep. And everyone's grandma knows that a broom will beat the dust out of a rug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get off my bridge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 21:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the watch did I just fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure looks similar on the surface. But, because he found the box and didn't make it or look for it, it might be coincidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael in Jane the Virgin. Happened so fast... Def a wtf moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen this issue with a worn out gear on the extruder. You often can't see the pattern in under extrusion because you can't see how much of the internal structure is under extruded.  I pushed some through slowly/manually and found a spot where the filament just slipped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 01:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be many things. Power to the motors or belt tensioner are often guilty for this. Looks like the layers are only misaligning on one axis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this a new build, or a printer that suddenly started having issues? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/shared?ci=cFNfs-sbapE

That's the recommended method from Dremel. But before you do that, have you rerun your test print? If so, is it still printing properly? If it is, you have a profile issue with your slicer, not a mechanical problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 17:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 months late... It's the ravioli episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible your extruder gear is starting to slip as the motor gets warmed up? Have you printed anything else to see if you get the same behaviour? I.e. starts off normal and transition to bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a smart man, but I know what quality education is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 06:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say the users live outside the net, and input games for pleasure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 23:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the MacBook work well as a printed? Never occured to me that it would be self heating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My brother says this is how life is with two young kids. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for being part of my church. I am a James Cameron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DS9 Episode : Defiant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 14:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting note. Watching the episode Defiant. When Thomas Riker asks for a status report on the ship, they report minor damage, and he uses the line "Tough little ship"

William Riker would later use this line in First Contact. Must be intentional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 13:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is anything half time shows have taught me, it's that left shark is perfect in its own way, cause god makes no mistakes. He's not the right shark, baby, but he was born this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 15:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair I haven't had time too confirm that it's not my installation. It is possible I need to level it slightly. It ended up being easy better then the original heated bed though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 15:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also did this last month and mine pitched ever so slightly down in the back. Overall very happy with it though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 13:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a male, I also hate receiving this compliment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 04:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dreamcast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had the same problem this week. Had to increase my extruder tension a little. Also using a simple metal. Filament was not perfectly uniform. It would slip a little on thinner parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same boat here. I have 10 open disputes for items ordered in November that are past their 60 day garauntee. I had ordered stuff at the end of October to be part of Christmas gifts and ended up having to source them and buy them.through Amazon in Canada to get them in time. The last of the October stuff showed up last week. In all cases, the arrival in Canada was within a week of them.being shipped out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 12:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here! I was explaining it to a friend and he immediately stopped me and said "did you learn that from the Batman cartoon?"

And my parents thought that stuff would totally my brain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 04:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only problem with that theory is that These Were The Voyages was written as a series finale. As far as I know it was written years in advance with the intention of having it wrap up however many seasons they got. So even if they got 7 seasons, Trip would still die in the last episode. That's why it's written for their tenth year in space, as Enterprise comes home to be decommissioned.

Could be wrong, but I read about it in a magazine when Enterprise wrapped up, it was supposed to be a Valentine for the fans of all star trek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 11:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And with a schedule in standard Tasmanian time, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 07:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sorry, but I can bearly see that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 15:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternative Fact.

There is such a thing as an alternative Fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What material are you printing in? I know with PLA I often raise the temperature up to 215 and lower the print speed when printing a thin object. Will increase stinginess and may make it more prone to warping, but definitely increases layer adhesion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 14:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this problem towards the end of one of my test prints. It ended up being a buildup on my extruder gear which caused intermittent skipping. Only a few layers were affected visually because the skipping often occurred during the infill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 18:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one knows for sure... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 15:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... Yeah that was pretty good. But where are Bob, Dot, and Enzo? I hate these filler episodes that don't link to main characters or further the plot in any way...

Edit: and my first reddit gold comes from a comment about ReBoot. I am happy this is the way my life has gone. Thank you kind stranger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enterprise already had a season 4... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the left shark. Look at that green mouth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did! I defined the new size of the bed in the firmware. After playing with it, the problem ended up being the slicer. Thanks for taking the time to reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 19:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like it was something Cura was picking up for the G29 settings. Adjusted them, and I seem to have access to more or less the entire bed. Doing a 7.5 " print right now, looks promising.

Was late last night, probably should have checked things before posting.

Thanks everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, yes, it's placing the edge of the print in the middle then attempting to extend the print beyond the border of the bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prints starting near middle of bed. (Xpost from /r/printrbot) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 06:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone! I've been using my Simple Metal for just over a year. This weekend I completed the XYZ upgrade from Matrix Precision. The install went perfect. I changed the X and Y for M211 (the wires aren't long enough for the Z axis, so I'll have more work ahead of me there)

I also increased the X and Y size in Cura. But, every time I do a print, it does its probe (at which point it is properly to the outer edges as I would expect)

When it starts to print, however, it starts printing near the middle of the bed. So, if I'm doing a print thats larger than 5 inches, it hits the right edge of the bed and starts grinding the belt.

I'm at a bit of a loss to explain it. I've posted my printer settings bellow in case I'm an idiot and miss something obvious.

Recv: echo: M205 S0.00 T0.00 B20000 X20.00 Z0.40 E5.00 Recv: echo:Home offset (mm): Recv: echo: M206 X0.00 Y0.00 Z0.00 Recv: echo:PID settings: Recv: echo: M301 P22.20 I1.08 D114.00 Recv: echo:Min position (mm): Recv: echo: M210 X0.00 Y0.00 Z0.00 Recv: echo:Max position (mm): Recv: echo: M211 X200.00 Y200.00 Z250.00 Recv: echo:Bed probe offset (mm): Recv: echo: M212 X0.00 Y0.00 Z-2.15 Recv: ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prints keep starting near middle of bed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 05:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone! I've been using my Simple Metal for just over a year. This weekend I completed the XYZ upgrade from Matrix Precision. The install went perfect. I changed the X and Y for M211 (the wires aren't long enough for the Z axis, so I'll have more work ahead of me there)

I also increased the X and Y size in Cura. But, every time I do a print, it does its probe (at which point it is properly to the outer edges as I would expect)

When it starts to print, however, it starts printing near the middle of the bed. So, if I'm doing a print thats larger than 5 inches, it hits the right edge of the bed and starts grinding the belt. 

I'm at a bit of a loss to explain it. I've posted my printer settings bellow in case I'm an idiot and miss something obvious.

Recv: echo:  M205 S0.00 T0.00 B20000 X20.00 Z0.40 E5.00
Recv: echo:Home offset (mm):
Recv: echo:  M206 X0.00 Y0.00 Z0.00
Recv: echo:PID settings:
Recv: echo:   M301 P22.20 I1.08 D114.00
Recv: echo:Min position (mm):
Recv: echo:  M210 X0.00 Y0.00 Z0.00
Recv: echo:Max position (mm):
Recv: echo:  M211 X200.00 Y200.00 Z250.00
Recv: echo:Bed probe offset (mm):
Recv: echo:  M212 X0.00 Y0.00 Z-2.15
Recv: ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thing belongs on crapmame...

As an example on how not to build crap.

Good work man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 02:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frantatic Four

Its all about Fran Drescher being closed 3 times and getting super power. Gotta be better than the latest movie. hehehehehehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 07:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yarr, me matey. Ye not be thinkin' about plundering a galaxy class starship in a runabout are ye? Ye may enter for a prize, but walkin' the plank in space doesn't leave ye much chance at survival. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ReBoot.com is back up and running. sort of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 02:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reboot.com/

Its got a fancy new reboot 404 page. Its a step in the right direction! I'm sure Megab... Bob will have it back up and running in no time.

Click the top-right and info, they say they are Rebooting the ReBoot website, and it has a 2017 copyright on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 20:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was 9 o'clock on a Saturday... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 15:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be this 
http://www.thingiverse.com/thing:602755 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 01:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will try the above and see how it goes!

Thanks for all the help!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far I have tested two mario games on NES and SNES, and both exhibit the same behaviour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 21:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, super weird issue. Not sure if anyone is using this much. I basically am trying to get a wired button to trigger a return to main menu. I launch mario, and I try to trigger select/start from inside the NES emulator.

Here is where things get weird. Select works on the main menu of Super Mario Bros. Start works on the main menu too. But, once the game starts, pressing start using the GPIO doesn't pause the game. But, if you kill off mario 3 times and get back to the main menu, you can use the start GPIO to start the game again, and select to change between 1p and 2p.

Not expecting there will be much anyone can do to help diagnose this, its very weird. GPIO input also works on the main menu for RetrOrangePi.

Very very odd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 18:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I ran the most recent one, and it installed, and everyone works good when I define the controller. So thats all good. But I am trying to configure it so the GPIO can be used to exit the game, activate save states, etc. Still having issues with that, but thank you so much for pointing me in the right direction! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RetrOrange Pi - GPIO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 05:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone managed to get it to work with the instructions contained here? 
http://orangepi.club/showthread.php?tid=44

I started with a fresh card. Installation from the RetroPie menu seems to go as expected. I then SSH into the box, and find a folder called 

orangepi_PC_gpio_pyH3-master

From this folder, I run 
sudo python setup.py install

which seems to complete without error. I then run
sudo service tz_gpio start

which complains that there is no tz_gpio.service 

I'm not very strong with my linux commands, so I'm not sure where I am going wrong. 

Thanks in advance to anyone that can help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
