<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to make my own pedal board to use with my live show running with Ableton. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 13:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any tips/recommendations? Complete rookie here. What will I need to run them through Ableton or my audio interface? Any help would be amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the funniest smelling thing in the whole wide world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 14:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How well can your machine lop the Griffen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 07:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it completely depends on the systems you guys are running, but I'd like to see some comparisons. My machine usually takes around 44 lops. I have heard that with the latest Griffen (the 29 Despos Model), a lop can be completed within 25 cycles!! The tubes I use to complete the lop in under 50 cycles are Vebrose 25 C tubes. 

A quick tip would be to lubricate the ends of your tubes using that prefoltute gel that comes in the box of your main routing system! Incredible stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 01:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya we are good friends :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 13:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm its a member of Losco. Pretty much just a side project for uploading ideas and swapping samples/synths with other prods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 23:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the only answer I have too. Amazing progression, not just throughout the album, but shlohmo himself. Best album of 2015 hands down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 07:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im confident he had some hidden association with it. Just because he was not listed, doesnt mean he didnt play some part in the production. Could have gave them samples, synths etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 16:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A straight Arca rip"

Dude. Arca produces 99% of her beats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 3] Ideas, Thoughts and Rumours Thread! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 01:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 06:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw him play couple of weeks ago. He was amazing!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I enjoyed Season 2 more than Season 1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 14:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 02:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their old merch team were lazy idiots so nick melons fired all of them. The new team is noticeably a lot better considering my order took around a week to ship to australia, whereas my other order with the old team took over 3 weeks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silva and aedfx - Magnetic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 14:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 18:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea but hes touring australia rlly soon!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 13:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry dude ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GTA - Red Lips (Skrillex Remix) [Not HQ, better than others hanging around] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 05:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silvan - Hannah Montana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 04:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 18:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hes been sitting on a lot. Hes going thru label problems atm which explains all the uploads.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 06:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 11:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4287 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 02:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully its just a tad bit better than the steam of shit abandoned ship was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 08:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have snake charmer which is now deleted/gone private off of his soundcloud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 05:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a great example. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gourmet butcher!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for some feedback on this loyalty card. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 04:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heres a screencap: http://i.gyazo.com/7a511620ae7a1eb685312ae64f593804.png

The main colors here are black, orange and white. What would you guys do differently to make it look more refined and professional?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need some ideas for sprucing up this loyalty card! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-20 03:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heres a screencap: http://i.gyazo.com/7a511620ae7a1eb685312ae64f593804.png

Our main colors are obviously black and orange but right now it feels a bit bland. I would like to read some criticism about the layout of what I have done and also what else could be added to make it feel a lot more refined and professional. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it will be groundbreaking!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there will be  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bout to go to sleep and i get smacked with this HEAT. TOO MUCH HEAT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kanye West - All Day (EPROM REMIX) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 17:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any idea on how to make your own live sequencer which can be controlled by a midi controller? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best effects/parameters to assign to endless encoders? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 04:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHAHAHAHAHGAHAHA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 13:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah mainly where it is produced and how difficult is it to find these places </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 18:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive read all these tweets but im gonna de-hype myself so i can appreciate it a lot more when it comes out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 09:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry boys

was tricked once again :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 09:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 07:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also interested to see what will happen tomorrow on here http://www.kings99.com/category/wedidit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 07:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same thing happened to me. luckily i bought pretty much everything else a while back before their order ppl fucked up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 14:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks so good considering you only paid a little bit over 500 bucks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah bro thats how it works. 

*looks at stats*
"Goddamnit ive been slept on again!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 02:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think op means like an Australian producer who has a big fan base in america and when he uploads something to soundcloud he gets no plays bc he is being slept on  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any love for 'This is 40"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 15:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished watching This Is 40 for about the tenth time last night. It's slowly becoming one of my favorite easy watch films. What did you guys think of it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best online sites for making your own shirt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any good ones out there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And shlohmo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 01:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry :/ saw a lil thread on twitter about it and kinda just believed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 17:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marshmello is wave racer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 15:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fuckin loved Contagion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 17:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> H </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 02:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Booorrriinnnggg.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 17:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact this guy lives on my street </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 02:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1/4 of Losco. I have some Explore songs that he has deleted if anyone wants em.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 06:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow good find dood. my guess would be its sophie's own edit/remix/iteration of hard. heres another one: 

https://soundcloud.com/starfin/id </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 11:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally loved the album. I kept my expectations low and hype down to a minimum which definitely influenced my thoughts about it. I can understand why a lot of listeners did not enjoy this album, considering hudmo's near perfect discography. Favourite tracks would be system, lantern, ryderz and the last track! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 18:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A big mac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-14 05:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks fam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 09:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not yet. can you recommend any? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Resolving Host" issues with PC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been having this problem for a while now. My PC will often have internet problems that result in Chrome saying "resolving host". I have singled out my pc to be the problem because I can use my macbook in the same spot and it will have no "resolving host" problems. Could it be my PCI card? I have already replaced it once because of this issue. Any help would be appreciated. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TWERL - Omenta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 08:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never get to tell this story! Its kind of messed up and involves an innocent party, gate crashers, and a lot of blood.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 18:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened a couple of years ago now. I was at a seventeenth birthday party with my girlfriend. I did not know the host personally as she was a close friend of my girlfriend's friend. The party was in a dodgy suburb but I sorta shook off that thought because it was a seventeenth. The party itself was fine, no dramas involving drugs or alcohol. A guy came out, turned the music down and told us to keep our eyes out because some people were trying to gate crash (get in to the party). Moments later, the host's mum comes sprinting through the gate screaming "GET INTO THE HOUSE!"  I hear glass breaking, look up and see a wave of bottles being thrown over the roof into where everyone was congregating. I was so out of it and thinking to myself what the fuck is happening? I let everyone into the house as I held the door open and I could see shirtless men running around bashing the absolute shit out of each other. So there was about 60 people huddled into the living room of this tiny house while absolute chaos was happening outside. People were crying, rumours were spreading and the noise was getting a lot louder. An older guy rushed into the house saying the gate crashes had brought back two carloads of friends and were destroying everything. Seconds later the hosts brother stumbles inside with his face COVERED IN BLOOD. There was deep slashes on his forehead and cheeks and he was bleeding very very badly. He was rushed into his room and at that point someone had called an ambulance and the police. News spread that the host's mum had been hit by a table while she was trying to stop the chaos that was happening throughout her house. Eventually the gate crashers fled and the police arrived. We all left one by one and the damage done to the property was just devastating. Glass everywhere, blood, broken furniture, beer bottles, their garden was ruined, neighbours cars had been broken into and damaged badly. It was a very bad end to such an innocent party. The brother had been cut with a machete and ended up getting plastic surgery. We were all very lucky that they didnt storm the house or anything crazy like that. I always think back on it and wonder how they are doing sometimes. There were a few articles online that I will try and find to link here. 

TL;DR: Innocent party got way out of hand and gatecrashers slit open a guys face with a machete. Damage everywhere. 

Have you guys ever experienced out of hand parties similar to this? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 02:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am definitely in the minority that really don't like artists like luca, oshi, cavalier etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Serious) Is it just me or does anyone else not give a shit about what is happening on Reddit right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 17:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 04:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure ! nets pretty slow but ill up em asap  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 04:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heres the boiler room version. sorry it cuts out half way thru. when i was downloading it i think it got taken down. 

https://soundcloud.com/shit-hair/sophie-physicalb-who-i-want-to-b/s-C23Tb

also have nice quality versions of higher, ooh, fizz and bodyrock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 04:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a pretty good copy of this from his boiler room. the file is corrupt though so only 3/4 of the song plays. the vocals are a lot better in the boiler room version! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any games that just completely sucked and fell off the radar within weeks of launch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 15:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole concept of like/follow to download never grew on me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of pyrmdplazas songs sound the same i recon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no interest whatsoever in artists like Rusty Hook, Oshi, Luca Lush, XVII etc. Nothing personal against them but i really hate that future-y sound that everyone seems to love making. 

Also people who use tone den. No thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 02:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scene where his wife leaves is the most depressing thing ive ever seen :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 01:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 08:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i could be wrong but he changed the name of sober ep to exodus ep. 
https://mrcarmack.bandcamp.com/album/exodus-ep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 23:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey chris, will this game be able to hold up to 3+ players during multiplayer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 06:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> trapconcertsonline.org </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 01:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. I got: $$0100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 01:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THE LAWNMOWER RUUUURURURUEUEURURURU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 17:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like Sinister 2 will suck because its pretty much a continuation of the part most of us hated from the first one. Sinister was a pretty good movie up until the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. You're right!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 13:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pitchfork is stupid bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 04:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found this gem through Wedidit's site which is now under construction. Accessed it through the wayback machine and Henry himself said this set is full of unreleased tunes remixes of his own songs and many more. Amazing Shlo-Fi vibes which highlight the pinnacle of his old and distinct sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare Live Shlohmo Set from 2009 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 04:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 16:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perth, Australia. With no membership/vouchers, $17. Sucks :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 16:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try googling
Or try youtube
Really low budget films will be hard to find 
Reality would be to purchase a physical copy
Especially if the movies are old
Nothing beats a physical copy
Thank you for your time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 16:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was squirming in my seat every time you saw 'it'. Is it just me or does the idea that someone slowly coming for you creep you the FUCK out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 14:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH SINJIN HAWKE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 10:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayy lmao fam bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rumor is that he's releasing an ep soon which is why various rips of his songs have been taken down by Numbers (label). I think I have a few songs that will be on the ep that are in pretty good condition (physical, fizz, higher). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup can confirm its a Sophie track. It does have a name but definitely wont be released any time soon. I always stay updated and check the PC Music forums just in case anything pops up.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-25 11:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think of the mac pro? Worth the purchase?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 18:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, for some reason I just could not for the life of me enjoy eternal sunshine of the spotless mind. I may have to give it a re watch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 10:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds absolutely disgusting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 01:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily Nick Melons just fired his whole merch production team. They were definitely aware of all the problems that were coming up. Hopefully the new merch team does a much better job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 05:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on mobile when i commented before. This is actually a different profile to the one I was talking about!! Good find man. I shoulda looked before I commented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 04:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really a secret profile. That was his name before he focused on his proper project which is his current soundcloud now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 03:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well i how i see it is that i like hearing someone play knowing that they have prepared themselves accordingly. it is much more engaging than just a dj set and the sets themselves are totally different. id rather hear someone perform live with a completely original set because djing can get boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 01:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely disagree. Makes the experience much better knowing they are playing live rather than a standard dj set.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 17:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butter is an extremely awesome album full of weird, off beat and intricate sounds. You can definitely see and hear his muscial progression throughout his career (his involvement with TNGHT, Kanye West etc.). I am excited for Lantern because he really has created his own distinct style that people can recognize straight off the bat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 04:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that sucks. I received mine in the mail AGES ago!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French (Toro Y Moi Remix) 320? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 17:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toro y moi remixed tyler the creator a while back and im wondering if anyone here has a 320! Been scoping it out for a while now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have a 320 of Toro Y Moi's remix of French by Tyler, the Creator? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 14:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 02:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god same. The movie itself was so creepy but the concept of someone just walking towards you is so scary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who has the most intense stage presence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 11:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lunice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 14:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hang in there man. I feel like you're both coping with it very maturely and without any bullshit. Hope it all goes well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What part of your job makes you happy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 17:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 12:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really like the way its shot. The way the kids interacted with each other was very interesting and it never got boring. The pacing and flow was great and the very ending (just after "that" scene) is absolutely brilliant. Its basically saying its just another day and everyone has their own lives to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 09:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids is my favourite movie ever. What didnt you like about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 01:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a large police cop shirt probably a month before the new merch came out. I never got an email saying the police cop shirt had been posted. I know this because after i had purchased some of the new merch, a couple days later i received an email saying my new merch had been shipped. The police cop shirt wasnt on there so im guessing my order has just been forgotten about. I tried emailing them, tweeting them but no replies, which is weird because i emailed them about when the new merch was coming out and i got a response within a few days. 

Totally agree. Really bad customer service. I understand where theyre coming from about just a group if friends fucking around making merch and music, but they really should hire a guy who just responds to emails or helps out with orders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. The "never have I ever" game was also incredibly stupid. All of their 'secrets' were just so exaggerated to try and have an impact on the viewer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the few of you who are planning on seeing Unfriended, read this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This movie will destroy your ears. I have never experienced a movie as loud and as ear-piercing as this one. I wasn't afraid of the content within the movie itself, I was afraid of the next huge wall of noise that I knew was eventually going to happen. 

I may as well share my thoughts about the movie too. It was very weird. I struggled to realize if I should be trying to take the movie seriously or just accept the fact that its a pretty far out there concept. The 'ghost' thingo taking complete control of their Macbooks, removing the red cross buttons, disabling certain controls and so on. It made me frustrated seeing a movie that relied on literally the loudest jump scares to pass off as a horrifying and shocking movie. 

What did you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone else said it on another thread but I feel like Foxcatcher never really came together. There were many scenes that throughout I enjoyed (like the brothers practicing together) but as a whole it just felt so weird. I enjoyed it, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 02:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like people rip on Flume a little bit mainly because of how many producers now are making music that is similar to Flume. Listening to his album when it first came out, it was extremely different and many people had not heard stuff like that before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 01:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yheti - Crack The Window. 

http://youtu.be/VIbeY2iAKzk

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 18:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like a very very serious movie with The Purge concept would be really interesting. All the violence on the streets would be kept in the background and the main focus would be on the politics behind it all (how it was passed, what caused it to happen).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 17:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The porter robinson remix of the thrill is actually insane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched Forgetting Sarah Marshall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 16:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was looking for an easy watch and I really ended up enjoying this film! What did you guys like about it? Can you guys recommend me some other films that are similar in hilarity? Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 17:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have it installed on my desktop! Amazing little program.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 16:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new update for the macbooks looks truly disgusting. Everything is so bright and ugly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes it does take a complete listen through to understand an album. Other albums I feel like that have to be listened through as a whole: Arca - Xen, Flylo - You're Dead, Hudmo - Butter, Shlohmo - Dark Red.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm i feel you. I really appreciate the way he makes you feel so alone    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else feel like they have a deeper connection to Shlohmo's Bad Vibes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may just be subjective, but every time I listen to this album in full, it seems to make me react on such a deeper level than I cant explain myself. I read people saying its a cool album full of cool beats but I just dont see it like that. Anyone else out there that feels the same way? Or on a broader level, is there a different album that does this to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What experience is highly overrated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 16:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 04:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flying lotus is a very creative artist which is why i like him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 23:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scene where she is signing the divorce papers and he has flashbacks about them was one of the saddest thing I have ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been meaning to ask this for a while now! I wasnt really into Songs to Break Up To. The whole ep/album just didnt go well when I was listening to it. What did you like about it? Id love to know :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 01:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im on mobile but recently he did a good interview for Diplo and Friends on BBC. He has remained a bit mysterious during his uprising on Soundcloud which I think is awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The horror movie Orphan would have made a great drama. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 16:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One third of the movie feels like a very emotional drama about a mother who is scared to adopt because of her abortion. I feel like it would have been a great idea for a different film. The tone of Orphan is awesome, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 16:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. I thought Orphan was a great movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting videos like this: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 15:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/qqnzYnO9Rp0 

Basically where people just casually tell a really funny story!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 02:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ending to The Hunt was just so horrifying. I won't spoil it but it did definitely scare me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 17:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it does sound a lot like a trap snare. just couldnt pin point which one though. thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sort of snare would this be? It sounds familiar but I cant pinpoint what it is! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 16:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets talk about Gears of War! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 18:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the worst errors in a film where you can see the camera and/or crew? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-19 17:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Examples would be great too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is happening to me too!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone elses Updates for PC bugging out?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 15:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downloaded the 5gb one, looses connection so I have to download it again. Download the ~300mb one and then the 55mb one, and then all of a sudden it starts downloaded the ~300mb one again?! Whats going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 03:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it works well with making sounds super-compressed and almost shitty sounding to a degree. Really good if youre going for a Gold Panda sounding beat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the coolest thing you can do in a completely empty house? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 04:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oops! sorry. i have an amd radeon r9 200 series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will I be able to run GTA V? Read desc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 03:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 03:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TNGHT are coming back 100%. Trust me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 12:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus! Cocaine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 13:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I copped the long sleeve, the hoodie, the acid casual shirt and the sticker pack! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 06:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> copped $250 worth of stuff...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 03:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them. Seriously, i cant choose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 02:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They tweeted it will be released today! Or tonight! Depending on where you live. Check their twitter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 18:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> drag a song into a sampler, turn the decay down so it sorta sounds like a stab with a very short decay time, add some delay and reverb etc  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emailed WeDidIt about the new merch today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 18:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a reply with: 

Most likely this Friday time to be confirmed - Would love to be more specific but Shlohmo, RL and Melons can be a little random from time to time and catch us all off guard!

I live in Australia so I have been staying up until around 2-3 each night this week hoping its gonna be released!! ahh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What experience is highly overrated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 15:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 13:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These guys live the life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 13:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 03:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah not jealousy. Hes a good example of how far you can get in the industry with little talent. His whole team and management is the only thing that has impressed me because of how popular he is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 02:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - high pass edm banger 
- make trap beat 
- be carnage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 18:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please tell me how it goes!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
