<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4170</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the Arkham season pass worth it?  I pulled the trigger on this but can get the pass for free with credit card points (well, a $20 PSN card). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There (almost) never is with flash sales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 00:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like metroidvanias and ~~Rome~~ ^dammit Greece, go get Apotheon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 22:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, it's a flash sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 20:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait...what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 20:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tip: Detroiters/Michiganders (yes, that's really our demonym) can be SUPER touchy about people assuming Detroit is a postapocalyptic wasteland. We're pretty damn sick of that old chestnut.  Might be better off approaching the question from a "how can I make the most of my time here" angle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 20:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've probably never seen anything like lake-effect snow, though.  Be prepared to re-learn how to drive.  [This article](http://exchange.aaa.com/safety/roadway-safety/winter-driving-tips/) might freak you out (its recommended preparedness level is "Batman"), but it's got some useful tips.  Welcome to Michigan in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 17:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50% off "[Bounty Train](http://store.steampowered.com/app/371520/)." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 16:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The daily deal ends at noon Eastern.  I think we can call it confirmed at this point :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a registered trademark then I'm not finding it in the USPTO's or the Canadian database.

There is an American potato chip brand named Munch**o**s and another Malaysian one named Munchy's but I doubt either are the same thing.

What part of Michigan was this?  Did you find it in an antique store or somewhere else?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 14:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sheep making the Night Howler venom were a reference to Walt and Jesse making blue meth in Breaking Bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metro Health may be joining the U of M Health System </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 01:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 00:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we tar and feather him yet?  Pretty please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 12:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you still get that crazy employee discount you used to share with GameStop about ten years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 06:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And?

I was talking about design language, and that snout has xB written all over it in terms of how it's dummied up.

KIA doesn't have a manufacturing presence in Ohio. Their American factory is in Georgia, so it wouldn't be them either. Honda, GM and Ford are a different story, but the latter two usually use Michigan plates for their R D.

Two hours before your comment I identified the vehicle as a 2018 Honda CRV.  The picture I supplied from Motor Trend even has the same wrap and rims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, didn't mean to sound snooty. Was just trying to help you nail it down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact it's pretty dead on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a garlic mincer. I'm not sure where ours is, if that gives you any indication of how useful it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asbestos was banned in 1978. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 00:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 80% certain you spotted a pack of testing mules for the [2018 Honda CRV](http://st.motortrend.com/uploads/sites/5/2016/04/2018-Honda-CR-V-side-1.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 00:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is definitely what's going on here. Those wheel hubs look like disguised VW logos, but the design language is harder to pin down for obvious reasons. Looks KIA or Scion esque to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 18:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's literally nothing out there I can find except Twitter chatter.  Kinda like how every once in awhile a celebrity "falls off a cliff." Trust me, mainstream media isn't perfect but they'd be all over this if it was true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious question from a civilian: Regarding all the people saying "OH LOOK HE GOT OUT AFTER 9/11," Do these cards have a set expiration date like, say, a DL or a passport? Could he just have posted an old one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 03:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not the person you replied to but i was 20 when Nemo came out and definitely thought the same then. Now that I'm a parent that goes double. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 03:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear I also saw it among the cars in the roundabout bit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 19:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My poor son. His swingset needs like half an hour's work before it's finished, but my drill died.  

Oh, I bought a new one, and it arrived from Amazon this week...but I haven't opened it. 

See, the lawn needs to be mowed, and the tractor needs a part that I haven't ordered yet...for the grass catcher. I'd rather not mulch, because that would get grass all over his play area where I'm almost finished with a really cool swingset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick DeVos wants a new Michigan flag. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 03:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 12:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you been to that part of the world? I'm no fan of the Detroit Metro but it's kinda hard to argue the whole area's terrible when said drive takes you past a Legoland and more than one Whole Foods, just to give you an idea of what I was talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 12:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flint is nowhere near Detroit proper. They're 70 miles (112km) apart and between them are some very rich suburbs, among other things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 12:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People at this income level often don't have the means to even consider it an option (you have to hire an attorney) or even the education to think it an option. 

I work in a nonprofit in Michigan and just tried to help a lady who lost her medicaid (basically zero income) because her mom left her $200K and on the advice of her friend who "knows about these things" she deposited the whole damn thing into a checking account instead of consulting an attorney or financial planner. There's not much we can do at that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best: found the Extractinator in the first fifteen minutes of a new PC game. 

Worst: there used to be a bug in the Android version where the goblin army would attack sometimes EVERY OTHER NIGHT. Can't do much exploring when you constantly have to warp home to fight off an increasingly squishable but nonetheless time consuming horde, just to keep your NPCs alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GoldenEye Reloaded is about as close as we're getting, I'm afraid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 14:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this! I was taking people at their word because it didn't make sense to me either, but the HDMI standards didn't support this earlier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 01:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's search history is making Google do Freudian slips... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 22:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roughly Fuller to Knapp to the Beltline to 196.  East of Creston, in other words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 21:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably bespoke.  Not too hard to whip up a block font. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 21:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like twee platformers with puzzles, buy it now and don't look back.  There isn't much action or anything, but it's well worth the price in my book.

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 21:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tekken is only free with Gold.  Limbo is free for anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 21:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 16 GB dumped onto an SD card? Hope whoever it is has ten minutes before security shows up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 21:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I thought OP was joking.  Guess I better get the sarcasdar checked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  Ever run up to a door in one of the Metroid Primes and have to wait for it to decide to open? Loading screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't remember any mention of a hybrid drive in the S.  Source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, UHD BD support.  It's Sony's standard, after all (well, the original BD was). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having played every single Zelda game, handheld or otherwise, it's the only one I didn't finish.  Not happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, "December 30" means "we dunno" in Amazon speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold up, they just said "came to an agreement with Activision" and then mentioned he'd be in Skylanders.  This sounds Spider-Man in the MCU-esque.  Sounds like they're holding onto the IP the only way they can, and letting someone else remaster the existing games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I just looked at it thinking "wow, I'd better jump on this...own it.  Own it.  Own it DAGNABBIT." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 05:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right but if they're publishing it there's pretty much no way it'll turn out to actually be a timed exclusive in a year or two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 04:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's-a Me! You a-killed my father! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 04:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In hindsight those are definitely the same eyes as in the trailer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 04:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sony - "And Skylanders!"

Crowd - "^yeah?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 04:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sony's publishing.  I really doubt it'll be multiplat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 02:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting $19.99 for Tekken

Edit: Figured it out.  You need Gold to get it for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 00:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we're counting between console releases here, not game releases. PS2-PS3 was six years, not 13. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 20:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna post a VGChartz link.  Got your grain of salt? Good.
http://www.vgchartz.com/game/48546/sly-cooper-thieves-in-time/

Now don't get me wrong, I'm one of those half million people, but it just didn't sell.  That's about on par with Michael Jackson: The Experience.  Know anyone who has that game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 20:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last gen was the exception, not the rule.  It's always been 4-5 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 20:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone tell me (if there's enough info) how this would compare to how one would expect a modern PC to run in, say, November of next year? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 18:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft stream link, still looking for the Youtube one: http://www.xbox.com/en-us/e3/live-event </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was pretty regular.  Can't expect "Fallout 4 This November.  BOOM." Every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you looked at your dragon's CO2 footprint lately? Totally irresponsible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more of a fun theory that NX=Nintendo on Xbox.  Haven't seen someone mention it without tongue firmly planted in cheek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Jet Force Gemini Zero
* The NX is Nintendo on Xbox but is revealed to be Amiibo support, and that's about it.
* Viva Pinata Online

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the name of the poem on the Statue of Liberty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The New Colossus is the name of the poem on the statue of Liberty.  It's also quoted by BJ at the end of TNO, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 14:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, this is for both PC and console, it is applied to both.

I was referring to the thread generated by my top-level comment.

Yes it comes off snobbish

There are dozens of ways to approach this without doing so.  I actually considered mentioning PCs in my original comment, but didn't because I feel like I shouldn't have to justify not having a roided-out PC (Edit: FWIW, current machine is a Haswell i7 laptop without a dedicated card.  It'll run Borderlands 2 on max, but not happily) nearly every time I mention owning a console around here.  So far that is not an exaggeration--it really has been nearly every time.  Personal preference be damned, that is super annoying.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are asking this question in a thread about a game that is being released on consoles.  In this context, can you see how it would be interpreted as snobbish to suggest someone just buy a PC when no one asked a question even tangentially related to that? 

Do you have any idea how many times people have replied to me with some iteration of "just buy a PC?" It's not that simple of an equation. I didn't ask anyone's opinion on what machine to get (what in the hell do these people think I'm typing this on?), but there it is being shoved in my face AGAIN.  It's frustrating.

When I went into Gamestop many years ago to pick up a PS2, I had to fend off the manager--THE MANAGER--trying to convince me that I shouldn't bother because the original Xbox was soooooo much better and you got to play Halo.  This is the same exact thing.  Dude didn't know a thing about me or my gaming preferences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be surprised to hear that I agree with you.  Might be even more surprised to learn I'm approaching 500 games in my Steam library.  

The main reason I'm even getting the Xbox is for exclusive games (Forza and Ori, which I can't run on my laptop).  That said, you are probably running Windows, and might've only had the choice to buy one of your games on Origin or Steam.  Exclusivity isn't just a console thing.

That doesn't mean I'm not sick to death of hearing people act like buying a PC is some kind of obvious choice I must've overlooked while stumbling from my one brain cell to the other.  I'm sorry if I opened up on you too quickly there, but you aren't the first person to point this out to me and I am REALLY sick of the PCMR snobbery I see around Reddit.  I just wanna play some games after work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 04:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UGH, *really*?

The PS4 was free.  The Xbox will be cost neutral (long story).  I don't have the space for a desktop, and don't have the money for a gaming laptop.  Also, SOME PEOPLE JUST PREFER CONSOLES, THIS IS NOT A BAD THING.  For fuck's sake, just enjoy your games and let other people enjoy theirs.

Edit: Aaand looks like there is more than one account now going through my comment history downvoting everything.  Seriously, whoever's doing that, go outside or something.  I'm not worth that kind of anger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 04:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looked like October 28 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 04:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me or did the XB1 clip look better than the PS4? Might've just been the shot, I suppose.

...Please don't hurt me, fanboys.  I own a PS4 and am waiting for tomorrow to buy an XB1.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 03:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently I had this confused with Deep Color Output, which I just confirmed is the feature in question on my PS3 slim...I'm still confused, but I'll take your word it's better since the last version I can confirm the ps3 supports is 1.4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 03:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't the PS3 and X360 support HDR? How is this different?

EDIT: FFS don't just downvote me.  I can't wait to get mine, I'm just genuinely confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 00:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally everyone so far has included John Bonham.  Love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 15:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I"m torn. I won a Steam card awhile ago and am waiting for that summer sale, but Sid Meier's Pirates is only $0.50 more than its historical low. I already bought enough in this sale to get Spelunky, and I have the original Gabriel Knight. Does anyone have an opinion about which platform would be better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 13:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I fully expect them to. I was just explaining the joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 04:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft accidentally gave away $110 worth of their biggest current title to who knows how many people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 04:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's implying Bethesda will never work with MS again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 01:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone mentioned these yet, so:

* The Unfinished Swan
* Okami HD if you never played the original
* Enslaved Odyssey to the West
* Puppeteer
* Does Flower count?
* Warhammer 40K Space Marine
* Katamari Forever (people seem to have forgotten there was a katamari on ps3 so I'm including it)


And seconding Driver SF, Sleeping Dogs, Ni No Kuni, 3D Dot Game Heroes, Alice and motherfreakin' VANQUISH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 00:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understood that reference! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The law of Poe is strong in this one. Yeeeessss.

Seriously, I can't tell if that was supposed to be funny or insulting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 23:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to say that whole time wasn't a black, moldy spot on our national history, but the smallpox blanket thing is now generally thought to be a myth also made up by a textbook writer, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 04:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *GASP* Welp, guess I'm a commie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 03:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Citation really fuckin' needed)

MEChA is a Chicano student organization which openly runs chapters in dozens of universities.  They wouldn't be able to if they really did what you say.

Also, "The Race" doesn't have the implications in Spanish that you think it does.

Edit: Also also, *You've got the wrong La Raza there.*

Go back to The_Donald with that misinformation.  Please.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 22:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, and he was her *older* brother if memory serves. I choose to believe he's still around. This is a comic book show after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 18:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article says that the brother who died on the show was her only sibling.  I don't remember if they have this correct (and I'm not sure they do), but if true then how does she have a niece?  That's what they're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Agent Carter Season 3 Twist Could Explain Connection To Sharon Carter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 18:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 07:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've now bought four PS4 games from them. The boxes have all been carefully cut open (through the security tape, which is often still on them) but otherwise untouched.  So far they've all turned out to be "special/day one edition" ones with working DLC codes inside to boot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
