<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2408</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's part of the symbolic language of anime, it shows an emotion or intent through easily understood symbols, it isn't a crutch, it's a way of quickly showing emotion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I was least expecting to find myself liking Kaji.

The way he's introduced makes him pretty unlikable but aside from that he's actually a pretty good character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure it is, random internet person of questionable taste! I'll just take your word for it. 

But really, again, I can't speak for it since I haven't seen it but I'm not just gonna take your word for it, I'll have to see it myself to decide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot structure: Uncommon, since the only one people really relate it to is Robocop.

Of course since I haven't seen the movie myself, I can't comment on that but the common complaint I've heard is that it's structure is very similar to a generic hollywood blockbuster. Maybe something like how Marvel movies are all formulaic. I guess pacing could fit into this as well.

Pretty much just a repeat of plot structure.

Yeah, no. Script as in the dialogue, how characters communicate, what they say etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you think cyberpunk is "generic sci-fi" then I have several dozen "we're in space and something goes wrong" movies to show you. Cyberpunk settings rarely show up in full feature films.

Setting alone is not what makes a movie generic. Plot structure, tropes, pacing, characters and script are far more important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't finish a lot of them though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Satoshi Kon's movies might work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tsuki ga Kirei has potential but the first episode was pretty slow.

Seikasuru Kado has an interesting premise but don't know how good it'll be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mob Psycho 100, Flip Flappers, most KyoAni shows have great character animation too if you like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! If I do end up watching HxH at some point, I'll watch the older one (and then maybe the 2011 one if I want more) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd probably enjoy Natsume Yuujinchou, it's by the same author as Hotarubi no Mori E and its 6th season just started airing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't go so far as to say that it's the movie he's been trying to make his entire career. It does revolve around themes that he likes basing his work around but the writing is different. His older works were different tonally. They were more melancholy and mellow and had less comedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For, the most part, yeah. The colouring in a lot of older series wasn't much different, but it didn't look too bad, but add the digital crispness and it looks ugly. There's still lots of shows with great colouring and shows that do make great use of digital effects work, though. As for HxH, yeah, it looks so ugly, I've seen clips of it and it looks so computerized and shiny. I've seen stills of the older series that looks really good. If the storytelling is just as good in the first, then I'd rather just watch that version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's still hand-drawn though :P And not all animators work digitally, lots of animators still work on paper. I'm not completely sure on this but I think the majority still uses paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't mean they aren't hand-drawn, though. The drawing is done by hand, some animators do it on paper, others on a computer using a tablet. Colouring and digital effects are all done on computer though. And a lot of early 2000s anime had thaqt look as well IIRC since digital technology was new and everyone wanted to use it without knowing how. I don't like the glossy look too much either but if done right it does look good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when things were still hand drawn that is.

They still are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
