<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject268</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 13:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was in Zimbabwe on a hike with 2 adults and about 12 teenagers, we were not following a path and just using a map on a three day trip to these waterfalls (car was there to pick us up). 
We come to a dam with a 20-30m aria of beach sand, this is very unnatural and caused a lot of discussion. Where the beach stopped there where granite boulders and large rocks, it was very attractive and we decided to set up camp early. 1 hour later someone finds this cave, the mouth was small and we had to go down on all fours to get in, but once inside, wow. 3m high ceiling and 10m long it was amazing. There was a crack in the ceiling allowing a beam of light to come streaming though. Naturally, the majority of us wanted to sleep in there. 
1am I wake up being shaken and the Leader of the hike is telling everyone to get out as there is a Leopard outside and this is his lair (they often chose caves to reside in). Im not too phased as this guy is always scheming up pranks and jokes, so I rollover and pretend to sleep. Next thing I know my sleeping bag is pulled off of me and Im being ordered to get now or Im responsible for myself. I then realised he was not kidding, and scurried out, lol. 
We all then sat as close as we could to the fire was we watches the eyes of the leopard pacing up and down in the dark less than a stones throw away but has the water to our backs so we where stuck. Fortunately the leopard did not like the activity and moved off, however they hunt at night and we are pretty much sitting ducks, so I didnt sleep much that night. Every sound was a threat and every moving bush was one step closer to the end of my life. Looking at the tracks the next morning that circled the campsite, we were pretty freaking lucky. 



TL;DR 

Pretty much set up camp in a leopard's cave and where stuck between a dam and the leopard when he came back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 15:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/hacking/comments/4up17b/i_am_a_lead_penetration_tester_ama/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
