<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis | Sean Spicers angry, lonely defense of Trumps wiretapping claim, annotated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Flynn belongs in a gulag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The verses and guitar stylings yeah, but the vocals on the chorus made me think it was MB20, with the band trying something new as they've done album to album a few times. (Bent sounds nothing like 3am and that sounds nothing like the later stuff, but Rob's vocals are pretty consistent.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And somehow it feels like a charicature of a 1930s/40s blacksploitation era movie side kick before he says "Oh, you right, boss. You right." See: Samuel L. Jackson in Django. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't remember hearing it in the 90s. I was young. I heard it for the first time in the late 2000's, early 2010's on some throwback station. I heard the chorus and thought it was Rob Thomas singing. You can't deny, it sounds a lot like Rob Thomas there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first 10 times I heard this on the radio I thought it was a Matchbox20 song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, what're we gonna need the fockin' rope fer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 03:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had is 1040. That will tell us nothing.  
And he paid taxes on it. If Trump leaked this, it was a great move. It doesn't hurt him in any way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that's terrifying.  
I'm starting to think we're not a democracy anymore. hmm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 02:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Math has a liberal bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 01:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good chance for the Dems to pick up a seat if they can find a good candidate for next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Kellyanne even knows when she's lying anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess Congress didn't get that e-mail Donad forwarded to them from his Hotmail address with the Breitbart article link proving Obama tapped Trump Tower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBO score gives Obamacare repeal biggest test yet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 12:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What religion is that? Honestly curious. I just assumed Ivanka is probably a Christian-by-proclamation because that'd be more likeable by the masses, just like her dad, but wasn't actually all that religious (doesn't go to a weekly religious service, doesn't have a history of studying any religion as a guide to her life, doesn't actually read any religious book daily or weekly), just like her dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment by Spicer was of the most insulting, slap-in-the-face comments from the Trump Administration to Barack Obama, the media, and sane Americans yet.  
Disgusting people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Looking at you too, Doug Martin. There is no Dougernaut. You're the Muscle Hampster. Always will be.](http://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/no-more-muscle-hamster-bucs-doug-martin-gives-self-new-nickname/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, medically, its against my beliefs because who really know whats in these vaccinations?  
  

um, doctors? And anyone who can read a wikipedia article or watch a youtube video about how vaccines work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like purples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 05:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Tell me something...](https://youtu.be/9OufCgFZCyU?t=55s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's bad news for the President. Oh, wait, nevermind, Presidents and Senators have full coverage under socialized medicine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't matter if it's nuts, it's the truth. It always has been. How are people just waking up to this? Conservative Christians think that the Jews will go to hell because they don't believe in Jesus, but at best, they still want to protect the Jews from persecution via Israel because WWII makes Americans feel warm and fuzzy, and we're all against the Muslims. That last part leaves them conflicted between their belief in salvation only through Christianity, and their love of the USA as hero/Jewish liberator in WWII. They definitely want to look out for the Jews, in the same way an owner looks out for their pet dog, but they don't want any Jewish influence on the conservative white Christian foundation the U.S. was built on in their minds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way Donald Trump plays the ball down like a real man. Definitely kicks it from the rough or from behind trees to the fairway. The ole hand wedge.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Business insider is such a clickbait site with these titles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 20:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's who Michael Flynn wanted to represent? Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're trying to make peace, man. Put them mower back in the shed this year and hear them out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Clinton lost his law license for lying under oath. Sessions SHOULD lose his license. And he should be impeached from office. And that, coupled with Flynn working as a paid foreign agent with one of Putin's biggest ally's SHOULD open up a massive independent investigation into this Presidency and their campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Alexa, is Amazon connected to the CIA?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republican Senators:  
  
... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 23:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOP House and Senate:  
No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 60 years, our grandkids will be looking for ways to reanimate Scott Pruitt's body just so they can kill him again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a great screenplay opportunity, but no one would believe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 18:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you live in that much fear, you don't take unnecessary risks on your escape.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, Bush didn't really choke on a pretzel.  
It was just enhanced digestion. For the Cheney told me so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if it passes, it means it's good time to be young, healthy, and/or wealthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds even worse with further context.   
But they too had a dream that one day their sons, daughters, grandsons, granddaughters, great grandsons, great granddaughters might pursue prosperity and happiness in this land.  
  
No, Ben. That's not what they had a dream for. They dreamt of going home, of being reunited with their families and loved ones. They dreamt of not being beaten and forced to work for a country they neither knew nor loved. The 20th century American dream you're painting was not even close to what they wanted. I mean Jesus Christ, that might be the most blatant white-washing of American history I've ever heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 23:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In order to accommodate guests further, the park has added a delicious seafood stall, accompanied (obviously) with a hot chocolate stand. A delightful combo for guests during those hazy summer days.  
  
what a monster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds positively revolting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump will take credit for this week of no fatal shootings. Somehow, he will take credit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 20:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew there had to be a good analysis out there somewhere. Hip Singing. So that's the term. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 00:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever that thing is female "indie" singers are all doing with their voices [[this thing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8SU0gFPMwP8)] these last few years, I've had enough of it. Enough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it was real nice when they said President Obama was born in Kenya, is a Muslim pretending to be a Christian, that he was a (literal) demon, and that Michelle is a transvestite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Kushner knew about the Flynn meetings and didn't tell Donald Flynn had lied to Pence AND that he (Kushner) had been there too?  
or  
Kushner told Ivanka (his wife) and/or Donald about the meetings and they all lied.  
or  
Trump knew all along.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sub Zero temperatures? Windows open? I assume the heat was off. Why would you sleep with the windows open in sub zero temps? That's just stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 01:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 02:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post is modern art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about reminding me. It'll never happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "...but we're not going to do anything to help that process along."  
-Paul Ryan, Mitch McConnell, Jason Chaffetz, James Comey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So was the rebounding stock market, but I don't see Donny blaming that on Obama. Hell, he's even taking credit for the current economy (despite not passing/signing 1 bill/order on financial regulation). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 22:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Cus I'm a little older than you are, and male, and I sit like that or in some other fashion with my legs under me on the couch all the time. We're not so old we shouldn't be bendy still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember the last time we underestimated Donald Trump and the size of his voter base? Yeah. Don't do that again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the YETI sticker. YETI is the new Browning deer antler sticker. Monster Energy stickers remain though the ultimate sign of "this person shouldn't own a gun." All I see with Monster stickers is a meth head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad the CNN president spoke out. I wish the network executives would come out strongly more often. It's never happened before, but if the presidents, owners, and CEOs of major organizations would go on camera to defend their organizations, and stand in front of their reporters, it would give the reporters a lot of cover to hit hard on their investigative journalism. And that's what we need right now. I believe it would also drive their ratings if the execs can come across as likeable and strong in their addresses. They are the 4th estate, and right now, we need them to be stronger than they've had to be in 200+ years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So much for Texas going blue in the next 30 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This had better be in Nebraska. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russians make up a pretty disproportionate cross-section of a lot of our assets.  
-Donald Trump, Jr. (2008)  
  
[Source](http://www.eturbonews.com/5008/executive-talk-donald-trump-jr-bullish-russia-and-few-emerging-ma) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL [Sean Astin](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sean_Astin) (aka Rudy, aka Samwise, aka the dude from Encino Man) is Patty Duke's son. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Mob' of 'entitled children' at Highland Park assembly gets called out by visiting author | Highland Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno. I just subscribed to Time and will be getting 52 magazines delivered to my mailbox for $30.00. Seems pretty affordable to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you would like to subscribe to/support a news organization, here are a few links to their subscription sites:  
[New York Times](http://www.nytimes.com/subscriptions/Multiproduct/lp8HYKU.html?src=3004 campaignId=4XUYF module=Subscribe-Now pgtype=Homepage)  
[Washington Post](https://subscribe.washingtonpost.com/acqbeta1/?nid=top_pb_subscribe promo=digital04_header_default oscode=RPWH wpsrc=CM0000447 destination=http://www.washingtonpost.com/pb/homepage/#/offers/promo/digital04_header_default/oscode/RPWH?nid=top_pb_subscribe wpsrc=CM0000447 destination=http:%2F%2Fwww.washingtonpost.com%2Fpb%2Fhomepage%2F)  
[The Guardian](https://subscribe.theguardian.com/us?INTCMP=NGW_HEADER_US_GU_SUBSCRIBE)  
[Time Magazine](https://subscription.time.com/storefront/subscribe-to-time/site/td-flswp1016.html?link=1019480 fpa_oc=Nongated+Order+Form+Test+Q416)  
[LA Times](http://ad.latimes.com/land-subscribe-evergreen/?int=nav2)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was a star I'd grab Donald Trump so hard. And he'd' let me to. When you're a star they let you do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the video of him running? All I see is 12 minutes of arguing and photo ops.  
edit: [Here's a Youtube link to the "running" incident](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0iZoChPbLXc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he was ever going to investigate Trump, it would be now. There won't be an investigation into his taxes, Russian connections, conflicts of interest, Flynn lying to the FBI, any of it. Not one the public hears about anyway, or that goes anywhere. Party over country. Better Red Than Dem. Long live the Comrade Congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
