<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9280</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will definitely keep this as an option if I must go back to trying more meds. thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ADD meds help me for about 4 hours each time I take one, but I experience severe side effects including zero appetite, dry mouth like sandpaper, gas issues, overheating, paranoia, and a huge huge crash everytime, not to mention feeling like im on speed the entire time

Kratom is truly great though.  When I take it every so often it helps for about two plus hours each time, but when I take it more than twice a week it doesn't work so much and makes me too sleepy and dehydrated
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to have to go back to trying more medicines if nothing else works but I've done that so many times and it takes so long and wastes a ton of time.  I waited years trying to different medicines and nothing ever worked, and shit fell apart hard in the meantime </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's flip flopped many times throughout the last many years.  Many times my social life and living situations were great, but the persistent anhedonia and physical feelings of depression never leave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found to trust people's experiences more and not so much what doctors always say, and I've spoken to many individuals who feel much cognitively slower and less "there" than they did before multiple ECT treatments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my exact issue too. /u/Pongpianskul I would love to try shrooms for help but I don't have a connect and don't want to risk the multiple legal and health risks of buying online </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping to get on TRT but I don't want to be fucked from an expensive clinic :/

I'm just not sure any other urologist or doc will treat me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey, what else have you tried? are you like me and running out of options? glad to hear we both aren't alone at least :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> medical marijuana is a fantastic thing but weed makes me more depressed and worsens my condition for me personally </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this has been reposted at least 100x in the last year alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he should have said that or blamed it on Matt Damon, that would have been comedy gold to end a 3.5 hour long show on a joke that good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell me what your numbers were originally before you got on TRT? My levels came back low but my doc says they're not low enough :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there was a huge mess up at the oscars last night when they incorrectly announced the best picture winner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe is the fuckin man. Fell in love with listening to him after discovering YouTube edits on certain topics, then discovered the JRE Duncan Trussell episodes, and from there I just kept listening to more and more

Joe is a crazy multi-talented individual who definitely respects his fans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i see what you did there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well played sir 

*tips fedora* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was waiting for Kimmel to say this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> insider trading... smh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *TREMENDOUS* FUCK UP

***SAD!*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let this distract you from the fact that the Warriors lost a 3-1 lead to the Indians and the Cubs came back 3-1 in the NBA Finals to defeat the Cavilers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 08:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you'll have to find him before he winds up dead in a desert out by the hollywood hills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtfffff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Harvey sitting at the crib like... #Oscars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Harvey sitting at the crib like... #Oscars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you said it sister </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 21:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch her head bobbing up and down when the questioner asks the question  The gears started to become loose in the robot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for username  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duncan's works so well!  Who knew he was also a swordsman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never attempted suicide but I've been close enough to want to for thousands of days.

I know deep down that if I ever attempt it won't be unless im positive I need to go.  If I ever attempted it would be in the most lethal way that I was almost 100% sure would work, such as jumping from a tall bridge or shooting myself.

The issue is that I desperately want to live.  I've seen life through the lens of it being good.  I know there's always a way to change my life around.  It's not that though.  The issue is that the persistent feelings of sadness and anhedonia never ever go away.  I know I don't want to kill myself, but therein always comes the next question to which I have no answer: what do I do to feel better? I've tried so much I don't see any options left for treatment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not gonna believe me but I already have this exact type of thing and do it often. I have six playlists each with about 120 plus songs and each playlist represents for me a different level of emotion. I've abused the playlists so much over the last two years since I made them that they don't help me anymore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meditate often and it helps me a bit but not anywhere near enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not 100% on top of my diet at the moment but in the past I was very much and still never felt any improvement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope i can get on it... thanks man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sex always fuckin sells </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that response that really helped man

These were my numbers for testosterone:

**First blood test**

* Total Testosterone: 288 ng/dl
* Free Testosterone: not measured in this one



**Second blood test**

* Total Testosterone: 417 ng/dl 
* Free Testosterone:  7.9 (I forget the unit type..)

My endocrinologist says the average range is 348-1100 for total T and says mine are okay but I know that this range factors in men up to their 90's and that the normal/ideal range for someone my age is 650-750 or higher. I'm also experiencing all the symptoms of low T so it just makes sense...

I'm just not sure how to find a doc or clinic that will treat me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gone to gym for months consistently and it has never helped my mood or appetite in any significant way :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had my prolactin tested and thyroid tested too and they all came back normal apparently.

What do you recommend I do in terms of should I go to a new doc or clinic first and try to get more low T and other tests? or should I pursue on my own and then find a new doc or clinic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't had E2 checked. I'll try to contact another doctor or clinic this week because I'd really like to get that checked too and try to get on TRT. I'm just worried that even ifI truly do need it I won't be able to find a doctor who will prescribe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 18:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes i exercise consistently for longer times but it never has helped my symptoms...
But my anhedonia has been here probably my whole life but I noticed it maybe 14 years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been considering that but my cognitive function already sucks, and if it doesn't work I'm gonna be left with no depression remission but more cognitive impairment.  I also did a similar brain stimulation therapy called TMS (Transcranial Magnetic Stimulation) and to no avail :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response

I went to an endo for this.  Should I look for a urologist or a clinic that specializes in hormone therapy? I really am nervous every doctor will turn me away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the past I've gone months with maintaining pretty decent diets and sleep even for weeks at a time, and it never effected my depression symptoms in any way unfortunately...

I've even maintained exercise and activities too for months and nothing has ever helped me :(

I'm glad to hear it helps you somewhat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been considering that but my cognitive function already sucks, and if it doesn't work I'm gonna be left with no depression remission but more cognitive impairment.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure what else to do, Please HELP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm almost 24 years old and I've been suffering from depression, anxiety, and ADD my whole life. My main symptom that I can never get over is the emptiness/anhedonia and I'm always tired and low energy and low sex drive and low concentration. I never have an appetite and nothing brings me any warm pleasure inside. It makes every moment of my life so painful.

I see so many posts of people on here who I know haven't tried hard yet and are already giving up and how terrible things are for them. I look at them and see so much hope that some therapy, some medication, some experimental thing will work that they haven't tried yet. 

Then I look at myself who's tried everything to get better and I want to die. I've tried 12 different antidepressants long term, I've tried 8 different ADD meds, I've tried ketamine infusions, TMS therapy, countless supplements, and now after finding out my testosterone levels are very low but not low enough for my doctor to give me replacement hormone therapy I want to die. There's nothing worse than being told for years that something will work and that there's hope and for years after years trying everything and never feeling any better.

My mind is in bit of a better place, and therapy and meditating has helped that, but in my body I feel like hell every moment of my life. Not sure what to do anymore please please help


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> second this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> please help me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 14:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm almost 24 years old and I've been suffering from depression, anxiety, and ADD my whole life. My main symptom that I can never get over is the emptiness/anhedonia and I'm always tired and low energy and low sex drive and low concentration. I never have an appetite and nothing brings me any warm pleasure inside. It makes every moment of my life so painful.

I see so many posts of people on here who I know haven't tried hard yet and are already giving up and how terrible things are for them. I look at them and see so much hope that some therapy, some medication, some experimental thing will work that they haven't tried yet. 

Then I look at myself who's tried everything to get better and I want to die. I've tried 12 different antidepressants long term, I've tried 8 different ADD meds, I've tried ketamine infusions, TMS therapy, countless supplements, and now after finding out my testosterone levels are very low but not low enough for my doctor to give me replacement hormone therapy I want to die. There's nothing worse than being told for years that something will work and that there's hope and for years after years trying everything and never feeling any better.

My mind is in a bit of a better place, and therapy and meditating has helped that, but in my body I feel like hell every moment of my life. Not sure what to do or why I'd go on anymore

please someone help me please god



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty positive this is legit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys wondering if I could get some thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 02:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **First blood test**

* Total Testosterone: 288 ng/dl
* Free Testosterone: not measured in this one



**Second blood test**

* Total Testosterone: 417 ng/dl 
* Free Testosterone:  7.9 (I forget the unit type..)

I'm 23 almost 24 and experience low sex drive, low energy, anhedonia, irritability, trouble sleeping, brain fog, etc.  (tried countless antidepressants, ketamine infusions, TMS, and stimulants and nothing worked.  My mind is in a good place but mentally I'm foggy all the time and my body always feels tired and super low energy)

Are my T levels normal or optimal?  My doc says the average range is 348-1100 for total T and says mine are okay but I know that this range factors in men up to their 90's and that the normal/ideal range for someone my age is 650-750 or higher, and moreover I'm experiencing all the symptoms of low-T so I need your thoughts because I'm considering going to a clinic or different doc for a second opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Powerful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 01:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 23:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant important in the sense of how idiots in the government claim weed is dangerous and how its important to "save" America from the "evils" of pot.

Everyone knows its safe and yes, obviously its important in the sense that putting innocent people in jail is an important issue but I wasn't referring to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah not surprised at all, Silicon Valley is very into futurist thinking and has been shaped based on psychedelic thinkers ideas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People with shoddy principles are exposed quite easily  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how Trump critiqued Obama heavily about federal govt executive abuse of power and now he's doing the same thing. I despise almost all politicians...

And weed is the least important issue at the moment that anyone should be focusing on, but I forgot how stupid the government is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I hope so too. Very surprised to see a YouTuber on JRE, never seen that before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> removing that jack was so stupid, not one person cares about a thinner phone more than having a headphone jack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/hailcorporate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once you've unsuccessfully tried every option to get better you have nothing left </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm almost 24 years old and I've been suffering from depression, anxiety, and ADD my whole life. My main symptom that I can never get over is the emptiness/anhedonia and I'm always tired and low energy and low sex drive and low concentration. I never have an appetite and nothing brings me any warm pleasure inside. It makes every moment of my life so painful.

I see so many posts of people on here who I know haven't tried hard yet and are already giving up and how terrible things are for them. I look at them and see so much hope that some therapy, some medication, some experimental thing will work that they haven't tried yet. 

Then I look at myself who's tried everything to get better and I want to die. I've tried 12 different antidepressants long term, I've tried 8 different ADD meds, I've tried ketamine infusions, TMS therapy, countless supplements, and now after finding out my testosterone levels are very low but not low enough for my doctor to give me replacement hormone therapy I want to die. There's nothing worse than being told for years that something will work and that there's hope and for years after years trying everything and never feeling any better.

My mind is in a good place, and therapy and meditating has helped that, but in my body I feel like hell every moment of my life. Not sure what to do or why I'd go on anymore 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^ check my reply to him i think you'll agree, you and I are def on the same page with this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 06:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just realized having too many hobbies equates to little mastery or true fulfillment in any of them.  Everyone's time is so limited to begin with after work and daily life that its important to narrow down to your most important hobbies and eliminate the rest as much as possible.

I love playing guitar and basketball and going to the gym and a bunch more things and i realized i had too many hobbies and was spending too much time on the ones that were the easiest but gave me the least fulfillment such as playing video games.  

I also am a believer now that you shouldn't keep anything you don't really plan on using again (unless you truly value it as a collectible which is an acceptable exception), so I sold my old PSP, my GameCube, my Xbox 360, my Gameboy Micro, and all their games and am in the process of selling my gaming PC because I don't value using these things as much as I value my other hobbies, and so I realized I don't plan on using them anymore.  The only console I kept was my N64 and the EverDrive I have for it because I value my N64 as a party console with friends and its portable enough for traveling with to places.

I read these posts while in the process of making these decisions and they really helped me decide what was right for me:

https://www.reddit.com/r/TheRedPill/comments/2o8d04/why_you_need_to_give_up_video_games_and_how_to_do/

https://youarenotsosmart.com/2011/03/25/the-sunk-cost-fallacy/

https://www.reddit.com/r/StopGaming/comments/3yv5b6/i_did_iti_made_it_a_month_and_my_life_has_changed/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still creepy as fuck even in my 20's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey i'm sorry you're in so much pain. I'm not going to say something trite or false to try to lie to you. But i can say i would bet a million dollars that if you TRY, just TRY, even a bit more than now it WILL get better slowly by slowly. Reddit loves you. I love you. There's help out there and people who care.

I found this song last summer during a very suicidal day, one of the most suicidal in my entire life, and it undoubtedly saved my life, I think it could save yours too

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EZzKb39rUQA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey i'm sorry you're in so much pain. I'm not going to say something trite or false to try to lie to you. But i can say i would bet a million dollars that if you TRY, just TRY, even a bit more than now it WILL get better slowly by slowly. Reddit loves you. I love you. There's help out there and people who care.

I found this song last summer during a very suicidal day, one of the most suicidal in my entire life, and it undoubtedly saved my life, I think it could save yours too 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EZzKb39rUQA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> solo sex toys and porn imo. especially that porn that's centered around anime. that is sad AF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol yes exactly, not sure why that dude is so annoyed. I was just curious at people's thoughts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude his wife is old as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it entertaining  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About to watch this, I wonder how much of a troll Gavin will be this time and how much Joe will try to get real concrete answers out of him

It's so hard to decipher trolling from sincerity with guys like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn this show truly hit you in all the feels. what a masterpiece nicktoon show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy shit that one was so fucking creepy too. I would watch these episodes and then be afraid to head downstairs or to the bathroom at night.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> almost as creepy as this clip from the show

**https://youtu.be/DRGogGbYaLU** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is a day well spent sir! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whats a candy cab? and third strike? lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've recently become more into simple living and sold all my gaming things I don't use anymore, and this video made me gasp, just watch i wanna hear all your thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> watch the Duncan Trussell episodes from the last year, the recent Shane Smith episode, and Hannibal Burress one. Those are all good ones. And if you're a Metallica fan I highly recommend the James Hetfield episode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever Duncan on its fucking great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> better than none at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putlocker.today just search game of thrones  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 11:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right that's more what I meant. on the internet it's hard to fully explain ideas when read on a line of text </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude so true. When he sang at the end of one of his recent podcasts I was like wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> definitely true  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 08:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well dude, Alex is hilarious and maybe not a bad dude, but he does have a ton of theories that have been disproven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jocko Podcast is great if you're into hardcore military motivation and a disciplined lifestyle. 


Stuff You Should Know is a good one if you're in the mood to learn something interesting from two nerdy dudes. I like listening to it when I get in the same mood as I would be in to go to a museum or read a history book.


The Ben Shapiro Show is my go to for when I'm in a shitty mood because the way Ben uses his high IQ and intellect to destroy assholes and dumbasses makes me feel all warm inside.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just did a secondary round of testosterone tests, not sure if E2 was in the bloodwork, but when I get the results back I'll ask my endo, and I'm praying my suspicion is confirmed and that my results once again show low T so I can try to find a solution for my anhedonia and other related issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats fantastic dude. I truly hope when I get my second bloods back that I have low T confirmed again so i can try to figure this out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's great to hear man, thanks for the response too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 07:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow everything you described feeling like is exactly how i feel all the time. Thank you so much for the response.  I'm so happy to hear you got better.  And it was the TRT right that made the anhedonia go away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [US-NJ] HIGH-END Gaming PC, Accessories, 82 Steam Games,   Much More!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm located in NJ, and I made a nice ad on craigslist of the item which has all the images and a very detailed description, and for the sake of convenience I'll post the link **[here](https://southjersey.craigslist.org/sys/6013357570.html)**.

I also have an image to provide as a timestamp which includes my username: [Timestamp](http://imgur.com/kgbEeGZ)

I'm willing to negotiate on the price in the ad and will accept PayPal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what should I have shown instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what made it invalid? I showed the items and had a handwritten note with my username and the date </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh okay. I put a timestamp though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i read the rules. which rules did i break? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 17:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmaoooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> found the 7th grader </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what about hiring real fucking boys? ones who can think and have genuine hopes and dreams? ones whom given the opportunity to do this would be ecstatic? this constant western philosophy of treating animals before treating humans is so fucking stupid 

It's the same reason why people are opt to adopt stray pets and care for them but let orphans stay in orphanages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> somebody gild this man to heaven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 08:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> upvote for Eagles fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GUYS, im all for SJW hate, and lets bring these SJW's to true justice, but saying "cuck" makes you sound like an angry 7th grader playing call of duty on xbox live. Why do we need to stoop to their level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOOD^LORD^JESUS  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats great to hear. thanks for the response, i appreaite it. how long after you began TRT did you start noticing any decent improvement in mood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when i just read your entire comment i heard Alex Jones' voice in my head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seconded to hell! it's ruining reddit lately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did u do TRT? and did u previously have anhedonic symptoms in your depression that later went away or diminished with the test treatment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did u originally start treatment for low E2 or low testosterone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude, not necessary cmon man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **TRAIN BY DAY, *THROW FECES BY NIGHT*, All DAY** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> time to unsubscribe.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The symptoms almost seem to mimic low testosterone it seems. when you got treated did you get better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
