<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9425</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 08:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you do have all the curses, I'd just use super restores, they give more prayer points than prayer potions. Also use prayer renewals, as they give prayer points over time, so if using turm+as drained it by five per second (idk if that's accurate) it will drain it by like 3.5. So really for an hour, I'd take about 12-15 4 dose restores </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 11:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is it so hard to start a slayer tab! I'm at 18.5m slayer xp and i find it so difficult to start a tab. I'll be three tasks in and be like I'm gonna sell this. How do you keep adding to it!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 01:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just quit McDonald's after 9 months of working there. I don't know about the U.S. but here in the UK it's a fucking nightmare working there. About a month before I quit I was cleaning a toaster, and I only just touched it, then I done what they said keep it under for 10 minutes. They then said you'll be fine and gave me some ice. Fucking bastards kept me working for another hour and a half whilst I was in serious fucking pain. I had to go to A E and get the blisters popped, the doctor said they were second degree. During the time after the accident I was the only one on the tills, and we had a fuck tonne of customers come in, and I couldn't do shit. I just waited until everyone came off their breaks. Thank fuck I left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, that's quite satisfying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What am I looking at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Noah, I was amazed by this work, I've been looking at it for about an hour and a half now, and I really want to buy one. This one is my favourite (I love the clashing colours) http://m.imgur.com/GQu4YbS
 However it isn't in the store :( is there any other way to buy it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 17:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes he is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 00:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do super range and magics if you can, all the way to your first extreme, then make those and stock up, then you'll be at 96 in no time. Super range and magics are from what I know the cheapest training. If you don't have the req, get it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 23:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAPPY 20th! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 12:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rs3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 12:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I fucking love your videos, especially your slaycasts, you're just awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 11:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're on Alien blue, change the view mode to classic, and at the bottom of the phone, when you're on the subreddit page, tap the open box with an arrow in it, a selection menu will pop up, and press view sidebar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youtubers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 10:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What Youtubers do you guys watch? For me it's Alkan, Munkydunky, a friend, Justice, Slayaholik, and Mradelaide. Do you guys know any more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 12:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/diiJ5Hb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of course we're number 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 20:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 20:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless upu need 50 fletching, you can use maples, and they give more shafts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 15:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try allocating more memory to it? Run on minimum graphics, and what I do, before starting the game I wait five minutes for my computer to boot up, I have a shitty computer. Try this is it doesn't work try running in internet explorer or Firefox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overloads and saradomin brews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 12:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to kill raxx, never done before by me, if I'm overloaded and use a brew dose, do I need to drink a restore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 02:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need spirit, yew, or magic seeds? Kill ganodermic beasts. They have a fairly high slayer requirement (95), but they're an amazing source for seeds as well as just money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 01:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're a skiller, kill ganos, it's a fairly hefty slayer requirement but they drop them so often, I get at least 2/task </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 10:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I peeled them off on Friday, got burnt last Monday. It didn't hurt because the skin was dead, and it was moist where my finger was sweating  with the plaster on. They were nice thick chunks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got burnt at work on a toaster, this happened after A E and got the blisters popped. Two days after the incident. So satisfying to peel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 01:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 01:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here comes /r/runescape
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 01:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far away from the largest star would we have to be to be able to sustain life? So where we are in relation to the sun, where would we be in relation to that star, to have the same climate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 20:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legendary pet with scavenge is unbelievable at automatons. The high health means slower kills, so the pet has more time to pick up the items. so its 98% pickup rate, the 2% are because of those kills that are simultaneous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 01:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, o loved the show, I watched it constantly and would watch it again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 00:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who just finished watching house, I couldn't agree more </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget to quest. With questing many more money making opportunities open, and skilling opportunities. Quests such as rotm, world wakes, fotg, and even as a last resort. Rotm = glacors, dbane. World wakes (full) = 6th ac, automatons, bunch of free exp, new abilities. Fotg = nihils, t75 div, muspahs. Even the easier quests can give great rewards, such as the replayables (dod, haunted house quest) dark light upgrade ( granted not as good as before)  and surgeon ring, t85 power ring, great for bossing.
 Quest, and more opportunities in the game open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 22:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There isn't really much, and I don't want to be the guy to say it, bust it has to be slayer. Armadyl God wars is a fantastic way, since legs and chest are hitting ~4m. Unfortunately most end game content is what brings in the cash. Automatons are nice, 67 slayer requirement except all those quests. If you have a legendary pet, set scavenge on, arm them until you get a drop, gloves are about 7m which is nice. I'm not a very efficient money maker, can stay stable at around 7m. Just kill things that have an expensive drop or slayer really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 22:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realise that its still a browser based game, but just a disclaimer saying except for chrome or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like this should be changed... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 22:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I didn't use them correctly here, I feel sorry for my examiner ;) I'll edit the post :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drifting away... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 00:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as people in Britain who are doing A Levels know, public exams start in about 9 days. I have my first exam on the 5th, and I'm not sure what for, hopefully C1 maths... Anyway, so at the start of the year, actually on the 31st of December, I bought a year membership.
 Now at first I was like yeah this is a great idea, but then as it came closer to exam season I began to realise what I'd done. 
Now don't get me wrong, I love the game, I really do, but I have seen myself just logging in, using keys, logging out. The game isn't getting boring, I'm just getting bored, I'm focussed on levelling stuff up and not actually enjoying the game. In all fairness a lot of the enjoyment was from quests, and after achieving QP Cape, I felt like a weight was off my shoulders, because I enjoyed it, but I wanted it done.
 Now what I'm trying to say is, don't think you HAVE to play the game. Runescape doesn't have to be a commitment, and if you see it that way, fair enough, but if you have other things that are more important, don't choose runescape over that.
 Tomorrow my Sport Studies course work gets sent off to moderation. I left 3 essays to the last minute. I had to complete 3 essays in these last two days, and get them marked, and from what I know, only one of them is good. If I hadn't prioritised runescape, I would've done excellent. 
Despite this, I'm not quitting runescape, I'm letting it dissipate for until I want to play it again, and it feels good.
For anyone about to sit public exams, I hope you haven't been as stupid as I have. Runescape is fun and all, but you need to prioritise.
Also as a side note; go to the gym, exercising will release a hormone called serotonin, which is known as the feel good hormone. His is similar to what is released playing games. Go to the gym, because you never know, you might get addicted :3
Thank you to the rs3 community for being so good, I'm always on this sub reddit browsing, and I can't wait to see the legacy mashup arrive, but as for now, I'll see you when I see you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new Superrewards seems a little to broken to me... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new Superrewards seems a little to broken to me... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 22:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It took nearly 8 years, but i finally got my quest point cape today :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 22:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] [Some like it cold] Hmm, it seems death didn't like his new office, and decided to move back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 23:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] Hmm, it seems death didn't like his new office, and decided to move back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you wearing insulated boots? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
