<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5181</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 22:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In English it's called A Void. 

I thought it was tedious and didn't finish it. I've realized lately that I'm not fond of gimmick novels. I get that the whole point of Oulipo is to be gimmicky, but that doesn't mean it's not better in small doses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who's Esther?

His fourth wife, to be named at a later date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 20:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, thought the same thing last night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool idea but you have to consolidate duplicate titles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the title was "Is Buying a House in 1920 in Queens a bad idea?" and I was like, if you've got a time machine, go for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a couple of Esther movies but they're terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 04:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You haven't been to the northeast if you think that. NY, NJ, and MA drivers are the worst and the traffic is even worse. I've driven in just about every state on the east coast and SC is a breeze comparatively speaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, historical. Didn't even occur to me. Yeah, wasn't Mel Gibson supposed to be making a Chanukah movie?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 01:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sort of plot are you imagining? Because I got nothin'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relatedly, you can say to them, "Age before beauty." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many weird ideas on Reddit today. What's going on, sunspots?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is that necklace? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps in this case the old Dr. Zhivago translation was bad but that's generally not the case with classics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is not a compelling argument against any of our other traditions, so why should it be so here?

Because in this case the Gemara clearly says it's for health reasons and not religious reasons. The Gemara is not our go-to book for health advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the dash then semicolon. It's old-fashioned and rarely used but it can be useful on occasion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly the same thing, but Battle Royale was re-translated because the original translation was terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's listed as a type of ad hominem attack on TV Tropes:

http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/AdHominem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two can play at that game:

Nope.

Yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 03:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's icky from a Jewish perspective too. It's child molestation, gay, or both, both of which are assur. 

It's just that in the olden days they didn't know what the alternatives were. But it's not the olden days anymore.

And it's a minority that do it. A majority of certain groups, but not a majority of all Orthodox Jews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of men who are not neckbeards who are like this. My boss is like this. He happens to be a nice man, but he doesn't know how to shut up and listen, especially to women. And see, that's the difference. When I hear him talking to men, most men will try to force their way into the conversation. When he's talking to women, the women will just stand there and nod pleasantly. 

It's not hateful to want to be heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lynne Stewart, Lawyer Imprisoned in Terrorism Case, Dies at 77 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 06:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 05:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about turning it around? A lot of men are not interested in what women have to say and are perfectly happy to chew your ear off. If you're quiet, they're happy. They don't know you, they don't want to know you, they're just using you.

While women don't like to see other women being excluded. They're trying to get you engaged in the conversation and your being quiet feels like you're rejecting them. I knew a girl like that once. She had the most fascinating life story and it was like pulling teeth to try to get her to tell it. I came to hate her after a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad started out college in the chemical engineering program, which is where I assume he learned to write in all caps. But his handwriting is shit so I'm not surprised he flunked out. If he wanted to write like that, he should have gone to medical school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is feeling "like a woman" the same as feeling feminine?

I don't know, it's a tough question. 

Thought of another one: Being the only woman in a room full of men. 

Also. Did you buy it??

:D

It was a costume in the Victoria and Albert Museum in London.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 05:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a girly-girl. Trying on a corset made me feel very feminine in a way that I normally don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 02:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't say I've ever done that specifically, but in general when in any kind of relationship with a person with a fairly serious mental problem, the important thing is to set the boundary that you're not his therapist. Another thing is that no matter what his problems are, he can't drag you down with him. These two things can be tough for a lot of people to insist on, so what you end up with is a non-relationship that you're just going to regret in the end, because you can't save him and he's going to make you miserable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 06:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is a very real and very large problem in clinical mental health with narcissists who have infiltrated the profession

It's well known that psychologists tend to have issues themselves, but this comes across as rather sinister. Sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 05:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/thatsthejoke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/oddlysatisfying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bizarre Goodreads recommendation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you liked A Separate Peace by John Knowles, we recommend Swimming with Giants: My Encounters with Whales, Dolphins and Seals by Anne Collet.

Description:

In Swimming with Giants, Anne Collet describes the power and majesty of being close to some of nature's most magnificent creatures. Combining science with a sense of adventure, she conveys the sheer excitement of her work, from riding the tail of a white whale to saving animals harmed by drift nets or toxic spills. 

And recently I read Fobbit by David Abrams, which they recommended to me because I liked Billy Lynn's Long Halftime Walk by Ben Fountain. That's a logical recommendation but I didn't like Fobbit as much as Billy Lynn, not by a long shot. 

GR's recommendations system needs an upgrade.

What good or bad recommendations have you gotten from GR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 16:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's newborn babies. Parenting starts as soon as the kid has any kind of agency and awareness - that's around 6 months old. People seem to think that whatever babies do is adorable, but you have to start out that young by not letting them pull your hair until it hurts, not letting them hit you or grab your glasses or delicate jewelry, and if they try to drop something on the floor seemingly on purpose, you don't pick it up for them. You tell them, you drop it, you lose it. 

Too many people wait until the kid starts walking or talking. But by then the kid who has learned who is in charge. And if you let them get away with that stuff, it's not you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every non-northern European, you mean. I don't see anyone claiming Swedish people are like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kevin Spacey's character in the Negotiator. Actually, I couldn't decide if I preferred to marry him or have him adopt me as his kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 21:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little. The trade-off is living a frugal lifestyle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was paying 60% of my income in rent for a 1 bedroom on the UWS. It's worth it not to have roommates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wouldn't say absolutely any premise can be a good story

I shouldn't have written "good," I should have written "viable." Good doesn't actually matter in a world where there is a movie with three sequels that are about a tornado with sharks in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 03:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two black Jews at my work that you'd never know were Jewish. There's a white man in my extended family that I guarantee you that you'd never guess he was Jewish if you just passed him walking down the street.

Your problem is confirmation bias. You recognize someone who's Jewish and find out they're Jewish and you're like, hey, I knew it! But what you're forgetting are all the people who are Jewish, but you don't think they are, and you never find out that you were wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Jews aren't a race. Can you tell a Korean Jew from a Korean non-Jew? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is April. The Earth went through a wormhole that sent it two months into the future. "They" are just keeping it a secret. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different type of exploitation, but certainly yes, you should avoid buying fast fashion and other products made in sweatshops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 05:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My skin is definitely not flawless, I'm 27 and still struggle with acne, blackheads, and dry/oiliness. I have perpetual dark circles under my eyes. 

So just use concealer. You don't need lipstick and mascara to cover up acne.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strip clubs are by and large exploitive of women. Most of them are there because they're desperate, not because it's an easy way to pay for medical school. 

But you're going to do whatever you want, so it doesn't really matter what I say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scotland Yard, Britain's Biggest Police Force, Is Now Led by a Woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 05:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open Orthodox? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mistrust nice people because if they're nice to everyone, then what evidence is there that they like me specifically and they're not just being nice to me because they're nice to everyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're at the beach, cringy and low class. Doesn't matter how good looking the guy is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bucket. That way someone can't claim that they don't realize they're taking up two seats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In what zombie movies/TV shows could you swap them out with killer bees and still have it make sense? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 03:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If ebooks don't work for you, don't read them. Tricks to help you concentrate aren't going to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 22:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read a ton. If I died tomorrow I'd be fine with not having read the books on my to-read list. They're not particularly important to me, they're just entertainment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you're sleeping with guys quickly under the assumption that it will deepen the relationship. In most cases it doesn't work that way. You might want to try dating and not sleeping with the guy until you've gone out at least a handful of times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
