<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9526</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can we tell how fast a gas giant rotates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 22:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't the gas move along at a different rate than the core? How can we tell that a "9.5 Earth hour" rotation at the top of the atmosphere isn't only 4 hours near the core?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 20:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Detox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 21:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eminem in Underground. "Gave Hannibal Lecter a fucking nectarine and sat him in the fuckin fruit and vegetable section and gave him a lecture." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 06:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eminem - Sing for the Moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 17:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yelawolf - Trunk Muzik </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 04:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Ferrell Lines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-23 04:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The Book of Three" by Lloyd Alexander. Incredibly capturing. Can't wait to read the next books in the series! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-22 07:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eminem - Rap God.

I don't seem to grow tired of any element of this song.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-22 08:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spruce wood and doughnuts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 03:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11 year old me, along with my family, were sitting at our table in Pizza Hut. Everything was going well, we had just made our order and we're quietly anticipating our food. 

Fast forward half hour and we are starting to get a little bit annoyed with how long we are being held for. We notice another family enter the restaraunt and make their order.

Fast forward another half hour, and this family is (to our disgusting shock) eating happily at their full table of food. My dad finally calls a waitress and asks what is taking so long, pointing out that another family just walked in and got their food before we were even considered. The waitress apologizes and points to the cook, saying "He must have forgotten." 

Fast forward another half hour (this is total 1:30 waiting time) and the family from earlier is paying their bill and leaving. The restaraunt was nearing empty. We were among maybe 3 other groups of customers sitting at the tables. We decide that this is a waste of time. As we were leaving, no staff gave any notice to us. My dad was furious, I could tell, but he was doing well to contain it.

As we were pulling out of the parking lot, we saw the cook that the waitress pointed to earlier, sitting on the curb beside the building having a smoke. I have never been back to Pizza Hut since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 03:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corn Pops... There's always at least one genetically altered pop in each box that damn near breaks my jaw. And don't even get me started on how quickly they go stale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 19:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Woman in Black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 06:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eminem - Lose Yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 06:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the ultimate goal for the human race is to fully understand / map out the universe, perfecting all ways of travel and confirming all theories. It's a shame none of us will be alive by a longshot to see our race expand into the universes and understand it, but at the same time I think we should be grateful that we were around to witness the beginning of it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
