<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3285</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It probably won't be until a few days from now.  I'll come back and tell you when I've posted one.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I never even thought about that. I'll check that immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ORMIE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate it, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I will be making another update within a couple days. I just hoe this ends soon. I can't take much more of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly hoping it is. I'd rather no that my Christina, Allis, and Myla truly do exist and are just sick in the head, than them not existing at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may have to. I just don't want them to lock me up in some asylum. I need to find my family, or at least some answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The woman definitely does. I unfortunately have no idea how to find her though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might have to do that, thanks. I just don't know who would orchestrate this situation to trap me in. I'm not anyone special, I don't have any enemies that come to memory. I don't know why this is happening to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The parallel universe is becoming more and more likely as time goes on. Whatever it is, the woman definitely knows something. I just have no idea how to find her.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides a few word conversation with the hotel staff when I was checking in, no. She's the only one who could be doing this to me. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't even joke like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. If it is a simulation, I have no way of finding that out or even fixing my situation. I don't know what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Wife and Kids Never Existed (Part Two) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Click Here To Read Part 1!](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/63hyrq/my_wife_and_kids_never_existed/)


I dont know if I can take much more of this guys. My wife and my two beautiful kids were everything to me, and so far they show no promise of returning. Everyday it gets harder and harder to continue this, and the events that are taking place arent helping. The past two days have added nothing but more confusion, and I want it to stop.

Let me start a little bit after my last post. I decided to go to a local bar and drown my fresh sorrows in some alcohol. Not the best choice of coping, I know, but I just needed to take my mind off things. I stayed at the bar until 9PM (I was only there for a couple hours) before they closed and kicked me out. Too drunk to drive home, I decided to call an Uber. For those who are unfamiliar with Uber, it is a taxi service where everyday people are the cabbies, and they use their personal cars. 

In my smaller town, its usually the same 3 drivers. However, the one who picked me up was new. She was this pretty brown-haired girl, boasting a tight blue-dress. She was chatty, but I honestly didnt feel like talking. She told me it was her first day (which was weird, usually drivers receive training on their first few days of work), asked me how my night was, the typical small-talk questions. However, she told me something I will never forget. Something that still sends chills down my spine.

As she pulled up in front of my house, I exited the car. I started to walk away, when I heard her window roll down. I assumed that maybe the payment didnt come through, or something malfunctioned, so I turned around and faced her. She smiled at me and said I hope you find them! Before I could respond she laughed and sped away. She turned the corner before I could get her license plate number.

What the fuck does she know about this? She has to know something, why else would she say something like that? Was this some sort of sick, elaborate joke? 

I got home and tried to put it out if my mind. Despite it only being 9:15PM, I decided to go to bed. I didnt sleep much. That woman was all I could think about. Who was she? How much did she know? I had no way to be sure. All I know is that this just ruined me. Instead of being sad, now I was just angry. 

I passed out about an hour later. I was startled awake by a call from No Caller ID. Ive always had sleeping problems (now more than ever) so I knew I wouldnt get back to sleep for another few hours. Expecting some night shift salesman, I answered. However, what the female speaker on the phone said was much worse.

I hope you find them.

I was angry, no I was furious. WHO THE FUCK ARE YOU?! I screamed into the phone. She hung up, and I threw my phone against the wall, and shattered it.

That was two nights ago.

I awoke the next morning with a sharp headache from the heavy drinking from the night previous. I just sat up in my bed, and stared for a little while. I didnt want to get up. I didnt want to leave my bedroom and find my wife not in the living room with her exfoliative face mask on, pretending to be an alien and chasing Attis and Myla around the room.

After a few minutes of staring and shedding a few tears I got up and went to make myself coffee. I sat down and decided to take my mind off things by watching the news. 

My now old-fashioned landline began ringing in the kitchen. The automated voice began to read off the caller ID Call from: I hope you find them. I got up and bolted into the kitchen. No number was present under the caller ID, even though it usually was. I picked up the phone, my heart sank and tears began to stream down my cheeks. 

There wasnt another human on the line, but an automated message. An automated message of a conversation between me and my wife. It was when my wife told me she was pregnant with Myla (my first child).

I couldnt listen to the whole thing. Hearing my wifes voice just hurt too much. I just sat there on the kitchen floor and shuddered; tears welled in my eyes. 

There were so many questions running through my head. How did they get this recording? What kind of sick person would call me and play this? I assumed it was the female Uber driver from the night before.

I just decided to leave again. I couldnt stay in that house. I couldnt stay in a house I no longer felt safe in. I drove to a nearby hotel, and decided to stay there.

I brought my laptop and conducted some research. I searched through every social media site and online phonebook possible. I even called the university Christina graduated from. No one had records of her existing. Not only that, but her family didnt exist either. I looked up their social media accounts and found nothing.

I spent the rest of the day watching TV and working out at the gym in the hotel, doing anything I could to not concentrate on my situation. I stopped by the local liquor store and bought two twelve-packs of beer to keep me company, and to wash away the damaged emotions I have.

That was last night.

I dont know why this is happening to me. What the hell did I do to deserve this? Why is this mystery girl tormenting me? I dont know what to do. I just want this to end. I just want my family back. 

[Click Here to Read Part 3!](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/64yl8w/my_wife_and_kids_never_existed_part_3/)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did. However, the phone number no longer exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few people have brought it up. I'm doing research on it, but it usually doesn't occur ti something of thus degree. If ny family disappearing truly is a mandela effect phenomenon, then I have no idea what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, hopefully this gets resolved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, it's in my house. I guess it's mine. I never purchased one though, nor have I ever purchased the pool table though. I don't know how they got here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm going to have to do. This might have to become a series... I just have to get this off my chest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 11:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard of the Mandela affect, but nothing to this degree. Usually it's just like peanut butter being spelled a different way, not your entire family disappearing over night. Thank you though. I'm gonna call off work, and research this shit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
