<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6959</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 08:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gartner:

Worldwide Smartphone Sales to End Users by Vendor in 3Q16 (Thousands of Units)				


Vendor	3Q16	3Q16 Market Share (%)	3Q15	3Q15 Market Share (%)
	
Samsung	71,733.50	 19.2%	83,586.70	   23.6%

Apple	43,000.70	 11.5%	46,062.00	   13%

Huawei	32,489.50	 8.7%	27,412.70	   7.7%

Oppo	        24,936.60	 6.7%	11,868.60	   3.4%

BBK 	       19,878.90	 5.3%	 10,437.40	   2.9%

Others	181,253.30 48.6%      174,812.80  49.4%

Total	373,292.50	100%	 354,180.20  100%


			



Strategy Analytics:

Strategy Analytics has released its estimates for the third quarter of 2016 on global unit volumes, and the market researcher estimates that worldwide shipments grew 6% in the third quarter to 375.4 million. Android continues to dominate the global landscape, and Alphabet is growing its share at the expense of all other platforms. 

There were nearly 330 million Android handsets shipped, comprising 87.5% market share. Apple's 45.5 million iPhones were good enough to grab 12.1% share -- down from 13.6% a year ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you sure?


That doesn't bode well for the LNP's plans for the people of Australia then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'd prefer to raise these kind of issues before they get to that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 07:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nay GaryGronk. Cry havoc and let slip the theropods of war! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No lean and hungry looks from me. You can bestride your narrow world in peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turnbull IS our Trump.

Same as Trump, he's a rich man after a trophy.

Both were elected as successful businessmen. Trumpeted as agents of change, someone different.


Trump will be about as effective in government as Turnbull has been. It was all a bait   switch.

Politics has become a rich man's sport, and the winner gets to put the head of the country on their wall for their friends to admire. They don't care what happens to the rest of the carcass.


The meat's being divided up amongst their mates. The vultures can pick at what's left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll fall by it soon...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 05:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.

The Snapdragon in the OnePlus 3T already benchmarks at 90% of the A10. The  Snapdragon 835 in the Xiaomi Mi 6 handily beats it.

The AnTuTu score for Xiaomi Mi 6 rakes in at an impressive 210,329, which is higher than the record score of 183,106 of iPhone 7 Plus. Talking only about Android phones, the Snapdragon 821-powered OnePlus 3T has been the record holder so far, with a score of 163,578.

http://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/xiaomi-mi-6-purportedly-spotted-in-antutu-tipped-to-be-fastest-phone-ever-1646199 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 05:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did that in 2014. How have sales been so far?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 04:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.

Period	Samsung	Apple	Huawei	OPPO	  vivo	 Others

2015Q4	20.4%	18.7%	8.2%	      3.6%	 3.0%	        46.2%

2016Q1	23.7%	15.4%	8.4%	      5.9%	 4.4%	        42.2%

2016Q2	22.8%	11.7%	9.3%	      6.6%	 4.8%  	        44.9%

2016Q3	21%	        12.5%	9.3%	      7.1%	 5.9%   	        44.2%


http://www.idc.com/promo/smartphone-market-share/vendor;jsessionid=B0F31B2F5D65CB1C5FCD7E49CC2E3EDC
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who do we put up against the wall when the revolution starts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've owned a mix of diesel and petrol vehicles for most of my driving life, and never mixed them up.


Quite apart from the fear factor, the smell alone is a wake-up call as to which fuel the vehicle should be getting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a /r/australianantisocialism for us introverts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What problem?

The way to handle people is to treat them like chickens. Take away everything they have by plucking all their feathers and then throw them a few bread crumbs. They will then follow you forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 02:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moora's in the WA wheatbelt, but it's only 180km from Perth. Not exactly the outback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 09:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Jan 2016 Communications Authority Kenya (CAK) report claims 74%, with most using mobile data.

Growth of smartphones there is over 8% per quarter, so published numbers are likely to be out of date very quickly.

http://gadgetry101.com/news-item/74-2-of-kenyans-are-on-the-internet

http://www.techweez.com/2016/04/08/internet-penetration-in-kenya/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the man's a walking fruitcake.

Still right about corruption though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 07:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as embarrassing as us mocking him despite him being absolutely right about the rest of it.


The letter then goes on to attack legislators in government, who he claims are sending [the] country broke. We are giving a subsidy of billions a year to corporations including state governments who have been and I believe continue to break the law of this country, he writes.

If the problem isnt resolved corruption will continue to be endemic.

Give the man a cookie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 06:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you drain it while you're showering it with gold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 06:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause or effect? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 06:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Kenya has less internet penetration

Only by about 13%.

With seven out of 10 Kenyans using the Internet, the country has the best penetration in Africa according to data monitored by the aggregation website InternetWorldStats.org.

http://www.nation.co.ke/newsplex/kenya-fixed-broadband-internet/2718262-3352180-q5r79vz/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.

Popular support is the first element which is necessary for the creation of authority. But an authority resting on that foundation alone is still quite frail, uncertain and vacillating. Hence everyone who finds himself vested with an authority that is based only on popular support must take measures to improve and consolidate the foundations of that authority by the creation of force.

The LNP is working to ensure continuity and stability of government. That means they will need to have enough information about __all__ citizens to be able to identify and control those who may decide to dissent.

At this stage, it will not be necessary to have administrative groups such as a Division of Garbage Analysis, but disturbing results from metadata analysis may guide them in that direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xiaomi Redmi Note 5 Specs Leaked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 02:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 01:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malcolm is trying to govern, and is guided by this principle:

The art of leadership consists in consolidating the attention of the people against a single adversary and taking care that nothing will split up that attention.


He just hasn't selected the right adversary yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview - An Open Industrial IOT Gateway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 01:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 09:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rumored to be around US$450. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THe GSMarena site has a bit more detail:

http://www.gsmarena.com/xiaomi_mi_6_runs_antutu_allegedly_scores_recordbreaking_210329_points-news-22596.php
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Distaste is growing, and it wouldn't take much to spark it into anger.

Malcolm Turnbull and Bill Shorten are the least desirable pair of combatants vying for the leadership of the country in more than 20 years

http://www.theaustralian.com.au/national-affairs/newspoll/malcolm-turnbull-bill-shorten-the-least-liked-leaders-in-20-years/news-story/140c9d4efa425378151c3de6ad7dc303 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 03:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should hang them on the back of the kilt then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xiaomi Mi 6 Tipped to Be Fastest Phone Ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
If One Nation thinks she's a little too extreme for their party,

Given that Ashby is now leading the party, I'd say her chances aren't good.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 11:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't a once-off. She's been flying to the Guild Coast on the public purse for years. 

We've probably paid for 20 times what she's admitted to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 07:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunlight and salty water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 18:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free adverts on /r/Australia, more like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quantum physicist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 10:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're wearing them wrong... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you'd rather spout ivory tower theory than recognise external reality? 

Your choice, but don't expect the rest of us to respect your choice of folly. 


Lowering the corporate income-tax rate would not spur economic growth. The analysis finds no evidence that high corporate tax rates have a negative impact on economic growth (i.e., it finds no evidence that changes in either the statutory corporate tax rate or the effective marginal tax rate on capital income are correlated with economic growth).

http://www.epi.org/publication/ib364-corporate-tax-rates-and-economic-growth/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 06:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get him to fix the Treasurer. That guy's even more clueless than his predecessor.

The Federal Treasury has not modelled the potential impact of Australia losing its AAA credit rating due to rising public debt.


Economic analysts have warned Australia has a one-in-two chance of having its credit rating downgraded next week after the Government's mid-year economic update



http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-12-16/treasury-economic-modelling-on-downgraded-abcc-credit-rating/8126608 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 02:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He may be playing the long game. I can see how his two recent ideas might be combined to gain some populist appeal.

Outspoken government MP George Christensen wants to do away with the prime minister.


http://www.heraldsun.com.au/news/breaking-news/majority-of-mps-back-republic-arm/news-story/a8ab96bf09b662dc94882ab25b798640


Either that, or they're just joining the growing pile of dead cats on the table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 02:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say "Pyne", I say "Potato", Neither, neither


Let's call the whole thing off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 02:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you have to admit, from a LNP perspective, he has a point. Australia has the ability to do this far better than the Philippines.

We now have metadata collection and retention on all devices Australians use. Police surveillance drones and fixed cameras can already invisibly watch people in real time. We have face recognition and number plate tracking already. There's a good chance untraceable cash transactions will be made illegal soon, and we already have detention centres that are underutilised.

We're at the point where it will be possible to easily identify anyone who has searched for hydroponics, bought suspicious items online, talked to the wrong people on the street, burnt the flag, done anything suspicious at all, in fact.
 
We could do this, cart anyone who's not been a good citizen off to a detention centre and apply strong, swift justice, or if there's no doubt about their guilt, save money by summarily executing them. Recidivism rates are over 60%, so why not? 

Australia could very quickly be drug and criminal free, a utopia. 

What could go wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 09:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It helps to have Brandis on your side...

George Brandis names former Liberal MPs for $200,000 tribunal role

Two Liberal MPs who lost their seats at the federal election and a former Labor speaker are among those tapped for plum positions in George Brandis's latest round of appointments.

http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/george-brandis-names-former-liberal-mps-for-200000-tribunal-role-20161215-gtc1wj.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You reckon 's worried the big chook might eat it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 04:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even that. This is more dead cat politics.


Turnbull is pulling some Nero-level fiddling with $100 notes, Potato Xmas, suing granddad, aussie republicans, 18C, backpackers, etc etc.


Meanwhile all of the real attention our economy and society desperately need are being ignored. 


It's getting pretty bad when I read Andrew Bolt, and think "yeah he's right again." Now I feel nauseous.

Andrew Bolt says Malcolm Turnbull is the worst Liberal prime minister since Sir William McMahon. That is most unfair  to McMahon.

http://www.adelaidenow.com.au/news/national/malcolm-turnbull-the-worst-pm-since-sir-william-mcmahon-thats-most-unfair-on-mcmahon/news-story/377bc8e49c0e3334da43bf5d4edd75ed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 04:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second-hand stuff.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 02:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labor's fault! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 02:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernardi is the lead now, isn't he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 09:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be Redhill? Their prices are astronomical. 

GENERAL WASTE

 
Cars/station wagons $33.00

Trailers (6x4) $58.00

Trailers (6x4) high sides $73.00

Tandem/horse floats ( 1 tonne) $107.50

Van/utes $56.50

The Australia tax is nothing compared to the WA tax...

http://www.emrc.org.au/fees-and-charges.html#wwcubic
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 09:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it isn't.

As someone who would normally consider "appeal to authority" as a logical fallacy to be avoided, but who also works in risk management, I can say some of the examples given go well past "near miss reporting"


At BPs oil refinery at Cherry Point, in Washington state, US, the report said there is no single aggregated list of safety critical equipment and there have been instances where getting replacement equipment up and running was compromised due to incomplete data. Response time to failure is compromised by the various sources of data. This is seen as a significant concern during a response crisis. Five years earlier the plant had been penalised for 13 serious safety violations, including failure to keep records.

This is how people die, because a company takes such a huge PR hit from adhering to safety reporting standards.

No. People die when companies fail to learn from previous accidents, and authorities fail to follow up when companies don't correct critical errors more than 5 years after they've been raised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 08:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's another /r/Australia Cadbury's promotional posting. It doesn't matter if you're excited, their social media marketing team will push this one to the top of the queue for the next few days. 

Either that or there's thousands of people just hanging around Reddit waiting for low quality, low effort confectionery to upvote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't humans have a penis bone? Scientists may now know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 08:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 06:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enough car-mountable Aztec death whistles for every man, woman and child bogan in all of Australia and New Zealand.

Oh, and a big bag of chapulines for my wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 06:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Third_Howard_Ministry
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 06:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The top 3 Google "What if" searches in Australia are:

1. Why is there a leap day

2. Why is the sky blue

3. Why is my internet so slow

http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-4030788/Google-reveals-10-searched-terms-Australians-2016.html

We need a real internet sooner rather than later. The press should be all over this, using public pressure to force better services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a huge market for the app, it'll be a winner if it gets to the wider public. 

The top 3 Google "What if" searches in Australia are:


1. Why is there a leap day

2. Why is the sky blue

**3. Why is my internet so slow**


http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-4030788/Google-reveals-10-searched-terms-Australians-2016.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just remember, Queenslanders are the Newfies of Australia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nokia Returns From Wilderness With New Feature Phones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autism linked to vitamin D deficiency during pregnancy, researchers find </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did.



This study examines how conversing with passengers in a vehicle differs from conversing on a cell phone while driving. We compared how well drivers were able to deal with the demands of driving when conversing on a cell phone, conversing with a passenger, and when driving without any distraction. In the conversation conditions, participants were instructed to converse with a friend about past experiences in which their life was threatened. The results show that the number of driving errors was highest in the cell phone condition; in passenger conversations more references were made to traffic, and the production rate of the driver and the complexity of speech of both interlocutors dropped in response to an increase in the demand of the traffic. The results indicate that passenger conversations differ from cell phone conversations because the surrounding traffic not only becomes a topic of the conversation, helping driver and passenger to share situation awareness, but the driving condition also has a direct influence on the complexity of the conversation, thereby mitigating the potential negative effects of a conversation on driving.

TLDR: It's safer talking to passengers. Passengers can also see traffic conditions and alert the driver. 

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/19102621 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hands-free phone chats while driving delays reaction, Australian study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stop time: Apple pulls software after reports of bricking Watches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was not that great as Minister for Communications. 


Not great? That's got to be the understatement of the century.


The Federal Government has been dumping a ton of money into the National Broadband Network (NBN) but this investment has brought down the country's net worth by $8.8 billion, according to the Parliamentary Budget Office (PBO).


http://www.lifehacker.com.au/2016/12/nbn-drags-down-australias-net-worth-by-8-8-billion/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> United States grounds Osprey aircraft in Japan after Okinawa crash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 03:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clever girl.

That's how they kill the snakes. If there wan't a road nearby, they'd drop it on a rock, but a truck or car does the job more efficiently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the lifeless drones in the LNP, it beats acting on evidence that could actually reduce costs. 

But imagine if they did something that would save far more than the cost of the unemployment benefits?

Early intervention is key to reducing the costly impact of poor mental health in Australia, says a visiting UK economist.

Mental illness has been put on the economic agenda, as its cost to the nation soars to more than $60 billion a year.

The National Mental Health Commission estimates the cost of mental ill-health to Australia is around four per cent of GDP or about $4000 for every tax payer.

Rather than waiting for a person's poor mental health to reach crisis point, the focus needs to be on prevention and early intervention, says Professor Martin Knapp from the London School of Economics.

http://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/2016/12/13/poor-mental-health-costs-aust-60b-year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 09:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying the data is fried? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still won't work, and liquid oxygen would be incredibly dangerous to transport in that context. 


The lake is more than 2km wide, and even if you only freeze the top metre of it, that's more than 4,000,000 tonnes of water (assuming it's longer than it is wide). 

Freezing that much water with liquid gas, even if it was possible to transfer the heat efficiently, would take several thousand supertankers full of LN*_2_* or LOX </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I should have googled that one - for some reason I thought they started in NSW in the '30s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bickfords in SA, Weaver and Lock over here in WA, Wondersnack in Vic, Smith's Snackfoods, I think is still Australian. [Edit] Nope, thanks /u/rcsgd. Smiths are not locals at all.


Then there's my personal addiction, Duke's chilli pea chips, made in WA. Seriously, do not try these things, not even once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The world could wipe out malaria. A new report shows why that isn't happening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have made a diamond that's harder than diamond </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 08:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a giant crater in East Antarctica, and it's very bad news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 07:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 07:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even then, trust in the financial numbers the government is claiming is very low. 

Ratings agencies are all-but calling the treasurer a liar, and warning him not to do it again.

Credit ratings agencies have put Treasurer Scott Morrison on notice, warning they wont accept unrealistic forecasts in next weeks budget update.

http://www.news.com.au/national/politics/credit-rating-agencies-warn-scott-morrison-ahead-of-myefo-budget-update/news-story/696947340bb87efaa3b7a33d28dbf6fd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an interesting number, around 70MB for every person over 15 years of age in Australia.

I wonder how it's structured. For raw numeric or text data, that's a huge amount of information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newspapers used to be where journalists worked. You know, the people who were trained in investigation, and skilled at communicating the outcomes?

There's been no real replacements for all of the lost investigators. 

TV journalism has its place, but that too is now a very shallow pool, especially since the ABC has been taken over and politicised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's better than you talking about their ABCC's test case against the CFMEU being "riddled with unsubstantiated hyperbole".


http://www.afr.com/news/policy/industrial-relations/abcc-loses-test-case-against-cfmeu-ringmaster-20161212-gt9228
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using metadata to track down whistleblowers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How pre-teens using metadata found a whistleblower in two hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 04:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 03:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That works when you can trust the numbers. 


With the ABS defunded, and Treasury politicised, my confidence in the general public's opportunity to accurately assess Australian economic conditions is at an all-time low.

Looking at job adverts, empty shopfronts, CBD vacancy rates, and other consequences of recessions tells me that it looks pretty similar to other recessions around the world, even if the Government's numbers say otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cassini spacecraft has sent back photos of Saturn's north pole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 09:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 09:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And just when you think it's safe to dive back into the NBN waters...

The Turnbull government will seek to introduce a new levy on telecommunications companies to help pay for the roll-out of the NBN in regional areas, a change it admits will lead to higher prices for internet consumers. 


http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/this-could-cripple-companies-like-us-government-announces-new-nbn-tax-on-broadband-companies-20161212-gt9hxj.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 07:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, Trump does have SOME standards.

Donald Trump releases statement distancing himself from Cory Bernardi endorsement

http://www.smh.com.au/comment/satire/donald-trump-releases-statement-distancing-himself-from-cory-bernardi-endorsement-20161103-gshdd1.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Matthews shipwreck off Australian coast mapped using 3D modelling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Refracta 8.0 Is a Pint-Sized Powerhouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 09:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dole already does exactly this.

The dole SHOULD do this, but does so very poorly, inefficiently and expensively. Many of the UBI options are actually neutral in terms of new costs (by balancing tax with basic income), but save money by eliminating the huge overheads of administering the dole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 09:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference between UBI and NIT is largely semantic, and either can be cost-neutral if the tax structures are set up to be so.


There's a good FAQ here: http://basicincome.org/basic-income/faq/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 09:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, given the size of the dino, I'd agree heat management and also camouflage would be bigger drivers of selection, especially given the earth-tone chestnut colour of the feathers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 08:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you've just invented the shuttlecock.

She'll probably just make a racquet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 07:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We are not an ATM*." 

.* ^^Unless ^^you're ^^a ^^coal ^^miner ^^and/or ^^non-tax ^^paying ^^multinational.


Turnbull to COAG when asked for infrastructure spending.


http://www.theaustralian.com.au/national-affairs/coag-meeting-jay-weatherill-tells-pm-his-job-on-the-line-over-carbon/news-story/bba23b610542a4af7478b6599a9b19c4

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 07:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, the WA equivalent of funnel webs, though as you'd expect from the Free West, much more chill.


http://australianmuseum.net.au/red-headed-mouse-spider-missulena-occatoria </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 07:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the worst is when you're riding a motorbike at dusk through the Pilbara bush, and run through a mulga grove which has been fully-webbed-out by orb spiders.

Not only do you come out the other side half-blind and trailing long sticky streamers of web, you also get to taste whatever they left uneaten, and feel many small(ish) legs scuttling inside your clothes and helmet, especially since they ALWAYS have hatchlings.


Believe me, it makes walking through a web seem like happy happy fun times.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 07:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think teachers are naive to think that ethical decisions can be divested from politics.

FTFY.

So they would be both negligent and naive not to teach that ethics and morality are important, despite the very poor example set by Canberra.

Teachers have a dual moral responsibility as both values educators and moral agents representing the integrity of the profession. 

http://files.eric.ed.gov/fulltext/EJ995231.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's fascinating is that this contempt for their electors from political leaders is global.

This article in an Australian national newspaper shows that the Australian government is preparing policy that will funnel 15 billion dollars from households and businesses to electricity companies.


The Turnbull government has been sitting on advice that an emissions intensity scheme - the carbon policy it put on the table only to rule out just 36 hours later - would save households and businesses up to $15 billion in electricity bills over a decade.


http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/government-killed-emissions-scheme-despite-knowing-it-could-shave-15-billion-off-electricity-bills-20161208-gt6v48.html


Despite this being splashed over the media, they've essentially shrugged their shoulders and said "tough, it's going to happen". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 09:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WWI ended because the Germans ran out of everything. 

By 1917, there were food riots in the cities, and their soldiers were relying on captured British equipment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia Wants To Save The Great Barrier Reef While Building A Massive Coal Mine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 07:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 07:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

Eradication 'a real no-brainer'

The independent report suggested eradicating the ants would be a highly cost effective measure, with each dollar spent on eradication saving $25 later on.


We're fucked. 


The LNP will see that as an opportunity to funnel 25 X the amount of money to their pest-management donors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama's legacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But without rules I wouldn't be so safe and would want the war to stop. Like, a lot.

Historically, that's not what happens. People on both sides believe they can win, and with complicit press and priesthood,  demonise the people they're fighting, so they can believe their foe is subhuman and worthy of extermination.

Like the war we're fighting now. We fight for freedom, they fight for faith. We are corrupt and ungodly, they are inhuman and cruel. Neither countenances loss or compromise, so variations of the same war have been erupting for decades, with no end in sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 06:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kind of the point.

The whole purpose of the LNP is to protect revenue streams for its sponsors. they're not eve bothering with pretense any more.



**Government killed emissions scheme despite knowing it could shave $15 billion off electricity bills**

The Turnbull government is sitting on advice that an emissions intensity scheme - the carbon policy it put on the table only to rule out just 36 hours later - would save households and businesses across the country up to $15 billion in electricity bills over a decade.

While Malcolm Turnbull has publicly rejected this sort of scheme by claiming it would push up prices, an Australian Electricity Market Commission report handed to the government months ago finds it would actually cost consumers far less than other approaches, including doing nothing.


http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/government-killed-emissions-scheme-despite-knowing-it-could-shave-15-billion-off-electricity-bills-20161208-gt6v48.html

http://www.abc.net.au/news/2016-12-07/political-donations-top-$1b-thanks-to-big-business/8097030
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primordial soup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you're not the only one who thinks that way, so that's how we end up with barbarism.

National and global social values aren't visible or solid or even easily definable, they're a fluid set of things that are accepted as a priori fact, or at least as important by most of the people participating in those societies.

There have been times and places in the history of humanity when women were seen as spoils of war, where killing all of your enemy's children was a sensible way of ensuring your supremacy, where putting captured soldiers in the belly of a bronze bull and lighting a fire under them was good sport.

Our society, at least the part of it I live in, gradually transitioned to a path where we accepted that other people think, act, and are more similar to us than they are different. Between us, we made agreements, laws, and contracts that limited how much we hurt each other, even when we disagreed. There was a trend towards reducing the severity and scope of conflicts where possible. Visionaries started to think about how we could create better lives, instead of how we could be better warriors.

Even many military people believed that doing so allowed for a path to peace after the fighting was over. It was seen as better than the centuries of anger and resentment to neighbours that happened after unlimited (except by technology) wars were over.

Now, we're losing touch with the reasons those agreements were important. Abu Ghraib and Guantanamo torture, rendition flights and drone assassinations that kill 30 civilians, all ratchet up the barbarism. 


You justify it by saying "All's fair", those 30 people who've never raised a hand against us were worth killing because we assassinated the leader. Meanwhile, someone in Daesh, who thinks very much like you, is saying they're justified cutting the heads off a different 30 non-combatants because it suits **their** political goals.


Both of you are making barbarism a self-fulfilling prophecy, because  neither of you value the society we **could** become. You only value the impact you can have on your opponents now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100%, eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 07:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The news story contains analysis of a (paywalled) Nature article titled "Origin of modern syphilis and emergence of a pandemic Treponema pallidum cluster". 

The text of the article summary includes the sentence "Although resistance to penicillin has not yet been identified, an increasing number of strains fail to respond to the second-line antibiotic azithromycin3".

TLDR: The title I posted is the unedited headline title of the linked news story, and reasonably accurately reflects the content of the Nature summary.

http://www.nature.com/articles/nmicrobiol2016245 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New antibiotic resistant, pandemic syphilis strain identified </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 07:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 07:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you're right, and in fact it actually says so in the PISA report.


If you compare Australian students in the top and bottom quarter by their parents' socio economic background, the bottom 25 per cent are on average three years of schooling behind the top 25 per cent. 

That's in all three tested areas in PISA: scientific, mathematical and reading literacy. And it means that a kid born poor, by no fault of their own, is on average getting a far crappier education than a kid born rich. The achievement gap is almost as bad for indigenous kids. 

You don't need to smash your PISA results to see that's deeply unfair, and a waste of human potential. 

http://www.theage.com.au/comment/australias-real-education-problem-is-the-equity-gap-20161206-gt5jwh.html

https://www.acer.edu.au/files/PISA-First-Look.pdf


Birmingham's response is especially smarmy when you realise Australian students have gone backwards relative to their international peers, but also relative to Australian 15-year-olds in 2000 when PISA started.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 06:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the GDP fall was caused by weaker government spending, so it's intentional on their part. 

The mock dismay is just for the cameras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's worse to come.

This discussion is a hot topic across /r/technology.

Australia is set to criminalise crypto research of government public data sets. Nine days remain to comment. So far there are two responses.

https://www.np.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/5gw8ix/australia_is_set_to_criminalise_crypto_research/

It's likely to kill set back online privacy research in Australia, leave our data (including metadata) more vulnerable, and put researchers at risk of prosecution.

Sadly, many of us who'd post this kind of info to /r/Australia have been banned, so it's mostly being discussed by Americans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a seemingly barbaric age, faith in the laws of war are dangerously slipping, Red Cross survey finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 05:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUDE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, it's endemic, but I don't think it has to do with not knowing. 

It's a sly method of casting doubt on an opinion they disagree with. They're asking questions instead of clearly expressing their own opinions, in order to make force you into being defensive without exposing their own position to scrutiny.

Superficially, it can seem reasonable, but in practice, it's pushing the onus of effort to one side of the discussion without contributing anything of equal value.

Leaners, not lifters maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've included a cite in my comment below:

https://www.np.reddit.com/r/australia/comments/5gvkby/police_will_no_longer_need_court_approval_to_get/davrxfk/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you.


Sealioning is a nasty practice, and more of us should stand up to them. If /u/electronicwhale was genuinely interested, they would have done their own digging based on your statements, and only asked for obscure or difficult-to-discover information.


FWIW, I checked how hard it was to find the information by Googling 'How long can police keep your dna on file "South Australia"', and the first link in the search result had enough information to validate that /u/AdamDaze was essentially correct.

The purpose of sealioning never to actually learn or become more informed. The purpose is to interrogate. Much like actual interrogators, sealioners bombard the target with question after question, digging and digging until the target either says something stupid or is so pissed off that they react in the extreme.


/u/AdamDaze responded politely, and explained reasonably that he was entitled to post an opinion without having to provide full cites. This is, after all,  a discussion forum, not an academic journal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 02:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been tracking prices and estimating total ROI, including all tariffs and costs like tree pruning.

For my location and current electricity costs, it takes too long to get the return for batteries to be viable, but with falling battery costs and ramping grid prices, we'll get to a cost/benefit crossover point eventually.

And since the WA gov't is planning on selling Western power, it'll most likely happen sooner rather than later, and when it does, it won't be a few nerds playing with new tech, it'll be a cascade of people escaping from expensive services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhones exploding and catching fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 01:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 6s Shutdown Issue Might Be Bigger Than Apple Thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 01:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your smartphone knows a lot about you, but what about your mental health? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 08:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drugs commonly used to treat delirium unhelpful, may hasten death in patients, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 07:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tests confirm that Germany's massive nuclear fusion machine really works </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 07:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oxehealth uses cameras to monitor your heartbeat from across the room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 07:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know:


When asked what he thought of the fact that Mr Tonkins only engaged the animal to save his dog, Baird was unrepentant. If its not a greyhound, I dont have to give a shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 04:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We still have him. His name's Turnbull. 


Same as Trump, he's a rich man after a trophy.

Both were elected as successful businessmen. Trumpeted as agents of change, someone different. We've been down this road before.

Trump will be about as effective in government as Turnbull has been. It was all a bait   switch.

Politics has become a rich man's sport, and the winner gets to put the head of the country on their wall for their friends to admire. They don't care what happens to the rest of the carcass.

The meat's being divided up amongst their mates. The vultures can pick at what's left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iris is an AI to help science R D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malcolm Turnbull:

* I have never supported a banking Tribunal.

* I have never supported a carbon tax.

* I am not the 2nd worst prime minister of Australia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 03:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, /r/Australia is recognised as the 2nd most negative sub on Reddit:

https://www.np.reddit.com/r/australia/comments/2aby40/raustralia_no2_most_negative_subreddit_xpost/


The mods here have a habit of banning people who post anything they don't approve of from submitting, so it's generally only the cynics who hang around.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 02:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have never been at war with Oceania. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hepatitis C drugs Australia's most expensive, cost taxpayers $1 billion in four months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 09:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 08:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I thought "rolled over like a ginger kitten" was worth a chuckle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
