<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject983</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 20:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, its clinical depression. I'm in CBT now and on an antidepressant. Neither has really helped much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 20:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any ideas on how someone as depression can integrate these ideas? I feel like everything I've tried to beat it isn't working.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 05:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally like the grilled chicken blt. 380 calories, 32g protein. Plus, bacon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 21:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly what I was looking for. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 18:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For heavy vs light, is that referring to all lifts, or is that just the main compounds and I keep the same weight and rep scheme for the accessory?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 03:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of it is the curlbro mentality as well. A bunch of people probably do a lot of chest and bicep work before starting on a full body routine, which can put their bench ahead of everything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 16:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinical depression  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 01:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he could have thought of it on his own and never heard of her: not everyone steals jokes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 01:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the social aspect of community college is completely non existent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-20 03:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question for the women: is the fact that I train in mixed martial arts a turnoff?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 05:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare you insult the jorts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 17:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Vlad. He can just hit you with his q whenever you try to last hit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 17:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to defend against it as a somewhat tech savvy end user? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 17:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did my first unassisted chin-up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 07:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the video and it was really informative.  My one question is about the intermediate stage and specifically how it relates to bodybuilding.  If one is training for hypertrophy, is it still feasible to have a weekly progression in the intermediate stage? I was under the impression that to have solid weekly progression , it would have to be a strength focused routine(IE Madcow).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 04:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen some videos, some of them by Layne, which seem to indicate 2x per week will stimulate greater growth.  

How would I be able to determine when I'm ready for phat then? 
Also for my 3 day split: could I just use the hypertrophy part of PHAT and do the last three workouts twice a week and just skip the power days?

EDIT: Also, what should my minimum lifts be before transitioning off SS then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 03:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any suggestions on a similar style of programming then? I'd like to hit each muscle 2x per week instead of the standard 1x per week in a typical 5 day split.  If I can't do a strength/hypertrophy combo I guess I'd rather focus on hypertrophy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggested lift stats before switching routines? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 03:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As of now I am running starting strength.  At 175lbs and 6' tall, maybe around 16%ish bodyfat, my current lifts are deadlift 205lbs, squat 135(I started with just the bar so its a little lower), bench 130, and OHP and clean are at 85.  I was also to get my first unassisted chinup yesterday! What numbers would you guys suggest hitting before switching to PHAT?  My main concern is having lifts high enough so that when training hypertrophy and the speed work I'm actually moving a decent amount of weight, but I'm not sure what the suggested benchmark is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 22:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer eclipse to notepad++ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 21:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm suffering from severe depression right now (I scored a 35 on the beck depression analysis) and today I did my first unassisted chin-up after working out for three months. It was the first time I felt like I truly accomplished something in a long time. For me though, the exercise hasn't helped my depressive symptoms on a day to day basis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 00:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I alternate calories, I don't cycle hi/low carbs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 23:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any benefit to a leangains approach without cycling the carbs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 05:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget hang cleans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 22:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit I didn't even notice that. My sleep has been way off for the past week and i started if about two weeks ago. 19 male here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 01:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is last few pounds recomp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 15:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Context: one of the leaders of my mma class said this during a grueling conditioning set: "If MMA was easy everyone would be doing it". For some reason that really stuck with me, and it can be applied to a lot of other situations as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 18:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started graying at 15 :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question for women that I would answered. I'm very familiar with all the things that guys do in conversations that appear creepy. However, it seems that women label me a creep even if I've never spoken to them. For example, going out of their way to avoid me, staring at me and looking away when I notice, and overall body language of dismissiveness (ie crossed legs or arms, body turned away, etc). What behaviors could I be doing that evoke this response?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 22:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the compliment, but asking for her number before she's even spoken? That's pretty creepy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 21:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a story of how not to do it. I was in Starbucks yesterday on my campus and was grabbing a coffee, and there was a girl in line in front of me. Some guy came up to the girl and told her she looked really cute. She hasn't even responded yet and then he says "can I have your number now?" My palm came in contact with my face very soon after that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 15:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 19 and at community college. Social life = null </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 23:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a specific sub for discussing mma techniques for people currently training or competing mma? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 16:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in my wow days, being a successful raid leader at age 15. Neckbeards can give you so much shit when your voice hasn't dropped yet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 16:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would there be any harm in doing greyskull styled resets on ss? (Instead of deloading and doing 3x5, I would deload and do 2x5, then 1x till failure until I reached the weight where I stalled, then transition back to strict 3x5)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 19:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone gets clinical depression  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 22:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't use your fists for regular punches. You'll break your knuckles. Stick to hammer punches, palm punches (think nick cage in conair when he kills the guy in the beginning) and elbow strikes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 18:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not wrong at all, just for me personally it was extremely hard to maintain form with the hi bar. I also find its easier for me to hit parallel with low bar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 03:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn how to low bar squat properly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 15:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Masculine energy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 04:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you're suffering from depression and nothing builds your confidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 22:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking out a women  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 19:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A grilled chicken blt is 380 cals at Micky D's. that's what I eat if I'm in a pinch and have to eat fast food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 01:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to begin this argument by making a case that allowing women to serve in combat positions and drafting women are two different things.  This isn't really that hard to do, as they actually *are* two different things.  One lets those women who choose to do so to serve their country to the best of their abilities.  The other says we're just going to randomly pull mothers, sisters, wives and daughters out of the civilian population and stick them down in combat.  Regardless of whether you think these two things should go hand-in-hand they are actually two different things.

But pulling fathers, brothers, husbands and sons out of the civilian population and sticking them in combat is ok?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 16:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \ tfw no gf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 19:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [le]terally  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 18:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on his bf % </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 15:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there like a picture of the end position I can see somewhere?  I'm trying to picture this in my head but I don't see how it could happen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 14:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I can't even do one of these. Shows how much I need to work on my flexibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 00:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3. 

HALF LIFE 3 COMFIRMED! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 19:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have any exercises/stretches I can do to increase my shoulder flexibility for low bar squats? I can find "the shelf" perfectly fine, the issue is I can't position my hands on the bar without my wrists going under the bar and the compression of the bar on my wrists causes them a massive amount of pain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 16:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think protein intake will be important here. If you don't get all the aminos your body needs it will have to break muscle tissue down for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 03:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL I've been benching wrong  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 00:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your post; it was very informative. When you say engage the cardiovascular system at least 3x per week, what would you recommend for duration and intensity?  And would a mma workout count as a day of cardio? ( they are 2 hour classes, 1 hour of boxing/kickboxing and 1 hour of jujitsu)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 00:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Runners high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 19:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is a great answer and hearing the science behind it was very helpful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 19:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mma classes have pretty much replaced the hiit. The first half of the class is boxing/kick boxing and it's a pretty good workout.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 19:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His definition of severe was based off one of the depression screenings that is commonly used. He said anything above a 30 on it was severely depressed and I had a 31.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 18:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing the lifting and mma because I want to, and the cardio is sorta both. I like to do the low intensity walks after lifting as a cool down, but I can't stand the hiit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 17:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wanted to try the natural options before going for the meds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 16:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wanted to check levels of some chemical in my blood. Getting the results this Wednesday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 16:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy pretty much all of it except for the hiit running.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 16:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say my fitness level is about average. Last time I weighed myself I was 182, at around 16-18ish% bf (6' 19 male). I'm not a runner, I'm more interested in lifting over distance running. If I tried I'd guess my mile time would b somewhere in the 7-9 minute range.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 07:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think mma works really well for me because of the mental aspect. It's sort of like chess, but with the human body. I think that's one of the reasons I don't enjoy running since their is no mental challenge to it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 06:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is running a blood test to check for low vitamin D and low iron levels, as well as like 20 other tests.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 06:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad has an amazing insurances policy, so cost isn't going to be an issue (It has no limits on mental healthcare costs).  I met with a psychologist a few weeks ago but she was really cold throughout and I got a very negative vibe from it. I have an appointment with my GP this wednesday and I'll talk to him about seeing a psychiatrist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 06:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a complete self diagnosis I'm saying right here, but I'm pretty sure SSRIs aren't for me. I think I might have low dopamine levels because my concentration and motivation levels are extremely low.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 06:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is a combination of life + chemical imbalance. I really didn't get depressed until I started community college so I figure that has something to do with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 06:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main reason I'm concerned about going to a shrink is that they'll just toss me on some antidepressants. I'm not opposed to the idea, but I don't just want to get on some meds and be tossed off to the wind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 06:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comparison I always use is telling someone with depression to snap out of it is like telling a diabetic to just produce more insulin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 03:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm at the gym I feel good I guess, maybe a 4/10 (that's high for me), the rest of the time I hover around a 2/10. I'm really happy with my results so far, and working out is definitely one of the best parts of my day. However, based on what my doctor told me and what I've read on the web, I was expecting my overall mood to increase when instead it has decreased.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 02:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my next appointment this Wednesday, he drew some blood last time and was running a plethora of chemical checks on it.  I'll make sure to tell him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 22:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 scoops chocolate or vanilla whey, half cup milk, 2 scoops mint chocolate ice cream. Absolutely amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 15:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On my last deadlift set, I failed my last rep because the outside of my right hip felt like it was going to be ripped off. What could have caused this? Poor form, flexibility issue or too  heavy of a weight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 01:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This ones worked for me so far: don't flirt at all  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-13 16:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm doing Greyskull LP, when would be the best times to add the Ab Ripper X in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 04:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blueprint decoded from RSD. I'm using it right now and it's the first a lot of these concepts have really clicked for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Issue with fit on jeans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 00:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok guys, I have a bit of a problem here.  I have a little smaller than average legs, but I have a huge ass.  This presents a huge problem when shopping for jeans.  I'd definitely prefer to go with a tapered fit, because that is what shapes the best to my lower legs. However, the issue then becomes the waist size, which is most prevalent on Levi styled jeans.  If I get a waist size that actually fits my waist, it is near impossible to get the jeans on.  If I select a larger size, my ass will fill up the extra material in the legs, however, because I have a smaller waist it leaves a huge gap between the the back of my waist and the top of the jeans.  Going up from a 34 (which is my real size) to a 36 allowed me to pretty much fit my fist in between my waist and the denim. This issue is on all Levi jeans I have tried, especially the 511's and the 514's, which were the ones I was looking for originally.  I tried on some other offbrand jeans, and the only ones that would fit me well in the waist/ass region were larger jeans in boot cut, but it left way to much denim flopping around on my lower legs.  Any ideas on jeans I could try?  So far the only pants in general I have found that fit me really well are the Lived-In slim series from Gap, but unfortunately they don't make denim version of those pants.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 02:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been there a few times, it seems like a circle jerk of self-loathing for the most part  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you overcome your depression?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 01:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 19:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at Dominicks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 07:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't have any pictures, you just remind me of a kid that I went to high school with: St Francis in Wheaton IL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 07:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danny? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-06 16:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really it just needs some variety in the cymbals.  As a drummer it was really painful to just hear that one crash ridden the whole song.  You could try adding a different crash on some of the downbeats.  Also around 30 seconds in, you have a transition to a different feel.  That would be a great time to maybe switch to the hi-hats or a china for the ride, just to mix up the sound.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 02:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends heavily on use; probably one week if used multiple times on a daily basis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 01:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My social life definitely needs work, I just have a really hard time meeting new people. I mainly suck at starting conversations, once one is going I'm perfectly fine. 

What do you mean by a creative outlet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 01:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't feel that I'm at a stage to be approaching women, namely because of my depression and lack of doing anything that is found interesting by the rest of society.  Based on the experiences I've had trying just to have conversations with other people during my first semester of college, I still can't get over the fact that it seems like I'm bothering them by trying to talk to them. Second is I really have no idea where to go sarge. I've tried just talking with people in my community college campus but all I've gotten were snappy or uninterested responses. I've tried library, cafeteria and Starbucks but had no luck at any of them. I guess I could try a bookstore or another coffee shop, but I've just had generally bad experiences approaching so far.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 00:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of it is probably my depression, most things aren't fun anymore. Hopefully the meds + therapy will help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 00:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't really like the rock climbing that much, so I'm probably not going back to that. I recently signed up for some free trial mma classes nearby so we'll see how that goes. 

I think part of the issue with quitting video games is the fact that they make such great time fillers. Lets assume that I get really into those mma classes. Even if I went to every weekday session from 7-9pm, did all my school work and went to class and continue my daily lifting/cardio, there would still quite a few hours of free time that I would have no idea what to do with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 00:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The number one goal is definitely improvement.

I guess I find it hard because I really enjoy video games, and when I've tried out other stuff it hasn't given me the same satisfaction as gaming.  I went out and tried rock climbing at a local place, but I really couldn't get into it and it was pretty boring.  Tried DnD, which I thought would be a good fit considering my background, but I didn't like that either.  

Part of it could be the fact that I'm suffering from depression, which I just got diagnosed with last week.  They've got me on some supplements now + I'm starting psychotherapy next week, so hopefully I can start to get this worked out.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 23:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are pouring your passion down the drain. 

Definition of passion from dictionary.com:
a strong affection or enthusiasm for an object, concept, etc: a passion for poetry 

If video games are something that is fun for me, how is playing them "throwing my passions down the drain"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 22:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if the only thing my program has for stalling is a 10% deload, will I just keep continuously deloading then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about stalling squats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 22:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 22:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the exact opposite.  I really love how I can get into the stories, plus it provides a great way to recharge my energy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 22:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kinda confused here, as I seem to be getting two conflicting sides here from seddit.  The first thing people always say is that you should recognize your passions and pursue them.  Mine are definitely programming and video games; my dream job would either be as a game programmer or an information assurance specialist.  However, here on seddit technological hobbies such as mine seem to be placed into a lower tier, and people say that I need to get "real hobbies", as though my choice of past-times don't actually count.  I'm really confused on how to move forward here and any advice you have would be appreciated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 02:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that was a really informative post. When do you think an appropriate time would be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 19:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen 40 year old virgin; that might be a good watch for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 19:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the input. I guess I've just had a really long streak of women like those you mentioned, and so based on my sample size it seems that this was a much bigger issue then it actually is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 19:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the most part it was just some flirting, and then she would ask some question like "where's the craziest place you've had sex" or "what's your favorite position", and that's when is say I'm a virgin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 17:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second no more mr. nice guy, and would also suggest the book of pook. The book of pook was the first time I really got some of the pua outer game concepts, while no more mr nice guy helped me start working on my inner game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the fact that I'm a virgin really that big of a deal? (19M) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 05:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally it doesn't bother me that I'm still a virgin.  Sometimes my guy friends give me shit about it, especially in high school, but I know they were joking. Now, I'm in community college and I've had some strange experiences with women over the matter.  On multiple occasions over the past semester, I had been having some pretty decent conversations with a woman and overtime the conversation would get a bit sexual.  When the fact came out that I was a virgin, their demenanor would completely change from being open and engaged in the conversation with me to turning away, avoiding eye contact with me, and becoming blatantly uninterested.  One girl who I was texting stopped responding the instant she found out I was a virgin.  This has never been a big issue for me until now.  Is the fact that I'm still a virgin really that big of a deal?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 23:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok sounds good. Is 20 minutes of hiit equivalent to 30 mins steady state, or is it more energy intensive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
