<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4639</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutler would so much rather be walking through a bar to the locker room. Minnesota is just rubbing it in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we about to see another win based off a special teams mistake? 

lol no </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish granted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their guest from ESPN Desportes or whatever in Mexico.  Yeah... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh he got like 3 extra yards cause they were all trying to hit the ball out of his hands rather than tackle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Cutler said fuck it and I'll just throw it down their shoelaces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great camera angle to choose for that replay... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that feel too well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the bonus of he makes Goff/Fisher look worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only mildly buzzed by halftime? What devilry is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh, you know, I don't follow College Ball at all, but my very first thought last week was "Why is Gruden with some dude who should be on College games?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some loser they picked out of the crowd.  No personality at all. Mayonnaise would be a better commentator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would have to be as a wildcard which is maybe less likely. Think that Giants D + Eli being just good enough = Super Bowl has been a proven formula. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also shops that use people holding signs and dancing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 03:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am so addicted to Rocket League lately. Cut to ads? Time to join a match. Ads are done? Leave match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 02:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We lost Woodhead for the season.  

Can has Sproles back pls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 01:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all the way back in the 90's

Welp. Now I feel old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 16:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really starting to wonder how much of it is Rodgers and McCarthy feuding behind the scenes. Their playcalling looked atrocious. How many times last night was Rodgers like "Fuck it, audible, I'll figure something out," which is usually a strength of his. But now it seems teams are used to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 16:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was actually basically advertising a company he endorses. I'm assuming the NFL cracks down on that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 01:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just need luck to work some magic with 1:51 left.

Edit: Or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 03:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Just 2 recent stories that both seemed to be hating on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 03:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's underwhelming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So minivans not retail vans. Did foodstuffs include meats? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 00:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What color were the vans? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why aren't there any Carl's stone cold etc of the week videos this season? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the deal with aj smith throwing shade at the chargers suddenly? He was fired a few years ago and only now decides to randomly shit talk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I did was point out how stupid it is to attack someone over autocorrect, which I hear is a popular meme with the kids these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 09:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess if you really want to call out people on the internet for typing "croc" and having it switch to "frog" then uh, have fun with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 19:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er croc. Stupid autocorrect etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link but nothing says the frog survived and they in fact say it's final death roll is his own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 16:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subreddit reposting has really made it worse. There will be a picture of a cute squirrel or something in /r/pics that reaches the front. Then it's posted on /r/aww/ and reaches the front. Then it's posted in /r/photoshopbattles/ and reaches the front. There are other sub combinations that basically chain together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also that first week... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey dude don't let the downvotes set you back. This was a fun read and seeing as I'm probably gonna be in a similar situation next season, I know the feel.

Edit: ps could do the Chargers next, since they're basically the Rams minus a Super Bowl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably my #1 most played album in the early 90s.  Produced so well.  Great album </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digable Planets - Jettin' [Hiphop] [4:39] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 21:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 04:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, literally 30 seconds ago I had a change of heart on this.  I was previously of the mindset, "sports media, this issue could easily not be a thing if you just stopped making it be a thing." 

But I do kinda agree with what is meant. So if the media keeps wanting to bring it up, I'm okay with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Automatic ice cube trays can make for nice rocks...and measuring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, those plays always get called back.  

One day I want to see a "dead ball" run back for a TD.  Anyone got a highlight?  (GBvCHI a few years ago I guess?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only just realized while texting a friend that lol is the touchdown signal in text emoji.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 05:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad for him. I think he's a good coach, just in a major league situation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait they...let the other team have points...? Really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did Rodgers make that pass... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there goes everything :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I suppose dota and kush is the real reason I don't remember last season really... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So um...anyone have a stream?  Every single one on that one subreddit has either gone down, or lags to hell.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of alcohol consumed last season has prevented recollection of last season.  As is tradition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, did t'eo finally stop impersonating his girlfriend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to everyone, we weren't supposed to look this good.

(Now that I say this, we will spectacularly crash and burn.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm kinda starting to get some of the deeper tactics in this. Was telling my friends since we're all lower level still and few in number we need guerilla tactics. Just hack for the most part and occasionally break their major links, while holding smallish out of the way fields. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't have cable or satellite. That's the only game on broadcast in my area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the only over-the-air broadcast in my area :(

TV is OTA, chargers main monitor, redzone second monitor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 19:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [football is back, and it's beautiful](https://i.imgur.com/aZ537SLh.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too bad Oakland already looks like it was hit by a meteor... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 17:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I ready for some football? [I AM READY!](https://i.imgur.com/vqx9cGqh.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 17:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my area the leaderboard is me and my 2 friends, who all started playing last week, plus two other people. The resistance has 15 active people. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 03:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 request - on the webpage, is there a way to make something there which shows how many people are currently playing? It would be nice if there was an easy way to check that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 16:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...you made a post about a housing market bust? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thanks to the folks in Northwest Crossing, we're heading right back to a bust as fast as we can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 06:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Propaganda! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 06:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean there were a ton of "dungeon keeper" and "dungeon fighter" and stuff like that in between the first "dungeon heroes" and the actual one in this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers Extended) Post-HoweverTheHellThisEnds, how do you picture Westeros/Esteros 1 year down the line? 5 years? 10 years? 100? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 06:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose this is also asking people to guess how the end plays out more or less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 05:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about a week in... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Poopypost] I have begun the trash talk wars in my area with the following... (I'm Enlightened) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resistance is measured by ohms.  The Enlightened is measured by ohmy's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 02:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google should be embarrassed about how far I had to scroll to find this in the play store by searching "dungeon heroes".  

Remember how you guys were like...a search engine once? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 21:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I called. They still had my email in their system for whatever reason and it was just an automatic message to everyone in their system apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh, I haven't had a Wells Fargo account in about 15 years.  Then the other day I got an email from Wells Fargo about my account.  

...maybe I should look into that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they were supposed to mostly run with seimian as qb. What's with all this passing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha same. It was the last gasp of off season bs  news and will finally soon be forgotten. I hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think last season they freaked because the few players they really followed all ended up cut.  So this season they decided to follow a lot more people, but a lot less deep, so they could show some "success stories" this season. But really we didn't get to know much about any players at all, except dumbfuck who doesn't believe in dinosaurs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I guess my real point is, why isn't this sub attacking Trump with the same/more veracity? He's the one basically giving Hillary the presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 16:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. This sub seems to be pretty anti-Hillary. And like, I get the part about not liking her; she's a career politician, she's done plenty of shady shit. 

But like, Trump winning the nomination has basically handed the presidency to Hillary on a silver platter.  Pretty much *anyone* else they nominated could have a real chance to beat her. 

If Hillary becoming president is part of some spooky big conspiracy, then Trump is equally a part of that. If not a bigger part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 06:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am totally anti-apple. Android fanboy.

If Apple had seamlessly (not needlessly) switched to a wireless format, they'd have my interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 04:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pfft surprise reveal 2/3s into the sequel, Viggo(?) shows up. Because he kept things professional too.

I'll even predict some sort of wick is losing consciousness and you hear a thick Russian accent asking, "Need a hand, John?"

Viggo has had to start from the beginning really. Different name because all that you said. He's a bartender facilitating drug deals for a cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, all the top comments, 20 remaining, this apparently didn't come up - 

"Dont be surprised when the Panthers look average because we are playing teams like Arizona and KC instead of teams like Jacksonville and Tennessee."

The subtle divisional diss.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit you saw dirty south. Now it's time for dirty east. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 10:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pretty much had to give up on game threads while watching streams anyway because of the delay. Even if the sidebar doesn't update, if I'm constantly refreshing I'll see a bunch of "TD!/INT!/Fumble!" etc comments before seeing the actual play.  

If a sidebar scoreboard is a spoiler, how aren't the comments themselves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 09:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait..what? He's talking about going to the subreddit right after the latest episode aired. I watch Game of Thrones but stay the hell away from the subreddit until 2 or 3 days later because I know there will be things I forget or didn't notice or I fell asleep etc.  And I'll probably want to watch it a second time before reading any of the stuff that happened.

Binge watching has nothing to do with that. 

Edit: Seeing some comments about spoilers during game threads.  Totally a dick move. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 08:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now I need to watch that episode again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] Vigo and the ending to John Wick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 08:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're reading this you know what goes down.  Puppycide, rampage of Archer proportions, culminating in Vigo getting a taste of the Wick.

Or do you?  ...know?...what goes down...?

Because it seems for the most part, all y'all think Wick killed Vigo, even if his death was maybe offscreen. To which I humbly submit; I am awesome, and you are wrong. 

Wick doesn't kill Vigo. Let's go over the FAQs! (Get it? Facts? Ah nevermind.)

1) Why wouldn't Wick go ahead and kill Vigo? 

A) It's not like he spared bullets in eye sockets or knives in tender vittles earlier. Oh, *now* the director decides to spare some red corn syrup? 

2) Uh...mercy?

B) Bitch please.

3) Well, Vigo was basically going to die right? 

C) Was he? (Why am I answering a question with a question? Ahhhh I'm doing it again!) He got the shit beat out of him and a knife in the shoulder.  Yes, big porno-shaming veins or arteries or what have you around there. But Wick seems to know what he's doing with the human anatomy and where to put sharp things into it, even moreso evidenced by purposely getting stabbed and only needing some staples and not-sugary-carbonated-liquid poured on the wound. If any melonfarmer can stab someone in the shoulder and miss the artery, it's Wick.

4) Well, Vigo says, "Be seeing you soon John," as his final words in the movie. That's kinda like a "see you in hell" kinda thing right? 

D) Or, it means they'll literally be seeing each other, as their line|s| of work will likely bring them together again. Which leads me to the **TL;DR**  (haha not) summation if you'd be so kind to ask...

5) So why doesn't Vick kill Wigo? (Kidding.  Vick killed dogs.  He's like the Russians.  He's a bad guy.)  

E) Wick has, at the very least, given Vigo a very bad case of the Mondays. Or he also like, killed his son, confidant, best bodyguard (only guy to survive 2 encounters!), and probably very seriously hampered (if not outright crippled permanently) his criminal organization. 

How does that fight start?  

"No more guns, John.  No more bullets."  And Wick tosses his gun.  We've seen before that he does indeed have a sense of honor, at least in some ways. And then Vigo is getting his ass kicked.  "What happened John? We were professionals.  Civilized."  "Do I look civilized to you?!" 

Aaaaaaand punkass Vigo draws a knife. In just a few seconds, Wick has some weird moment of clarity kinda shot and decides to let Vigo stab him in order to dislocate his elbow. 

**Real TL;DR? Maybe?** Wick had been on a rampage, yes.  But it was a rampage with rules. But he realizes, maybe he has crossed lines that he wouldn't have intended to cross. Sure, Vigo pulls a knife after convincing Wick to toss his gun - but maybe John has done some things like that along the way too ("Do I look civilized to you?!"). 

He lets himself get stabbed in order to end the fight with neither man dying. He returns to being a professional. He leaves Vigo with a wrecked empire, beaten half to death, stabbed, son killed, and sitting in the rain (and some pee).  He has beaten Vigo.  But there is no real reason to take things with Vigo personally.  Everything was his dipshit son, and him (understandably) not wanting his son to be murdered.  

__________

A loose end or two...or are they?

Sigma) Well, Vigo still looks like he's kinda dying. 

Jupiter) Yep, there's a shot where it looks like it might be his last breath. One *could* (if they didn't want to be a big dickhead) view that as a huge exhale - relief from not being killed, exhaustion, realization of everything that had happened.

Bojangles) I mean, he really looks like he's kinda dying.

) He was also walking toward his helicopter. Or something? Well it looks like cranes are in the background.  But theoretically a helicopter pilot who gets paid by this guy is in the area. If you're in a helicopter and there's a landing spot at a hospital with a helicopter pad can you just like radio in and ask to offload some dude?  I don't know, but these are the important questions. 

Wick let Vigo live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 05:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This man does not lie. Rated as equal to grey goose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish there were edit timestamps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At half I went to play a game of dota bc this was obviously over. WHAT THE FUCK HAS HAPPENED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 03:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure that camping world is the IRL margaritaville. Is the economy doing okay? Then camper/rv companies start popping up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 01:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 03:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOW LIVE, NOW KILL

Lots fun so far :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 17:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg I need these so bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 17:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, the version I heard which I've had great success with is just press your tongue against the roof of your mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 06:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kaepondernick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can we not keep someone named Kenneth Farrow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did a sudden red tint kick in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I uh...don't think the lights are out on purpose anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any chance? I heard there was some possible scheme to force it to be counted 50/50 instead of two thirds. Any chance of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://cdn.meme.am/instances/500x/53144613.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else get the ad for the new stadium proposal? Was entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha they're even going to promote the new stadium proposal. They're really pushing this angle hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That really was leading to a firework show right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just like the name McCoil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit 3 did get rolled up on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you miss the Goff pass 2 yards past the LOS? Refs are in preseason form too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least not Hobbit length. That would be ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clemmens just did what Russell couldn't. 

(/s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I feel if it was a scenario like Palmer with the Cardinals, I wouldn't feel so doomed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so too. They never cut back so I'm hoping he got up and there was nothing to cut back to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clemmens won't win us a game. But I don't think he'll lose one either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you need a story sports radio can use for 2 weeks. Andrew Luck pees on flag because he just realized how much he's losing to taxes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 04:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a questionable talent? Need to see just a little more? Want to feel deep regret for keeping a player you shouldn't have, but he did look pretty good that one time?

Then dial 1-800-CHARGERS today! 

(Agreement does not guarantee their "pretty good" status will continue in the future. Agreement does guarantee they will not.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 03:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sideline Reporter : So how is the loss of Teddy Bridgewater going to affect the team? 

Player : Well obviously it's not a good thing. It's always unfortunate when something like that happens. But we still have to come out here and do our jobs and play and win. Teddy's a competitor, we all miss him, but these things happen and we still need to come out here and play. 

Repeat 8x while inserting a random Vikings player in the interview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 03:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even my favorite shows have been such a drag. But it's basically the last week of shitty sports radio until may/June. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 02:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man his strides look super slow but somehow no one can get within 10 yards of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 02:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ, semantic harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 02:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously like at least 2 yards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 02:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your 480 link isn't showing this game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, and, I have tried going to the website through Chrome/Opera and clicked the same link there that Sports Devil gives me. Sports Devil doesn't work, Chrome/Opera it works.  I've also tried the stream on my Win10 box through Kodi and the Sports Devil links work fine in that. Even when at the same exact time my linux/Kodi gives me an error message. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to vipbox's website, when they detect a mobile device they give you an HTML5 stream instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 19:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For live sports, Sports Devil links to websites such as vipbox, roja, firstrowsports, etc.  All of those are flash-based streams.  On Windows/Mac, that's not such an issue because flash is easily installed system wide. On linux you have to tinker and run a bunch of command lines to get flash to work with separate programs like Kodi. It was a bit of effort just to get flash to work in some browsers. 

If it was a Windows system, Flash would be a system-wide service, which is why those streams work fine in Kodi/Sports Devil. In linux it is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Sports Devil] Running Kodi on a Linux box - Live Sports links in Sports Devil don't work because they're Flash. Anyone know of a way to integrate Flash into Kodi/Sports Devil on Linux? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 17:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My googlefu has only found a single link as a way to "fix" this and it was a pretty crappy link, which TL;DR would only really work if I only use one specific URL for all sports streaming. (Doesn't really work when switching between Football games, watching Soccer matches, etc.)

So Sports Devil is kinda useless to me atm because Flash streams don't work which is pretty much all of them.

Hoping there are some linux pros on here who have figured out how to do this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If those were drivable I would love it so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 02:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only eaten there 3 times, but every time I eat plenty of the cabbage stuff. Never had am issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 04:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shall disappointedly huff at the utter lack of drama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still really dig the "BROWNS" down the lower thighs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 05:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But regardless, that's why killing the emperor didn't cause the empire to collapse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 04:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your starting QB just got hurt. And you call a **designed QB sneak** for your backup?! Wtf... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 19:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain the reasoning for the Chargers not wanting to give more of the signing bonus in 2016? Does it not count against the cap if more of it is paid in March 2017? 

It's the only reason I can think of for them being so hard nosed about this. But now it's stupid because if you wanted more cap room to get free agents, 1) they've scared a lot away because of this, and 2) it's not like there are a bunch of big names still unsigned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 19:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were on the verge of invading western Europe.  Yes they had an empire still, but it didn't stretch from one ocean to the other, as it would have had Genghis not died. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 17:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to think this too. But, just because Luke defeated the emperor, it didn't mean he defeated the empire. As we've seen in episode 7 what remained of the empire still had considerable resources and power.

It isn't like when Genghis Khan died and the Mongol hordes did a 100% retreat. Think of it more like the collapse of the ussr. Sure a lot of territories were lost, but Russia remained a big bad power with many of the former apparatuses still basically in place, just rebranded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 19:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only part 2 was given a proper fleshing out or a second volume. the end felt so not Neal Stephenson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 17:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's their own goddamn idiot fault. They complain about lack of ratings and they were hoping for more online viewers? I live in the US, but my mediabox PC hooked up to my TV runs linux.  And apparently NBC's online services thinks linux is from a different country or something. So about 99% of my viewing was through a VPN to Canada to watch the CBC's coverage instead (which, by the way, had a waaaaay better website for navigating what to watch). 

Region lock a *worldwide* event? Fuck you NBC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere in between? As I mentioned elsewhere I was charging him $100 a month, waaaay below what he could get anywhere else. But he just got divorced, had a great job opportunity up here and needed somewhere to live asap, and regardless of him living here I'd be paying the same amount anyway. It wasn't like we decided to find a 2br place together. So he payed a token amount because it's in my best interest for him to find his own place so I could live alone again, and I'd be paying that rent regardless, at least I get a months (or few weeks) worth of whiskey out of it.

And im fairly sure he made it clear to her that I was giving him a very friendly deal on staying here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 01:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, well, if I could defend myself a bit here -

I wasn't expecting payment, or a drink, or whatever. If she had said "hey let me get you a shot of whiskey!" I would have thought "awesome!"  But I wasn't expecting it. 

And my friend who is staying here, I'm "charging" him $100 a month. Long story short, he's a super awesome dude, he had to move here on very short notice bc of a job offer, and it's in my greater interest to continue living alone, so the sooner I could help him save up to find his own place, the better. 

When he sent the "she's taken off" text, I replied "Huh, not even a goodbye or a thanks."  When he came home from work that day, he brought me home 2 of my favorite Belgian ales, and I could tell that he was pretty appalled by the extended length of stay/abrupt departure. I had to reassure him that whatever I thought about her didn't reflect onto him. 

Maybe my contrast story of the other guest made you think I was expecting something? But that was a text I received at work, "hey guest2 is making a bigass meal and there'll be plenty if you want some" - awesome! She didn't make it for me, she made it for herself and my friend. But there was a lot, and I was invited, and I was thankful for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the act of kindness was "a few days" which then become "longer than a week" (my friend seemed as confused at their duration of her stay as I was). 

And she was no introvert. Pretty typical east coast girl who spoke her mind whenever and wherever she felt like it. It was really the lack of a goodbye or thanks that soured me. When I got the text saying "She's taken off" (while I was at home, where she had just been as well) I was just, well, shocked. 

feeling entitled to somebody's time 

If she doesn't want to hang out, she's free to do whatever. Even my friend complained about the "conversation blackhole". If she wants to just sit on her phone the whole time, sure. Just don't expect me to open my doors to her a second time. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Travelling and staying with a friend who has roommates? Show your appreciation to the roommates for letting you stay, not just your friend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 20:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a friend who's been staying at my place for a few months (he had a job offer, had to move quickly, I had a spare bedroom).

He tells me he has a friend who's camping/travelling around the country.  She'll be in the area for awhile, and might spend a few nights here.  Sure.

It turned into 9 nights.  She left yesterday.  She didn't say bye.  Or thanks.  Didn't so much as buy me a drink any of the nights we all went out. And the majority of the time she was here, her face was buried in her phone while we were watching the Olympics in the living room.

Contrast that with another friend of his who was here for one weekend. One night she made a home cooked meal to which I was invited. She bought me a new handsoap for the bathroom after mine went kaput.  We placed quarter bets on Olympic swimming and had a lot of fun.

One of those two guests would be welcome back any time.  The other will not be allowed to return.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 00:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There were 11,397 before me. Who here is in that group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 17:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 16:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohai </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 02:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 01:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought I mentioned in the parent comment it required a bachelor's.

The tests are meant to be taken in a "neutral place" such as a library or something. And you have to have a proctor present, someone watching you to make sure you don't cheat. 

Apprenticeships, send out cover letters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 01:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) You should do that just generally.  If you're heading to the store and see a for sale sign and some flyers, pick one up.  

2) I don't know, though that is a kinda plus, but it requires learning about that area you move to. You can basically call the lenders and ask where hot places/understaffed areas are. But that's kinda a thing to do when established. Not so much when first starting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 05:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After about 3 months, my main thought was, "why the fuck have I been working cafe jobs for 10 years?!"  

And I could probably teach you 80% of the job in another 4-5 comments. The other 20% are the quirks, specific to your area. Like I said I don't know basements at all. If those are common in your area, your supervisor should give you an idea of how to value them. (hole in the ground = nothing, finished walls = $5/sf? insulated, full electric, nice flooring = $20/sf?  Or they'll let you know that this one neighborhood is SoDoSoPa and it's rapidly increasing in value only because of its name really.  

But yeah a really great start would to just be any time you see a flyer for a house for sale, grab it. You should have a good idea of what are the good/meh/bad neighborhoods around, compare the values of those flyers to one another. Two neighbors are for sale, but $100k apart? Why? One has hardwood flooring, central air, quartz countertops, stainless steel appliances, the other does not, and it's 500 sqft larger ~~smaller~~. 

Just grab flyers, they're free after all, and try to get a feel for the areas around you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Each time you start a report, you merge it with a previous report. If you merge it with a very similar place you recently appraised (same size, value, etc more or less), then yeah, it's basically just changing the specific numbers and then a few words here and there.

Sorry but kinda need to correct myself there.  Even if you merge with a recent report, you still need to do a new search for comparables, a new MCA/One Line report, a new statistic analysis...

Eventually they become relatively rote. Just felt like I was being misleading in terms of the ease of new appraisals.  If you have two nearly identical houses next door to each other selling at the same time? Sure you can probably use the same comps/mca/one line/stats, but otherwise you should really do new searches for that stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Each time you start a report, you merge it with a previous report.  If you merge it with a very similar place you recently appraised (same size, value, etc more or less), then yeah, it's basically just changing the specific numbers and then a few words here and there. 

But there is more work in terms of finding comps. One of those minor rants would be - you're required to bracket. Which means if your house is 2000 sqft, you need one bigger and one smaller. And you have to bracket *everything*. So you might find a house which is completely typical in every way except for some reason only 1 garage space. And all your comps have 2. So you need to cast a super wide net to find a kinda-similar place with 1 garage (or with central air conditioning, site size, view, etc etc.). And sometimes there just plain isn't one, and so you need to choose a really really shitty comp just because it has a 1 car garage, and you end up with 165% net and 234% gross adjustments. So even though that's a terrible, awful, horrible, disgusting clusterfuck of a comp, you *have* to use it in order to bracket the 1 car garage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 02:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I missed 2 other parts. 

I'm sure there is also more besides judging the price of the house that you need to do? That seems like it would take very little time every time.

Depends where you live. Are you in a major city with lots of suburbs? You can probably do the jobs a lot more quickly. Where I live is some weird mix of like 1/5 golf resorts, 1/5 houses from the 1920s, 1/5 super new trendy, 1/5 typical suburbs, and 1/5 semi-rural. Some are a lot faster/easier, others more difficult. But, yes, last week I had 3 jobs that I finished in 3 days. If I wasn't still fee splitting, that's $1800 in 3 days.  With the cherry on top of a 4 day weekend, since I thought I'd need Monday/Tuesday. (If money was my main priority, I could have taken on a tougher job/higher fee and worked those 4 days.)

Skills - ummm...be kinda okay at math, you don't need to know anything beyond like algebra. But if you can kinda look at a comp and think "it's 300 sqft larger, I'll probably adjust by $50/sf, so that's a $15,000 difference" (note: I used a calculator for that, even though that should be easy :P ). 

Deductive logic? Basically, comparables should end up comparing. It's 300 sqft bigger, so now it's $15,000 too low. But, it doesn't have a mountain view. So, it would seem that a mountain view is roughly $15,000 in value, because that would make the subject/comp closer to being equal. Once you make adjustments, they should be a good idea of the value of the subject. If something is out of whack, there is a reason for that. ("Ohhhh, this comp was downslope of the house behind is, so their neighbors behind them are basically staring down at them into their house/back yard. That's a shitty lack of privacy, so maybe a 5% adjustment to location?  Hey, that 5% adjustment ends up making that comp a lot closer to the other comps. That explains it!") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still some time before track   field starts, no problem ;)

Okay, [here](http://www.goodfaithappraisals.net/xSites/Appraisers/GoodFaithAppraisals2/Content/UploadedFiles/Appraisal-1004-Sample2.png) is one of the pages of forms you fill out, this one specifically about comparing the subject and comps.  Far left is the subject, comparables the next 3. A lot will look like gibberish. 

For instance view is N;Res; - neutral, residential. If a mountain view, B;Mtn; (beneficial) or A;Factory; (adverse). This can also apply to location (B;Resort; or A;BsyRd;).

So top to bottom mostly self explanatory up til Site adjustment. It seems like the subject was located in a semi-rural area where a larger site isn't *that* important. In a tightly packed suburban neighborhood, those adjustments would probably be bigger. Looks like he gave it around $0.75 per square foot difference. 

The age adjustments he did...in an interesting (pretty shitty) way. It should be a certain % multiplied by the square footage (and rounded, usually nearest $500). He just did a flat rate.  Oh well.

The 1 year olds are given C1 condition since they were just built, subject is C3, it's been lived in awhile. This can be somewhat subjective and it's good background data to get if you say, see a neighbor got their house painted. So the appraiser probably thought, "if we installed new flooring, maybe new counters in kitchens and bathrooms, fresh coat of paint, that's worth $20k."

He didn't adjust for the number of bedrooms which is kinda odd. (That adjustment would go to the right of "Total|Bdrms|Baths".)  Bath adjustment below that, he decided a 1/2 bath is worth $2000. (Also it's 2.1 as in 2 full, 1 1/2.  If it was 3 full and 2 1/2 baths, it would be 3.2.)

Square foot adjustment, he did by $20/sf.  That seems a bit low. The way I've been trained is 40% of replacement cost, which is from something called cost approach which isn't worth going into here.

Basements I pretty much never deal with where I live. I don't really know valuation methods for that. 

I guess subject had a small porch and deck and he decided that was $5,500. These can also be kinda subjective. Maybe a house has a 10'x20' covered porch, but it's concrete, versus a 8'x12' nicely stained wood deck with no roof/cover? Some people might prefer the first, some might prefer the second. So I wouldn't adjust for those. But comps 1 and 3 straight up had none at all, so an adjustment is made. 

The porch/patio/deck is the last of the ones you *need* to fill out and you have the 3 lines below to add other things.  He added fireplaces, which is odd for where I live, but this is Minnesota, so I guess that's worth an adjustment. 

Fence/shed/other I often do ("Outbuildings") when working on the next town to the south of me, because detached large shops are popular down there.

Okay, the next row of significance is the net adjustment total with the X boxes. He did something kinda bad here; typically in your first 3 comps you want at least one positive adjustment or one negative adjustment; he has only negative adjustments. But again, rural area, it might not have been possible.  

Next are net and gross adjustment %'s. This is usually what tells you what your best comps are. Comp 2 has a 1.1% net and 8.9% gross, the lowest in both. That's the strongest comp. Comp 3 is 6.6/12.0, probably second strongest. Comp 1 is 8.7/11.9, probably weakest. So, the value of the subject should probably fall between Comps 2 and 3, but with a little pull closer to 2 from comp 1. $295k sounds like a good conclusion. 

Some of this could have made me go on some minor rants about the bureaucratic crap I mentioned in the cons. But track   field is starting.  Maybe later :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I can't speak nationwide about competitiveness.  But right now we're turning down around a dozen jobs per week because we're pretty much booked through September.  And along those lines, when I started about a year and a half ago, the standard fees were around $350-450.  My supervisor told me that's basically the fees they'd been getting since they started 20 years ago.  In the past 4 months, our standard fees have gone up to $600-800. In one particular job, was doing a refinance on a house owned by a realtor. And she was curious about wtf was going on, because she had a house "sold" except it would take 2 months to get an appraisal done on it, and the deal couldn't close until that was done. 

So at least where I live, it seems like the well of appraisers is definitely drying up pretty quickly. As for others being clued into it, see my parent comment.  I never see this job come up in any sort of list of jobs people should look into.  

I kind of think there'll probably be a crisis soon, which might lead to easing trainee requirements.  As my supervisor told me, "How I was trained to be an appraiser? I got hired by a bank and started doing appraisals." 

And one piece of advice I was told when I started was, "Always put a bit aside in a savings account, because you never know when the slow times will come, but they will come."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 08:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this very Olympics a free kick was awarded to the Brazilian female soccer team in the waning seconds which almost went in.

On replay, obvious dive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fourth of the tournament? Someone isn't learning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The opera browser includes a free VPN so you can watch the CBC (Canada's website). Set the VPN to Canada. Only reason I installed opera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, fair enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Brazil, at least you don't have to worry about a potential 8-1 in the final. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, oh well (insert shrugging ASCII guy here) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the Swedish keeper does dropkick style, where the ball hits the ground before her foot makes contact with the ball, would it be legal for someone to try to block the kick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two extra times in a row in Brazilian weather?  Doubt they hold up. Calling brazil scores 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Tho I might have been pissed if you'd scored and it was a legit penalty, because that would have been just a bit too Hollywood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My stream paused momentarily when replaying the Swedish player stepping on the Brazilian to set up the final attempt. Was it a dive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 02:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I heard that too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 00:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that he's on the Texans, his nickname should be "Brock Hossweiler" or just "Brock Hoss". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 07:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to take and pass 4 exams, which might be slightly different per state. I'm in Oregon which for some reason is a lot harder than other states. They run about ~$800, and can be payed in installments of you go through mckissock. If you find a good supervisor, they might partially/fully cover the cost as it can be written off.

This is one con I left out mostly because it's a bandaid effect. The classes (can all be done online) are dry as fuck. I had to answer questions in a test about how many chains make a mete, and how many metes make a bound. Like, 17th century measurements I have never once used in work so far.

But like a bandaid, grit your teeth and rip through them. If you go full bandaid approach you can probably get through them in 2 weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 21:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not glamorous, but pays pretty fucking well. 

Basic rundown - someone needs a loan for their house (purchase, or refinance, sometimes foreclosures) - the bank wants to know, "You're buying this house for $300k?  What is it actually worth?" so they know how much to loan out. So they hire us to go check things out, we look up similar houses, we compare the subject with the comparable houses (1 car garage instead of 2 car? mountain views or not? next to a factory or in the suburbs?) - apply values to the differences, and that (should) give you a good idea of the value of the house.

Pros - 
1) About 95% of the job can be done in your underwear. Very little interaction with humans.  But you do deal with homeowners, and sometimes meet some neat characters, and (rarely) some jerks.  
2) Jobs have a due date.  As long as you turn in the job by that date, it doesn't matter when you work on it (mostly).  So when you're filling out the report, you can do that 9-5, or 7-3, or 2am-8am.  
2b) This also leads to a lot of random three day weekends (or longer).  A job normally takes about 2 days. Sign up for 3 jobs per week thinking I'll turn them in Tuesday, Thursday, Monday. Turns out all 3 jobs were super easy and only took 1 day each.  Suprise! You now have Thursday and Friday off!   
3) There are official go to work for a bank appraiser jobs with normal hours and whatnot. Independent, you throw out bids for jobs. The advantage of this is if you want to take a week off? Just don't bid on jobs that week then.  Have a happy vacation!  
4) Currently, and this was confirmed when talking to some reps from US Bank, the vast majority of appraisers are basically in their 60s.  They'll be retiring soon. There aren't many young people going into this profession.  Fewer people doing it = higher fees per job in the near future.

Cons - 
1) You have to be a trainee for 2 years. So you need to find an appraiser who will be your supervisor. A good one, who gives you at minimum 50% of the job's fee.  Some will sit back, do nothing but put their signatures on the report, and try to take a majority of the fee.  
2) There is some amount of bureaucratic bullshit. For the most part it's background noise you get used to.  For instance, a report I recently had to revise - there is a freaking checkbox for a line "Are there any adverse conditions that might effect value? []yes []no" - I checked no. The report was returned, and I had to actually write down elsewhere "There are no adverse conditions that might effect value" even though there's a *freaking checkbox* for that.  
3) It varies with the market.  Right now, in most places, the markets are bouncing back from the recession.  But if another recession hits? Real estate takes a big hit, so your job takes a big hit (and this is when you're more likely to do foreclosure jobs, which are always kinda sad to do).

But overall, you can easily earn $50k per year, plus or minus $20k depending on how hard you want to work/how good of clients you can find. You can work from home if you want, or find an official job at a bank if you want. If you work from home, there's no "ladder" to climb so you'll just be doing jobs forever.  But you can also take classes to become a commercial or industrial appraiser which pays a lot more. 

I pretty much tell every friend who complains about their job to look into doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 18:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something that never makes these lists and is never really brought up - real estate appraiser. It's pretty fucking awesome. Could do a pros/cons breakdown if people are interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 01:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tis also a Friday afternoon for the Yanks/Canadians, probably lots of DVR action later tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 20:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mohr Stories by Jay Mohr.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 06:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But isn't the point of the article that an old-ish, outdated computer should be priced along those lines? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 06:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Apple users are looking for a cheap, if just okay, computers now...?

something something pc? something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My "favorite" part was during the grand finale, when some crazy trippy stuff is going on in the stadium, they instead cut to Gisele fucking Bundchen every 5 goddamn seconds, and then crowd shots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 08:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds really ignorant now, but I believed your 2002 success to being a host country and attempting to promote the sport there by seeing the host(s) do well.

But after that I saw the Japanese/Korean leagues definitely invested in their youth programs. There were so many "great-one-touches-per-game" more than a US match.

I probably overlooked the 2002 squads, but I'm always suspicious of host nations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 04:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man this second half has looked sloppy as fuck.  I guess the Manaus factor really is in play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in a bit less than 90 minutes we've seen 12 goals? (Not counting South Korea's first half.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what a shitty clearance

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At that time I thought their success was more from them being hosts and maybe some calls/matches going their way because of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, 2006 is when I started thinking Japan/South Korea would win one before the US (if any of them ever won). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The director(s) for some of these are just terrible.  During one of the Women's matches, during a corner kick, they kept the camera on the person who took the kick about 5 seconds after she kicked it.  So you didn't see where the ball went or anything. If a goal had been scored, oh well wait for a replay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fans in the stands - "There are dozens of us! DOZENS!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 03:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any reason you think that might be? 

Does the national game in Japan feature a more striker-minded offensive system in general? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interested in some live looks at US Bank field? At 8PM CDT (40 minutes?), first major event (International Champion's Cup) will be televised there. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 02:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Chelsea vs AC Milan, two pretty good teams.  But, this is kind of the equivalent of preseason for them.  It's better than the NFL preseason, the typical stars/starters will play a number of minutes similar to what they'd play during the regular season, but they're only playing maybe 80% speed? 

I was planning on watching this anyway, but getting some nice live looks at the new stadium in action is a sweet bonus.  

It's on ESPN2   3, frequently you can stream ESPN2 for free with a cable subscription login.  Or you can find it in the soccer variation of where you'd find NFL streams.

(Also, Chargers fan here, just thought you guys would wanna know.)

Edit: Looks like pretty much every stream is reliant on ESPN and they've still got 10 minutes in the Bayern/RM match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion - Saving Private Ryan] Some questions and observations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 00:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) If every main character in the squad survived, which would have the hardest time returning to civilian/"normal" life?  Which the easiest?  Which the most "same shit, different day"/whatever attitude?

2) It seems like the death of each person in the squad is kinda a reverse of their introduction^^1.  Jackson (the sniper) runs solo through a field of fire.  He dies surrounded by others in a static position.  Wade (medic) is introduced surrounded by other medics, not caring the least for his own safety.  He dies with no medics around, crying for his mom.  Mellish cries over a Nazi-youth knife at the start; dies by one in the end.  Miller is shown utterly shell-shocked and looking horrified; dies after coming out of shell-shock, and totally gleeful (even while dying).  


^^1 
^^- 
^^Not 
^^necessarily 
^^their 
^^first 
^^appearance, 
^^but 
^^when 
^^their 
^^character 
^^is 
^^"established."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
