<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1935</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my younger and more vulnerable years my father gave me some advice that Ive been turning over in my mind ever since.

Whenever you feel like criticizing any one, he told me, just remember that all the people in this world havent had the advantages that youve had.

2 dollars might be nothing to you. For some people that could fuck your budget and be another turd on your big turd pile of a life.

Or also that person could be an asshole. Sometimes it is hard to tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what would be great? If the elements only appeared if you completed the side mission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They still make good games with great stories, so I keep on buying the games I am interested in. A lot of people argue that they haven't topped The Walking Dead S1 and maybe that's true, but the bar they set with that game was really high. Wouldn't it be great if everything was that great? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Telltale build for mobile markets too. I don't really expect them to make the same game from scratch twice just to match the fidelity of AAA releases. Also considering that they go for a toned down comic book art style, why would they?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 12:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman was an update engine. I get that a new engine may have issues. They released a pretty big update to Batman between episode 2 and episode 3. That solved most problems for me. No problems with a New Frontier.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm not understanding you. The 73% is good reviews v bad. Also RT is telling me 74% for top critics on Ghostbusters with a 6.7 out of 10. The percentage score requires a four star minimum when calculating the score. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 10:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I specifically stated that the US Military hypothetically has been devastated (including the navy) by a different military (let's say Russia).

So for your rationale for an improbable thing to happen, first another even more improbable thing needs to happen?

Also tyrant and tyranny mean specifically someone in power with no legitimate claim. Usually a king (Tyrannosaurus Rex basically means King Lizard king, Rex also meaning king). So an elected official is never a tyrant, unless they rigged the election. You could argue that Jim Crow laws did do this and guess how they were overturned. Dr. King's peaceful resistance.

I remember reading Chuck Klosterman talking about the very issue you are raising. Lots of people said Hurricane Katrina was mishandled. But imagine if the Bush Administration did actually nothing. Sure the people of New Orleans would be upset, but would Kevin in Portland or Bill in Jersey do anything? Are they going to take up arms and march to Washington to form a violent coup? No they are not. No one wants the US to become a warzone on the streets. and they react badly when that does happen. Just look at the Ferguson riots or Malheur. There was not popular support for either of those events. Look at what's happening in Flint, god knows they have earned a riot or two.

But in truth no American, no matter how much they love their guns, are looking at these issues, thinking 'How many people do we need to shoot before the government removes themselves or institute change?'. People want diplomacy, not violence to solve issues inside the US and an invasion from outside is just not happening.

The only legitimate takeover of the US government I can think that could possibly happen involving guns is a military coup from the inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That can't be right. Have you got a source? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 17:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So China is able to move enough troops to Mexico avoiding a navy bigger than the rest of the world's navy combined? And Mexico is okay with this? Oh and China has a motive for this?

As for an elected tyrant? That's why there are elections every four years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are still aggregating reviews. That aren't saying if a critic gives it two stars out of 5 they count that as a positive review. Also from what I can see GB is at 73% for all critics and 74% for top critics.

So 74% of critics thought it was a good film, not necessarily a great film but they cam out enjoying it more than they hated it or were neutral on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the reason it was included. I'm saying it really should have no baring on today's gun debates. And I'm of the opinion that those reasons don't hold up today. 

The US has the largest military and Navy in the world by a long shot. The chance of a US land invasion is nil. So the security of the state will not depend on militia. It will depend on the huge industrial military complex it has going. In fact a lot of nations depend on the US military for security, including unarmed ones.

If an alien invasion was probably, I would say the original reasoning stands. Until then it's just dated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 15:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have an example? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they have incentive, but IMDb is a database of every movie ever. They just put a link to the DVD. DVD's are such a small part of their business anyway, I think squeezing a few more sales isn't really going to be worth it.

It's worth noting that Warner Brothers own Rotten Tomatoes but the DC movies get savaged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that an overall Fresh rating? That's possible. But are you saying that they take negative reviews and pretend they are positive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Founding Fathers wrote the constitution at a very different time in history. You brought up Washington. I am asking why his views at the time should reflect on a modern perspective about things.

If you really want to bring Washington's intent to it, he also never wanted political parties and believed the constitution should be rewritten every so often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 13:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not making any assumptions. I just don't see the point of considering the opinions of a bunch of rich dead guys when talking about modern problems. It's like that quote from the head of IBM about there only being a market for five computers. Relevant at the time but has nothing to do with today's world.

Also democracy is older than the USA by thousands of years. You make it should like the invention of George Washington. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 12:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really understand when Americans try to do what the founding fathers would want. My grandparents are from 80 years ago and some of their opinions are insane. I can't imagine why you would ignore 200 years of progress and factor in the opinion of someone from then who was cool with owning slaves and also fucking the prettier ones on occasion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the free form of the first game. Technically a battle could happen anywhere. ME2 was a better game but I didn't like the fact you basically had a hub and battle stages.

ME3 was okay, but it really felt like it was more about finishing out story threads rather than its own story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, Knives needed Scott to unlock her potential cool. Now she's too cool for Scott and Scott was a shithead to her, so it would be really sad for her to get back with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scott is a way worse person than Ramona. This is especially apparent in the comics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Move to letterboxd, a much better experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get what you are trying to say. Plenty of negative reviews on imdb. The Neon Demon, an Amazon Studios movie only has 6.3. If you are implying that Amazon are fixing scores to sell DVDs there is no proof of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 11:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a movie has a star rating, it would need to have 4 stars for RT to categorize it as a positive review.

I find there is a general swarm intelligence in aggregating reviews so a 70% usually is a seven out of ten. It doesn't work in every case (BvS is a bad movie but is it really one out of ten bad, it deserves a three) but it happens a lot. As long as you see RT as a way to see if a movie is worth watching and not a ranking, it's fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 07:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be honest, even if the prices were reasonable, let's say 20 - 25 dollars people will still pirate them. Even if they were five dollars. Students are tech savvy and money poor. They won't turn down free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheap flights create their own demand. Gdansk is a city I would probably never purposely visit, except hey tickets are cheap, why not head to Eastern Europe.

|If you are a Bostonian hankering for a European adventure on a budget, you'd throw down 100 each way and spend some time in Cork. Then you will start seeing businesses catering to these blow in tourists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 14:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you serious? I was just putting pieces together from anime tropes.

Maybe it was subconscious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miyazaki has step out of retirement more times than a black guy in an eighties buddy cop movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 11:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they never take that extra step to actually clarify this means I can redownload games I previously purchased on Switch at not extra charge

You can do this already with the web store. The issue is when you switch hardware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 11:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Did she commit hit and run and get away with it? 

I mean, so did Matthew Broderick. Not excusing C. Jenner but I see people bring this up to demonstrate that she is a horrible person, but people still quite like Matt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 10:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of the best lockins are on Good Friday. Don't take that away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 10:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see way more cars breaking reds than cyclists. In Ireland drivers seem to think amber means go faster and red means No need to stop because it just turned red so I'm grand. In fact it's just turned red and those two cars snuck across so I can too. I've been honked at and dangerously overtaken for stopping at amber lights or lights that have just turned red. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i also hate the belief that there is some piece of magic legislation that will turn us all into cafe style Euro wine drinkers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 09:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a race riot on St Stephen's day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already purchase games through my Nintendo account. But it still assumes I will only own one console. Has Switch confirmed to be totally account based? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Sony or Xbox honour games that work with backwards compatibility bought digitally on a previous console? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Zootopia was a fun film, but the metaphor was a bit forced and the film was really more about being fun and having gags than doing anything different. I haven't seen Moana yet but it looks like it has the same goals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And lets be honest, anime is frowned upon. Ghibli is in a class of its own, so it gets away with being anime. Most people presume most anime is about a high school-aged romance/band/loner/scientist have an adventure involving time travel/aliens/shinto spirits/ghouls/genetically altered monsters with a wacky animal/ghost/zombie/pervert as comic relief.

On the off chance the characters aren't high school aged, it might be long listed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I am saying is if someone says they need counselling, let them get it. Lets not joke about whatever reasons they say they need it, because getting overly stressed about small things is reason enough. Or no reason even.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 12:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  shes openly being interviewed by newspapers, if she was truly upset and in distress do you thionk that would happen? 

Maybe. I don't know. I do know everyone has different reactions to stuff and to ascribe only one way to behave is a bit ignorant. Cultures, people and a bunch of random stuff can dictate how one should react. I still get worked up about making a spelling mistake in front of the class when I was 10. Right now I am worried about whether I left my front door unlocked even though I double checked it. None of these should bother me and they don't too much. If they did bother me a lot I would probably need to talk to someone.

We are just laughing at the fact SHE claims she directly needs it BECAUSE of this incident. 

Maybe she does. If you think this incident is a mild inconvenience that is fine. If for some reason she thinks this is devastating despite the fact she was only delayed a couple of hours, maybe she does need counselling because she is over reacting to things outside of what she can control. You are still laughing at someone who claims they need help. That's not cool. Even if she is 100% completely in the wrong, maybe talking to someone will get her to that place. 

Instead you laugh at her for not being able to handle life. Not being able to handle life is the exact reason to get help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 12:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I didn't see the pre-approved list in what you can seek therapy over. 

If missing a flight can cause you high anxiety or undue stress, maybe there is something else going on that therapy can help with.
Or maybe being in a wheelchair and needing assistance is stressful, but that's okay because you are with friends. But now you are split from your friends and stuck with people who have already demonstrated that accommodating you is a huge deal for them. Not only that, you have the prospect of navigating a new airport and city on your own when you arrive at your destination, where you need to rely completely on strangers to get you to your holiday. Or if your friends do wait at the airport, you have the anxiety of if you are going to be able to find them.

That sounds like a lot of stress there and counseling might help.

It is perfectly fine for us to say she should have been more prepared, but lets not start stigmatizing people by telling them they do or do not deserve counseling. General rule of thumb should be if talking to someone makes you feel better and less stressed, do it, even if you think the reason is dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 10:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ireland has a stigma with people getting help for mental health issues. But sure laugh at someone who is open about seeking help. 

You are just seeing this case in isolation. This could easily be the straw that broke the camels back. Also with the flood of abuse people, especially women get, when coming out public against something and people turning against them, she probably will need consuling.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 10:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know specifics but the thirteen minute thing seems a bit moot, since Ryanair wait until the last possible minute to start loading passengers. 

She could have been an hour early and their would be no way for Ryanair to know that she would need assistance if it wasn't stated previously.

That said, air travel has become a race to the bottom, especially with Ryanair. Their whole model is based on doing as little extra as possible and everyone should know this by now. I feel bad this girl was embarrassed and it was out of line that someone asked if she could walk. It also seems like this isn't the first time Ryanair did something like this. But also when travelling with Ryanair, I wouldn't assume anything as a given.

The best case scenario out of this is, if a person who needs assistance changes their ticket, the assistance request will transfer with that. At the moment, travel insurance doesn't even transfer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 10:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a lot of the past couple of decades, Sein Fein were the political wing of a terror organisation. People would be flipping their shit if some Korean had made a picture that made it look like Irish kids supported DPRK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bulk selling and trusted browser apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to sell some cards but selling one by one is painfully slow.

I found this app:https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/steam-inventory-helper/cmeakgjggjdlcpncigglobpjbkabhmjl?hl=en and I just to know is it trustworthy. Has anyone tried it before?

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 19:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They will never stop used game sales aside from selling the game digitally itself and they know it.

If not the next generation of hardware, the generation after that will be sold like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The outcry was more because they attempted to cover it up by changing the map slightly

I i have learned anything for gamer outrages, even if they came out and said it, people would still complain.

If a free game that no one ever heard of was able to kick off the biggest internet shit storm of the last 5 years by getting a potentially biased review, this shit would not stand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it is more to stop used game sales for which they don't get a cut. Release a game and then release digital only DLC. People won't sell their game on because then they have a useless digital product they can't use.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presales and DLC are what keep game development going. We always see people saying we should wait for reviews and to stop preordering, but if we did, dev would grind to a halt. 

The reason devs and publishers love presales is because they all account for the week one chart. They can spend two months selling presale and that all counts as a week one sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest boon for planned DLC is that game dev continues. Before a single game might get a patch or two, that you would have to actively seek out from a website. Now that teams are still working on a game, you will see more bug fixes.

Of course the flip side to this is, that they know a game can be released with more bugs now because they will get to work on it longer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 12:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zero day patch means something different than you think it means. A day one patch is the term you are looking for. Zero day is usually a patch for an exploit.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zero-day_(computing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 10:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally about tropes. And there was some home video market stuff as I mentioned. But it never looked as good as Kung Fury. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to counter sue to recoup those loses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are cheap places, but they never end up on daft. They are handed off through friends. If you are moving out, ou have twenty friends who would love to grab the room so they just pat your deposit and take up your tenancy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, if Craig never makes another Bond film, does that undo the days between the last Bond movie and the next one. When does he 'officially' stop being Bond? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, by the end of the book, I think everyone knew. Or I would hope so. But we were assigned chapters to read every night. So most of the class were about half way through and Boo was still elusive. I imagine an American would not have to think twice to know Boo's race. Without the same history lessons about segregation and the civil rights movement, it's not so clear to begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Primer is just a bunch of guys talking at different locations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if it is a fan film why would people invest in something they know they can't profit off?

Cease and desist is incoming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 11:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. They have the plans for the house, but then the unqualified decide that they want a skylight, and French windows and large doorways and just throw them into the plans without any thought. That is exactly what a McManson is., hence the website. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 10:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of redditors are pretty technically and get all flustered when they are watching TV and see an IP address formatted wrong.

This is the exact same thing. She is a student of architecture and houses like this were built by wanna be architects. They want impractical things like grand opening hallways (a bitch to heat) or they copy stuff from a mesh of style without trying to integrate them so they become a hodgepodge. You probably don't notice it because you haven't studied it. Like how you only notice bad kerning if you know what kerning is.

Actually here is the best analogy. [Watch this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rNlmRId2FVQ). That is Halle Berry as Catwoman. In the scene she is 'playing basketball'. What she is really doing is a bunch of cool ball tricks that, while they look cool, she isn't actually playing basketball and if you know the rules of basketball you will realise this immediately. 

This site is made by a professional basketball player watching in frustration as people play basketball like Catwoman. Except it is real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but if you live in Ireland and don't know anything about Jim Crow or segregation, his race might not occur to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A great comparison is Series of Unfortunate Events, where there is a gay couple. It was for a younger audience and they never explicitly say it but anyone over 14 would read about them and know what the story was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So was A Ham. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because that is also a turn of phrase. When I hear pale as a ghost, or turned pink or they were feeling blue, I think of character traits, not physical ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He lived and hung out in the white part of town. A lot of people in my class thought he was black because he was ostracized and shunned by most people, and sure wasn't that why we were reading the book, so as to learn not to ostracize and shun people because they are black.

At least that was where I think the confusion came from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 13:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if that were true, Rowling would never have featured it in her books. Dumblebore was supposed to be an openly gay man but she had him so far in the closet in the books and movies that no one knew until she mentioned it after the books were finished in an interview. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 10:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasted three hours to find out he wasn't even English. Wasting my time. False advertising bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 10:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After forgiveness, Jesus spent most of his time talking about helping the poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 10:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The meat industry stuff is about the first third of the book before the protagonist moves on and spends the next third of the book as a hobo. You can't miss the pro Labour elements. It's very explicit. What happened was people cared more about the unsanitary conditions of meat processing industry where they got their food from, than the message about downtrodden immigrant workers, not that they missed that message entirely.

You misinterpreted the response to The Jungle. We have come full circle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 09:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when I was doing Mockingbird for English a lot of people in my English class were under the impression Boo Radley was black.  Our teacher wouldn't tell us either way because he said the answer was obvious. 

We were a bunch of 13 year old Irish boys with no particular knowledge of the American south at that time so I don't think the answer was as apparent as he suggested. It blew my mind that Atticus had a maid but still considered himself poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throwing toothpicks on the ground and counting them might be calming and relaxing, but it still doesn't mean it's not pointless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  finally caught up to the long time standard of not having to call customer support to retrieve anything if you got a new system.

Is there any proof that you can do this? Games are already linked to your account, but as far as I know you can only register that device on one device per type (one WiiU, one 3DS, etc.).

Even before the Nintendo ID your Nintendo account still knew what games you both. For digital purchases you could log onto the site and click through to claim Nintendo stars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 3DS has been updated. You can buy 3DS games with your Nintendo ID.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is now. You can buy a 3DS game on their website with your account and the game will start downloading to your 3DS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A console, cords, controller and docs. Maybe a game. You can check by reading the *contents* part on the box or the product description.

Done. 

Unless you are afraid they might pack jumping snakes in the box and give you a slight fright. That has never happened, so don't worry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 12:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I thought we all decided to stop posting unboxing videos when we all collectively decided how pointless they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where?

I think maybe on the roads to the cities might have had guard towers, that were different but not by much. The Eagle Points in the city were different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But time wasn't an issue in that case. Link had all the time in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 10:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I meant as a protagonist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but Lin has said he was just finishing with In The Heights and picked up the largest book he could find because he just wanted to pass the time. The largest book he found was a Hamilton biography. I like to think if he picked up a Burr biography the play would be told from a different perspective.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's saying soul. And the boy is Hollywood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he does like not being an outcast anymore. Gotta pay the troll toll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt many 60 year olds are interested in superhero movies.

Outside of Batman, I wasn't until Guardians of the Galaxy. Now I keep on watching them because I want to see what happens when the Brat Pack goes after one of the Goonies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realism in games would suck. All shooters would be 99% camping. Tomb Raider would be 60% uneventful walking. Ezio would be completely wrecked after about 2 minutes of parkour.

Bullet sponges work in shooters, which is why they have never gone away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in the first AC game, climbing to an Eagle Point was a little bit like a puzzle and you had to find a route up.

By AC 3 they copy pasted the same tree as an eagle point several times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arkham Asylm is such a perfect game. Everything from progression is so tight and makes sense, in game and in world. In the sequel they went open world and progress tree. It ruined how well the first game flowed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the world is ending and someone wants you to pass on their love letters it is a bit stupid. I like how Zelda games do it. In Link's Awaking you win a Yoshi doll. Another character will trade that up, although it is not instantly apparent. Then you keep trading up unitl you get the boomerang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think the musical would have been very different if you picked up a Aaron Burr biography.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like a lot of things. Kung Fury was really funny. Then they did that KickStarter and decided to make it a short film. The 'trailer' had all the best gags. All the short film did was extend those jokes until they weren't as funny.

Sometimes less is more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it wasn't a direct parody of any 80's movie in particular.  It does seem to be a combo of a bunch of different 80's movie tropes but no solid one thing. The dinosaur and Hitler things seems to come from something much older, like B movies like The Manster and They Saved Hitler's Brain. Not 80's at all.

The blue grid stuff was very eighties design aesthetic but it was used mostly in instructional videos or small private video productions, not movies. Escape from New York /LA would be the only direct influences that are obvious. And having an arcade. In the 80's the thugs were always punks who hung around in arcades.

There are also some allusions to the home video market which would usually have the keyboard synth soundtrack and some mad max esque back drop with bondage costumes.

So there is some of the 80's there but nothing really solid, just a hyperizied meme version of different non connected sources.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The initial trailer was great. The short film sort of ran the joke into the ground. A sequel is just flogging a dead horse.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a decade ago, but you are right. DVD, thumb drives and CD-Rs with movies to watch. Everything from The Goonies to Evil Dead, Dr. Strangelove, The Room, Magic Mountain. Apocalypse Now and Redux were big favourites. Hearts of Darkness: A Filmmaker's Apocalypse was also shared. Apocalypse Now isn't Three Days of the Condor, it is still widely watched today by students and young people, not just your Dad.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Ep 3 was cancelled. It was in dev and announced. HL3 was never an officially announced project.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever seen The Deer Hunter. It's a good movie but it really is far too long. And you would think a movie that long could have  good transitions, but no. One moment you are at a wedding, then a bunch of mates hunting. You sneeze, or go to get a beer or maybe are just opening a bag of chips. You look back to the screen and suddenly you are in a prisoner of war camp wondering if the DVD skipped a scene. Then you realise you still have 4 hours of a movie left and you just spent all this time at a wedding that you really don't care about and has nothing to do with anything. Much like any wedding a family member or girlfriend drags you to where you know no one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On those classics you can also include films like Ghostbusters, Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas, 2001: A Space Oddesy. Apocolypse Now is like Pink Floyd. People will always be revisiting it no matter how old it gets.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe my college experience was different, but it seemed like everyone was watching movies like Pulp Fiction, Apocolypse Now, THe Godfather, 2001 and others for the first time. DVDs were being traded and people were really looking to expand their horizons.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or it might just mimic the hellish production of the movie and come out with a decent finished product despite all the set backs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brick and Mortar have limited shelf space and costs of holding stock, whether in a warehouse or in a store. They need to know what stock their customers want because any stock on a shelf or in a warehouse is costing them money. Amazon don't have that issue with third party sellers. Steam don't have that issue because everything is digital. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes, and they also have high teen pregnancy rates

I couldn't find a source on that, but generally pregnancy happens between a married (or engaged) couple. They marry younger and have more kids and fewer partners. Monogamy for life is also much more prevalent. That has nothing to do with how people dress. When settled people became more accepting of sex before marriage, less religious, contraception, these values didn't change in the travelling community.

So the only thing that has changed in the community is the dress. Everything else is more or less consistent over the last three decades. Are you saying that Travellers get married younger because of how the girls dress? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that was a bait and switch.

If adults feel things they shouldn't around teen girls, don't call the girls or the girls dress 'deplorable'. That is their problem.

Travelling communities have dance events where the teen girls dress far more 'provocatively' but that community also has a lot more people who wait until marriage. Clothes don't reflect how sexual a person is. Communities set that expectation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 12:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's more to do with appropriate dress. Like you won't get into the Oscars wearing a tracksuit. No one thinks you are a slut for wearing shorts are just wearing it for attention. They just think you are not in the right clothes for the venue. A girl in a GAA jersey won't get into that venue.

What is happening in the Fusion ball is girls are wearing appropriate clothes but are being judged on them anyway.

You can see how the two things are different right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 11:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should rephrase, because this is a formal event. I was talking in generalities. 

These comments are complaining about how teenage girls dress. None of the complaints are about them going to a formal event and their dress not being formal enough. The 'deplorable' (what a word, they aren't saying the clothing is inappropriate for the event, they are saying people who wear it are deplorable regardless of venue) dresses are formal. So girls are wearing dress appropriate clothes, but they are still being judged.

My point was men aren't being judged for their clothes, just the girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
