<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3180</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 18:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might already make something similar but [this](http://showmetheyummy.com/greek-yogurt-chicken-salad/) is my favorite chicken salad recipe (made with greek yogurt, dijon, cashews, and craisins). It's absolutely addictive. You do have to be a bit careful about serving sizes with the cashews, and I buy the reduced sugar craisins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 02:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe about 15 minutes, sometimes longer depending on when I leave. I go in the morning, and from the gym it's then another 20-30 minutes to work, depending on traffic. I live in the Boston area, so traffic is inevitable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 02:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooo... good idea. I might try that for a third coat! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 15:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

And honestly the rounded corners and edges were like that when I started (I possibly made them a bit worse because I'm not sure how to sand already round corners! Although I actually hand sanded the entire table, no power tools involved here.). 

It's definitely an old table and had a lot of wear when I got it. The edges were unevenly rounded in some places, I suspect from lots of feet being kicked up on the table with previous owners. I don't mind, though, kind of gives it character! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm so glad to have one nice piece of furniture! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to know, and kind of what I was suspecting, thanks! While it's continuing to harden I'm trying to decide how much it bothers me and whether it's worth sanding and doing another layer to see if I can do a better job.

What do you use to finish furniture other than poly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 18:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! 

And maybe... I have absolutely no experience with this stuff so I just started reading up on options today. I sanded between the two coats but I was worried sanding at the end would ruin the nice glossy finish and/or remove too much of the polyurethane? Maybe I should sand again, do a third coat, and then sand with even finer grain? Either way, I need to let it dry for a bit longer I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first DIY - refinishing an old coffee table </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 17:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 16:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing the US from the post, but yeah, that would definitely help determine what's reasonable for a week.

OP, I haven't been but if you're looking for a combo of partying and exploring, I've heard great things about Montreal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop, I peed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the best! I knew it was based here but couldn't remember if it was sold elsewhere... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 01:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Teddie, but it might be local to my area... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 21:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I found crepes at the gym, I'd eat the shit out of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 15:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked around quickly the other day and it looks like that actually is one of the new premium features. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 15:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've actually always had ads (not sure if they're going to change or be more visible) - clearly they're not that annoying because lots of people didn't notice them! :)

But no, otherwise as far as I can tell it's exactly the same. You're not losing anything.

Some of the new features seem cool to me - not $10 cool, but if they lower the price or go the reddit gold route and eventually make those free features while adding other new premium ones that would be awesome. I'm sticking around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 22:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing. They are just adding additional features that you pay for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 16:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same way, I hate it! I always thought it was because I'm so pale, too, but I guess not. I also hoped it would go away as I got in better shape, but nope. Even if I run a couple miles and it doesn't feel particularly difficult, I look like I'm dying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 15:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could try cleans - front squats, or if you can handle it, clean - press the bar over your head and bring it back down behind your neck - back squats. You'll want to make sure you feel like you can fail safely (I recommend youtube videos for that) and that you protect your floor in case of dropped weights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 15:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost went for blue, but changed my mind and went yellow instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are able to take a video and post it here, people will definitely be able to help! It can be hard to troubleshoot without seeing it.

To clarify, if you do a bodyweight squat to proper depth is that fine? How are you with third world squats? Have you tried goblet squats to help work your way up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely take a break - sometimes I find myself really needing a break, so I take a week off of lifting, and then I seem to come back better and stronger after.

Five months in a row of bulking can be tough. Are you underweight right now, or just trying to add muscle mass? How large is your calorie surplus right now? I would take the week off of everything, but when you come back I might recommend dropping to maintenance for a few weeks as well to kind of reset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 16:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that they each appear to be wearing half of an outfit. It looks like he stole her pants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 19:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carb cycling doesn't directly cause weight gain or weight loss - only a calorie surplus/deficit will do that. Carb cycling typically just refers to the "timing" of when you consume your carbs. 

I do some amount of carb cycling - I tend to focus carbs around my workouts, and I eat lower carb on days I don't work out. The goal is really just to help me prepare and recover from lifting as much as possible, while also losing weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with me. You can absolutely use tampons with an IUD. I guess there are some *rare* cases of someone accidentally yanking on the IUD strings... mine are trimmed and wrapped up around my cervix and it's never been an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 21:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would double check your macro calculations first. 224 g of protein is really really high, and right now your macros add up to 1792 calories unless I mathed wrong (224x4 + 134x4 + 40x9). (Edit: fixed formatting).

Your carbs look really reasonable to me. I would make sure you're actually eating 1500 calories, not 1800, and lower your protein target (and maybe up fat just a tad).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 18:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-25 17:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ZBT at my university was known as "the geeky Jewish guys who barely count as a frat." In my experience, it varies widely from school to school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had older Nike Free's that were similarly sock-like - I had to size up because they were tight as well. I always wore socks with mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 18:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to whine about my total first world problem, which is that I'm in Vegas working at a conference instead of in Boston celebrating Marathon Monday. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 20:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I would recommend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 20:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the biggest thing to keep in mind is that calculators are a starting point and you can and should adjust them to work better for you. You will lose weight as long as you are at a calorie deficit. Within your calorie target, you can shift the macros around to support your goals.

I think a lot of the macro calculators out there are designed to support athletic performance - carbs are important for that. I know personally if I go too low carb, my lifts start to suffer. Carbs will likely also make it easier for you to spend an hour on the treadmill.

Other people find it easier to eat at a deficit and avoid cravings if they eat low carb, higher fat. So YMMV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 18:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the non-flat version and I also like them a lot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 22:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/Fitness/wiki/faq#wiki_do_women_get_bulky_if_they_lift_heavy_things.3F

But if she doesn't want to lift and dieting to be skinny is consistent with her goals, that's ok too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 20:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out the FAQ in the sidebar, there's lots of great information there about diet and exercise to lose weight.

The primary thing you'll read is that losing weight is mostly diet. You don't necessarily have to drastically change what you eat - just start keeping track and then eat less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well can't comment on your training then. Start by reading the FAQ  and tracking what you eat so you know how much you're actually eating (not just "some fruit and bread" but X number of calories and Y grams of protein), and then eat even more than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Science is wrong because my friend lost weight by eating fruit for breakfast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual for any YouTube video... don't look at the comments below the video unless you want to repeatedly smash your head against the wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you following a strength training program?

How many calories are you eating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 20:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I had any advice... Unfortunately I think this is a pretty common issue.

My dad is in awesome shape - he's never been particularly unhealthy, but a few years ago he suddenly decided he wanted to lose weight and get in better shape. He started eating less and eating better, had a trainer for a little while, and now hits the gym every morning and runs half marathons - he's probably in better shape than I am! Ha!

My mom on the other hand is overweight (probably technically obese) and has been for as long as I remember, but she's always got an excuse up her sleeve (usually some sort of mysterious "health issue"). She falls victim to the idea that she's eating well because *antioxidants* and *superfoods* and *yogurt* and *oatmeal* - if it's a fad diet food, she eats it, but she's still very overweight.

Any time I try to have a conversation with her, my ideas are dismissed because I'm only 25 and haven't had kids so I still have "good metabolism". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 19:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.openbiome.org/stool-donation/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 15:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That happened to me... I went to a deadlift clinic and everything was awesome and my deadlifts felt perfect, and then I deadlifted something super light the next week and everything felt *so wrong*. I think I was overthinking things. I got back in the groove a couple weeks after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 20:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think it's less about motivation and more about routine. It's hard to start out, but once you get used to it and adjust your overall life routine and sleep schedule, it becomes much easier. I don't even think about it much anymore, and on the occasional extra tired morning I think about how bad I'll feel if I don't go, how busy the gym is in the afternoon, etc.

Other than that, I pack literally everything ahead of time (all my food for the day, my work outfit in my gym bag, and my gym clothes and shoes ready to be put on) so it requires minimal effort in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 17:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well obviously you don't want to lose all of it, but isn't excess visceral fat a big health issue for very overweight people?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, no I'm glad to see someone else had the same reaction! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 16:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Supplements" or even "muscle building supplements" is such a ridiculously broad term. Plenty of supplements, including [Creatine](http://examine.com/supplements/Creatine), one of the examples they listed, have been well-studied and found to be safe and effective.

The other example they listed and linked out to appears to be a test booster, which, in my incredibly unscientific opinion, seems more likely to be related to testicular cancer. 

Saying "supplements are linked to cancer" is almost as broad as saying "food is linked to cancer" - too broad and unnecessarily scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree. As shallow and terrible as it sounds I've been really afraid about how much kids will wreck my body... If OP looks this great after kids *and* losing 115 lbs, I think I could be ok! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! I read this at first like you're living with your ex and was wondering how that could possibly be good... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
