<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9664</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 15:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call it Old Sandy P's Lovely Hilltop Band </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where did you get (/would you get) video for your website? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to market my freelance videography services to small businesses. If you have a video on your website, who made it and where did you find them? 

If you wanted to have a video made, where would be the first places you would search? Obviously for many people Google would be the first port of call, but I'm trying to figure out other ways to get hold of businesses that might be interested in my services. Thanks for any help or insight you can give me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 16:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A child aged 4 is going to have an easier time learning a language in a new country than someone age 24. That doesn't mean 4 year olds are more intelligent than adults. It's easier to acquire new skills at a younger age, this is the same for every generation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great reply thanks. The videos I do would be things like product demos, brand videos, talking heads, shots of the actual business, so I'm not really competing with what people can do with stock elements in that sense. Good point about potentially taking away work from the website side of things. Perhaps a way around that would be the developer approaches the client about potential videos after the website has been set up, or something like that.

Thanks for the response, I'm still obviously just figuring things out atm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice needed: Videographer looking to build relationships with local web developers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 21:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a freelance videographer (Surrey, UK), who wants to build some relationships with local web designers and developers in the New Year. I would really appreciate it if anyone could give me some advice regarding my plan.

What I want to do is have web developers offer their clients video services, and then refer them to me to do the work. My rate would be around 450 depending on the project. The web developer could mark up the price to what they feel is appropriate, say 600. They can be as involved or not involved as they like in the process.

I get more business my way, the web developer gets money for very little extra work, the client gets a service they need. No one stands to lose very much from the deal. 

From a web developer perspective, what are the pros and cons of the deal for you? Do you think it is a deal that many people would go for? What would be the best way to approach them? I am not naturally a great business thinker, so any advice would be greatly appreciated. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 21:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought this said "have actual sting play" and couldn't figure out the connection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 00:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The analogy doesn't work in any way because you're comparing something that doesn't matter o something that does matter. If someone agrees to sign a petition without asking what your intention is then they don't care about your intention. If someone sleeps with you without it asking what your intention is then they may well still care about your intention. Yes there is some responsibility in them to find out what your intention is but that still doesn't make it right on your part. I don't think it makes you morally appalling, I just think it makes you a creep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 22:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The petition analogy really doesn't work in my opinion, because a petition is always FOR something. But if you want to go down that route, I would suggest a more fitting analogy would be if you were collection signatures from people and using them for something you know they wouldn't agree with, eg a racist organisation, or something like that. I'm sure you can charm them out of a signature without telling them what it's for, but is it ethical to use those signatures for an organisation you know they would disagree with?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 11:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably you would not tell anyone that you are with about your goal beforehand. How many of those people do you think would have turned you down if they knew about your goal of 100 people? I think this is where the problem lies. I would think about what your goal really is. Is it to experience a good time with a lot of people? Maybe then it is best to focus on the people and the experiences rather than on the numbers.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means that different people like different things? You seem to be the one making the straw man. I haven't said or implied that any of it doesn't have a place in metal or that people shouldn't like it or that other people don't relate to it. It's great that people love these genres of metal and embrace the culture and the aesthetic, I would never argue otherwise. I am saying that I am glad that there has been a shift in recent years towards things that I personally relate to better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking about the average fan, I'm talking about the images and styles that are associated with metal. I don't think I've ever seen anyone wearing corpse paint in my life, but it's and image that is associated with black metal. Type in "black metal" into google images and all the images are black and white, corpse paint and illegible band names. I personally don't mind that aesthetic, but my only point is, I am happy that it is becoming more common to take the sounds that I like from these more extreme genres of metal, and combining them with an aesthetic that I personally relate to more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 16:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing against anyone who dresses like this (or any way) but long hair, studs, tattoos, leather, huge baggy black t-shirts, make-up, chains, skulls, corpse paint etc isn't really my thing. I like some of it, but a lot of it isn't really what I'm into and it's so common in metal. I do sometimes wish there was a bit more diversity in visual style in metal. Frankly I do quite like that deafheaven have less of that stuff in their image. Not that any of it is really a big deal, when it comes down to it, if the music is good, it's good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 16:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've loved metal for years, but I'm very glad that it's becoming more common to see bands wearing more "normal" clothes, because I've always hated metal fashion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 19:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YEAHHHH, takes me back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 17:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To put it bluntly, people enjoy eating in restaurants. You might as well say that theatre, sport, bars, cinemas and amusement parks are useless to society. People enjoy them, they are (mostly) a luxury that people use to treat themselves.

If you enjoy food a lot, (I do), then eating at a restaurant is an opportunity to eat food that you cannot cook yourself, due to insufficient skill, patience or equipment, and socialise whilst doing it.

Also when you cook yourself, it is easy to get into habits of using the same techniques and ingredients. Eating out offers inspiration and variety.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 16:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the time, in my experience, I have found that people assume the "pretentious douchebag" part just based on their interests or fashion. How many times have you read on reddit "pretentious douchebag" just based on a photo of someone with facial hair and a record player or something like that. No one knows if that person is pretentious or not, they just have a beard and like vinyl records, or old films or foreign food.

There are pretentious douchebags amongst people who like mainstream stuff too. Many of them call people hipseters for liking alternative stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 20:03:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realise that this is a somewhat lazy post by me, but this Stephen Fry video really nicely articulates the problem with the using the sense of wonder at nature as evidence for a god.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2-d4otHE-YI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that how hard working you are refers to your natural and acquired potential and how hard you work is what you actually do with it. 

Unless your view is all pride is pointless regardless of everything. You can say that there's no free will, life is deterministic and we're just a bunch of atoms bouncing around, but what's the point? Why would you  want to deny yourself and others a positive emotion that you have earned through hard work. Regardless of circumstances and genes, hard work is still hard. Reward yourself with pride over your successes and use that list for pride to help you succeed in life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say there is a difference in how "hard working" you are and how hard you work. It's more difficult for a naturally lazy person to put the work in but that doesn't mean they can't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 15:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's take the best athletes in the world in their respective fields as an example. They are superior partly because of their genes, partly because of the circumstances of their birth and upbringing, and **partly because of all the hard work they have put in**. I don't think there are many (any?) athletes who have reached the top without extreme amounts of hard work and self discipline. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 18:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he's a moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 17:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was referring to a tv show called SpongeBob SquarePants, where the titular character lives in the pineapple under the sea. It's just a cartoon though, it's not a real pineapple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
