<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject405</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 22:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a very strange interpretation of the Homeric Question indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review: The Homeric Hymns and Herne the Hunter by Peter McDonald  audacious and authoritative insights | Aingeal Clare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 20:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 18:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two NewStoa websites:

* [NewStoa.com](http://newstoa.com/)

* [NewStoa.info](http://newstoa.info/)

According to [this announcement in November 2015](http://newstoa.info/article185.html) Giulia Harding took over the position of Director of the NewStoa Council. There is also [this announcement on reddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/2xp47i/big_changes_coming_at_new_stoa/) you may be interested in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicureanism vs. Stoicism | Izhaarbir Singh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 17:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need to escape from the planet of the apps: Apps should be either useful, interesting, or fun  but getting a notification now means Im about to feel guilty or inadequate about something | Bella Mackie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I tend to think that Epicurus was setting them up as examples to follow.

I should have cited the end of the [Letter to Menoeceus](http://www.monadnock.net/epicurus/letter.html) yesterday:

 So practice these and similar things day and night, by yourself and with a like-minded friend, and you will never be disturbed whether waking or sleeping, and you will live as a god among men: for a man who lives in the midst of immortal goods is unlike a merely mortal being. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](https://www.academia.edu/23387065/Madhyamaka_Ethics)

 There are two main loci of contemporary debate about the nature of Madhyamaka ethics. The first investigates the general issue of whether the Madhyamaka philosophy of emptiness (*nyavda*) is consistent with a commitment to systematic ethical distinctions. The second queries whether the metaphysical analysis of no-self presented by ntideva in his *Bodhicaryvatra* entails the impartial benevolence of a bodhisattva. This article will critically examine these debates and demonstrate the ways in which they are shaped by competing understandings of Madhyamaka conventional truth or reality (*savtisatya*) and the forms of reasoning admissible for differentiating conventional truth from falsity and good from bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Madhyamaka Ethics | Bronwyn Finnigan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](http://www.un.org/en/ga/search/view_doc.asp?symbol=%20A/RES/65/309) and [here](http://www.un.org/en/ga/search/view_doc.asp?symbol=%20A/RES/66/281) are the original UN resolutions: The official name is *International Day of Happiness*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Today is the Twentieth of March, the day of the month designated by Epicurus to remember Metrodorus and himself and the philosophy of happiness they developed and taught.  Today is also "[International Happiness Day](http://dayofhappiness.net/)." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peace and Safety for Your Twentieth of March: If [happiness] be absent, ALL our actions are directed towards attaining it. | Cassius Amicus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I tend to think that Epicurus was setting them up as examples to follow.

That is, something like the Epicurean equivalent of the Stoic sage? Epicurus did some related comparisons indeed:

 The body cries out to not be hungry, not be thirsty, not be cold. Anyone who has these things, and who is confident of continuing to have them, can rival the gods for happiness. (Vatican Sayings 33) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 11:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 11:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that participation in religious ceremonies, the decision which religion to follow and the decision not to follow any religion at all is completely personal and voluntary. Unfortunately, that does not seem to be what these parents agree to. Being dependent on their parents, minors don't have as much choice as adults in cases like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 11:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *In cases like that...* I am no native speaker, I thought 'here' can be used in that context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 10:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, minors often don't have much choice here without major bad consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 10:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to society where maintaining a certain image is more important than what you actually are. It is quite hard not to participate in this kind of hypocrisy at all. Apart from that, such ceremonies also belong to folklore in a way and are not taken completely seriously by many participants.

 I really hate they spend so much money on me just for something I never wanted to take myself. I feel crap for that, I don't want them to spend money.

In this case you may say that you don't want to receive money and suggest that they may donate that money to a humanitarian organization of your choice instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can we learn from Stoic Week 2015? | Tim LeBon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 22:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 17:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Seriously; did you know that by heart or by google?

I have read a good biography and therefore I knew it mostly, but I had to use Google to get the name with all titles right and I was not sure about his exact birth name.

 He was adopted as an adult?!

Hadrian adopted Lucius Aelius Caesar who should have been Hadrian's successor. Lucius Aelius Caesar, however, died before Hadrian. Then Hadrian made Antoninus Pius his successor, but Antoninus had to adopt Lucius Aelius' son Lucius Verus and Marcus.  That is, Hadrian wanted him to adopt Lucius Verus, while the adoption of Marcus may have been Antoninus' suggestion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 09:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was his name, which changed several times:

Marcus was born as *Marcus Annius Catilius Severus*. After his engagement with Lucius Aelius Caesar's daughter Ceionia, his name became *Marcus Annius Verus*. Marcus was adopted by Hadrian's successor Antoninus Pius and his name became *Marcus Aelius Aurelius Verus*.

When Marcus became emperor, his name changed to *Marcus Aurelius Antoninus Augustus*. At the time of his death his full name including all titles was *Imperator Caesar Marcus Aurelius Antoninus Augustus Germanicus Sarmaticus, Pontifex Maximus, Tribuniciae potestatis XXXIV, Imperator X, Consul III, Pater patriae*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 07:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may have a look at this [commentary](http://dharmafarer.org/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2009/12/8.7-Sannoga-S-a7.48-piya.pdf) on the [Saoga Sutta](http://www.accesstoinsight.org/tipitaka/an/an07/an07.048.than.html). There is also a [commentary](http://dharmafarer.org/wordpress/wp-content/uploads/2009/12/21.9-Methuna-S-a7.47-piya.pdf) on the Methuna Sutta which may be of interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddhist Nonviolence | Paula Green </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 23:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The thorny issue of Stoic emotions | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 20:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nicholas Roerich - Tibetan Art, 1928 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 08:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> La Mode Retrouve: Looking for Prousts Muse in Paris | Madison Mainwaring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 23:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emotionlessness? The Epicurean View Is the *Deeper* Experience of Emotion! | Cassius Amicus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 17:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 17:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not in the UK and it works (obviously). As far as I remember, I have already posted the program about Epicureism last year. These radio series is excellent indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 08:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are not useless without accepting Stoic theology and metaphysics, they actually work very well (and with some adaptions for Epicureans as well). But it affects the theoretical foundation of Stoic ethics. If Stoicism is to be more than (efficient) self-help or a way of life, it will have to be founded differently. The question is, how far one can go without leaving Stoicism.

When I wrote

 I see much value in Stoic ethics and the therapeutic framework. We shall not forget that the most effective psychotherapy is based on Stoicism and it is also the most scientifically validated one.

I referred to cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT). If you are interested in the effectiveness of Stoic teachings, you may have a look at *The Philosophy of Cognitive Behavioural Therapy: Stoic Philosophy as Rational and Cognitive Psychotherapy* by Donald Robertson, which I liked very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Van Dyck at the Frick, Documenting Aristocracy | Roberta Smith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 23:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 18:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Happiness**](http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p005489g)

 Melvyn Bragg and guests discuss whether 'happiness' means living a life of pleasure, or of virtue. It is an old question, and the Roman poet Horace attempted to answer it when he wrote; 'Not the owner of many possessions will you be right to call happy: he more rightly deserves the name of happy who knows how to use the gods's gifts wisely and to put up with rough poverty, and who fears dishonour more than death'. It seems a noble sentiment but for the Greek Sophist Thrasymachus this sort of attitude was the epitome of moral weakness: For him poverty was miserable, and happiness flowed from wealth and power over men, an idea so persuasive that Plato wrote The Republic in response to its challenge. What have our philosophers made of the compulsion to be happy? And how much does this ancient debate still define what it means to be happy today? Are we entitled to health, wealth and the pursuit of pleasure or is true contentment something else entirely?

 With Angie Hobbs, Lecturer in Philosophy at the University of Warwick; Simon Blackburn, Professor of Philosophy at Cambridge University; Anthony Grayling, Reader in Philosophy at Birkbeck College, University of London. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BBC Radio 4 - In Our Time, Happiness | Melvyn Bragg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 18:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 08:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of misconceptions indeed and I am quite certain to share some of them, too.

Stoics believe that *logos* is immanent in everything, *logos* is one of two first principles and identified with god by the Stoics, thus they essentially believe in the god of Spinoza. According to the Stoics, human have an extraordinarily big part of *logos*. Because this god is perfect, we are exactly where we are supposed to be, no matter how miserable our living environment is. We are to fulfill the role which we are intended for by perfecting our own essential nature: As rational and social beings we shall therefore excel in wisdom, justice, courage and self-discipline. That is, being a good person is necessary and sufficient for happiness.

Stoicism offers a therapeutic framework (this is also true for Ancient Stoicism). We cannot control external things, for example that we are living in a miserable living environment, but we can always control ourselves, our opinions, our value judgements, everything we need to be virtuous, which is the one and only good. Therefore, we can be completely free and happy even under the worst circumstances. The Stoic sage is happy even while being tortured the worst possible way.

I am no Stoic. I don't believe in divine providence and Stoic theology and metaphysics. And I don't think that virtue is the sole good. As an Epicurean I agree that being virtuous is necessary for being happy, but disagree that it is also sufficient. However, I see much value in Stoic ethics and the therapeutic framework. We shall not forget that the most effective psychotherapy is based on Stoicism and it is also the most scientifically validated one. I am also very fine with Stoic cosmopolitanism. Stoicism was one of the most important philosophies for 500 years and there were some excellent Stoic philosophers. One of the two most important Ancient logicians was a Stoic. I think that studying Stoicism is rewarding even for Epicureans.

That being said, I think that many people of /r/Stoicism don't believe in Stoic theology and metaphysics, either. Divine providence is nothing we read much about there. I consider this as a very important part of Stoicism, since everything else follows from that in some way. Most people are interested in Stoic ethics and techniques, which are efficient indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Art Gone to Hell: A Boschian Bestiary | Daniel McDermon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 16:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 14:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I meant to say the negative kind of opinion.

There is a kind of far-fetched criticisms lacking any logic at all. This kind does not belong to criticisms needing deep reflection indeed. However, this one

 This whole post is because of the critique my friend gave me on my evaluation.

is nothing like that. At least it is based on a psychological evaluation. And being on a high horse is something Marcus Aurelius is warning himself of again and again. If a Roman emperor is warning himself of being on a high horse, who are we to not taking care of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 14:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  haha, no, I wasn't being sarcastic.

Your words appear sarcastic, because they are a very bad caricature of Stoics concerning pleasure (and maybe not even that). The most hardcore Stoics treated pleasure more differentiated than that. Read, for example, the excellent FAQ of /r/Stoicism, especially the section: [Is enjoyment of life's pleasures a goal advocated in Stoicism?](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/wiki/faq#wiki_is_enjoyment_of_life.27s_pleasures_a_goal_advocated_in_stoicism.3F) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 11:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And all forms of criticism or opinion others have of me, I do not let it get to me.

Stoics are expected to be self-critical and to reflect on oneselves daily. We have a whole book by a Roman emperor, Marcus Aurelius, which consists to a major part of self-reflection. Not listening to other people's opinions and criticisms at all is really bad advice, because constructive feedback of other people is a very valuable source for critical self-reflection and self-improvement. You are certainly not supposed to automatically accept all criticisms, but rational people at least reflect on them before accepting or rejecting them. I consider this to be very related to the thread's title which you chose to be *"Tips on practicing humility or 'getting off the high horse'"*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 10:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You shouldn't listen to what other people say about you.

Of course we should listen to constructive criticism and reflect on it. Having reflected on it, we are free to accept or reject it though. This is what rational beings, which humans are, do in such cases. We are not above criticism and feeling otherwise is nothing a virtuous person is characterized by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 10:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks! Contrary to the common prejudices, we Epicureans prefer the simple and quiet life. To many opponents, a true Epicurean life seems to be more ascetic than hedonistic. Videos like that fit quite well to Epicureanism indeed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosophy Core Concepts: Epicurus on Practical Reasoning | Gregory B. Sadler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 23:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosophy Core Concepts: Epictetus and Stoic Cosmopolitanism | Gregory B. Sadler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 23:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alexander the Greats Humanistic Education (Plutarch, Alexander 8.1-2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 14:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 09:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](https://ddd.uab.cat/pub/mirabilia/mirabilia_a2014m1-6n18/mirabilia_a2014m1-6n18p6.pdf)

 Epicureanism was seen by its opponents, both pagan and Christian, as the philosophy of pleasure and atheism. From the theological point of view, the accusation of atheism was incorrect, since Epicurus and the Epicureans admitted of the existence of deities, and posited them as models of moral perfection, while denying their interest in human affairs, i.e. providence. This denial aimed at guaranteeing their imperturbability (*ataraxia*). From the ethical point of view, the ideal of pleasure (*hdon*), on which I shall concentrate here, was grossly misunderstood or distorted by the opponents of Epicureanism, who generally did not take into consideration the moderation, equilibrium, and serenity that the superior catastematic pleasure (Epicuruss real ideal of pleasure) involved. I shall analyse the attitude of late-antique sources, especially Christian, toward Epicureanism and its ethics. A great many of Useners and Arrighettis fragments of Epicurus indeed come from Christian late-antique authors, such as Clement, Origen, Eusebius, Lactantius, and Augustine, but other patristic authors should be added, such as Basil and Gregory of Nyssa. Even if patristic interest in Epicureanism is often critical, and sometimes imprecise or distorted, nevertheless it is tangible. I shall focus on the authors who make the most interesting use of Epicurean sources, particularly with respect to the ethical doctrine: Origen, Dionysius of Alexandria, Lactantius, Ambrose, Jerome and Augustine, Gregory Nyssen, and Nazianzen, the only one who really understood and praised Epicuruss notion of *hdon*. I shall also argue that the fading away of the availability and use of good sources on Epicureanism, along with the disappearance of the Epicurean school itself, brought about an impoverishment in the understanding of, and hostility to, Epicurus and Epicureanism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rejection of the Epicurean Ideal of Pleasure in Late Antique Sources: Not Only Misunderstandings | Ilaria L. E. Ramelli </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 09:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Compared (with others) in relation to the necessities of life, the wise person knows how to give rather than take, having gained such a great store of self-sufficiency (Vatican Sayings 44) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 00:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 17:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is just a Stoic analogon to the [fake Buddha quotes](http://fakebuddhaquotes.com/) and it certainly is not the only fake Marcus Aurelius quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 11:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have found an earlier thread concerning this quote: [Aurelius quote source/translation?](https://www.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/3j9dt0/aurelius_quote_sourcetranslation/) However, I downloaded the copy of the mentioned [translation by Thomas Gataker](https://archive.org/details/meditationsempe01gatagoog) as PDF and did not find the quote at III.9 as claimed in the earlier thread (but I did only a rather quick check). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the Age of Giorgione review  defiant, forgotten face of Renaissance art | Jonathan Jones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 10:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 09:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With activated custom styles, this crappy image makes reading impossible. But then, who wants to read bad Eastern philosophy anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buddhism, Radical Critique and Revolutionary Praxis | John Clark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 15:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside the Unpublished World of Allen Ginsberg | Bill Morgan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 11:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Destination Venus: how Botticelli became a brand | Kathryn Hughes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 11:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How often does psychotherapy make people feel worse? Patient experience of negative effects of psychological treatment: results of a national survey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 11:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homer's Iliad cast a spell on me | Philip Womack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 07:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 22:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be great indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert Schumann - Symphony n2 in C major - Leonard Bernstein / Bavarian Radio Symphony Orchestra (live recording 1983) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 21:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battling the Gods: Atheism in the Ancient World review  disbelief has been around for 2,500 years | Emily Wilson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 20:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My date with Michelangelo (a visit to the British Museums Study Room containing prints and drawings by Rembrandt, Michelangelo and more) | Sophie Hardach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 20:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The linked article is about Francis Towne, but highly interesting nevertheless. Many thanks for posting it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 15:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Musonius was Epictetus' teacher and it is quite surprising that he is one of the most neglected Stoic philosophers today. He asked interesting questions and what he lectured about is still quite relevant. He clearly is one of my favorite Stoic philosophers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While we are on the journey, we must try to make the later part better than the earlier, and when we come to the end to be in joyful equilibrium. (Vatican Sayings 48) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 07:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could David Hume Have Known about Buddhism? Charles Francois Dolu, the Royal College of La Flche, and the Global Jesuit Intellectual Network | Alison Gopnik </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 21:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alison Gopnik also published an interesting article about her findings in Hume Studies, Volume 35, Number 1 2, 2009, pp. 528: [Could David Hume Have Known about Buddhism? Charles Francois Dolu, the Royal College of La Flche, and the Global Jesuit Intellectual Network](http://www.alisongopnik.com/Papers_Alison/Gopnik_HumeStudies_withTOC.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oxford Uehiro Prize in Practical Ethics: Should You Switch to an Altruistic Career? Written by Benjamin Lange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 20:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Musonius Lectures | Massimo Pigliucci </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is possible to live decently with meagre resources which the unreflecting person finds about as hard as does the person whose life runs to excess through a failure to observe limits (Vatican Sayings 63) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 11:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 09:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting rid of emotions is nothing a Stoic is aiming for indeed, Stoics are no statues after all. I think you are quite right, although the word *meditation* may be a little bit misleading for people identifying *meditation* with the Buddhist meditation.

You may be interested in a passage of the book *Reforming the Art of Living* by Rico Vitz, which I found when I searched for *eupathe* with Google. You can read it [here](https://books.google.at/books?id=LrbkBAAAQBAJ pg=PA43#v=onepage q f=false). This is very closely related to your question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let us sympathize with our friends not with wailing but with thoughtfulness (Vatican Sayings 66) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 22:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicurean Ethics: Hedonism   Virtue | Elise Woodard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 08:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wider Implications Of The Epicurean Warnings About Passionate Love | Cassius Amicus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 22:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keeping Watch With The Epicurean Chorus  Happily Thriving And Alive With Joy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intellectual Child Abuse (by Steven Novella) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 22:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Historical consciousness and traditional Buddhist narratives | Rita M. Gross </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can virtue be taught? (by Massimo Pigliucci) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 18:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Stoic Metaphysics leads to Stoic Ethics | Henry Folse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 08:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Epicurean Metaphysics leads to Epicurean Ethics | Henry Folse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 08:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The pros   cons on Stoicism (a discussion with Dan Kauffman and Dan Fincke about what a modern, practically useful Stoicism might look like) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 20:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Original Wagner (by Martin Filler) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 23:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shakespeare and Asia (by Michael Dobson) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 22:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicureanism: eat, drink, and be merry? | Catherine Wilson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 22:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 22:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like him very much, too. However, he seems to be more into Stoicism than into Epicureanism. Today I've found this announcement: [Farewell from the old Stoicism Today Editor, Patrick Ussher, and A Warm Welcome to the New Editor, Greg Sadler](http://blogs.exeter.ac.uk/stoicismtoday/2016/03/01/farewell-from-the-old-stoicism-today-editor-patrick-ussher-and-welcome-to-the-new-editor-greg-sadler/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 20:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may have a look at /r/pencils. That being said, I love my Rotring 600. There are other great mechanical pencils like the Pentel Graphgear 1000, but the Rotring 600 is my personal favorite. My favorite leads are Ain STEIN from Pentel, because they are very hard to break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 20:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your quote is actually about providence, which was a very basic part of ancient Stoicism indeed. I am not saying you should believe in providence, but the question what one can take from a philosophy without arriving at a different philosophy is a rather common problem.

That being said, I don't believe in gods, either. However, after centuries of Christianity the word "god" has a different meaning to us than to ancient Stoics. The Stoic god is a pantheistic god and therefore not even similar to a deity like the Christian god. The Stoics identified god with *logos* which is one of the two first principles pervading the Universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 22:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marcus Aurelius was neither theist nor agnostic. Stoics were pantheists (their god was very similar to Spinoza's god) and Marcus Aurelius was no exception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicurus Handout: Epicurus on Happiness, Prudence, Justice, and Friendship | Gregory Sadler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 20:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Siphnian Treasury, Delphi (Pediment and Frieze of the Siphnian Treasury at the Sanctuary of Apollo at Delphi, c. 530 B.C.E.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 20:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Universal Reason  The Guide to Stoic Practice (by Chris Fisher) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 18:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Rome (A project between Khan Academy and Rome Reborn - with Dr. Bernard Frischer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 07:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoicism 101 - A brief introduction to the history, theory, and modern practice of Stoicism (by Massimo Pigliucci) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 20:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicurus Handout: Comparison Between Aristippus' and Epicurus' Hedonisms | Gregory Sadler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 16:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 09:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your analysis is interesting indeed. I think posting this video in a text post with your analysis would have been better than just dropping the link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 22:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living according to nature basically means excelling by perfecting our own essential nature. As rational and social beings we shall therefore excel in wisdom, justice, courage and self-discipline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ethics In Street Photography; The Black, White And The Grey Of It (by Amruta Mohod) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 18:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosophy vs rationality vs therapy (by Massimo Pigliucci) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 18:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Being a Stoic: A Documentary (by Katie Bolte) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 23:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The race is run: America's abandoned space history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 22:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plunge Into One of the Largest Star Nurseries in the Near Universe (by Phil Plait) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 23:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 21:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Financially successful.

It is obvious that Donald Trump is financially successful, which is exactly what many (if not most) people understand under being successful. However, since we are in a Stoic discussion forum, it's reasonable to look at somebody's success from a Stoic point of view.

Being successful in something indifferent is not virtuous, it is indifferent. He can be virtuous in what he does with his financial success, though. Unfortunately, I don't see his statements of the last months as particularly virtuous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 18:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think, one should at least hesitate calling people like that successful, since it's living a good (virtuous) life which constitutes a successful life from the Stoic point of view. Being driven by fear or being fucked up is not really virtuous, no matter how much it may help in making money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 18:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks for pointing that out, since I did not know Carneades and the linked article is interesting indeed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epictetus vs the Epicureans and the Academics (by Massimo Pigliucci) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 13:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9 timeless lessons from the great Roman emperor Marcus Aurelius (by Richard Feloni) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 23:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you post [this](https://np.reddit.com/r/Stoicism/comments/46kxxb/reading_stoic_texts_i_often_get_lost_due_to_my/) a second time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is philosophy therapy, or is it simply a search for truth? (by Jules Evans and Nigel Warburton) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 23:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 Ways Stoicism Applies to Entrepreneurship (by Mike Fishbein) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 23:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gregory B. Sadler: Epictetus on Irrational Fears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 20:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gregory B. Sadler: Epictetus' Criticisms of Epicureanism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 20:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoicism turns lives upside down (by Chris Fisher) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Inclusion Problem in Critical Thinking: The Case of Indian Philosophy | Anand Jayprakash Vaidya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 19:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Achilles is brutal, vain, pitiless  and a true hero (by Sam Jordison) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 12:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Homer's Iliad speak across the centuries? (by Sam Jordison) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 19:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Traditionalist Representations of Buddhism | Richard K. Payne </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 18:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 09:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I am concerned, I appreciate your ideas very much. A dictionary like that can help a lot indeed, but more for being able to refer to it than for maintaining the illusion that people would read it before asking their questions. I have no doubt that people will continue asking the same questions based on the same misconceptions again and again. We already have an excellent FAQ. If you read the FAQ and the other wiki pages, you will know a lot about Stoicism.

I also think that using the original terms can be helpful indeed, although I'd prefer to add them in parenthesis following the English words (eventually with links to the dictionary), if that makes sense within the given context. This would make it clear that Stoics often don't use common words in their common sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Luciano Pavarotti recounts some 'Embarassing Moments On Stage' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 21:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 19:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Abstract**

 Epicurus is one of the first social contract theorists, holding that justice is an agreement neither to harm nor be harmed. He also says that living justly is necessary and sufficient for living pleasantly, which is the Epicurean goal. Some say that there are two accounts of justice in Epicurusone as a personal virtue, the other as a virtue of institutions. I argue that the personal virtue derives from compliance with just social institutions, and so we need to attribute only one account of justice to Epicurus. I show how this interpretation makes sense of claims about justice by Epicurus and his followers, including Hermarchus, Lucretius, and Diogenes of Oinoanda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicurean Justice | John Armstrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 19:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 18:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The autor responds to some critical comments coming from participants of Stoic conferences, namely that 'virtue' is being talked about very much, but not precisely about what virtue is and how we can become more virtuous. While Christopher Gill has already answered the first part of the question, Tim LeBon answers the second part in this article basically by looking at modern evidence-based psychologies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Become Virtuous by Tim LeBon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 17:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 21:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Abstract**

 Epicurus argued that death is no misfortune, because when a person dies, he no longer has sensation, and sensation is a necessary condition of value for a person. This argument, however, faces a powerful objection. Contemporary philosophers argue that death is bad precisely because it deprives one of good experiences one would have had, had one not died. I analyze and evaluate the Epicurean response to this objection, showing how, according to Epicurus, this objection reflects mistaken and unhealthy ideas about how lives should be evaluated. Uncovering and addressing these modes of evaluation constitutes a central aim of Epicurean therapy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicurus on the Fear of Death and the Relative Value of Lives | Benjamin A. Rider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 21:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Franz Liszt - Il Lamento S. 144 (Saskia Giorgini, piano) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 16:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy Wars: Spiral galaxy M81 and irregular galaxy M82 being locked in gravitational combat, as they have been for the past billion years [1406x1200] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 17:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 17:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's so easy to get into theory-crafting philosophy and not get around to putting it into practice.

Being a philosophy, theory is certainly an essential part of Stoicism and therefore it shouldn't be neglected. However, it's totally wrong to stop there indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic spiritual exercises: II, from the Meditations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 13:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is enlightenment off-limits to laypeople? (by Narayan Helen Liebenson, Tenzin Wangyal Rinpoche, Sallie Jiko Tisdale) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 04:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic spiritual exercises: I, from the Enchiridion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 13:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Young Luciano Pavarotti sings "Ingemisco" from Verdi's Requiem (Oct. 10, 1970 at the Basilica di Santa Maria sopra Minerva, in Rome) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 19:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole video is great - You should really watch the first 4:32 minutes. Many thanks for posting the link! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Piety of Marcus Aurelius (by Chris Fisher) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Homer is Like a Setting Sun (Longinus on the Odyssey) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 08:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Does the Odyssey End (and Why?) Aristarchus, Aristotle and Eustathius </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 19:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 22:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks for pointing to the other thread and your insightful comment in particular! I was not aware of that when I posted this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How We Work with Koans and How They Work on Us. Joan Sutherland, Judy Roitman, and Bodhin Kjolhede examine the practice of koan introspection, how different traditions approach it, and how the way we engage with koans is changing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 21:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the Faults People Will and Wont Admit (Epictetus, Discourses Collected by Arrian, 2.21: On Inconsistency) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 21:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jacques Maritain, Moral Philosophy: Ethics Triumphant (Stoics and Epicureans) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 23:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jacques Maritain, Moral Philosophy: Ethics Triumphant (Stoics and Epicureans) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 23:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Rolling Shutter Phenomenon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 18:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicureanism and Stoicism | Eric Gerlach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 18:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 07:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always good to read good arguments against one's opinion to refine or correct it indeed. However, in this case, when I read

 **POINT:** Say to yourself in the early morning: I shall meet today ungrateful, violent, treacherous, envious, uncharitable menI can neither be harmed by any of them, for no man will involve me in wrong, nor can I be angry with my kinsman or hate him; for we have come into the world to work together.

 **COUNTERPOINT:** Honestly, fuck you.

I think, Marcus Aurelius is perfectly right here and this "rebuttal" just proves his point (I'd add "stupid" to the list). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 23:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](http://www.faculty.umb.edu/adam_beresford/courses/phil_381_08/1_lucretius_death.pdf)

 This paper identifies two possible versions of the Epicurean 'Symmetry argument', both of which claim that *post mortem* non-existence is relevantly like prenatal non-existence and that therefore our attitude to the former should be the same as that towards the latter. One version addresses the fear of the state of being dead by making it equivalent to the state of not yet being born; the other addresses the prospective fear of dying by relating it to our present retrospective attitude to the time before birth. I argue that only the first of these is present in the relevant sections of Lucretius (DRN 3.832-42, 972-5). Therefore, this argument is not aimed at a prospective fear of death, or a fear of 'mortality'. That particular fear is instead addressed by the Epicureans through the additional premise (found in the *Letter to Menoeceus* 125) that it is irrational to fear in prospect an event which is known to be painless when present. This still leaves unaddressed the related fear of 'premature death', which is to be removed through the acceptance of Epicurean hedonism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lucretius, Symmetry Arguments, and Fearing Death | James Warren [PDF, 27 pages] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 23:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 18:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One needs tremendously low standards to call something like that a rebuttal of anything (regardless of whether Stoicism is right or wrong). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Franco Fagioli sings Haendel's Lascia Ch'io Pianga (Les Victoires de la Musique 3 Fvrier 2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 21:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyond The Dream: 7 Lesser Known Facts About Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 07:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Julia Lezhneva Speaks to Classic FM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 21:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overcoming the Faith and Science Divide by Alister McGrath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 17:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problems and Prospects for the Study of Chinese Philosophy in the English-Speaking World | Bryan W. Van Norden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 23:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Better Cope With Stress, Listen to Your Body </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 23:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> N. T. Wright on Atheism [3:14] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 20:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 10:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evangelicals are far from being a homogenous group and therefore no movie can give an accurate picture of all evangelicals within only 90 minutes. But a good movie can give an accurate picture of a certain group within the evangelicals and I think *Jesus Camp* achieves that indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 09:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Instead of getting mad at being ripped off, next time, just shrug it off, and carry on. It is a great character that forgives offenses.

Very well said! We cannot control other people's behavior, but we can control our reaction and attitude to some degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicurus and Annihilation | Stephen Rosenbaum [PDF, 11 pages] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 22:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 00:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes indeed, it certainly is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive High Heel-Shaped Church Built to Attract Women to Worship in Taiwan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 00:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epicurus and Friendship | J. Hilton Turner [PDF, 7 pages] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 23:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sviatoslav Richter plays J.S. Bach's English Suite No. 6 in D minor, BWV 811 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 07:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sviatoslav Richter: The Pianist Who Made The Earth Move (by Steve Wigler) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 23:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 22:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](http://jffp.org/ojs/index.php/jffp/article/view/599)

 This paper reconstructs Gilles Deleuzes interpretation of Epicurean atomism, and explicates his claim that it represents a problematic idea, similar to the idea exemplified in early, barbaric accounts of the differential calculus. Deleuzian problematic ideas are characterized by a mechanism through whose activity the components of the idea become determinate in relating reciprocally to one another, rather than in being determined exclusively in relation to an extrinsic paradigm or framework. In Epicurean atomism, as Deleuze reads it, such a mechanism of determination can be found in the famous atomic swerve. It is necessary to bear this interpretation of Epicurean atomism in mind when understanding Deleuze and Guattaris promulgation of a new image of thought in *What is Philosophy?*, which has an explicitly Epicurean inspiration. The paper argues that this inspiration is particularly evident to the extent that Deleuze and Guattari identify the sub-representative feature that lies at the heart of their new image of thought with chaos, defined as infinite speed. I claim that infinite speed, this otherwise puzzling feature of *What is Philosophy?*, ought to be understood in the light of Deleuzes interpretation of Epicurus. Moreover, the Epicurean distinctions between different speeds must be read together with Deleuzes appropriation of the metaphysics of the ancient Stoics, who, although widely recognized as Deleuzes Hellenistic counterparts, lack important theoretical resources that the Epicureans provide for Deleuze. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deleuze and Epicurean Philosophy: Atomic Speed and Swerve Speed | Michael James Bennett [PDF, 29 pages] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 22:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bathing in Immortality (about the oldest and largest religious festival in the world, the Kumbh Mela) | photographs by Alexandra Wey, Beat Niederer and Andre Getzmann </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 22:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Are Tibetans Setting Themselves on Fire? | Tsering Woeser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 20:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 18:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are also *link options*. I am not sure, if these two sections for filtering also work for text submissions, though. It certainly isn't perfect, but it can be improved even without using extensions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 08:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Is there some way to filter posts with non-positive karma on it?

You don't need an extension to do that, the preferences are sufficient. Just set the option *don't show me comments with a score less than* in the section *comment options* to your likings. There are more options like that, so you really should have a look at the preferences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 22:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](https://www.academia.edu/9994555/Is_Epicurean_Friendship_Altruistic)

 Epicurus is strongly committed to psychological and ethical egoism and hedonism. However, these commitments do not square easily with many of the claims made by Epicureans about friendship: for instance, that the wise man will sometimes die for his friend, that the wise man will love his friend as much as himself, feel exactly the same toward his friend as toward himself, and exert himself as much for his friend's pleasure as for his own, and that every friendship is worth choosing for its own sake. These claims have led some scholars to assert that Epicurus inconsistently affirms that friendship has an altruistic element. I argue that the Epicurean claims about friendship can be reconciled with egoism and hedonism in psychology and ethics. Friendship is valuable because having friends provides one with security more effectively than any other means, and having confidence that one will be secure in the future either is identical to ataraxia, or the grounds on which one has it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Epicurean Friendship Altruistic? | Tim O'Keefe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 22:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Claude Debussy - Images I   II (Arturo Benedetti Michelangeli) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 22:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 19:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was an interesting read! It's great to be able to find so many interesting papers and stories about Epicureanism and its exciting reception history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Vonette Zachary, co-founder of Campus Crusade for Christ, came to know Jesus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 07:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 23:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](https://www.researchgate.net/publication/276152459_The_Benefits_of_Behaving_Badly_on_Occasion_Successful_Regulation_by_Planned_Hedonic_Deviations)

 This research tests the idea that goal-pursuit that requires extended inhibition of desires, such as weight loss and financial saving, can benefit from including planned hedonic deviations in the goal-striving plan. Two controlled experiments (simulated and real dieting) demonstrate that including planned goal deviations during extended goal striving, compared with following a straight and rigid goal striving process, (1) helps regain self-regulatory resources, (2) helps maintain consumers' motivation to pursue with regulatory tasks, and (3) has a positive impact on affect experienced, which all contribute to facilitate long-term goal-adherence. A third study, conducted with current goal-strivers provides further evidence of the benefits of planned hedonic deviations for goal pursuit across a variety of goals. This reveals that it may be beneficial for long-term goal-success to occasionally be bad, as long it is planned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Benefits of Behaving Badly on Occasion: Successful Regulation by Planned Hedonic Deviations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 23:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 20:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please add me, I am not a bot. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 21:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10902-006-9037-y)

 Confucianism, Buddhism and Taoism are three main classic Chinese philosophy schools, which all deal with the question of how one should live. In this paper, we first review these ancient recommendations and next consider whether they promise a happy life in present-day society. Recommended behaviours found in the ancient texts are compared with conditions for happiness as observed in present-day empirical investigations. Classic Confucianism appears to offer the most apt advice for finding happiness in present-day society, in particular because it recommends that one should be involved in real life. Classic Taoist advice is second best: its strong point is that it advises us against too much social conformism and bookishness. The advice given by classic Buddhists is better not followed in modern society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Chinese philosophical advice: can it help us find happiness today? | Guoqing Zhang, Ruut Veenhoven </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 21:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 21:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Abstract**](http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs10902-006-9036-z)

 Epicurus was a philosopher who lived in Greece in the 3rd century B.C. Like his contemporaries, he was much concerned with the question of how to live a good life. In his view the Chief Good is to decrease pain and increase pleasure. Though Epicurus is reputed for advocating the pursuit of refined sensorial pleasures, he recognized the need for deferring gratification or enduring pain. He advised his followers to lead a modest and contemplative life in friendly communities. His advice can be characterized as serene hedonism. This paper explains that position and considers its applicability for the present day. It concludes that Epicureanism was quite accurate in describing the conditions of happiness and that he offered valuable guidelines in dealing with hardship and difficult emotional content. His ideas that happiness is the same as the absence of pain and that one should withdraw from society are less fortunate. It made him assume that happiness automatically follows if one is in the right state of mind, and that there is no need to actively seek interaction with the environment for the betterment of the circumstances of life. However, Epicurus advice might have been a good option for his contemporaries given the societal turmoil in his times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happiness in the Garden of Epicurus | Ad Bergsma, Germaine Poot, Aart C. Liefbroer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 21:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How it became so easy to ignore the poor. Growing income inequality and economic segregation have insulated our privilege </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 17:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I learned about pleasure and happiness from Epicurean philosophy | Dale Davidson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 23:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Splendors of the Dead: The Greeks from Agamemnon to Alexander the Great | Garry Wills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 22:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 21:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Message* has already been suggested, but you may also have a look at the *New Living Translation*, the *Contemporary English Version* and the *Good News Translation*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 21:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's only for the New Testament I think

Eugene H. Peterson, the translator of *The Message*, translated the complete bible (that is, the Protestant canon). The New Testament was completed in 1993, the Old Testament in 2002. It can be read online [here](https://www.biblegateway.com/versions/Message-MSG-Bible/) at BibleGateway.com. It is a very idiomatic translation indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While many American teenagers hold a positive opinion of the Bible, most don't regularly read it, according to survery results released by the American Bible Society </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 09:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 08:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is certainly impossible to distinguish wanted from unwanted submissions both automatically and reliably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 18:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We shall not forget a similar passage (Isaiah 65:17 KJV):

 For, behold, I create new heavens and a new earth: and the former shall not be remembered, nor come into mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ludwig van Beethoven: Violin Concerto in D major, Op 61 (David Oistrakh, Stockholm Festival Orchestra, Sixten Ehrling) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 18:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Old Testament Told in Only 5 Minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 18:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the mouth of the Lord hath spoken it: The real meaning of Handels Messiah (by Albert Mohler) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 11:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 11:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lots of high quality subreddits do similar things, e.g., /r/askhistorians.

Are we talking about personal messages or public replies? /r/AskHistorians does not do the latter which I assumed to be what /u/sleeps_with_crazy suggested and that's what I'd consider annoying. I am ok with personal messages.

However, I don't think personal messages are the reason for the quality of /r/AskHistorians anyway. The moderation of that sub does an excellent job and I don't see any other way than that to ensure quality. Thus, we have arrived at:

 you can't force absent moderators to moderate.

There may be people who like being active moderators instead or in addition to inactive members of the current team.

 Accounts should have to be at least a few months old with activity elsewhere on the site.

I think this is way too long. I'd suggest two weeks to be allowed to post replies and a reasonable number of comments and a certain amount of comment karma in this sub to be allowed to post submissions. And one should need a verified email. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 09:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things not belonging to this sub will continue to be posted here with and without that automatic reply by the AutoMod. The really big change is that people posting good content would be annoyed by the AutoMod, too.

A better solution may be a more active moderation which deletes such submissions with a comment similar to the text of the sidebar:

 Homework problems, practice problems, and similar questions should be directed to /r/learnmath, /r/homeworkhelp or /r/cheatatmathhomework. Do not **ask or answer** this type of question in /r/math.

And it may be helpful to simply not answer these kind of questions more consequently than it is the case now.

A sub can be configured such that submissions from brand new accounts are impossible. This may be helpful, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family Ties   Buddhist Nuns in Tang China | Jinhua Chen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 09:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 00:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Earning a lot of money certainly is not bad *per se*, it basically depends on how one earns money and what one uses it for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fleecing the Flock: A Snapshot of Americas Richest Pastors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 00:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic Epistemology | G. J. Mattey, University of California Davis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 22:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Never Get Angry: 3 New Secrets From Neuroscience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 22:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weirdest Stephen King Moments That Could Never be Adapted to Film (by Nat Brehmer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 21:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Johannes Brahms: Violin Concerto in D major, Op 77 (David Oistrakh, Cleveland Orchestra, George Szell) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 17:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 17:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can't manage getting in a *long tube with a bunch of demons*. Is this really real? If the Onion posted that, everyone would call that ridiculous. Reality beats satire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 11:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! These lecture notes about Stoicism and Epicureanism are excellent indeed and I am quite happy that I've found them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic Ethics | G. J. Mattey, University of California Davis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 08:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bronislaw Huberman plays Max Bruch's Kol Nidrei, op. 47 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 23:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stoic Physics | G. J. Mattey, University of California Davis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 23:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
