<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK government integration expert says she 'wants to see faces' of Muslim police officers and midwives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 13:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Power of psychedelic drugs to lift mental distress shown in trials: 'In 80% of cases, patients distress was lifted and remained so for six to eight months.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 03:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin: "Good luck" * click * 

and thus a retired CIA agent goes on a rampage... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno...the article says 

 U. S. President-elect Donald Trump paid a visit to the 93-year-old strategist after he won the election.

and then this visit to China by Kissinger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceland's Pirate Party invited to form government: Iceland held a snap legislative election on 29 October but no party gained a clear majority </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Norway urges Donald Trump to announce clear policy on Russia amid fears of military activity in Arctic: They have been re-establishing their 'bastion' defence concept, she told Reuters, referring to the Soviet Union's Cold War strategy of heavily defending maritime areas such as the Barents Sea. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 02:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German universities to reintroduce tuition fees for non-EU students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Journal article

http://jop.sagepub.com/content/30/12/1163.full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Power of psychedelic drugs to lift mental distress shown in trials: In 1970 US authorities said drugs like LSD had no medical use, but two tests may just have proven that wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 16:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The $40m 'magic pipe'- Princess Cruises given record fine for dumping oil at sea: Caribbean Princess discharged thousands of gallons of polluted bilge waste along British coast, while other ships used rigged sensors to hide contamination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 07:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The $40m 'magic pipe' - Princess Cruises given record fine for dumping oil at sea: Caribbean Princess discharged thousands of gallons of polluted bilge waste along British coast, while other ships used rigged sensors to hide contamination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 07:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denmark deports woman for begging for the first time: Court sentences woman to 40 days in prison before she is expelled from the country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI Just Gained Sweeping New Hacking Powers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI Just Gained Sweeping New Hacking Powers: ...'judges will be able to issue warrants that allow the FBI to remotely access electronic devices anywhere in the United States and possibly even abroad.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI Just Gained Sweeping New Hacking Powers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 18:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hourly parking in London costs more than the National Living Wage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia passes bill to detain terrorists indefinitely </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Shkreli downplays efforts of Sydney Grammar students who have recreated the active ingredient in his company's expensive Daraprim HIV drug for just $20. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 15:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German spy arrested over Islamist bombing plot also a gay porn actor: Politician says episode is 'bizarre' and 'scary' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 14:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catholic Church fined for overstating number of members to receive more state funding in Norway: Diocese of Oslo faces accusations of adding immigrants with Catholic names to member list without their knowledge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Testing begins on new vaccine that could be 'final nail in the coffin' for HIV: Researchers excited by 'historic' drug trial that could lead to HIV prevention drug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 16:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tobacco firms fail to stop UK introduction of plain packaging: Court of appeal rejects companies latest attempt to block rules that will force them to remove distinctive branding from packs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Slow, Painful Death of the TPP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 14:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fearing Trump intrusion the entire internet will be backed up in Canada to tackle censorship: The Internet Archive is seeking donations to achieve this feat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 14:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.nature.com/articles/srep37018 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seemingly peaceful gorillas join 'mobs' and beat up rivals: A surprising series of observations of mountain gorillas in Africa's Virunga Mountains has overturned the view that gorillas, like bonobos, rarely turn violent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German arms company Heckler   Koch to no longer supply undemocratic, corrupt countries: The move would rule out arms deals with Saudi Arabia, Mexico, Brazil, India and even Nato member Turkey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sturgeon confirms Scottish talks on free abortions for Northern Irish women: Women from the province, where there are strict curbs on terminations, currently refused free abortions on mainland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comcast Takes Heat For Injecting Messages Into Internet Traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 16:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela's currency now worth so little shopkeepers weigh vast piles of notes instead of counting them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela's currency now worth so little shopkeepers weigh vast piles of notes instead of counting them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 22:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 18:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barbaric practice in a city that the world one helped to rebuilt after the 2004 Indian Ocean earthquake caused a tsunami that devastated the city and killed thousands - sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Higher water temperatures in 2016 caused the worst destruction of corals ever recorded on Australia's Great Barrier Reef, a study has found. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Higher water temperatures in 2016 caused the worst destruction of corals ever recorded on Australia's Great Barrier Reef, a study has found </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nestl and Coca-Cola Attempt to Block National Parks From Banning Bottled Water Sales: Plastic bottles are a huge part of the waste littering America's national parks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 07:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Standing Rock Water Protectors Get Ready for Stand Off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 07:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Koreas Trump Rises in Polls as Voter Anger Fuels Populism: 'Lee Jae-myung wants to break up the countrys biggest companies, meet unconditionally with NK leader Kim Jong Un, and throw President Park Geun-hye in jail over an influence-peddling scandal.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 05:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Class-Action Lawsuit Adds to ExxonMobil's Climate Change Woes: Investors allege Exxon should have adjusted its accounting of oil reserves based on what it knows about climate change and coming climate action. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 03:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Government Uses Aid Money to Back Oil Drilling in UNESCO World Heritage Site: 'The Foreign Office pledged thousands of pounds in aid to support drilling in Lake Malawi, where the UN warns that a spill could wreck the fragile ecosystem' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Government Uses Aid Money to Back Oil Drilling in UNESCO World Heritage Site: 'The Foreign Office pledged thousands of pounds in aid to support drilling in Lake Malawi, where the UN warns that a spill could wreck the fragile ecosystem' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI Hacked Over 8,000 Computers In 120 Countries Based on One Warrant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The FBI Hacked Over 8,000 Computers In 120 Countries Based on One Warrant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 02:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A church that was essentially disguised as a coffee shop was denied tax exempt status by the IRS because  wait for it  it too closely resembled an actual money-making coffee shop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana advocates sceptical about Canada path to legal pot: "It's the government's intention to legalise it. So why is the government still arresting people?" asks advocate Marc Emery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 16:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Earlier this month, Mr Rao caused consternation by announcing plans to destroy the state government complex due to it being "unlucky" and erecting a new one at the cost of 42m. 

So.. not contented with a new home that has a bullet-proof bathroom he also want a brand new office - at taxpayer's expense, of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A senior Indian politician has caused outrage by building a large mansion including a bullet-proof bathroom using 5.8m of taxpayer money. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five member states want EU-wide laws on encryption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an ominous report, researchers warn that as many as 19 various 'tipping points' could be triggered by the increasingly warm temperatures in the world's northern polar region. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 17:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ms Park, whose five-year term ends in February 2018, has apologised twice over the affair, but is resisting calls to resign.

 Her disapproval rating rose three percentage points to 93 per cent, according to a poll by Gallup Korea, which is not affiliated with the US-based Gallup, Inc.

93% disapprove of her and she's still hanging on? I thought resigning as a matter of honour is a highly valued principle in South Korean culture such as the case of the [daughter of Korean Air chief who resigned after kicking out stewardess over bag of nuts](http://www.scmp.com/news/asia/article/1658222/actions-daughter-chairman-korean-air-lines-being-investigated) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A UK academic is campaigning against sex robots, arguing they are dehumanising, isolating and will encourage people to consider women as property. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 16:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an ominous report, researchers warn that as many as 19 various 'tipping points' could be triggered by the increasingly warm temperatures in the world's northern polar region. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 15:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump is going to do to you Muslims what Hitler did to the Jews: California mosque threatened </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 14:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hundreds of thousands protest for fifth straight week against South Korean President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 14:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Supreme Court Pick Would Criminalize Gay Sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 14:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jerusalems Top Rabbi - Homosexuality Punishable By Death': Outrage grows after top rabbi says the Torah demands death penalty for gays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 01:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google is warning prominent journalists and professors that nation-sponsored hackers have recently targeted their accounts, according to reports delivered in the past 24 hours over social media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Netflix tax" may be coming soon to your bill: Pasadena city has a 9.4 percent tax on streaming video. Theyre calling it a utility, so it can be taxed like water and electricity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German court rules cops can have breast implants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 16:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The number of young people who want to leave the UK has doubled since Brexit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 15:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 03:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pasadena City Councilman Tyron Hampton says the surprise tax was designed to make up for lost tax revenue from people getting rid of cable TV and home phones.  

Is that how this works - lose revenue here, tax something else there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Netflix tax" may be coming soon to your bill: Pasadena city has a 9.4 percent tax on streaming video. Theyre calling it a utility, so it can be taxed like water and electricity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 03:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Netflix tax" may be coming soon to your bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 03:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge criticised for sympathising with 'nubile' 14-year-old's sex attacker because he was 'not made of steel' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 15:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the world's most unequal countries revealed in one chart: Global Wealth Report 2016 identified Russia as the worlds most unequal country, with a staggering 74.5% of the nations wealth controlled by the richest 1% of people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 18:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter Says Its API Can't Be Used For Surveillance, But What Does It Think The FBI's Going To Do With It? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla powers a whole island with solar to show off its energy chops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla powers a whole island with solar to show off its energy chops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 17:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Potential gold-import ban by India could be biggest bombshell since Nixon 'shocked the world by taking the dollar off the gold standard' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hopes for new Alzheimer's drug dashed: Patients on solanezumab did not show any slowing in cognitive decline compared to those treated with a placebo, or dummy drug. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 16:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AT T responded to the FCC this week in a letter that tries to claim that giving its own content an unfair advantage is somehow good for consumers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American-Born Panda Twins Have Trouble Adjusting To Life In China: The pandas cant understand Chinese and dont want to eat the local food. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 16:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 80,000 Reindeer Have Starved To Death In Siberia Because Of Melting Sea Ice: Add them to the growing list of animals directly threatened by climate change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 15:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesco accused of discriminating against state school children by making them queue outside a store while private school pupils can come and go as they please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 14:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creationist Ken Ham: Science is Silly Because It Changes Over Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 12:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time to decriminalize drugs, commission report says: 'Global Commission on Drug Policys annual report recommended that countries should end civil and criminal penalties for drug use and possession' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doctors face prosecution over genital cosmetic surgery in London clinics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Government Confirm Move to Force ISPs into Blocking Adult Sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 14:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Government Confirm Move to Force ISPs into Blocking Adult Sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 13:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked map reveals chronic mercury epidemic in Peru: People living upriver from gold-mining are the most contaminated, according to US-based scientists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 14:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russias foreign ministry spokeswoman claims the Jews knew Donald Trump would win the US election. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 13:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk says the solar roof that will be sold under a combined Tesla-SolarCity will likely cost less than a normal roof to install. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 13:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk says the solar roof that will be sold under a combined Tesla-SolarCity will likely cost less than a normal roof to install. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 13:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archbishop of Canterbury, Justin Welby: It's time to stop saying Isis has nothing to do with Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippine President Duterte met the man he calls his hero, Russian President Putin, and unburdened his gripes about US "hypocrisy," "bullying" and foreign wars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifteen years of decriminalised drug policy: Portugal treats addicts as patients, not as criminals, after 15 years of decriminalised drug policy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 04:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rise of proudly-neo-Nazi party unnerves a European nation: 'Kotleba - The Peoples Party Our Slovakia - won almost 10 percent of the seats in Parliament in March. It openly admires the Nazi puppet state which the country was during the World War II' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 02:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scotland considering offering Northern Irish women free abortions, Nicola Sturgeon says: Last year, a high court ruled Northern Ireland's abortion ban is a breach of human rights legislation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 02:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 02:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Radha Stirling, the founder of Detained in Dubai, told the Independent that Dubai police assumed Western women were "looking for it".

 She said: "There is the social perception that if a woman drinks alcohol, she has consented to it.

 "And theres also a racist mentality of thinking, Shes British so she was probably drunk and asking for it.

 "We get people contacting us asking whether they should report a crime and  whether it be a rape or anything else  I often say no," she said. "Absolutely not."

Dubai - the 22nd most expensive cities in the world with one of the most expensive hotel rooms in the world and one of the best places to live in the ME.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brits urged not to report Dubai crimes after 'gang-raped' woman arrested for extra-marital sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 01:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brits urged not to report Dubai crimes after 'gang-raped' woman arrested for extra-marital sex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 01:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 50 countries vow to use 100% renewable energy by 2050: The signatories are countries who are disproportionately affected by global warming such as Ethiopia and the Maldives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 00:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 50 countries vow to use 100% renewable energy by 2050: The signatories are countries who are disproportionately affected by global warming such as Ethiopia and the Maldives </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turkish bill clears men of statutory rape if they marry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scotland considers legally enshrining the 'right to food': '...it would mean the Government and other public bodies would have a duty to ensure everyone has secure access to adequate and affordable food.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 14:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Citizens across the world are suing their governments over climate change: a group of American youths officially won the right to sue the United States government for failing to curb climate change </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand quake - preacher under fire over homosexuals claim: An online petition calling for the church to be classed as a hate group and lose its tax-free status has been signed by 100,000 people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 15:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paris climate deal ratified by UK: Theresa May signs up to landmark agreement | The Prime Minister 'can be proud that she is upholding Mrs Thatcher's tradition of basing climate policies on scientific evidence' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 15:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have discovered a new way to edit DNA that could fix broken genes in the brain, cure previously incurable diseases and potentially even extend the human lifespan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 00:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ken Ham, Who Spent $100 Million on Noahs Ark Park, Says We Shouldnt Waste Money Studying Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 22:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the first time ever, a patient will fight lung cancer with CRISPR-edited cells: it involved editing immune cells from a patient with aggressive lung cancer and then injecting them back into the patient to help defeat the disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australia's dirtiest power station to close: One of the world's dirtiest power plants, the coal-fired Hazelwood station in Australia, is to close in March of next year. The plant has been in operation since the 1960s, with environmentalists welcoming its demise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 16:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New supersonic jet faster than Concorde unveiled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese company installed secret backdoor on hundreds of thousands of phones: In mistake, AdUps collected data from BLU Android phones in US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese company installed secret backdoor on hundreds of thousands of phones: In mistake, AdUps collected data from BLU Android phones in US. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alaska Airlines made history flying the first commercial flight using the worlds first renewable, alternative jet fuel made from forest residuals, the limbs and branches that remain after the harvesting of managed forests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global climate change action 'unstoppable' despite Trump: UNs Ban Ki-moon expresses hopes that the US president-elect will drop plans to quit a global accord aimed at weaning the world off fossil fuels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 17:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria's food production edging nearer to collapse, UN warns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 16:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Isis commander calls Donald Trump a 'complete maniac' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 11:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hydroelectric dams emit a billion tonnes of greenhouse gases a year, study finds: Impact of dams on climate change has been underestimated, researchers warn, as rotting vegetation creates 25% more methane than previously thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2,500 year old mummy found in 'very good' condition: The body was bound with linen stuck together with plaster in a brightly-coloured wooden sarcophagus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Article: 

http://bioscience.oxfordjournals.org/content/early/2016/10/02/biosci.biw117.full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hydroelectric dams emit a billion tonnes of greenhouse gases a year, study finds: Impact of dams on climate change has been underestimated, researchers warn, as rotting vegetation creates 25% more methane than previously thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mystery as Canadian houseboat washes up on Irish Beach: The boat is believed to have been built by eco-adventurer Rick Small, from Thunder Bay, Canada. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-thirds of the world's internet users live under government censorship - report: China ranked as the worst abuser of internet freedom for the second consecutive year, followed by Syria and Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two-thirds of the world's internet users live under government censorship - report: China ranked as the worst abuser of internet freedom for the second consecutive year, followed by Syria and Iran. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 14:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 will be the hottest year on record, UN says: It means 16 of the 17 hottest years on record will have been this century. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 12:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedish neo-Nazis stage biggest ever march in wake of Donald Trump victory: 600 far-right demonstrators from Swedens Nordic Resistance Movement clashed with anti-fascist protestors in Stockholm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 01:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change Has Already Altered Nearly Every Ecosystem on Earth: Some animals are already shrinking, as a smaller body mass helps stay cool on rapidly heating planet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 17:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook forced to apologise for censoring burn victim's birthday photo: Former fireman lost his ears, hair, and eyebrows in an explosion in the Swedish city of Gothenburg 35 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berlin likely to semi-legalize marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 14:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Berlin likely to semi-legalize marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 08:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump presidency a 'disaster for the planet', warn climate scientists: 'At the heart of his energy and climate thinking is an America first policy where draconian climate rules are repealed and the US escalates its production of coal, oil and natural gas.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 02:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disgraced former Italian Prime Minister Silvio Berlusconi has said comparisons between himself and US President-elect Donald Trump are "obvious". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 02:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Richard Dawkins and Other Prominent Scientists React to Trumps Win: Richard Dawkins urges New Zealand to offer them citizenship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 06:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appeals Court Affirms That Ten Commandments Monument Outside NM Municipal Building is Illegal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU president Jean Claude Juncker says US-EU relationship at risk after election: 'I think we will waste two years before Mr Trump tours the world he does not know.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Privacy experts fear Donald Trump running global surveillance network: Concerns raised that current US and UK surveillance system is ripe for further abuse under an autocratic, power-obsessed president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia accused of 'faking terror plot' to make them more likeable to Donald Trump: Ukraine has accused the Kremlin of inventing a terrorism plot in Crimea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 18:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTA

 It was still dark when four men boarded the packed commuter bus heading for Mexico City and ordered the passengers to hand over their valuables. They gathered up mobile phones and wallets, but as they prepared to leave near the town of Toluca, one passenger stood up, drew a pistol and shot the four assailants, killing their leader instantly.

 The three injured robbers stumbled off the bus, but the gunman followed them out and shot them dead at the roadside. Then he returned to the bus, handed back the passengers belongings and disappeared into the darkness.

 ...many Mexicans  fed up with crime, corruption and impunity  took to social media to praise the unidentified killer. None of the bus passengers have offered information to police, saying it was too dark to see him clearly.

Reminds me of those Charles Bronson movies: Death Wish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuel economy of American vehicles continues to drop: down to an average of 24.8 mpg, down 0.4 mpg since September </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 17:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico's 'avengers' backed by public sick of crime and lack of punishment: A wave of vigilante killings  such as the bus passenger who shot four robbers  has struck a chord with Mexicans fed up with crime, corruption and impunity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 16:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treatment of sex assault victim condemned after lawyers quiz her on defendant's penis size </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 15:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treatment of sex assault victim condemned after lawyers quiz her on defendant's penis size: Alexander Wagar is facing a retrial for accusations of raping a woman, now 24, in a bathroom after flashing people at a 2011 house party in Calgary, Alberta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 15:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Too Late For President Obama To 'Dismantle' The NSA's Mass Surveillance: 'Evan Greer wrote a piece asking President Obama to "shut down" the NSA's mass surveillance systems before Donald Trump gets control of it all.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 15:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red squirrels in the UK carry leprosy, scientists discover:Chances of catching disease are extremely low and those living close to the animals should not worry, researchers say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 11:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents found using bleach to 'treat' children with autism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents found using bleach to 'treat' children with autism: Substance promoted as a 'cure' for several serious diseases and conditions by a secretive church founded by a former Scientologist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Could Spell Big Trouble for Broadband, Net Neutrality: 'Trump has made it clear he vehemently opposes net neutrality, despite repeatedly making it clear he's not entirely certain what net neutrality even is.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK High Court awards 5m to aspiring model who lost memory after herpes virus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 16:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Could Spell Big Trouble for Broadband, Net Neutrality: 'Trump has made it clear he vehemently opposes net neutrality, despite repeatedly making it clear he's not entirely certain what net neutrality even is.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research article: 

http://www.nature.com/news/brain-implants-allow-paralysed-monkeys-to-walk-1.20967 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paralysed monkeys walk again after scientists fit 'brain-spine interface': 'For the first time, I can imagine a completely paralysed patient able to move their legs through this brain-spine interface' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They elected Trump; now conservatives own climate change: Anyone who voted for Trump shares the responsibility for the climate damages resulting from his presidency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Move to New Zealand? US migration inquiries rise 24-fold after Election Day: Immigration website takes strain as thousands of Americans explore their options away from a country that will be led by Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK 'flash crash' trader Navinder Sarao pleads guilty in US </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 11:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 01:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie wasn't at MLK march in Selma: 

http://www.snopes.com/sanders-mlk-selma-march/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China convicts dozens for last year's giant explosions in Tianjin: Judges have convicted 49 people for their role in explosions that took place at a chemical warehouse in the industrial port city of Tianjin in 2015. Nearly 170 people died. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The punitive California Air Resources Board (CARB) has figured out how Audi cheated on a particular run of several hundred thousand of their cars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 16:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
