<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow

I had no idea there were so many climate deniers in this sub

 anyway, This is a peer-reviewed study published in Geophysical Research Letters journal. Wikipedia says about this journal

 Geophysical Research Letters is a biweekly peer-reviewed scientific journal of geoscience published by the American Geophysical Union that was established in 1974. The editor-in-chief is Noah Diffenbaugh.

According to the Journal Citation Reports, the journal has a 2015 impact factor of 4.212.[3] Geophysical Research Letters was also the 5th most cited publication on climate change between 1999 and 2009.[4]

here's the citation, the abstract, and the plain languagesummary

http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017GL073613/full

since you feel so strongly perhaps contact the Journal and tell them they are publishing junk science. I'm sure there are avenues they have to challenge the research they publish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Environment

thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This merits additional scrutiny over the coming years.

ya think?

I mean it's only the main source of oxygen for the planet. No big deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CITATION: Takamitsu Ito, Shoshiro Minobe, Matthew C. Long and Curtis Deutsch, "Upper Ocean O2 trends: 1958-2015," (Geophysical Research Letters, April 2017). 

Abstract

Historic observations of dissolved oxygen (O2) in the ocean are analyzed to quantify multidecadal trends and variability from 1958 to 2015. Additional quality control is applied, and the resultant oxygen anomaly field is used to quantify upper ocean O2 trends at global and hemispheric scales. A widespread negative O2 trend is beginning to emerge from the envelope of interannual variability. Ocean reanalysis data are used to evaluate relationships with changes in ocean heat content (OHC) and oxygen solubility (O2,sat). Global O2 decline is evident after the 1980s, accompanied by an increase in global OHC. The global upper ocean O2 inventory (01000 m) changed at the rate of 243  124 T mol O2 per decade. Further, the O2 inventory is negatively correlated with the OHC (r = 0.86; 01000 m) and the regression coefficient of O2 to OHC is approximately 8.2  0.66 nmol O2 J1, on the same order of magnitude as the simulated O2-heat relationship typically found in ocean climate models. Variability and trends in the observed upper ocean O2 concentration are dominated by the apparent oxygen utilization component with relatively small contributions from O2,sat. This indicates that changing ocean circulation, mixing, and/or biochemical processes, rather than the direct thermally induced solubility effects, are the primary drivers for the observed O2 changes. The spatial patterns of the multidecadal trend include regions of enhanced ocean deoxygenation including the subpolar North Pacific, eastern boundary upwelling systems, and tropical oxygen minimum zones. Further studies are warranted to understand and attribute the global O2 trends and their regional expressions.

Plain Language Summary


This new paper describes the analysis of the dissolved oxygen in the global ocean using the most recent version of the World Ocean Database for the period of 1955 to 2015. After careful examination of the data, we found that a statistically significant, widespread O2 decline is emerging beyond the envelope of natural fluctuations. Our study also reveals a tight relationship between O2 inventories and the ocean heat content. The spatial pattern and magnitude of this relationship are consistent with expectations derived from mechanistic ocean climate models forced under climate warming scenarios. Taken together, the trends we document here are suggestive of the effects of the ocean warming beginning to supersede natural variability and emerge as a recognizable signal. This merits additional scrutiny over the coming years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plummeting ocean oxygen levels stun scientists. The trend of oxygen falling is about two to three times faster than what we predicted." The man-made climate change induced trend also started far earlier than scientists previously believed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, the researchers conclude, the evidence is consistent with anthropogenic warming acting as the primary driver of long-term trends in ocean O2. The trends we document are suggestive of the effects of warming beginning to supersede natural variability and emerge as a recognisable signal.

Just in case anybody wants to argue about the "man-made climate change induced trend" concept </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plummeting ocean oxygen levels stun scientists. The trend of oxygen falling is about two to three times faster than what we predicted." The man-made climate change induced trend also started far earlier than scientists previously believed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ocean oxygen levels falling much faster than predicted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://climatenewsnetwork.net/ocean-oxygen-decline-greater-predicted/

LONDON, 10 May, 2017  US scientists who have been warning that warmer oceans are more likely to be poorer in dissolved oxygen have now sounded the alarm: ocean oxygen levels are indeed falling, and seemingly falling faster than the corresponding rise in water temperature.

That colder water can hold more dissolved gas than warmer water is a commonplace of physics: it is one reason why polar seas are teeming with marine life and tropical oceans are blue, clear and often relatively impoverished.

In 2013, an international consortium of marine scientists warned that oxygen levels in the oceans could fall by between 1% and 7% by the centurys end. And this could, other scientists predicted, lead to what they politely called respiratory stress for some marine life.
Ocean warming

Ocean ecologists in the US and Germany warned last year that parts of the deep oceans were already showing signs of oxygen deprivation with corresponding dead zones.

Earlier this year, another research group looked at the computer simulations for the years 1920 to 2100 and predicted that the hazards were likely to increase with warming.

Now the team have returned to the issue. They report in Geophysical Research Letters that they looked at data for the last 50 years and found the oxygen levels started dropping in the 1980s, as ocean temperatures began to climb  and falling unexpectedly rapidly.

***The trend of oxygen falling is about two to three times faster than what we predicted from the decrease of solubility associated with ocean warming,*** says Takamitsu Ito, of the School of Earth and Atmospheric Sciences at the Georgia Institute of Technology, who led the study.

This is most likely due to the changes in ocean circulation and mixing associated with the heating of the near-surface waters and the melting of polar ice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes

Rumored intelligence. It's chatter. Taken with a grain of salt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Claude Taylor @TrueFactsStated

Just hearing back from a source on this. "Comey was ready. He anticipated this".

----------------------------------------------

 Claude Taylor @TrueFactsStated 6h6 hours ago

More RUMINT. Trump/Kushner family and associates transferring large sums of money offshore.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well FFS could this bull shit get any more complicated?

anyway, just give guns to everybody and sooner or later they will all be dead. Seems to be the American philosophy

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this doesn't seem to download properly.

I download it, and it gives me the window that says "allow this app to make changes on your computer." So I hit "yes" and then Nothing. Nothing happens after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, I downloaded that and it says "the tool was unable to resolve the issue."

the other one doesn't seem to be downloading properly for some weird reason. I'll try again

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you,

how do I determine if I have 64-bit?

 EDIT: nevermind, yes I'm running 64-bit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> helloooooooooooooooooooo

Is there anybody out there?

Can anybody hear me?

Is there anybody there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this a better strategy to take here?

https://answers.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/forum/windows_10-windows_install/error-another-instance-is-running-configuration/eef22430-066b-4e61-ac21-ce14703ddd45

That's actually the complete error message I'm getting

"Another instance is running Configuration System failed to initialize" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLEASE help me with this problem "configuration system failed to initialize" in Windows 10. Google is not helping me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep getting this error message "configuration system failed to initialize" at random times and sometimes my computer crashes. I am obviously not the only person who this is happening to. However, when I Google it I get all kinds of different answers and all kinds of different suggestions on what to do.

https://www.drivereasy.com/knowledge/configuration-system-failed-to-initialize-windows-10-solved/

I did the first thing suggested in that link above. But it did nothing.

Seriously, when I googled this I get so many different responses. I don't know what to do. Please help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the 58% is the percentage of **voting age** millennials who turned out.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 2 Months

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay?

And?

are millenniums actually getting GET OFF THEIR ASS and vote?

Or are they just going to continue to whine about it onlinewhile refusing to actually vote?

Because if it's the latter I don't want to hear about it.

Millennial voter turnout for the 2016 presidential race was 58%. That's abysmal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.

The show is a tragedy. Breaking that was a tragedy also.

Both shows are about people who try really hard to screw up their lives on an epic level and succeed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is no doubt Kim is going to experience SERIOUS blowback because of her relationship with Jimmy

It's actually tragic because you know it's coming, you just don't know when it's coming. Plus, she seems to be a pretty awesome person, the only person in the whole show doesn't deserve being shit on, and yet that  will happen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here's the thing though Chuck really IS sick!

It's just that he has a mental illness instead of actual physical illness.

And mental illnesses can be  much much worse than physical illnesses!

In other words, he's not  faking it, he's just confused as to what is true illness is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very curious about this too. Sounds like a bizarre way to do business!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow!

Never heard of this guy, but he's super interesting! He was one of the founders of the biomedical engineering industry. He also built Israel's first rocket, although he never talked about it, even to his closest family members.

But also very spiritual. Unique person, thank you for posting this.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Itzhak_Bentov </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so?

Still throw the ball away. You don't take a sack </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be Frank here.

the pizza gate thing was dumb as hell, but That spirit cooking thing was legitimately creepy as hell. I mean, the woman is literally talking about the difference between a real Satanic black magic ritual and one done simply for art. Not to mention the whole realistic dead bodies that were meant to look like sacrifices.

I'm sure I will get down voted for this opinion, but seriously I thought it was creepy and disturbing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even saying they should not have attempted a pass. I'm just saying that Matt should not have taken a sack right there, and he is a veteran and should really know that. You throw the freaking ball away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Falcons lost the Super Bowl because Matt freaking Ryan took a sack that destroyed their chance at a game clinching field goal.

That is literally the one play that cost you guys the Super Bowl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> meh, not buying they can get that lucky that many times.

But whatever, I know a lot of people is simply can't even entertain the notion that pointspreads could be fixed so I don't talk about it much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this happens a SUSPICIOUSLY large amount of times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds very difficult, very challenging.

The thing is You MUST care for yourself. The dark circles under your eyes are due from lack of sleep. You need to schedule a really good nights sleep. Maybe use a melatonin or another sleep aid.

As for your mother, spend as much quality time as you can with her. Tell her you love her, say everything you need to say to her. when her time comes, give her permission to go. I personally believe we will all meet again in the afterlife

One thing that has really helped me come to terms with death has been studying near-death experiences. There are really some absolutely wonderful uplifting beautiful experiences people have.

maybe this will help reading some of these for you?

http://www.nderf.org/Archives/exceptional.html

I wish you the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the ancient legends suggest it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or Here's a concept!

A DB who can Wait for it ACTUALLY cover a tight end out of the backfield!

Can you imagine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bahaha!

classic bait and switch right there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> get this book for him 

"no more mr nice guy" by rob glover 

excellent book! it will really help him. seriously, this book is EXACTLY what hee needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thinking more pointed question to ask is - is MONEY the one and only important thing in the universe?

is money the one and only thing that really matters in life? Because we modern Americans seem more and more to think so.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No politician will ever be perfect. 

You have completely and totally missed my point.

My point is that Hillary Clinton is NOT a left-wing candidate! I am a left-wing person. I would like to vote for a left-wing candidate. I don't care if they're perfect. I just would like to have an actual real-life left-wing candidate to choose from. But really, we don't right now. at all.

Hillary Clinton is a warmongering, corrupt, center-right politician. She is NOT left-wing. Not even remotely.

the republicans throw out some baseless claims of corruption (which she was cleared of),

lol, you can't be serious. Her whole foundation was nothing but a money-laundering scheme. It was a means to allow anybody, ***including foreign government officials***, to "donate" to her, in order to influence her policies. Of course none of these were donations, they were BRIBES.

Yes, she was and is a very corrupt politician. I stand by that. is/was She more corrupt than Donald Trump? Probably not. But so what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, I've been saying this for a long time. The Democratic Party is absolutely 100% pathetic

They are a lame, half assed pathetic excuse for a "leftist" party. Which in fact they're not leftist. They are center-right. It is no left party in America anymore. It's been destroyed by corporate interests and the right wing.

The sooner America wakes up and realizes this, the better off we all will be.

I mean, the best the Democratic Party could do was Hillary freaking Clinton, a fantastically corrupt out of touch war hawk who ran possibly the worst campaign in American history.

The Democratic Party either needs to be reformed or abandoned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you!

Book and TV series Two different things! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read the books at all and I loved it.

some people are complaining It was confusing I wasn't confused at all. I mean there are a ton of unanswered questions, but that's to be expected

then again, I like shows whereyou don't really know what's going on rright away. Keeps me interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes I love pushing daisies.

Really too bad about that show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am absolutely LOVING the look and feel of 'American Gods'. The color palette, lighting, the mood, and the cinematography are all fantastic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> let's face it, most TV shows have very standard lighting. One TV show pretty much looks like the next when it comes to lighting.

But American gods is very different. Lots of deep shadows, lots of dark contrasts, and I love it.

The cinematography is something you would expect from a high budget film, rather than from a TV show.

(Slight spoiler) . The scene where the black lady devours that poor son of a bitch in bed, then it cuts to that beautiful tracking shot in the bar where you are inside an enormous alligator mouth with enormous white teeth. They are telling you You are inside the belly of the beast. Beautiful filming.

The blood is over-the-top bright red and gushing out in ridiculously large volumes. it is such a stark contrast to the otherwise subdued color palette.

the show has a very unique feel to it, and I really appreciate that because it's rare and hard to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Facebook thing felt natural, but the Arby's thing felt very forced. Did not like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the thing that's bugging me The gluing of the mouth closed.

Why would that fuck up who got hired to steal the stamp glue that old man's mouth closed?

It doesn't make any sense! Seems like there's more going on here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> easily my favorite episode so far.

I've been complaining that season 3 so far has been too derivative of season two, but definitely not this episode! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just look at his reporting. He absolutely hounded Ted Thompson for every mistake he made, while refusing to give him credit for all of the Smart moves he made.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he really did have a vendetta against Ted Thompson

People who deny that are denying reality. He was unrelentingly negative towards every move Ted Thompson made.

However, his scouting contacts were phenomenal. So for me it was both good and bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, got it.

Thank you very much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm right there with you.

He's good at what he does, excellent even. However, his relentless negativity got to be old, and in some cases was even bizarre.

It just seems like he started hating Ted Thompson and looking for any reason to crap on him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is that what they're serving?

I can't really tell from that article </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> casual fan checking in!

Is that good Or bad?

I literally don't know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ghee = clarified butter.

Regular butter will be just fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love curried red cabbage

slice cabbage in thin strips, fry it up with olive oil, salt to taste, and curry powder.

yummy!

Add a bit of ghee to make it extra delicious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Northside right now is currently underpriced relative to real estate in the Madison market.

in my personal opinion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is going to be VERY interesting to see how well it does. That area basically has zero foot traffic, since Oscar Meyer plant hogs most of the space.

Also, if you haven't seen this new development it's actually a very attractive with classic looking architecture. I like it

Maple Bluff is a good target market, but Thompson said he's really focusing on the North Side in general, and even outlying northern communities like Waunakee.

That's nice and all, but it sounds like this thing is going to be very expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a result of the changes, global sea levels are set to rise faster than previously thought. The new estimates are almost double those previously made by the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change in 2013. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IPCC UNDERESTIMATED sea level rise significantly. Sea level rise estimates in IPCC report are now obsolete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/major-report-prompts-warnings-that-the-arctic-is-unraveling1/

The report increases projections for global sea-level rise, which takes into account all sources of melting including the Arctic. Their new minimum estimates are now almost double those issued by the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) in 2013 for some emissions scenarios. In fact, the latest calculations suggest that the IPCC's middle estimates for sea-level rise should now be considered minimum estimates.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. That makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  OKC isn't the worst place

this should be their motto right there!

"Oklahoma - there are worse places to be!"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, I wondered if he's using it as a preservative.

Although he claims that he makes it fresh daily. So </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wwell, that could be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   It will also create enormous opportunity for those with the capital and management platforms to feed on the carnage.

lol, capitalism at its finest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tthat was directly in the wake of the 2008 economic crash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, I think you make some good points </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people have been saying that retail stores are going out of business at record rates for the last 10 years?

I don't think so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adding citric acid to hummus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching DD   D , and they were at a Lebanese restaurant in Minneapolis. I think it was called The temple Or something?

anyway, they showed the owner making the hummus. He put all of the usual suspects in like tahini, garbanzo beans, lemon, garlic, oil, And then he added citric acid.

I have never seen or heard of anybody adding citric acid to hummus.

Has anybody tried this, or heard of it before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the job loss from the retail collapse has really only begun in earnest. Very recently.

Those numbers have not been reflected in unemployment figures from the government. Yet. But they will be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The retail apocalypse is creating a 'slow-rolling crisis' that is rippling through the US economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The retail apocalypse is creating a 'slow-rolling crisis' that is rippling through the US economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am right now very bearish on the US economy. This is an underreported story that is actually really really big news. Retailers are going bankrupt at record pace Right now, and nobody is talking about it.

As they go bankrupt they are shedding employees left and right. These are low skilled employees, when they get let go of retail, and there are no other retail jobs to go to, they are screwed!

this is going to have cascading effects across the entire economy.

http://www.businessinsider.com/retail-job-losses-are-hurting-the-economy-2017-4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an underreported story that is actually really really big news. Retailers are going bankrupt at record pace. Right now, and nobody is talking about it.

As they go bankrupt they are shedding employees left and right. These are low skilled employees, when they get let go of retail, and there are no other retail jobs to go to, they are screwed!

this is going to have cascading effects across the entire economy. The near future for the US economy is very tenuous right now, and nobody is talking about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The retail apocalypse is creating a 'slow-rolling crisis' that is rippling through the US economy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly, it's just a rreally sad situation. Really wish the OP all the luck in the world dealing with it. Sounds difficult. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean Sure. Counseling is always a good idea.

But this woman forged a deceptive mask and wore that mask for YEARS, in order to manipulate her husband into marriage and kids. Then she rips off the mask and reveals that she's been lying and deceiving. The whole time and she thinks OP's beloved brother is nothing but a pathetic interloper that should be discarded immediately.

then she acts like nothing is wrong, and she wants to have another kid

I do not believe there is any counseling strategy that can get over that. What on earth is a counselor going to say to move past that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so Tedy "somehow everything is about the patriots" Bruschi still has a job, but Jaws doesn't?

Give me a freaking break  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he is a psychopath.

it's hilarious how people think he's nice or a good guy or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some people are functionally blind, but they can still see, although very poorly.

So if possible that with the audio and with their limited vision, they can still make out what's going on in a movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because the kid can't learn the playbook and he bounces around like a billiard ball on crack instead of following his blockers

dude has all the talent in the world but he just can't put it all together
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's the only old timey money denominations I could think of.

lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well? Was it exhilarating? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zen master learns how to levitate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a Zen student read about the ancient Masters and how they learned superhuman abilities. He decided he would learn how to levitate.

For years and years and years he worked at learning how to levitate. After 30 years he finally succeeded. One day the Buddha came to visit his village. He was overjoyed. He ran up to the Buddha and told him he wanted to show him something. He sat on the edge of the river, levitated up, levitated over the River and to the next bank.

He opened his eyes and waited for the Buddhas reaction.

"That's nice But the ferry is only 20 shillings." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no worries  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have a link to this 600 K literal shack?

Would love to see that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> next he should do a commentary on that one movie "live by night"!

"Holy crap. These people just keep talking and talking and talking I mean, they're gangsters for fucks sake! shoot somebody! have a car chase! Who made this boring drivel Oh Right Me" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Santa Cruz syndrome" - $1.2 million for broke down shack that used to be a meth lab?

What a bargain! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really? lots?

Other than Rivers, name a few </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm quite the opposite of worried, actually. Succeeding in this league with a poor throwing motion is not impossible, however, it makes life that much more difficult.

Now, if he sits for a year or two and they rework his throwing motion Then yes. maybe he will be really good? Anything is possible. otherwise, I do not think he will amount to much of anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you remember Rogers' mechanics and scouting reports pre-draft?

Excellent point! And this is why Mike McCarthy doesn't get the credit he deserves for completely deconstructing and rebuilding Rodgers' throwing motion.

He sat for several years  while Mike rebuilt his form and turned him into the greatest quarterback in the history of the league. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rivers is also freakishly tall with long arms, which really helps, 

Mitch is not quite as tall or long

Also, saying, "neither throwing motion is better or worse" is just wrong. There really is such a thing as optimal throwing motions, if only from the physics standpoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> look at every single throw He makes in that video. Every single throw is the same kind of throwing motion. If you can find an example of him using optimal throwing motion I would really like to see it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know, ask Ryan Pace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is what I noticed about Mitch Trubisky's throwing motion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mitch cocks back his arm and launches the ball from his shoulder area. You can see very plainly what I am talking about in this video

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UhWz8SGetFM feature=youtu.be

Now compare this to drew brees' throwing motion. Look at exactly the 12 second mark on this video. Look how high his hand is above his shoulder when he releases the ball.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ngel-VlrgAk

Brees has nearly perfect form. That is how you should throw the ball. Rogers and Brady throw it very similar. Why is this good form?

In a word: physics. think about a 1 pound rock being thrown from a catapult with a 3 foot long arm. Now think about the same rock being thrown from a catapult with a 9 foot long arm. Obviously, the rock is going to go further with the 9 foot long arm

The longer you extend your arm before releasing the ball, the more velocity and power the ball will have on it

Now it's not impossible to succeed in the NFL with Mitch's throwing motion. Philip Rivers comes to mind as somebody who launches it from the shoulder and has been successful in doing that. However! It is not the optimal method of throwing the football.

to read more up on throwing motions Here's a good article, which backs up my point.

http://www.authorityfootball.com/x-and-o-labs-and-the-quarterback-mechanic/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about their history of systematically protecting child rapists from prosecution? 

It's actually much worse than that. They were ***actively running a pedophile ring*** for several decades, at least, possibly several centuries. It is a sin monstrous proportions that the Catholic Church hasn't even begun to make up for yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, well!

I'm certainly glad to know I am "only" one flavor of heretic But certainly not a different flavor of heretic! I'm only mildly heretical. Apparently,

And I'm really glad the Catholic Church has these convoluted distinctions So the rest of us paupers understand where we stand in God's eyes
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the ending was pretty good , yes

But I never really felt emotionally invested in any of the characters at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben has been fucking whores in Las Vegas for years now. I'm not sure he really cares that much about his marriage. Although the divorce is off again Apparently. Jennifer can't leave it alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which is weird because he spent a lot of time making that movie and allegedly it was his baby </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes!

Here's the thing, as soon as you get them wet, all of those little stingers are not a problem anymore. But yes DEFINITELY beware of the stingers when you're harvesting them, best thing is to wear leather gloves

Also nettles are INCREDIBLY nutritious. Very high in all of the vital mineral the human body needs, iron, calcium, potassium, etc. a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if it wasn't a Star Wars movie Everybody would've already forgotten.

What is hilarious is that all of these Star Wars fan boys around here can't seem to understand that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> live by night was just plain boring.

Good grief. They just talked and talked and talked and talked.

I mean, they're freaking gangsters! Shoot something! Have a car chase! fuck a whore!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when will people realize Emma Watson is really boring actress to watch?

Whatever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how How HOW In fuck did the dudes/chicks who made the matrix make that movie?

I mean that movie was bad! Really, absolutely just bad!

How does something like that even happen? I watched it on video and I only lasted about 30 minutes. Holy shit. It was just awful and boring in terrible. Unbelievable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> right. We should keep our troops there and then in five years

"If Afganistan becomes iraq 2.0 because we pulled out too early we will be worse off than keeping military in the country."

So we keep them there. Then five years after that

"If Afganistan becomes iraq 2.0 because we pulled out too early we will be worse off than keeping military in the country."

So we keep our troops there. And five years after that

Ad infinitum

Military-industrial complex wins again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck yeah they are!

neighbors going to a walleye tournament next weekend and he promised I will have fresh walleye in the freezer When he comes back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dougherty: Ted Thompson saw the writing on the wall, and is revamping the defense with speed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dalvin "fumble machine with a glass shoulder" Cook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  well aware.

I'm just talking about a "type" of receiver that this guy can cover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really? sounded like the love him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PERFECT guy to cover those tall receivers like Julio Jones, Megatron, etc.

Love love love love love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did anybody else see Wilbon absolutely losing his fucking mind regarding the Trub pick on PTI this afternoon?

LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean Who doesn't? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kegel exercises are one of the best natural ways to control urinary incontinence. These simple moves can help many women and men, regardless of your age or what's causing your problem. They strengthen your pelvic floor muscles, which support your bladder. When these muscles are weak, you're more likely to have leaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Coke Life

no, it has that Stevia bull shit in it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Westside story is SUPPOSED to be the a rehash of Romeo and Juliet

That is a given.

This is an anthology series.  Each season is supposed to be different

Season one and season two were VERY different. They did not have a fundamental similarity between plots.  Seasons two and three are definitely very similar plot wise. It feels like lazy writing to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who else would like to see Coca-Cola create a version of Coke with 50% of the sugar that is in there now?

NO bull shit artificial sweeteners!

The only sweetener would be sugar, just half of what it currently is

I would love it. Anybody else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man, I love this show But this season's plot line is kind of a rehash of last season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> both seasons include-

An established successful family in the Midwest, with a strong rivalry among brothers, is threatened to be taken over by a larger, more powerful, criminal organization

an ordinary shlub gets caught up in a world of criminal activity spurred on by his good-looking wife/girlfriend. The woman seems normal at first, but is slowly revealed to be more and more out there while spouting New Age aphorisms

I mean, that's the foundation plot lines of both seasons.

I think Noah bit off more than he could chew will running this show and Legion. It's too much for one man. One of those shows was going to suffer and it turned out to be this one.

still going to watch it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Colossal" - have you seen this? Is it worth watching? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curt Schilling is an unhinged lunatic constantly spouting off at the mouth all kinds of crazy hate stuff. Should've been fired a long time ago.

Giving Caitlin Jenner the award I agree is completely and utterly ridiculous. That one I will give you.

ESPN the actual Corporation officially endorsed black lives matter? Or some athletes did it?

The last example is just political correctness out of control, and it affects all kinds of organizations everywhere.

that stuff with Sage Steele I don't know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Their decision to peddle in far-left politics

wwhat now? huh?

Have they been shilling for a livable wage? hAs Scott Van Pelt been pounding his fist on the table demanding the upper-class pay its fair share of taxes?

single-payer health care?

what does this even mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!

There was a lot of really good links and resources there. I am reading up on cognitive behavioral therapy right now because of this. Interesting stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you blame them though?

Do you want State Street brats upscale classy sophisticated ambience ruined by low class ruffians and rabble-rousers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow!

I had not heard anything about this aat all!

This whole thing flew totally under the radar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is pretty cool!

Can you tell me what mall that is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true

One of the major cause of the fall of Rome was an ongoing drawn out very expensive military misadventure in the eastern part of the Empire in what is now currently Iraq and Iran

sound familiar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the Enlightenment literally started in cafs around Europe.

No joke. This is one coffee for started to become widely accepted and served across Europe. Coffee and the enlightenment principles became intimately entwined Because of this

http://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=130595037
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you, great comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ssee now all of that sounds like a really smart planning to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan have absolutely nothing to do with national defense

In fact, both wars have made our country weaker, more vulnerable, unable to fund desperately needed infrastructure, unable to fund education, etc.

nearly all of our military actions in the Middle East have created MORE terrorism than was there before



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> it is supposed to rain for the next 10 days straight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes!

, That's exactly what I'm talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea.

Then again, I live in a country that is willing to spend $6 TRILLION dollars (and counting!) on wars in Iraq and Afghanistan without blinking an eye. Not to mention spending billions and billions and billions of dollars on a stupid senseless Needless tragic "war against terrorism" that is accomplished nothing but misery.

We will drop hundred $150 million on one airstrike on a  abandoned Syrian airfield and think nothing of it.

But when it comes to stuff like our own infrastructure, or making awesome things for us like an indoor park We can't find the money.

Oh well, that's just America I guess

it's really tragic how those awful terrorists are so brainwashed, though, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is my wacky idea on what to do with one of these failed malls.

First counter intuitively put in a very large grocery store. It's an odd choice for a mall, but it's one of the few brick-and-mortar stores that aren't going out of business.

Then convert large area inside the mall into a indoor park. Install beautiful water features, some nice walking paths, playground playthings for the kids, and indoor growing grass.

People will come for the park. They will love it. Then bring in stores near the indoor park that cater to what people want. Maybe a bowling alley? Or a laundromat?

That way you can do your laundry, do your grocery shopping, and enjoy a relaxing afternoon in the park at the same time

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> both of your posts come off as extraordinarily judgmental, not to mention entirely unhelpful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's typical for this sub, but you can't explain WHY it's typical or your comment will be deleted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good grief. He's not "throwing a massive tantrum", he got hit with a broadside, and he's trying to figure out what his next move is.

Please don't crap all over person who is desperately trying to figure out what's going on and how to deal with it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The mall, in a sense, functioned as a "downtown." It was the only area were town residents mingled in a public space. 

yes, I think this is a really good point. People NEED a place to go and hang out and be together. If not the mall Fine. But it should be somewhere

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brick-and-mortar retail stores are finding it impossible to compete with online sellers, and are closing physical stores, left and right.

Apparel retail has been particularly hard hit, with The Limited, Wet Seal, BCBG Max Azria, and Vanity Shop of Grand Forks each seeking court protection in 2017. The latest victim was Payless Inc., which filed for bankruptcy April 4 and said it would shutter 400 stores. 

Rue21 may be next. The embattled teen apparel chain is said to be filing for bankruptcy as soon as this month, according to people familiar with the matter. Or perhaps it will be Gymboree, which Bloomberg News reported is preparing to file for bankruptcy as a June 1 debt payment looms.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US retailers are going bankrupt at record pace. In 3 short months 14 retailers have announced bankruptcy. Electronics sellers, and clothing shops are most at risk. Trend is likely to accelerate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably the most intelligent post on this whole thread

All of these experts talking out of their ass have no idea what retailers are up against, or basically how totally screwed They are simply because they're competing in a landscape they can't win at currently </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's actually a really great point!

I honestly don't think I ever heard anybody make that point before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great comment.

I hope OP reads that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay thank you

however, it's just interesting to discover how a small thing like the closing of the Panama isthmus created MAJOR climate shifts all over the planet.

I mean, if I'm reading the article correctly from the Woods Hole the only reason parts of North America and northern Europe are even habitable today are because the warm ocean current shifted after the Panamanian isthmus closed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoa! 

so basically the whole ice ageWas caused by the closing of the Panamanian isthmus?

http://www.whoi.edu/oceanus/feature/how-the-isthmus-of-panama-put-ice-in-the-arctic.

The principal engine of this global circulation, often called the Ocean Conveyor, is the difference in salt content between the Atlantic and Pacific Oceans. Before the Isthmus of Panama existed, Pacific surface waters flowed into the Atlantic. Their waters mixed, roughly balancing the two oceans salinity.

About 5 million years ago, the North American, South American, and Caribbean Plates began to converge. The gradual shoaling of the Central American Seaway began to restrict the exchange of water between the Pacific and Atlantic, and their salinities diverged.

Evaporation in the tropical Atlantic and Caribbean left ocean waters there saltier and put fresh water vapor into the atmosphere. The Trade Winds carried the water vapor from east to west across the low-lying Isthmus of Panama and deposited fresh water in the Pacific through rainfall. As a result, the Pacific became relatively fresher, while salinity slowly and steadily increased in the Atlantic.

As a result of the Seaway closure, the Gulf Stream intensified. It transported more warm, salty water masses to high northern latitudes, where Arctic winds cooled them until they became dense enough to sink to the ocean floor. The Ocean Conveyor was rolling, drawing even more Gulf Stream waters northward.

snip

On their journey to the North Pacific, these deep waters became enriched in nutrients and carbon dioxide. In the Subarctic Pacific, these deep waters could have upwelled, rising to the sunlit surface to provide the ingredients to spark enormous blooms of phytoplankton. Great abundances of silica and opal (the preserved material from the phytoplankton shells) in seafloor sediments are evidence of both the blooms and the strong upwelling.

The upwelling may have been so strong, however, that the phytoplankton did not keep pace with the upwellingthat is, more carbon dioxide upwelled than was used by the phytoplankton. Consequently, the excess carbon dioxide leaked back into the atmosphere, adding a greenhouse gas that warmed the planet.

What shut down the Mid-Pliocene Warm Period about 2.7 million years ago? And what finally caused Northern Hemispheric glaciation at about the same timebut nearly 2 million years after the Isthmus of Panama formed?

Neal Driscoll and Gerald Haug proposed one solution. They postulated that moisture carried northward by the Gulf Stream was transported by prevailing westerly winds to Eurasia. It fell as rain or snow, eventually depositing more fresh water into the Arctic Oceaneither directly, or via the great Siberian rivers that empty into the Arctic Ocean.

The added fresh water would have facilitated the formation of sea ice, which would reflect sunlight and heat back into space. It would also act as a barrier blocking heat stored in the ocean from escaping to the atmosphere above the Arctic. Both these phenomena would further cool the high latitudes. In addition, Arctic waters flowing back into the North Atlantic would have become less cold and saltyshort-circuiting the efficiency of the Ocean Conveyor belt as a global heat pump to North Atlantic regions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So atmospheric CO2 levels just reached 410 ppm, first time in 3 million years it's been that high. What happened 3 million years ago? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what happened 3 million years ago to cause CO2 levels to be higher than they are today?

https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/we-just-breached-the-410-ppm-threshold-for-co2/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they also said, "GeoCities" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Mayer -once one of pop's biggest stars- had vocal cord surgery 2011, moved to Montana, matured, and is now happy quietly making moderately popular music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh fuck yeah....offices!!! 

wooooooo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoa!

I did not know they were going to have a schedule again this year!

Crazy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sodium is the extracellular electrolyte, potassium is the intracellular electrolyte, combine that with chloride and you have the three main  electrolytes.

most Westerners get plenty of calcium, but if you feel you need a little bit more magnesium try magnesium chloride, instead of magnesium citrate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The vitamin C might do a number on your empty stomach.

Getting electrolytes is so incredibly simple and people make it complex.

Get some potassium citrate capsules, and some table salt. Now get a bottle of water. Open up a potassium capsule, add it to the water. Now, add a dash of salt. boom, Done.

Do that to all of the water you drink and you'll be just fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you see how fast Darrell Revis dropped off the cliff?

It could happen anybody.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> once you hit 30 years old. Anything can happen.

Remember, a cornerback doesn't have to lose a step, the only need to lose half a step before they're no longer elite.

Losing a half a step after age 30 is Pretty common </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there anything more romantic than hiring a dumbfuck retard to rob your own brother to scratch together enough cash to buy your betrothed a ring?

really brings a tear to your eye </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure it's meant to be a mystery.

I don't think anybody knows what the hell is going on with that just yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  FFS MEW is absolutely hot as fuck!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why do I have the weird feeling that this robbery is going to go horribly wrong?

LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can anybody else hear Ewan's Scottish accent leaking out?

It is there, although subtle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are lots of reasons to fast. I am at a healthy weight and do not need to burn fat off, for instance. But I still fast because there are many benefits to it Besides weight loss



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ?????????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exogenous ketones work wonders for this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly, dude it's not that hard.

The problem is these ballers are screwing around with low class chicks

There are high-class escorts that charge $20,000, $30,000, $50,000 per session. They are the ultimate professionals. They're gorgeous, high-class, and you would never know by looking at them in 1 million years that they are call girls. Because you can't afford them.

And they don't talk to TMC, and they don't look like ho's. They do their job and leave. Or you go to a exclusive mansion party where this kind of stuff happens in the basement. And trust me, there are no paparzzi there.  Why would they talk to TMZ when they are making $40,000 a pop? that would be stupid. Their entire career would be over in a moment

high-class corporate executives, Senators, governors, movie stars, etc. this is who they use. Those types are getting laid all the time and never get caught. Because they're smart and they are rich and they're willing to spend the money on it.

Unlike this moron Carmelo who has unprotected sex with a stripper. Dummy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
