<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6570</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn that sounds horrible! be careful!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful!! I'm not sure what you can trust there . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I'd run far far away and never look back! O.O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know there's several films in which light harms the so-called ghosts. But I don't think you guys understand. This was not a person in bad make up... That...thing was made of shadow, it was massive, tall to the ceiling! And that smile that went outwards from its own body. I don't know what's going on, but this for sure is not so cheap horror movie.

 About moving, I certainly can't. You have no idea the prices of apartments in Hong Kong. I paid for a year in this place and that was almost all my savings. We're talking about the city with the highest land prices in the world. What you pay here for a tiny cubicle would get you a penthouse in the US. I can't afford moving! And yet...I dare not go back to my apartment here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever heard a ghost laugh? [Part 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://redd.it/6a0w2s)

 Okay, Im back. The photoshoot was okay. I was distracted and I think I didnt do my best work today, but its the best I could do under the circumstances. I havent slept in 20 hours, but I found a hotel where I can rest and think what will I do tomorrow. Im not going back home. Not tonight. Not after what happened last night.

 So, after the whole alley thing, we walked to the nearest MTR, and parted ways. I was exhausted and just wanted to get into bed. My apartment in Hong Kong is tiny, as any place in Hong Kong is. Being one of the most expensive cities in the world when it comes to housing, I had low expectations. Luckily I found a clean place, renovated a few years ago and that I could afford. The apartment is one living room the size of an american bathroom, a tiny hole in the wall (hard to call it room) with a bed, another room with a kitchenette and a fridge, and the smallest bathroom I had ever seen. Still, it served its purpose. I didnt plan on staying indoors much, I wanted to explore and enjoy the city as much as I could.
 
 I arrived home, carefully placed my gear in the living rooms table and went straight to bed. All the neons outside had died for the day, so the apartment was pitch black. I fell asleep right away.

 I dont think I had slept much when something woke me up. I cant say if it was a noise or a breeze or what, but I found myself suddenly awake. I kept my eyes closed, and tried to get back to sleep. That turned out to be impossible. I was freaking exhausted but couldnt sleep. There was something that didnt feel right... That feeling when someone is watching you crept into me as I lay on my side, facing my living room and my windows, with my eyes still tightly closed. I knew it was from all the ghost talk earlier that night, it must have affected me more than I thought. As the grown man I am, I opened my eyes to assure myself everything was fine and get the slumber I so badly needed.
 
 And there was nothing there. The living room was empty, and the windows were shut. Case closed.

 But just as I closed my eyes again I realized there seemed to be a big shadow in the corner of my living room that didnt quite belong there. I instantly opened my eyes again and looked straight into it. It was a shadow of some kind, but I was not sure what was casting it. Something from outside? From another building? Luckily the switch to my bedroom light was close to me, so I turned out the lights without leaving my bed. The shadow disappeared, but I could swear it disappeared a fraction of a second too late. It was still visible when the lights first flashed. I could swear it was...but it was late and I was half asleep. There was no one there, the shadow must have been cast from outside. Lights out and back to try and get some sleep.

 But the feeling didnt go away. It kept nagging at me. I still felt...watched. I felt...not alone? Im not sure how to describe it. I wanted to turn around and turn my back to my living room, change position to order my body to go back to sleep I felt unable to. For some reason I didnt want to turn my back to my living room. But at the same time, I didnt want to open my eyes, I was sure there was nothing there! I didnt think the ghost talk could affect me this way. I didnt even believe in all that crap! To prove myself I was being stupid I opened my eyes, but I didnt move. The lights were off, the living room was dark...and still I could see perfectly a shadow in the corner. It was a tall shadow. Almost 8 feet tall Id say. The top was close to the ceiling. I could see no shape. It was just...a tall shadow. I stared into it, trying to see...well, anything! I kept staring at it and I could swear at one point it shuffled a bit to the right, away from the window and closer to my bedroom. Only one inch, but it was enough to make me shiver. I kept staring. I had to make sense of what that was.

 It moved again. Just an inch, but this time towards the centre of the living room. Again, closer to my bedroom. My hand dashed from under the blankets and turned on the light. It was gone again. This time I could swear it stayed longer after I had turned the light on. Like when you look at something very bright and you see it in the corner of your eyes burning through for a few moments.
 Was it still there? I kept looking. Was it gone? Did the light scare it? Or was it simply invisible? Was it shuffling closer towards me now that I couldnt see it? All this and a hundred more thoughts rushed through my head, and against my better judgement, I closed the lights again.

 And there it was. It had moved to the centre of the living room. Now it was halfway from the corner where it was standing earlier, to my bed. Standing perfectly still. A blurted shadow without any recognizable features and yet I knew it was facing me. I could feel it looking at me directly. It had no eyes, and yet I could feel its stare. I wanted to talk, to shout, to ask it what it wanted. But something inside me didnt want to give it that power. The power of acknowledging it as something real. I wondered if I was hallucinating somehow, one of those sleep paralysis episodes I saw in that weird documentary. But I could move. I was not sleeping. This was happening. There was something in my living room, and it was trying to get close to where I was.

 As I kept watching it from my bed it took one step closer towards me. This time I saw it clear, it didnt shuffle, it took one very clear step, with one very clear shadowy foot towards me. I shrank back into my bed, against the wall and I froze there. I was unable to think, unable to move. I know I should have bolted right there right that moment, but I simply couldnt move. My body didnt respond. 

 For a while it didnt move again and nothing changed. I have no idea how long did I spend looking at that nothingness of darkness in my living room, but suddenly I started seeing something on the top part of the shadow (its head??). Something looked less...shadowy? Like it was being broken or cracked. And the crack started getting wider, so very slowly. But I could see it growing horizontally. When it was halfway within the borders of the shadow, it grew wider. And thats when I saw it. It was not a crack. It was a smile. That..thing was smiling. Slowly I started to see teeth, an impossible amount of teeth as the smile kept growing inside the shadow. I didnt even blink for I dont know how long. I started shaking uncontrollably as that thing smiled at me. Or to me. The smile grew outside the borders of the shadow, stretching it out with it.

 Then it took one step closer.

 I couldnt take it anymore. I screamed at the top of my lungs and ran out of the apartment, trying to stay out of its way and smashing the door behind me. I dont remember how I went down 14 sets of stairs, but I found myself three blocks away from my apartment and still running. When I stopped I noticed I had grabbed a backpack from besides my bed. My travelling instinct I guess, my backpack always comes with me. Even when I dont think... And thats the one strike of luck I had that night, because it was my bag from the morning before, from the beach, so it had a set of clothes and shoes. Then I realized I was barefoot and was running around the city at the break of dawn in shorts and nothing else.

 I looked around to make sure that thing didnt follow me. It was nowhere to be seen...but again, the street lights were on, so even if it followed me, I had no way of knowing. I put my shoes on and kept walking until my legs stopped shaking. I ended up in a McDonald's in Jordan, the one in Nathan Street, just behind Temple Street.

 I havent turned off any light in my hotel room yet. Im not sure I will tonight.

 I will have to go back to my apartment eventually. All my stuff is there, and I paid a whole year already. I cant afford another place. I dont know what to do.

 I will call Sam in the morning, but Im not sure what to tell him.

 What can I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
