<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject348</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe Chris Benoit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy Ritchie on making King Arthur and other things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i kind of just think of the big one [His death](#spoiler) ,   but it's actually got quite a few 'oh shit' moments to it thinking about it now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha this is huge if only for the complete absurdity of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the fact that [He can actually turn into the Beast](#spoiler) was probably the craziest thing for me. Don't know why but it just really caught me in a "oh shit" moment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh i totally forgot this came out this year. Yeah that's a good one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think is the biggest Film Spoiler of 2017 so far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there hasn't been too many major block busters released this year as of yet, so loosely including late last year, What's the biggest spoiler you could give to someone who has yet to watch a single film in all of 2017, including plot points, character deaths, and also Film announcements made this year?

If there are too few contenders so far, then how about if you include tv series released in 2017.


 

And though this is obviously inviting any and all spoiler discussions, lets also try and use the spoiler tag just to be a little courteous! *
           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you found the title, It's definitely a fun film and easily one of the weirdest i think i've ever seen! Hope you like it the second time round! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah i must have misremembered then, sorry. Shame though cause otherwise it works so well (especially with the flowers as someone mentioned)! 

Anyway funny you asked this today, i literally only watched Split last night finally after having meant to ages ago. and how good a film is it, hey?! The sequel should be fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't remember where i read it, but didn't M Night himself confirm this was the case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably Safety Not Guaranteed or Donnie Darko </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool read about the two rock-islands, didn't know Little Diomede was populated at all

Mainland Alaska and Russia then* point remains the same </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the closest point between Alaska and Russia is only 85km and can even been made on foot. Its only been crossed successfully twice though; once in 1998 (they literally almost died), and a second time in 2006 where upon arrival they were immediately detained and deported. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW my girlfriend steals the blankets AGAIN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean not when it's a reply to "Aldo looking sharp"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Past instances in which i professed to like you were fraudulent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
