<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4533</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very very little.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reveal of the title was my favourite part of Covenant. It was done really well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree about the cgi. Just looked off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah theres one scene of the engineers in the new one. Lasts five minutes tops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw it yesterday. I thought it was pretty average.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a movie dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its as standard as it gets. it wasnt impressive, but it was a fun time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> id say it the trailer represents the movie pretty well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the fingering scene. do you think it was intentional? the whole scene reminded me of the trailer starring kirk lazarus and tobey macguire in satans alley (tropic thunder). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i hate to be the bearer of bad news but yeah the characters aren't too bright. everything happens very quickly and theres some pretty dumb shit throughout. go in with low expectations and youll probably have a blast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> id say a blend between sci-fi and action. shit hits the fan pretty quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you disliked Prometheus this movie will bring back bad memories.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got back from an early screening of Alien: Covenant! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to answer any questions. Id like to keep it spoiler free but i can message people if they really want to know what happens throughout. I won a double pass to see it through Xbox's Crack the Code comp. 

Overall rating of the film: bahahahahahahahahahahhahahaah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad you enjoyed it for the most part. 

The film started off incredibly well. The title scene left me absolutely gob smacked. Hands down best part of the movie right there. It was immersive, up until they all hop off the ship. If you disliked Prometheus, Covenant is goddamn deja vu. So. Many. Stupid. Decisions. Its too much. I understand where youre coming from but to me it was an absolute mess. 

Kinda spoiler: This movie features the most hilariously bizarre scene of the year. The whole theater was cracking up. It was ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> highly suggest everyone on this sub to check out his streams: 

https://www.twitch.tv/jonmakesbeats

streams every thursday with a special guest for four hours. so far he has had diabia$e, kiefer and jeremiah jae. he also does a few unannounced streams whenever where he just messes around with samples viewers send in. this is just one of the seven beats he made with kiefer, highly recommend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jonwayne and Kiefer making a beat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> god imagine another scene at the dea office and hearing hanks voice ever so faintly down the hallway or something. id probably di </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch the commentary with michael cera and the rest of the cast - its really funny and they speak about heaps of cool stuff behind the movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst shows currently on free to air? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I briefly watched some of The Voice tonight and fucking hell is that show a train wreck. All the judges do is scream me me me and the show is full of random ad breaks. What do you think is the worst show currently airing on tv? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing this early on tuesday! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> comes down to the person watching i guess. i have never really found a horror/thriller comedy that has tickled my fancy because i dont like the middle ground that it sits between. 

for get out, i dont think it was culture specific, as in american to australian kind of thing. it sort of laid itself on the surface of basic black person reacts to crazy white people shenanigans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just saw Get Out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Get Out only just came out in Australia yesterday. Overall i enjoyed the movie. The pacing was nice and i liked that every scene fit together like a puzzle as the movie drew to a conclusion. 

For me the humour fell very flat. The jokes were very much for the younger kids i felt. Most of them were cracking up when the TSA scenes played out. On a side note why do characters feel the need to describe what they are doing to the audience. Stuff like that makes me feel like im being spoon fed. Minor complaint is when Chris kills the brother - how did he not hear him get up? 

 Probably the best part of the movie was when the guests all stopped when Chris walked upstairs. That gave me chills right there. 

It was pretty fun when I think back on it. It wasn't bad but it wasn't amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? I dont mean that in a negative way. I just dont think there was so much of a jump in that scene, for me at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was average. Glad you enjoyed it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shout out to the water physics team behind Kong Skull: Island. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although the movie itself was a bit average, my god did the water look fantastic when Kong was strolling through. The huge waves culminating as he walked around in lakes was so satisfying. Even the buckets of water that dropped off of him during some scenes was so cool. It honestly looked believable. Great job, whoever was in charge of that department!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah well i like it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If youve seen The Survivalist, did it remind you of that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyers listen to Eminem's 'Lose Yourself' in National Party copyright case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its on Amazon. Will definitely buy the blu-ray in the future. I had to uh, find it my own way, so to speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I understand where youre coming from. Hyping up a slow burn movie has its ups and downs. In this case, though, i think its perfectly reasonable to give it some attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give it a watch! Not too sure if i have a favorite but recently I have enjoyed:

The Eyes Of My Mother

The Witch

Scream

Alien

Green Room </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can definitely see how this movie was received on the other end of the spectrum. Luckily, it resonated with the things I find scary the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Blackcoat's Daughter. I don't think I have ever been this terrified. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished watching this. I can't believe how petrified I feel right now. Watched it in the dark with headphones on. My mind is completely numb right now. I goddamn love horror movies. This had everything I ever wanted in a horror film. I watched the trailer thinking it would be a little thriller of a film revolved around a group of school girls. I can honestly say that I was not prepared for this movie at all. Goddamn fucking christ almighty there goes my sleep tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wouldnt you recommend it? I think its a great film. Usually rewatch a few times a year. Theres definitely a few heavy-handed scenes but overall its a great movie. The performances are so interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this cover on blu ray. I get shivers every time i see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. Do people not use the search function? You can sort by new if you want recent posts. r/horror is especially bad at this. Theres like a post every few days asking about what movies to watch on netflix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trailers so far have been underwhelming. But its made by A24 so i will be jerking off to it on release.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the game is called "Everything". 

http://store.steampowered.com/app/582270/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only scene i liked was the very ending when Ed and Lorraine were dancing together. Such a beautiful way of finishing both the movie and the two main characters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank goodness someone said it. Everyone here was saying this game is the pinnacle of emotional story telling. It was just simply not my kind of game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a situation that has occurred in your life that you think you handled really well? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is my only problem. Might postpone Fargo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have the first season on blu ray. will be the next series to watch!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else watching Better Call Saul, The Leftovers and Fargo all at once? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All three into their third season. I do not deserve this much good telly per week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be great seeing Walt again in his rookie days. I can definitely see him being mentioned in passing later on in the series if it gets up to that stage. Im also loving the black and white scenes at the beginning of each season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. This is early on in the life of Jimmy McGill. Its probably his first dirty job he's done like this that is related to stalking so of course he is going to be nervous and make mistakes. Mike didnt tell him if it was cartel or drug related but i think jimmy definitely knew it was something in that area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers) Anyone else feel like S03 E02 just elevated the show to a new level of greatness? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish i could describe this more effectively, but the most recent episode (2) filled me with such nostalgia and excitement that i just couldnt contain myself. That huge buildup to the los pollos sign made me so goddamn giddy. The pacing was perfect and it really feels like the show is in a nice place. Every story line is following along at a remarkable pace. I cannot wait for the rest of the series to unfold!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the reply! ive been looking for something like the doco you linked. cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats not about it. The decisions those idiots made ruined the entire movie for me. On top of that, none of the characters had chemistry with one another and their delivery of lines was forced and laughable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the right answer. Regardless i still thought this part was a bit of a stretch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahhh its all coming back! thanks for the comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the front page! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for commenting! Cannot wait for the rest of the series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoilers S2 + 3) Need some help clearing a few things up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 11:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished the first ep of season 3! Its been a few months since i have watched season 2.

- where did johns wife go? was this touched upon at the end of season 2? i kind of got the feeling she left during the years after her daughter died.
- where did the black baby go? 
- who is that new little kid? 

sorry if these a dumb questions!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe draw them out? If youre having trouble visualising what a rotated tetris piece looks like, draw out its possible rotations. You could even do it for each piece and use it as a reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont surf but i lived in esperance for a few years. Depends on what beach but twilight beach and the areas surrounding it are generally seen as the beaches that attract more sharks. Just have your wits about you and check online before you go. The beaches are beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got smashed with downvotes but i completely agree. Some trailers can tell you absolutely nothing and be really great but this one was just not enticing at all for me. Ill definitely check out out the movie when it comes out though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> correct-a-mondo. sorry if the arrangement was confusing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the stars align completely out of nowhere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im confused. Is this so called term saying that a movie's plot occurs because the characters are stupid? Or that a movie's plot is ruined because the characters are stupid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way the camera moves throughout the the nightclub scene is absolutely insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this goddamn movie.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the reasoning behind putting the title of a movie at its end? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 10:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> forgot to add that to the ones i have watched. i cant wait for season 3! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have an eight hour car ride tomorrow. What are some binge-worthy shows I can watch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 11:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really only buy from amazon. Am i too missing out on some great deals? In in australia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can one up you. Sam gellaitry is closing the gobi stage on friday. Absolutely insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i grew up with most of these films. i loved mulan the most. such beautiful films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that beauty and the beast one is just gorgeous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 13:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it comes down to how the player likes the story, so to speak,  delivered to them. If youre expecting a "all will be revealed" type ending, then you will probably be disappointed. I could elaborate further but id just be rambling. Simply put, i loved the mystery behind the game and im okay with things not being explained. Sometimes that doesnt work, but i believe INSIDE did it very very well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved this ending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you say that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean the movie itself comes across as extremely realistic. No part of the story is stylised at all. I think it was deliberate to film and edit the scenes like that to maintain the realism. Theyre sweaty, panting, and its a bit awkward for the viewer. I need to rewatch this movie because i absolutely love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So many little things i love about this movie. Going to rewatch it today!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha you are full of shit mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>     Funny how, generally, people who like superhero trash don't get Prometheus. 

what does this even mean?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just totally not into the idea of understanding the origins of where the aliens came from. Whats wrong with some mystery and questions? I hope Covenant wont delve too deep into all of that. Unfortunately based off the trailers all i see is explosions and really pissed off aliens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some thoughts on Prometheus (Spoilers). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watched Prometheus for the first time on blu-ray. Overall the movie was a bit dull. Here are some notes I wrote down throughout the movie that I hope will get some discussion going! 

- The intro credit scene was awesome. Amazing landscape shots. Laughed a bit when that guy (engineer) took off his hoodie - he looked like a life size action figure or something.
- The first scene in Scotland felt unnecessary. It was an iffy introduction to the two main crew members.
- The first few scenes introducing David were mesmerizing. The movie could have easily started with these scenes.
- Charlize Theron played her character terribly. She had the "i am 100% not trust worthy" look on her face the whole time.
- The two main characters (Shaw and Holloway) had terrible chemistry when acting together. The scene where he mentions life and birth in general (talking about what they were discovering) and she literally just gets sad to make it obvious that she can't have kids. That whole scene was very soppy.
- Their whole venture is based off of a bunch of cave drawings found around the world. How did they pinpoint the exact planet they were travelling to out of a bunch of cave paintings?
- They are only briefed of their mission AFTER their two year hibernation. 
- Holloway had the most random death in the entire film. Within minutes he gets this "disease" and hes literally just like "MEREDITH KILL ME" with his arms open wide. Meredith kills him without an instant even though the ship is equipped with a more than capable medical bay. 
- The ship lands exactly where the huge shrine rock thing was. Did they have coordinates as to where this was? Did the cave paintings ever show this huge rock thing? The chances of finding that as soon as they pass through the clouds must be pretty low (unless theres more than one, which i dont think is ever mentioned). 
- The entire crew just wander into the rock thing. Why didn't they take their time? It seemed as if they just aimlessly strolled in and found the shit they were looking for. 
- Two of the crew members get lost even though minutes ago they plotted out an expansive detailed map showing every nook and cranny of the place. The captain is then just like "aight boys yall gonna have to stay the night there its stormy as shit". Why didn't he tell them where to go? The 4d map he was looking at had tracers on each members - he could have easily directed them out of the cave complex. 
- David completely fucked over Holloway for no reason by spiking his drink. Also, he spikes it RIGHT IN FRONT OF HIM. As in, I am passing you a drink, you're looking at the drink, and I dip my finger tip that has black gooey shit on it into it as you're looking at the drink. The fuck?
- The main guy somehow is smoking weed in his fucking space suit while on a planet that has never been inhabited by anyone on Earth. And he gets stoned and wanders around. 
- They extract DNA from an engineers head and it matches with human DNA - complete with computer screens that literally pair the two together and spit out the words "DNA MATCH".
- Theres these strange hologram recordings that show the engineers running around the place. Is this technology built in to the cave complex? Do these holograms just play randomly? Or were they triggered by the crew people strolling in? To me it seemed like a cop out idea to keep the plot moving forward quickly.
- The movie itself looked incredible. My favorite parts were the huge panning landscape shots throughout.

Hopefully Alien: Covenant doesn't follow the same structure as this or has the same errors. That would be a real shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shia and logan have both openly talked about their time spent on set and their prep for the movie. Didnt seem bad at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no knowledge about linguistics but one thing that slightly bugged was was how they gathered enough information from the aliens that allowed them to interpret their language. Names seemed to be the most straightforward area, but how in the fuck did they determine that this small circle is the word "culture" or this lil circle right here means "war"? What were they basing this research on? Its been a while since ive seen it so my memory of the specifics is a bit hazy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 12:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can someone explain to me his uprising? it seems as if his imprisonment has been reported about on every major music news site. the songs he has on soundcloud are pretty weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just copped a metal cover version of The Wolf of Wall Street. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 04:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The packing itself looks amazing. But. There is only ONE special feature! A commentary would have been great, a gag reel would have been awesome. Slightly disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is No Mans Sky doing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was oddly invested in the huge yet bizarre build up to its release. Ever since the thread that showed how many features were promised but left out of the game, it seems as if the buzz has completely stopped. 

Is this due to the quality of the game? 

How is the game now? 

Has there been consistent patches so far?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The action scenes were easily the selling point of the movie. The way Keanu spoke felt forced and a bit cheesy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao what? How can that make you disappointed? Just because its been leaked doesnt mean he has to go change it. At least, thats what i understand youre saying?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. Will just stick to Amazon. Cheers ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would literally drag my balls through five miles of broken glass just to hear A24 collectively fart through a walkie talkie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for these sites! Know of any others? Forgive me for saying this but most of the releases and scream factory and cc are quite old and i am not very familiar with films from those time periods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite blu rays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just watched The Eyes Of My Mother on blu ray and loved it. The special features were great aswell. Any other recommendations?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how about in two when all the cupboards open. watching the entire theater jump at once was awesome.

edit: also when mika showed up on screen in two and it revealed it was a prequel - the whole theater gasped! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That had to be my favourite bit. Definitely adds to its creepiness and it represents the main character very effectively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely agree about the ending. Felt like an easy cop out and it could have ended more ominously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Eyes Of My Mother. Wow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bluray copy arrived this morning. This is definitely not for the faint of heart. I can confidently say that it takes a lot to crack me in terms of gore and a disturbing nature. This movie absolutely obliterated me. I was squirming. You know that feeling you get that can only be described as complete hopelessness? Its like that but very subtle and it lingers. 

The general consensus is quite divided, but I can easily recommend this film to any horror fan who enjoys putting themselves through such bleak situations. My only criticism is the ending as I feel like it ended too abruptly. Apart from that, 9/10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you enjoy the intro bit of Antichrist? That part was easily the highlight of the movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain to me how Youtube's video player works? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Why does it never load the whole video? 
- If I am halfway through a video and I skip back to the beginning, why does it reload the whole video?
- Why does the video pause when you change the playback quality (eg. going from 480 to 720)? IIRC it never used to pause. It used to slowly transition into that quality . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the first trailer didn't really sell me for some reason. 

edit: just rewatched it damn that was LIT  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was good. it felt very personal which i think was the only effective approach. some scene natalie's accent was a bit off but overall she blew me away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably could have elaborated on my comment a bit more. I found some parts irritating. She goes to leave the island the first time without any food or water - wheres the logic in that? She was supposed to be the goddess of the ocean, yet, she only uses it to push the big guy off the boat. When she gets back, her parents have no issue about where the fuck she was. It was known that her father was very strict about her leaving the island, yet when she arrives back he is 100% all smiles. 

Overall i found it to be enjoyable but these small errors irritated me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 13:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Visuals? Outstanding. Songs? Catchy and loveable. Story? Absolute rubbish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People on the porter sub are worried hes gonna harm himself over this. Its not like his goddamn career is over lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao relax fam </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you use this exit to get to curtin, get off at south terrace before. Its easier and takes probably the same amount of time to get to curtin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering there is no release date for Live 10 as of this moment, I would definitely buy 9. They usually offer some sort of discount to customers who have previous versions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im gonna casually drop this here and say I think Leo was a bit of a miscast. I dont really have any convincing reason behind why i think so, I just feel like someone else could have played the role a lot better. The film was beautiful, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here had their ears cleaned out professionally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you go? Was it worth it? I am interested in seeing how much is in there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This this this!! I went November last year and as soon as I peered in I was just absolutely speechless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australian actress, well known for her roles in The Good Wife, Friends, The Slap and Triangle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else watched the Sunday Night story on Melissa George? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 14:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How bizarre was that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 12:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would LOVE to do this! would you mind linking me where you got your frames from or the frame size?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was the show? Did everyone perform well?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shared the exact same thoughts as you. I pushed through season one and thought nothing of it. Then i watched season two. Jesus fucking christ was it good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmm id say definitely stick with it. while i completely enjoyed every season off breaking bad, the general consensus is that the first two seasons are a bit of a struggle to get through. i won't try to hype up your first viewing but you're in for a wild ride if you commit!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else hate it when you're driving on West Coast Highway and the person in front of you randomly stops to let a person walk across? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 09:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the biggest of problems, but c'mon. Its unnecessary. Just keep the flow of traffic going and that person can wait until they can see a break which will allow them to cross the road. Maybe there are a few exceptions, but I see it happens all the time!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was great in true detective season two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been paying for pro for well over six years now dude. It would easily benefit them in the long run if they paid a little more attention to their mobile apps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The folks over at Soundcloud need to fix their iOS App ASAP. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 10:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus fucking christ where do I even begin? What is going on over there at HQ? Have they employed babies to work on their iOS app? 


1. The app itself takes a lifetime to load up. 90% of the time the loading bar gets stuck (my internet coverage is fine) and I have to restart the app after which the loading breezes through.

2. The repetition glitch. This happens to me all the fucking time. Youre scrolling through anything; your feed, someones tracks, someones liked tracks. You realize that all youre seeing is the first ten or so songs repeating itself into infinity! Sometimes this never ends, and sometimes it loads the next ten tracks and then decides to repeat those. This has to be the worst out of all the bugs. I cant even explain how annoying this in practically any situation. 

3. No love for artists/people who USE THE BASIC FUNCTIONS. Wheres the inbox/messaging features like in the old app? NOPE. You gotta have a whole different app for that! Want to see who's following you? Well, you can't. Want to see your notifications? Well, that is no where to be found. Want to see basic statistics on your tracks? Nope! Want to edit your spotlight? Nope!!!

4. Sometimes when you initially go to scroll through the waveform of a track, it will shoot you to a position that is always somewhere towards the end. A small, but highly frustrating bug. 

Surely others are experiencing these bugs and more. The worst part is that the app is frequently updated but none of these seem to be fixed/addressed after each update. Their dominant focus seems to be revolved around their new subscription service. Im all for Soundcloud's strategies to increase profits, but please PLEASE fix the iOS app if you want me to stick around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed the film but I think it ended out of nowhere. It kind of left me disgruntled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 10 using a large percentage of bandwidth when using ethernet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 06:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I stop this? 

Theres things like "System and compressed memory", "service host: local service" and "service host: network service. I am aware of switching on limited data while over wifi, is there a way I can do the same for ethernet? Its stopping me from playing any online game. Any help would be greatly appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 00:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had seen this before and absolutely loved it. Tried to watch it with my girlfriend last night and we turned it off half way through. Just not her type of movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 09:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sold out in like a minute lmao. lucky i copped mine the first time it came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a big movie here in Australia during the "Video Ezy phase" of movie distribution. Despite its realism fading away in the last third of the movie, I think it was one of the first Australian films to legitimately make people scared of the outback.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 02:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely they could have thought of a better name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 04:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> taken from ere: https://www.mixcloud.com/NTSRadio/rip-fm-w-wedidit-18th-november-2016/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> D33J and drip-133 - Ultima </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 05:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 00:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were easily some scene where her attempt at the accent became more noticeable. But for the most part it was perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 01:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand everyones responses. Didnt mean to come across as entitled or rude. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 16:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey asshole... the cinema held a screening of Arrival with Dutch SUBTITLES. It was their decision to do so. I am merely commenting on that fact that Arrival's subtitles wherent very thought out effectively with the alien scene, as there was only dutch subtitles throughout that scene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 15:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the scene only had the aliens speaking in their language alongside dutch subtitles so we had no idea what they were saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 10:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah we pretty much had that mentality going in. on a side note, who is usually in charge of subtitles for foreign cinemas? i imagine it would not be difficult to identify which scenes need dual subtitles (like the scene op is telling us about). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 08:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my friend and I saw this in amsterdam. the whole movie was in english with dutch subtitles except for this scene that had ONLY DUTCH SUBTITLES.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best three player board games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends and I enjoy Articulate and Catan. I am looking for something that is enjoyable, easy to set up and not too difficult. We usually play them whilst drinking. Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry bout that. You're correct. I think there is easily a common assumption that M.Night films must have some sort of twist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts on M.Night's Split? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 15:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a bit on the fence about this movie after walking out of the cinema. I have a few areas I'd like to bring up. Overall I thought it was a very well done film. NOTE: SPOILERS AHEAD!


No jump scares - This was something that surprised me definitely. Not only is there no jump scares, there is strong tension up until the ending. 

The therapist - I think some scenes with the therapist were a bit drawn out. Im not too sure if I accept her involvement in the movie just yet. Would have been great if the film let the audience figure out all the little details about Kevin, instead of a few long scenes with the therapist where she vomits out everything she knows about him. I think her main role was to give the audience information about him and Im not too sure if i liked that. 

The "beast" reveal - I am happy that Kevin didnt go all out and transform into a crazy werewolf beast. In saying that, there was so much build up to this beast that I am guessing some people would have been disappointed with how he looked. 

The beast through the bars - Wow. My favourite part of the film. Kevin slowly bending the bars to get his face in. That close up shot of him should be ICONIC. And him screaming all those demonic/preachy things, CREEPY. 

Supporting actresses - They played the parts great. I was just disappointed that they didnt make it to the very end. Their deaths seemed too sudden and Im not too sure if the beasts cannibalism was explained too much throughout, as I was quite confused when it was revealed that he had eaten them.   

Ending twist/reveal - I have no opinion on this as I have not seen Unbreakable. This ultimately did not effect the movie for me!

All in all, very fun and interesting movie jacked with tension.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> these songs are absolutely magical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 14:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly everything she said in that movie. At one point shes like "do i swim over there?.....no....not there.....somewhere else".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 01:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loved the movie right up until the ending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best ice cream in Perth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 03:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine there is a preference towards ice cream much like there is for coffee. Favourite ice cream joints? Amico cafe make their own which is really nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any films where the obliviousness of the parents is done right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 01:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it when horror films have really dumb parents and pretend none of the shit is happening. Id say the worst example would be Paranormal Activity 4. Are there films that do it realistically and correctly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flume moshpit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 11:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was there a point to the beginning of the film? The part where he runs over that animal thing? I thought that scene was very interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 00:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To the front page we go! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 03:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats definitely how found footage movies are right now. I hope that in the near future some more effective and realistic ones pop up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 02:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not enjoy this movie at all. Its pretty much the polar opposite of the original film in terms of immersion, tension and believability. The characters are stock standard and you can pretty much guess the order they are going to die in from the get go. I really wish this movie wasnt made because in my opinion in changes how you perceive the original film. Part of the reason why the first film is so effective is that it feels authentic, and this "sequel" distorts that authenticity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a movie typically edited starting from the beginning and ending with the credits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 15:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the whole process of editing both interesting and strenuous. Sometimes when I watch movies I imagine myself in the editing room, paying attention to the people with their eyes on the screens getting every little detail perfect. 

I am interested in understanding how a movie is edited from start to finish. How many people are involved? What rules/processes are taken into consideration in order to make sure the whole movie flows right? Does the art of editing a movie change much from an independent movie to a full scale hollywood blockbuster? Do editors have full control over the placement of the score and the audio in general? How many people contribute in total? 

I hope these questions stimulate some interesting discussions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girlfriends 21st is coming up. Any cool gift ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sort of sick of the usual gifts like jewelry, small goods, candles etc. I want something memorable and unique. I was looking at a hot air balloon ride or anything along the lines of that. Anyone here have some cool ideas? I am open to anything!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 03:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that. Cant wait! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched Alien </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 01:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy moly what a movie! Enjoyed every second of it. Now, is it worth watching the next two sequels? Or is it okay to go straight to Prometheus? Are the two sequels any good?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I need to watch all three Alien films before I watch Prometheus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 08:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 15:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why platforms like Soundcloud are so great. Go to your favourite artists profiles and scout through their likes and who they are following. Regardless of followers, there are some really talented individuals on Soundcloud. Instead of waiting for music to be delivered to you through big Youtube channels, do some digging on your own! 

Edit: Adding some accounts I follow: 

https://soundcloud.com/mishahook

https://soundcloud.com/streetcornermusic

https://soundcloud.com/iampools

https://soundcloud.com/songsbymaxblack

https://soundcloud.com/duskky

https://soundcloud.com/yayay 

https://soundcloud.com/djflp

https://soundcloud.com/tesla77

https://soundcloud.com/dj-mastercard

https://soundcloud.com/entroemcee

https://soundcloud.com/wwweirdkids

https://soundcloud.com/cerspence

https://soundcloud.com/vague002

https://soundcloud.com/wearecrazylegs

https://soundcloud.com/islandjoints

https://soundcloud.com/silvabeatss

https://soundcloud.com/3lll

https://soundcloud.com/diversas-hidden-cave

https://soundcloud.com/whispers-beirut

https://soundcloud.com/wearetar

https://soundcloud.com/amaixamai

https://soundcloud.com/sergicandlyka

https://soundcloud.com/con_tour

https://soundcloud.com/aerba

https://soundcloud.com/fleece

https://soundcloud.com/tishvair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roast him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 17:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best areas to buy small gifts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 12:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 17:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has to be one of my favourites. Was so disappointed with the recent sequel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 11:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely took me a while to understand the controls and the game mechanics. Theres not much progression as it gives you all the levels to complete from the beginning so definitely play the easy levels first and read the tutorial a couple of times. 

Its really satisfying pulling off a hard level with no casualties! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
