<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3080</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is going to do something huge like bomb North Korea to take attention away from this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does everyone assume there will be a Comey replacement anytime soon? He can just leave the job vacant, leaving the agency paralyzed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a stream? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CNN has helicopter view of Comey motorcade on the big screen. 

The NBA playoffs are going on. 

What year is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor lad.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excerpt from The Atheist Muslim. This needs to be reposted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/qOnSTh5.jpg

Apologies about the highlighting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies about the highlighting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excerpt from The Atheist Muslim. This needs to be posted again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a non flash link / html 5 version available? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Travel Cover for TaylorMade Catalina Cart Bag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi folks,

I'm traveling home to Ireland this summer for a month, and I want to bring my clubs. I have the TaylorMade Catalina Cart Bag, and I'm wondering if any of you fine folks know where I could get a cover/casing for it.

I've seen the horror stories of bags being dragged along the ground at airports and I want to ensure my bag is in an outer plastic shell/casing.

Any ideas where I could find one that fits my bag?

This is her (although mine is in white   black): http://taylormadegolf.com/Catalina-Cart-Bag/DW-SQ821.html

Looks like this might do the job - TaylorMade confirmed it too.

http://taylormadegolf.com/Player%27s-Golf-Travel-Bag/DW-SY073.html?dwvar_DW-SY073_color=N23239 cgid=taylormade-accessories-travelGear#start=1  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started it ages ago to keep track of this stuff. I need to put it all into a searchable database. It's the gift that keeps on giving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleepy mister. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/PastorArrested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Books in 30 Days: Imagine Me Gone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is how it is for me as well. 

It depends on how tired I am and what mood I'm in, if there's any distractions around me as well. If I'm reading while someone is watching a TV beside me it can be hard and I'll definitely read at a slower pace. I don't read that quickly anyway to begin with. For example it took me over seven hours of continual reading (according to my kindle stats) to finish Roger's Version by John Updike. I know people that have finished it in 4 or less.

I like to take things in though, and take it slow. If I fly through a book (which I have done in the past), I'll find that a few months down the road I can't remember a whole lot of the book so what was the point? But the flip side of that is reading a book again a few years later is like a new experience.

I'm rambling, apologies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion/God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christopher Hitchens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your favourite book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've done this every year since Derbycon 1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you love doing as a teenager that you never do now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ed Sheeran is borderline insulting. Even OSX renames his surname as Sheehan, because it fucking hates him as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hijacking top comment to remind folks to visit /r/PastorArrested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hijacking sticked comment to remind folks to visit /r/PastorArrested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Christian Brother found guilty of indecent assaults of former pupil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pre existing condition. You're fucked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excerpt from The Atheist Muslim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/qOnSTh5g.jpg

On point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he has photos taken with them. I have a few photos at home that I will check.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect he means exactly that.  

The Druze are a tightly-knit religious sect whose origins can be traced to Egypt a thousand years ago. They believe that God was incarnated on earth in the form of their leader, al-Hakim bi-Amrih Alla. The Druze do not have their own homeland. Thus, many of them migrated to the isolated mountains of Lebanon, Syria, and Israel, while others settled throughout the Middle East. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writers Corner - May 2017 Essay Submission Thread. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies for the delay. We already have one submission outside of this thread - thanks to a delay on my part - so I've included a link to it in this post below.

I'm not going to limit anyone to a topic for the first month we are doing this. Feel free to write about anything you like.

I have a few things going on this month but I should be able to dedicate a few afternoons to this, and hopefully you can too. :)

Enjoy folks!

**Submission 1**: [Christopher Hitchens is Dead by /u/TheColdestFeet] (https://www.reddit.com/r/ChristopherHitchens/comments/68sbgh/writers_corner_christopher_hitchens_is_dead) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome thanks! Yeah we have two other showers thankfully so I'd be ok without this shower for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a leak under the shower (which is tiled). Any idea how much this could be to fix? I'm guessing $2500 - $3500 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She was missing for an hour </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tame and Friendly Fox in Howth, Dublin, Ireland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're gorgeous! I used to see foxes on the Shannon golf course all the time when I was golfing as a kid in the 90s. None of them would come anywhere as close as this fella though. Amazing. So glad this was captured on film (should we say film anymore?)

Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, you can do it! Put in more time on the range and practice area than the course, and you'll do it in no time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With their water guns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump can barely read and write. I consider him to be largely illiterate. He enters into contracts all the time. Watch his deposition if you haven't seen it already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The laws of the universe were not suspended. It's total bullshit. He was an illiterate peasant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be honest, I got as far as "frenemies" and noped the fuck out of there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those checkpoints were just resting in the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Custom Built-in Bookshelves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any recommendations on someone in the area that can make and install custom built in bookshelves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you fucking kidding me? Read Carl Sagan's A Demon Haunted World. Religious people believe(d) in demons, and that they go around at night and steal sperm from men and impregnate women.

They've always been idiots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writers Corner - May 2017 Topics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a moderately good response to the writing proposal.

We're all extremely busy living our lives so I'd rather give folks a month to come up with something, as opposed to two weeks. After running the book club here, it's obvious that a lot of us just don't have the time so I don't want to push deadlines on people.

Submit your topics for the first month here. I'll close the thread on May 1st when we can begin writing. I'm OK with people writing about anything they like as long as it's not sports related (where did I get that from eh?). I'm also OK with folks writing about different topics if they wish to do so.

I'll submit a couple of topic ideas:  
1. Why pining for Christopher Hitchens is not what he would have wanted.  
2. I survived the first 100 days of Trump.  
3. The Pope's involvement in the murder of approximately 1 million innocent women as "witches". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like this. I don't even really care about a "winner" at all. I'm just interested in the content more than anything. By provoking thought in this manner we all win, essentially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any person that holds a fictitious status of "gods representative on earth" is evil, in my opinion (who else's opinion could I possibly be talking about?), and it's compounded by the fact that the current pope helps hide criminals, rapists, and does not unequivocally apologize for the murder of innocent women committed by previous popes.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only because he wouldn't get away with it now, but when the pope could get away with it he oversaw the killing of approximately 1 million "witches". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I honestly can't keep up trying to remind people of /r/PastorArrested

This is a daily occurrence. I wish I was joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Durban sex-predator pastor arrested on the run </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I left NH in 2014. You're not wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The pope is a good dude. 

Remember that time the pope sanctioned witch trials and the murder of innocent women? 

Pepperidge farm remembers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on your perspective really. 

RTE are using oauth 1, which was designed to go over http. It's out dated, they should be using oauth 1a or oauth 2.

They're not a bank, you're only going to gain access to so much by exploiting someone's RTE Player account. 

The scope of this is irrelevant though. At the end of the day they're using a vulnerable authentication method over http. End of, really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use dsniff, a Linux utility to dump all http requests on a network and it will reveal the rte login requests </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm saying I don't care about information revealed, I'm talking about the examples you gave. You said it's all publicly available, name email etc. That is all available for some people, sure. 

If this particular request was encrypted, and went over SSL, then I wouldn't be able to sit on a public network and sniff this information. By this information I mean the oauth login tokens which are sent over http.

You're confusing both of those items. Customer personal information vs oauth information.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't see what you're achieving with the exploit.

"Compromising someone's RTE player account" barely makes sense, since it only contains their email address, DOB and county (if they choose to provide it). All information that could ge gleaned from most people's online presence without any effort.

This attack can be used to take control of someone's RTE Player account. You can log in as them. That's not a huge deal, given that everyone *should* have a TV license. Now considering you can log in as them, you can use it to take control over the account. 

The information contained in their account is irrelevant really. I don't really care about the information you can see when you take over someone's account. The issue is being able to take over their account to begin with.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What does this amazing vulnerability actually achieve?

Sorry, but who said it's an amazing vulnerability?

You wouldn't even need to be on the same network as the person to get this data from somebody.

You're ignoring how this can be used to compromise someone's RTE Player account completely, and focusing on the social media aspect.

You might want to re-read what was said above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I updated the wording to help clarify - cheers.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I updated the wording to help clarify - cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect the latter :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah - apologies.

In layman terms, you can create an account on RTE Player using Facebook/Google+. When you do this, you give the RTE application permission to use your Facebook/Google+ account. It does this via an oauth token. Currently the RTE app has permission to view your private email account associated with Facebook/Google+.

If I was on the same wireless network as you (or wired network), and you were using the RTE Player Application on your phone, I would be able to compromise your RTE Player account completely using this vulnerability. 

I would also be able to use the oath token to get your email account associated with Facebook/Google+, even if you have selected to have it available "only to me". 

I could then use this info to attempt a phishing attack, and if someone did fall for it and click the link in the mail then I'd be able to completely compromise their Facebook/Google+ account. 

Not everyone falls for phishing attempts obviously, but a large number of people still do.

So the social media aspect of this isn't huge or earth shattering, but you can completely compromise someone's RTE Player account. Most people have a TV license so that's not a huge deal either I suppose. But not all of us live in Ireland anymore. :) 

**EDIT** updated to help clarify. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goodreads mobile application sends Facebook/Twitter oauth token in plaintext over http </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goodreads mobile application sends Facebook/Twitter oauth token in plaintext over http </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goodreads mobile application sends Facebook/Twitter oauth token in plaintext over http </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RTE Player mobile application sends oauth token in plaintext </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RTE Player mobile application sends oauth token in plaintext </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have any of you looked into the windows 10 data collection that Microsoft performs?  

Even though I have opted out of data collection and the user experience stuff, using fiddler I see regular json HTTP POST calls to microsoft.com and bing.com with a list of running processes, and list of installed applications, and some other information.

It appears to be the "searchui" process that's doing this.

One of the URLs it sends the HTTP POST request to is https://www.bing.com/threshold/xls.aspx

Lots of metadata being sent, stuff like:  

"{removed UUID}\\BurpSuitePro\\BurpSuitePro.exe","DName":"Burp Suite Professional","LAD":"2017-04-18T18:34:22.590Z","AppLnch":22,"Args":0,"MDN":0,"Ext":".exe"}

"System.ParsingName","Id":"Microsoft.Office.lync.exe.15","DName":"Skype for Business 2016","LAD":"2017-04-20T12:02:11.691Z"

"System.ParsingName","Id":"{removed UUID}\\Microsoft Office\\Office15\\lync.exe","DName":"Skype for Business 2015","LAD":"2017-01-24T21:49:26.227Z"

Id":"{removed UUID}\\Wireshark\\Wireshark-gtk.exe","DName":"Wireshark Legacy","LAD":"2017-04-18T02:13:47.773Z","AppLnch":0,"Args":0,"MDN":0,"Ext":".exe"}

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows 10 data collection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't - now I'm excited. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christopher Hitchens, George Orwell, Bill Bailey, Alan Davies with Stephen hosting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prioritize reading over watching TV, over dicking around online, over social interactions (some times).  

I haven't read as much as I would like the past couple of months, because I just bought a house so I have been really slacking as I've only read 13 books so far this year, I'm already 11 behind schedule. Life happens though, so whatever.

Now that things are settling down again I'll get back into it. I love watching QI, so some times that will get priority over reading for a while. No harm in that either, QI is amazing and if you're unfamiliar with it you're the worse for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Walden thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never read Walden before, despite it being on my "to read" list on Goodreads for years. I was strolling downtown with my wife yesterday afternoon after a late lunch/early dinner and we stopped by a bookstore and the book practically jumped into my hands. I love it when this happens.

I stopped the book I'm currently reading by John Updike - Roger's Version - in favour of Walden. I'll go back to Updike's novel afterwards.

I read 55 pages of it yesterday. The first 30 pages or so, were a bit of a slog honestly. It's an interesting style of writing, but it appears to be pretty smooth sailing from 31 - 55. I'm loving the discussion around house ownership, given that I just bought a house a month ago.  

Any fans of Walden here? Looks like I'm in for a real treat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you beat your wife with that beard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of folks in the states complaining about this letter, saying it was illegal as it violated the Logan Act.

Makes it more admirable in my opinion.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton led Trump by 2-3 points.  
Remain led Leave (brexit) by 1-2 points.  
Macron leads Le Pen by 26 points in runoff polls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I Ate] Steamed seafood platter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noted, thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is World Book Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that finnish people recieves a top hat and a sword when completing their doctoral degree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salisbury. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Gates, circa 1990. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I've eaten at Backfins Crabhouse which was amazing. I'll try Farm Table next. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, NC General Store on the main street. They have lots of it in there. A few bottles in the fridge and then there's boxes of it under some of the shelves if you want to get a 24 pack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing. I'm a fan. Going to go and take a tour of the factory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I would ruin the title with my potatoes fingers. Arse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time to see what a the fuss is about. Found some in downtown Wake Forest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah. There's a small forest out the back of our house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think this is my kid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went back to check and you're right. Nicely done. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure which species this fella is but he caught dinner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seen at the march today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop that :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tastes great though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Easter egg has had better days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ramen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question haha. It was between Raleigh and Creedmor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah this went from nothing to insane in honestly 10 - 15 seconds. That was all it took. The fire brigade were there ridiculously quickly. Some idiots were driving by real close, real slow, trying to see... I was shouting at folks to get back that it could freaking explode.

Luckily they put it out in time. No idea how the driver is/was. I hope they're ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christopher's son Alexander is teaching a class on terrorism at George Washington University this summer in DC. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dutch pastor arrested in Cambodia on child pornography charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avoid highway 50 - closed due to a truck on fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just dropped my breakfast all over myself before I had my first sip of coffee. You're already miles ahead of me haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would any of you be interested in an essay writing competition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would any of you be interested in an essay writing competition?

To follow in Hitchens' footsteps, all topics except for sport(s) would be permitted. Something like a 1,000 word minimum with no maximum limit.

I understand we're all busy, I just bought a house and I'm in the middle of moving, but I was thinking we could have a month to produce *something*.

It would not matter if the essays were terrible. The point of the exercise is to get the creativity flowing and to get one thinking critically. 

It doesn't even have to be a competition. We could create an area in the sub for members that wish to have their thoughts heard and criticized. A place to foster discussion. 

Any thoughts on this? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called fat and lazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What dumb or embarrassing things have you done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a young fellow of kings.  
Whose mind was upon higher things.   
But his real desire.  
Was a boy in the choir.  
With an ass like a jelly on springs.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favourite limerick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad. It was against John Lennox. 

https://youtu.be/jB6BTb8Dinw
It was the debate after this interview. 

I will get a link later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He lost against Bill Donohue. Not because Bill was right, or anything like that, but because Hitchens didn't have the responses required which is a tad unfortunate. But whatever, everyone can have an off day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't mistreat the planet just because Mother Nature mistreated your face! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just assume the gender of that protest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did lose a debate you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is /r/ChristopherHitchens afterall - nevermind how people **feel** what's important is how people **think**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all is the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rich were taxed at 92% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long has it been? Perhaps they're checking if they are part of a larger operation or something. I dunno though, that sucks. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed - I should have said that honestly. Wouldn't expect people to call 911 over this but I'm sure they get calls for dumb stuff all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's just happy his friend is ejaculating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved to the states in 2011. Every year since then, my credit card info has been stolen from an employee of a store/restaurant/whatever. Last year a card I only used in one store was stolen the next day. The account had no activity other than the transaction at the store, and then the fraudulent transactions. The store was 100 feet from the police station, across the road. They never caught the guy. Ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victims of robbery and theft, what happened and how did you deal with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I figured I'd ask here first. Definitely reporting him from now on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could be any animal past or present, what animal would you be, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone see that crazy decorated truck on 540 east between exit 7 and exit 9? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some lunatic erected a cross and added some signs that says Jesus is coming. It's fairly distracting, and I saw a few cars swerving as they passed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favourite non default sub? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half of the people in prison in this country suffer from a mental illness, which is often the reason for their arrest. They get no help from the system here. They are punished for being sick. The government doesn't care, as long as they continue making license plates and keep turning a profit.

This country enslaves mentally ill people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be illegal. Money shouldn't be in politics. Lobbying should be illegal it's completely fucked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orwell's novels are not great, but he was one of the best essayists of the past two hundred years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as many dog hours that's for damn sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Currently reading The Portable Atheist. Found this quote by Chapman Cohen extremely important given our current predicament. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facts are facts, and sooner or later we are compelled to deal with them. Theories may ignore them, but the consequences follow just the same. It is not merely our duty to face the facts, it is to our interest to do so. All life is an adaptation of organism to environment, and all healthy mental life is the expression of a harmony between our ideas of facts and the facts themselves. And without posing as a philosophical Gradgrind, one may confidently assert that the man or the philosophy that ignores facts will sooner or later come to grief.

-- Chapman Cohen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought a house (closed on March 22nd).

We got the keys the day we closed. You're supposed to get them at the attorney's office.

Congratulations!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Easter! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How close is the case? Like, a few feet, a few inches?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, did you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to join us over on /r/ChristopherHitchens </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rest easy old stock. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I replaced my clubs recently the the M2 set. Added 40 yards to my drives instantly, and my irons are a lot more consistent. 

Highly recommended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to take your advice. I always leave mine in the car. I will start doing this. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Arrests Prominent International Pastor, Husband of American Citizen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Honestly **you people** and the media are pathetic, I am against trump and his administration and you're saying that this is defending hitler? He was comparing Assad to being worse, agree with it or not the media is trying to spin this to sound pro-hitler. And **you people** are eating it all up.
 Pathetic. **You people** are pathetic, after trump **you people** will elect and even bigger idiot because you aren't capable of independent critical thought.

"You people"? How tolerant of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hijacking top comment - /r/PastorArrested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which tool are they using to fuzz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I started /r/PastorArrested

On average a pastor is arrested daily. Sometimes it's a lot more than that. 

These incidents are reported locally but not nationally. It's a fucking scandal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Isnt the Media Pointing Out That the San Bernardino Shooter Was an Outspoken Christian? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, he mailed me back the three masks in the gif are 4500 each. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got this email from him:

Thank You for your interest!
Here are my current prices, Standard shipping is $25 USA, $90 International:  
Cry baby $550 or "Reject" $300  
Disgusted Baby $450 or "Reject" $350  
Happy Baby "Reject" $500 (Signed and numbered sold out)  
Trump $4500  
Putin $4500  
Kim Jong Un $4500  
Hillary $4500  
Bernie Sanders $4500  
Tyrion $4000  
Heisenberg (Walter White) $4500  
Ron Jeremy $4500  
Mike Tyson $4000    
Charlie Sheen $4500  
Newborn $3500  
Little Girl $3500  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's going on with the smoke all over the Morrisville area? It stinks, and is covering the sky. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read David Hume and Spinoza and you will find out why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/PastorArrested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP please join the sub I started to keep track of this -  /r/PastorArrested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he never says "we hit it into the water today", he takes the blame for the shots he misses.

OP I suggest you find another sport to watch honestly. Not sure golf is for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Faldo's commentary of The Masters is always a joy to watch and listen to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've loved Nick's commentary ever since he became an analyst after retiring. He's won 3 times at The Masters so knows the course extremely well. His commentary of The Masters makes it all the more special.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. Reminds me of the guy that owned the last house I rented. He wanted to fix everything himself. Our heating went in a blizzard. He came out and "fixed it"... he rebooted it and left... had to get him back again. Ended up without heating in like -20 degrees for almost 6 hours or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's rough man, sorry. Do you lads have a HOA there? Get them on his case. He shouldn't be doing that shit without HOA approval.

Get him to hire professionals in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of practice, and lessons. When I started again a couple of years back I couldn't hit the ball 20 feet. It would run along in front of me. I felt so awkward and out of place. But I kept going to the range to try to find my old swing. It took months of persistence, and fun to be honest. I loved the challenge. 

When I felt in a position to join a club, I joined one with a great PGA Pro Swing Coach - one of the top 40 in the USA. I had a few lessons with him, and he was able to see some things I was doing wrong instantly - stuff that would have taken me years to figure out myself honestly.

I injured myself in Oct/Nov, went back out there in February and I was swinging poorly. I went and had a lesson and he saw that I was favouring side I had injured, when swinging. 

I made a tiny adjustment and I was hitting them brilliantly again.

I just haven't been out lately because we bought a house (moved in last week, boxes are all around me as I type this), and I've been dealing with all of that since early March. 

The issue I have now, is that I'm over an hour from my course, and my swing coach. Going to have to find another course closer to me. The house is worth it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not too old. I played as a teenager, didn't play again until a couple of years ago. I was shooting in the 100s, got down to scratch last summer. Haven't played much since November mind you, but getting back out there on Tuesday.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sergio Garcia climbs a tree to hit one-handed shot at Bay Hill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sergio's to lose now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sergio 2/5, rose 15/8
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's kind of fitting for a Rose to be in the Trees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not today. My nerves are shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I was a genius and timed it perfectly. Dammit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90 words isn't an essay, it's a thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been sad since the sun started to go down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet   Sour Chicken, Seafood Lo Mein, Shrimp Spring Rolls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could've three putted too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How soon until they tee off again? I have to pick up some chinese food... fuck lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drunk assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY FUCK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tuesday for me. Played maybe two rounds since November.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The south.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bababoey brigade are out in force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is some finish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rose didn't look good after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sergio, get that monkey off your back and do it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pieters did very well for his first time in the Masters... if it wasn't for a bad day yesterday who knows what would have happened. Great experience for him. I honestly do believe he has a Masters in him, maybe even a couple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make this final hole your bitch Pieters!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sun is starting to set. I don't want this to be over. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where the hell did Sergio's ball land? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping the Belgian takes it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah. He didn't slice it into the trees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sink that eagle Pieters!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sergio vs Rose. Winner gets Gibraltar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well out Sergio. That was a great shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon Pieters! Fuck yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really pisses me off. I've gotten in trouble for trying to silence drunk people at these events.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crowd is drunk. Fucks sake I hate this shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pieters getting closer. Needed that eagle but delighted with the birdie. Go get another Thomas!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I BELIEVE! 

EDIT: **fuck** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, his masks are made better for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just said this a few minutes ago to a mate of mine. It's brilliant!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon Pieters. I believe!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's great to see. He had a 341 yard drive a couple of holes ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your bias is showing fella. SAD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huge par from the trees, and the bunker. 

You could see what it meant to him too after it went in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
