<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1121</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if your goal is to be entertained, there are thousands of good movies you havent seen yet. Why give your money to a mediocre one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know.  The movie looked bad, reviews agreed.  Whats cynical about criticizing bad movies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they dont.  They do expect it to be good though.  Which apparently this isnt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.avclub.com/review/king-arthur-legend-sword-dull-blockbuster-sends-du-255019?

AV Club found it dull, gave it a c+ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AV Club: King Arthur: Legend Of The Sword is a dull blockbuster that sends up dull blockbusters. C+ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen those Daily show videos where they go to the Trump Rallies and find people saying stupid stuff? Like why didn't Obama prevent 9/11 and stuff like that.  I watch those, but would never assume them to be indicative of the truth of the average trump supporter.  

This video holds about as much weight.  We dont know how many people he talked to total before choosing the responses he prefers. Its not serious journalism, and anyone taking it seriously has sadly low standards on what they are willing to believe.

Besides, who cares about New York.  There is no voter ID law in NY.  The average person on the street doesnt have to go through with that sort of thing. 

Besides, we arent talking about NY.  We are talking about Wisconsin. Where the population is poorer, and access to transportation is worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> using a youtube video as evidence

whup tee do, glad he was able to find circumstantial evidence.  

literally all of the things you listed can be done with out of state IDs.  Voting in WI requires EITHER a passport or an in state ID.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said, Desperate times call for desperate measures. I cant imagine Tarkin, Vader, or Palpatine found it easy to do what had to be done, but I am sure they slept well knowing that the empire would live another day.

Of course, Alderaan would have been unnecessary if the Rebels had not attacked US first, or if Princess Leia had been honest in the location of the Rebel Base.  Its a shame Yavin IV wasnt destroyed as well.

To put it in perspective, when the Empire fell, countless people died.  Soldiers, civilians, men, women, children, etc. Some from the anarchy and warfare, as the new "republic" failed to lock down control.  Some from starvation, as the empire was the only way to effectively manage the whole realm. Many continue to die from crime, which palpatine kept in check.

I would destroy a thousand alderaans if it meant a return to order for myself and my children.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> desperate times call for desperate measures.  Imagine being Tarkin, or Palpatine, or any of the fine men in charge.  We know they aren't bad guys, but they had a choice in that moment, and they chose to serve the empire selflessly, at the cost of their own humanity.  True, there was a known Alderaan Terrorist on board the Freedom Star, but we know for a fact that Alderaan has been opposed to the Empire from the get go.  We know, even if we cant prove, that Bail organna is colluding with rebels.  We can be sure there are were likely whole terrorist networks on Alderaan.  

In that moment, Tarkin had to make a choice, between preserving the empire and protecting the lives of an entire galaxy, or acting justly towards one small planet.  He did what had to be done, as I am sure we all would have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> buy alcohol or cigarettes

can be done with out of state IDs.  You are also unlikely to be carded once you hit 30 or so, at least in my experience.

open a bank account

could have been done previously, before their ID expired

apply for food stamps

i dont know the requirements.  Could possibly have been done via other means

apply for unemployment

does that require an in state drivers license?

 medicaid/social security

same

but i should be able to vote without an ID

yes.  IF IDs cost money, its kind of like a poll tax.  If IDs dont cost money, they should be both easy and convenient to receive. I should not need an in state ID if I can prove residency through other means.  Clerical issues should be easy to resolve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i prefer this soundtrack, but I would agree that the timing isnt as good as the one written for it. Just thought it was a cool thing to watch.  If i made this and had sound editing ability, id try to weave a few different things in there, Bodi on the surface and the physical collision of the hammerhead doesnt work great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> since we are talking about WI, and I have myself had to go to the Milwaukee DMV, I can say it is open during business hours.  so your point is bullshit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do they?  I havent seen or heard much of it, but I must be mistaken.  


My point was, Nolan doesnt seem to be held in the regard of improving with each film.  TDK and Memento seem to be held as high points, with every other film regarded equally highly, but not necessarily improving over his previous efforts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you need specific kinds of ID for registering to vote in WI. Specifically, a WI drivers license OR a passport + pay stubs.  If you live in WI, have no passport, and used other forms of ID to do your I-9, youre shit out of luck. If you got your drivers license in your home state 20 years ago and renew it online every few years, you're out of luck.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1). If you dont drive, getting a drivers license makes no sense

2). If you dont drive, getting to a DMV may be a challenge if it isnt near you

3). If you dont drive, and rely on busses, it will be hard to get to a DMV in the limited time allowed on a lunch break

4). If you have other things going on in your life, such as kids, certain types of jobs, etc, getting to a DMV between 9 and 5 could be a challenge

is it fair to make it harder for poorer urban communities to get IDs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that historically urban communities (regardless of race) have less need for cars, are less likely to have a drivers license. I think communities that make less money/work hourly jobs are going to be less likely to be able to get time off work to go to the DMV, which is only open  during the workday.  I think IF the government is going to require an ID to vote, it should not be a hassle to receive said ID </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nolan has not arguably improved though.  TDK is considered by many to be better than its sequel, Inception (while getting good reviews) is rarely talked about, and Interstellar isn't held in the same high regard it was immediately following its release.  Obviously, Nolan is very talented and everything he does is universally liked. But to be honest, out of everything I have seen of his, Memento was the best, and it was an early film of his </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, bring up feminism on your average subreddit. Or black lives matter.  Suddenly we sound like the comment section on a conservative facebook page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rogue One - Battle of Scarif with John Williams soundtrack. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newt Gingrich is an asshole, people who support "family values" are assholes (coded words for anti lgbt), and people who claim their morals are better than mine are assholes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> far left

Reddit is center left at best, and a lot of reddit is far right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because he isnt doing such a good job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *footage not found*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd work if there was competition for ISPs. Which there isn't. That's why everyone sticks with the ISP they have, even though they hate them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, our president is a Republican. So yeah, you do support Republicans more than Democrats  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an issue limiting all protests to the legal kind. Something about asking the government's permission makes it seem like they could be easily ignored. If a protest causes no inconvenience, it won't make a big difference. No one will care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you're so edgy. I'm guessing...13? 14?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When was the last time you could safely leave your doors unlocked in a halfway major city? The 1700s? Early 1800s? Even then... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> youre being downvoted because a lot of people are excited for the movie.  Granted, you're only at -1 so of the many people who saw your comment, most just scrolled past.  2 people didnt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, the book did not end with Deckard being a replicant, if I recall. I hope this movie deals with the idea of a dying world, like the book did, which the first movie avoided. As for how it works with the blade runner ending, I am sure they worked out a way for it all to make sense...or at least i hope they did.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they said earlier that he wouldnt appear until the third act, though i would hope that they wouldnt give away so much of the 3rd act in the trailer.  Gosling is the main character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the first one is a must watch in general.  Just make sure to watch the most recent "final cut", instead of the older "directors cut" or "theatrical cut".  Its safe to say the final cut is the canonical version in terms understanding the sequel, and it is the only one Ridley Scott had complete creative control over the editing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didnt like making blade runner because of personality clashes with Scott, but I thought he was pretty pleased with the outcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but he seems like an asshole, which is all I think when I see him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a roku USB thingy, so im not thrilled to be considering purchasing another playback device.  What are the issues with the browser playback? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea, but I think he said it isnt working for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i remember being super excited for this when I was a kid, and falling asleep when I actually got it on video months later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Filmstruck currently worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been looking forward to filmstruck since it was first announced, but havent got around to actually signing up for it yet.  I would like to (so I can branch out in watching more movies and such), but how is the current state of the browser app?  I would ideally want it on roku, but I know it isnt out yet (i have an HDMI cable to nbd).  Is the current state good?

EDIT
Thank you for the feedback.  Based on the strength of the library (as you guys were saying), I decided to sign up and see how the trial goes. I watched Bananas by Woody Allen on an Apple laptop, connected to my TV via an HDMI cable.  The quality was overall good, some splotches in the shadows, but overall comparable to Netflix. The interface leaves a little to be desired, a few more recommendations or means of sorting (also, something indicating the language the film is in). Hopefully a Roku app comes out soon, but in the meantime I am happy so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how dare the least popular candidate lose the election </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean, it isnt all that funny, but funnier than the joke i downvoted, for instance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick question, have you met any muslim people in real life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, the jokes just weren't funny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so, good on you.  Worth reminding you that 45 did not do that, and spent ages trying to convince us all he was born in Kenya.  Same with more than half of all Republicans.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference is that your joke doesn't work half as well as colberts did. So it's not a double standard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's the obamacare repeal going?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll get the job done  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try reposting, that's a good trick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> paid 


If you actually believe that any significant portion of commenters are paid, you're stupid.


Anyways, I'm liberal for free and I couldn't be happier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You keep using this word, jabroni...and it's awesome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love ben garrison's avatar.  Its like he pictures himself as some Clint Eastwood type, but in real life he looks like he should be managing a canadian trailer park.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their political section isn't run like the rest of the site and hires actual journalists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also a real American here, under the ACA I stayed covered while looking for my first good job, and my first good job was required to give me insurance options by law.  Beyond that, the coverage of birth control by the ACA has helped a lot of people in my life, as has the funding of planned parenthood.  As a real American, I am very concerned about people who will see their rates rise due to pre existing conditions, some of which are beyond their controll.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rotten tomatoes found overall positive reviews.  Said it was a good movie, if maybe not as good as the original  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> implying imdb is a good source of anything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get the Fuck outta here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, segregation was basically that, and its illegal now (and criminalizing it was constitutionally upheld).  So private organizations cant just do whatever they want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> do you actually not see a difference between rules for joining a seminary and denying adoption based on sexual orientation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they feel like real movies, the Marvel movies all kind of feel commercials for other marvel movies sometimes.  A lot of branding, not a ton of personality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> services do not have a right to discriminate.  Religion is not an excuse
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is wholefoods still open

/r/me_irl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well thought out editorial from a respected publication: few hundred upvotes, 20 comments

Trump critical clickbait: several thousand upvotes, hundreds of comments


good to see where our priorities are... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of lower middle class people would not be able to afford life saving heart surgery.  You're basically telling them to either never have kids or get huge credit card debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did you condone any courses of action to lead us to war?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've yet to see a liberal publication say the FGM is okay, or acceptable. 100% of any press related to FGM is (rightfully) very negative </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not believe that the majority of Americans hate LGBT individuals, but the majority of republican voters are willing to turn a blind eye to legislators that do. Like you said, they dont care.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No body gives a shit about the gay community

thats the problem.  you have troublemakers in the GOP trying to do weird bathroom laws, allow conversion therapy, rollback protections for LGBT individuals in the workplace, and the GOP voter base doesnt care. Not caring is more homophobic than colbert implying trump sucks putin's dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reads like something out of subreddit simulator lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good blu ray players have algorithms to make the upscale look okay via smoothing and whatnot. better than just playing it on a big tv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for a true restoration, the digital effects could be re-rendered to 4K. The liveaction scenes are stuck, but Lucasfilm might be able to at least figure out a way to make it look good at 4k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the republicans have failed to agree on much other than trumps appointments so far.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> some of which had very few people in them.  Doesnt sound fair to me.  Why should the majority of Americans lives be dictated by people in Montana? 

If you look at the counties Clinton won, 60% of the population lives in them.  The majority of Americans do not live in rural areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> guys, we can do better than shareblue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> majority of americans

you mean majority of Americans living in predominantly rural areas.  Since the majority of people voted for democrats, and nearly every densely populated area voted for democrats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets be honest, there's a lot more exciting things to look at than a forest.

not really... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is no doubt why his tweets about healthcare have produced a good healthcare solution


oh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2017

not understanding the relationship between establishment power and racism

ignoring systematic racism   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lies

Thats great, after 8 years of the GOP and trump lying about Obama (being a muslim, being born in kenya, being the antichrist, being a socialist). After 8 years of all the shit you put us through, you're going to complain about lying?

have fun with that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i mean, its hard to protest Chechnya from the USA, so theres that. Its on the social media news frequently in the circles im in, which is a largely liberal/womens marches crowd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Climate change is just a globalist plot to wrest power from businesses

1). Are there any peer reviewed studies to back this up?

2). Is big business really worth defending? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I've read, its impossible to do a good study on it.  there are simply not enough men not playing violent video games, and there are too many other factors influencing if people become violent or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i liked tiny furniture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its easier when you have the actor there in person.  But even so, young tony stark looked creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why are you trying to kill unarmed people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are a bunch of knock off cards against humanities. At least part of the reason is that small hobby and games stores no longer carry it (they are exclusive to a few big chains) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...or he said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe, more likely youd just get hit with a missile or something </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just pointing out that owning a gun does not put you in a good position to fight the government.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good luck rising up against drones and tanks with commercially available weaponry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> impeaching a President =/= coup. All Presidents impeached have been democratically elected.  People have legitimate concerns over if Trump is following the law, and most people opposed to him do not think he has done anything impeachable yet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> return power to the people where it belongs

Ill take my groupthink over yours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> couldnt be less excited for this, unfortunately.  Maybe it will surprise me, but i have doubts.  the trailers are just so devoid of color </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the average college grad isnt making 70k, not right off the bat anyways.  Most of the ones I know are between 30k and 50k, plus student loans. A few lucky ones (and specific STEM fields) get a good paying job day one, but not a ton </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the combination of all the things and the way you write it that makes it seem unrealistic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're thinking of /r/oldpeoplefacebook  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space quest 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoops, typo.  That should read Shouldn't  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont care why, i care that the problem exists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, theres gotta be some spacequest fans at Lucasfilm.  The hero of Episode 7 was a space janitor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if he wanted

not exactly.  I mean, impeachment is just the process.  It doesnt mean he is actually convicted of anything.  Clinton was impeached, but found innocent.  If trump is impeached and found guilty, then he is booted.

I mean, i guess he could just pull a coup and stay in power, but thats against the rules </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly, films should be shown in the medium they were originally presented in.  Black and white films shouldnt get color conversions, color films should not get turned black and white.  Remember, the artists behind the scenes crafted their films to look best for their respective mediums, in regards to color or lack thereof.  

I wish more modern movies would choose black and white, since I like the look.

Anyways, to answer your question, Francis Ha, A girl walks home alone at night, and goodnight and goodluck

EDIT: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you serious?  that movie was front page when it was announced, the trailers, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always loved the Life Aquatic.  it isnt perfect, and my favorite Anderson film is "moonrise kingdom". Life Aquatic has a strange quality to it.  It feels almost like an animated movie, done with actors.  I agree with you, it is very emotional for me.  Especially Ned's death, and in general Steve's depression throughout the film is very effective. 

As for the technical construction of the film, I dont know that sloppy is the word I'd use.  The tone changes towards the end are a bit jarring, but other than that, I think it was pretty carefully done. Some of the weirder/sloppier aspects may have been by design, since Steve was a failing documentary filmmaker gradually getting worse and worse. At least thats how I interpreted some of those things (like the bizarre special effects). 

Its not his weakest film.  I like it more than Grand Budapest, which I quite like, but I find that it doesnt hit me on an emotional level. grand budapest feels like a living doll house sort of movie.  Its great fun, but it fails to utilize everything it has going for it into a more emotionally affecting finale. Like I said earlier, it isnt as good as moonrise kingdom, which really has the best balance of everything we typically see in Wes Anderson's films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episode 1 was the only one explicitly "for" kids of the PT.  Lucas struggled with comic relief, but I wouldnt say that 2 or 3 are child oriented.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honestly, at this point it wont make a difference.  Go out and make some memories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hate speech

does not mean what you seem to think it means.

Anyways, Trump bullied our former president.  Why would anyone want to be associated with him?  The GOP bullied the wife of our last president, why would anyone be associated with them?

you have a short memory, friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he just looks presidential... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its negativity for negativity's sake.  of course I downvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> buying physical copies of PC games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi, ho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why would the PC be grainer lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldnt support that sort of thing at all.  Of course, I would definitly support cutting the budget in other ways.  Foreign wars, for instance... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
