<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5081</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is. I just finished it yesterday and it's been great. Very atmospheric!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which is? I'm not familiar with it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This time, Elon Musk is wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your reply - I missed the previous post. I'll wait for the next patch then! In the summer I'll upgrade my GPU as well so there's that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Obduction finally playable with a 970? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys

As per subject. I held out playing it as I wanted to enjoy the experieence. Anyone had luck playing it with a GTX970?

My other specs are: i5 6400k, 16GB ram, SSD.

I'm craving a good VR adventure game and Obduction seems right up my alley. If performance is still an issue, I might check out Wilson's Heart!

Thanks for your help!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for trying out! I am still skeptical because I do love myself a bit of cyberpunk but no native version scares me, and the developer has no intention of releasing one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, sorry just read or I would have linked there guide for you. Did you try Technolust? Any good with revive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! I will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup, same. I got it in the bundle and installed it right away. The atmosphere is great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it's old but I'm so into Bowie these days

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zLnPd7lzT4g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing "Inside" - it's Limbo's successor and casual enough to play 5/10 minutes during breaks. And Fifa 17.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No native Vive support tho... ReVive... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a separate network just for the Nvida GameStream. I'd use that same network for the Wireless solution (should it use the 5Ghz spectrum). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great write up. The community in this sub has changed greatly in the past year - now it feels like it's made of spoilt rich kids who don't understand a single thing about tech, but since they have the latest cool pricey toy, they feel entitled to everything.

Developing games takes time and money. From a technical standpoint, Batman VR is almost perfect. Incredible graphics with plenty of options, the best reverse kinematics I've seen in VR so far, super atmosphere, good story, superb voice acting. 

It's much better than seeing a movie in a theatre, and cheaper. I loved it and wish there was more like it. I'm actually tired of indie games - after the first *wave* of them (pun intended), devs aren't pushing indie games out that are creative (like usually happens normally with indie; I don't have the budget for fancy stuff so I offer you great ideas and gameplay), so a polished game/experience like Batman was a breath of fresh air.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're both part of what defines quality. And this game has both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Component company. People that will find small but important breakthrough tech that will be used in 2019 HMDs. Eye tracking, spatial audio, high-quality lenses, etc... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, I was surprised! Also, they'll ship with a plugin/sdk to enable eye tracking foveated rendering in the main engines (Unity/Unreal). 

It seems too good to be true! I thought eye-tracked foveated rendering would have been here in 2018/2019. I like when I'm wrong this way! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thing claims ~ 5/6 ms latency.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if that's true, it's huge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Troy and Abed in the moooooooorning </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donde esta la biblioteca? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  90% of VR games are small indie games

And I totally get it! However, both Unity and Unreal are implementing these options in their main engines. Source2 already has it built in iirc. Which means that's gonna be easier and easier.

Plus, what I think I want to say is, after you put out your game, if 970 is not the entry card, work towards it. Performance is the first thing in VR - it's what creates immersion!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yw! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You choose one or the other. Multi res shading seemed qualitatively better - they're similar but different. 

If you want to read about it: 

https://developer.nvidia.com/vrworks/graphics/multiresshading </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me feel worse :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing, interesting insight (albeit it is what I expected by frequenting this sub!) :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, but I see a terrible shift in the force - people feel entitled as fuck for EVERYTHING nowadays, without a real understanding of ANYTHING.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for being reasonable! There's not many of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And kids, that's how you program a game for VR. For the second time in a short space (Batman, Rick and Morty) my 970 has demonstrated itself to be a good enough card for VR. 

For all those devs that require a 980, 1070 as minimum: optimise, optimise, optimise (and use foveated rendering) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here! But a Roomba please :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it. I still have to play B W cause I don't want this game to end  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, even tho I use homebridge only to have my favorites switches etc in my Mission Control on iOS. Homekit just isn't there yet with customisations etc, while with HomeAssistant I managed to have a setup to make Iron Man envious ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait, how do i hung up pictures and swords and where? Did I miss something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are a bit of a geek and have the will to set up a little server app (mac or Raspberry), Homeassistant is what you're looking for.

come visit us at r/homeassistant !!



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you. It's a new medium. In GTA I cannot grab and shoot 99% of the world like I expect to do in a VR game.

Of course, 5 years from now it's gonna be different. But we all were conscious to be early adopter, were we? I was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 13:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maugly - how does it work if I wanted to be a teacher? I am bilingual and worked in language education for businesses for a good amount of time before starting my IT career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point about radiations. Im thinking more about transfer efficiency than costs here. But good point indeed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interplanetary communication will also resemble how Google etc ship massive amount of data when needed: with a courier service. I know seems stupid but if you need 200TB transferred, chances are physical mail with a copy is still faster (in most areas of the world).

So until we'll crack quantum communication, Netflix will probably send small, economic space-mail packages with ruggedized hard drives as soon as a new season is ready, so for example, shipping game of thrones season seven now would arrive just in time for the July premiere.

Also, I do believe we'll need a base on Luna or just orbiting Earth for launch of those small probes with data, so not too have to break orbit every time with the single package </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 48 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly it's 115 grams of difference. And there's pros and cons to the new cable- it's not a change that favors consumers but manufacturing processes.

I would keep it, but if you want to return it, it's understandable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sir I'm sorry to hear that! :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to go watch Bojack Horseman then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you! I do and appreciate something so well done! Quality over quantity my friend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, we're all different! But I prefer to pay more for a short but very good experience than less for a longer but not that amazing one :) making a game is like making a movie, it takes a lot of people and a lot of work to make that small 1.5 hours of content!

That said, I enjoy indie movies and indie games as well, but I do not expect to pay the same price nor to have the same production quality that of a AAA studio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I've played Onward for 50+ hours, but the level of polish is not even in the same league. I mean, do you understand the amount of money/work to reach that level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read another guy having the same issue, and apparently he fixed it with a complete driver uninstall / clean install. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are you SuperSampling? Because at native res you shouldn't have any issue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally! Your reasoning makes sense, I was addressing a more wide spread sentiment about VR pricing :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evento more impressive then! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed - also, the amount of objects, polygons, reflections is very high throughout the game, and there was not a single hiccup. So if I had to bet, I'd say they are doing some juju with forward renderings etc. 

Do you know which engine they use? Is it Source?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree, because it's one of the most hilarious, polished, performing VR games I've tried. And I'm here since wave1, so I know what I'm saying. Without the Rick and Morty IP that game would stand on its own, but all things considered (and including the amount of people I'll throw in this game) I think it's worth the money. 

Developing a game is hard, developing a VR game is harder and the market is very small. If you go to the movies with your SO and buy popcorns and a soda - here's your 30 bucks, for 1.5 hours, which are not even remotely comparable to a VR experience.

That's the issue I think - we keep comparing VR games to regular games, while it's a totally different new medium with which we happen to play games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Settings of SteamVR There's a performance pane, you can activate it for frame loss + be notified in the headset. 

Also, in OpenVR advanced settings you have missed frames and reprojected frames.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, behave, prickly-muffin! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great development. Totally worth the money for such a cool experience!

(also, I love your username ;)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best 45 minutes in a long time my man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Performance in Rck and Morty VR... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is AMAZING. No stutter, no reprojection, just a buttery smooth delight of a game. 

And I have a 970. So kudos to the devs and thanks for doing your job right and optimising the shit out of this game. 


My man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the ideal world I'll have the PSVR comfort, the Touch controllers, and the Lighthouse tracking system. 

But because we aren't in the ideal world, go with the Vive, cause the tracking system is hands down the best. And before people say 'yeah but PSVR and Oculus are just as good ' - no, they aren't. And a slight issue in tracking kills immersion. And immersion is the key in VR. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's the future anyway. I like that you can interact from VR with your non-VR friends, but of course as VR adoption is gonna scale up, this kind of social is gonna be great. I have my best friends scattered all over the world, and while VRChat (my fave) and AltSpace are great, they're stand-alone, meaning that to interact you have to install the app and create the account - the winner is the one that's gonna offer a seamless experience. 

Hell, Steam Voice Chat doesn't work yet, so any advancement is welcomed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok- totally with you. I would be pissed of as well if my GPU would not use the most common techniques for smooth VR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is. My 970 is. The devs that don't use those cards as minimum entry aren't optimising.

Look at The Lab. Super sharp graphics and zero issues with my 970. 

Indie games aren't a good comparison term. Big studios know that the more they optimise, the more people will buy. Also, many indie devs don't have access to all the hardware to optimise. Maybe they have a 989 and that's all the optimisation they'll try. 

EVE:Valkyrie has one of the best graphics I've seen and it works perfectly on my 970. So again, optimisation is key. 

970/390 = basic experience with low graphics. That should still be the entry for VR. It's a dangerous game that indie devs are playing. 

Of course, now it's almost a year since VR is out, and surely more demanding titles are around the corner (FO4). We're bound to upgrade soonish if not for the prices of latest gen cards. I'm saving up for a 1080ti - just because I want the best experience possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will never rest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you like giant women </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still Remember the 'keep out' locker - me and my friend tried to remade it in our rooms :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can start by adding more controls to gun access!

Harder access to guns = statistically much much much less possibility of dying like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, you're playing it right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It worked for me, thanks!! My friend tried immediately after and I guess they discovered it cause his order was blocked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 10:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other hand, this makes horror games unplayable for me :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 09:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here, I had this attitude the whole game. I'm in a zombie apocalypse. I need to survive. 

It added layer after layer of immersion. Same with Solus Project and so on. 

I guess the biggest factor for great immersion is still your fantasy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow - thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are pretty accurate "guesses" tho... I've seen those figures referenced in a lot of places. Of course until there's gonna be official sales figures, those are just deductions, but from what I've seen, that's proportionally accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's unreal! care to share how did you set this up? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's why you vape dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 11:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the confirmation. Closing down the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 09:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And 20 MB hard drives that you would make "bigger" with DoubleSpace

and 640kb or RAM "are enough for everything" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 09:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am looking forward to play this game A LOT - why do you suggest the Xbox one bundle?

Plus, if I do buy the xbox game, how do I get a key for the PC version? Or am I missing something?

thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The resolution of the GearVR is higher but that has nothing to do with my statement. Even the custom made screens for Oculus/Vive are 'cannibalisation' from smartphone tech. 

It's a fact, confirmed by Gabe Newell himself:

"The current headsets are essentially piggybacking off phone panels. Now people are looking at display technologies that aren't bastardized phone technologies. Once you start building something just for a VR headset you can go much faster than the phones.

"We're going to go from this weird position where VR right now is kind of low res, to being in a place where VR is higher res than just about anything else, with much higher refresh rates than you're going to see on either desktops or phones. You'll see the VR industry leapfrogging any other display technology. You'll start to see that happening in 2018 and 2019 when you'll be talking about incredibly high resolutions."

Source: http://www.polygon.com/features/2017/2/15/14616192/gabe-newell-interview-vr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm torn, because I agree with your statement in general, but early foveated rendering test show a 30% improvement in performance - pair this with eye tracking and single pass rendering... And maybe.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't buy on G2A. Ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made those calculations myself a while ago but didn't factor in VR specific tech advancements (foveated rendering, eye tracking, single pass stereo) that will lower the specs needed for high quality VR. So I believe with a 1080ti we'll be super fine for next gen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 09:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually that's only partially true - the reason VR displays are still low-res (for VR) is mainly because VR as a market didn't exist and there were no investments in the field, so current gen uses cannibalised smartphone displays, which weren't made for that particular use. There's already superb VR-made displays we're gonna see soon.

Also, because there was no market/hardware, software is very straightforward thus requiring full rendering of the image @90 FPS. 

So now we have lowish res displays that require an insane amount of power.

Both Nvidia and AMD are working on software improvements to maximize VR performance; eye tracking with foveated rendering will also make the entry specs much lower.

My prediction is that a 980ti will be a good enough GPU to drive next gen headsets (retina-level) with the advanced technology in SW/HW.

Source: I'm a software engineer and VR enthusiast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope when gen 2 of VR will be here, prolly 2018, I can buy just the new lighthouse-compatible HMD from whoever makes it, the knuckle controllers from whoever makes them, and any other accessory from whoever makes accessories. 

That's why I bought the VIVE - not for HTC (although I've to say my opinion of the quality of their products improved drastically and 10/10 would buy HTC again) but for the lighthouse system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 09:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife who doesn't really get hyped for VR loved this one
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 09:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second **EVE: Valkyrie** as the best multiplayer space shooting game out there. The graphics are the best I've seen in VR and the amount of polish is insane! I always feel like I am piloting a Viper from BSG. It also has custom keybinding if you have a HOTAS.

If you want a space fighting 'indie' with a small but fun campaign, then **House of the dying Sun** it's good for you.

I have both, I come back to EVE because it's a multiplayer experience and I want to be ready for when the government will need me to defend us from aliens (cit.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just hope for Pavlov to get better graphics then. Onward became popular because it was one of the first Shooters, but it will stay popular because it's a strategic game. If you make it consumable, it will be replaced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True! I don't know if there's a similar peripheral as this one. If there is, great. I tried Bluetooth controllers but the lag ruined the gaming experience :(

I mentioned iOS only because that's how I do it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sources? Genuinly asking, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're welcome! :) enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's the Moonlight app on the official App Store, nothing strange required - then you enable Gamestream from turret Nvidia panel on your PC. 

Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, it's a game changer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a iOS device lying around, you can buy a Gamevice controller and use Moonlight (Nvidia Gamestream client for iOS).

I did it with my iPad mini... Hello, Witcher 3 while in bed.

https://gamevice.com/products/ipad-mini/

EDIT: I suggest this peripheral because I've personally tested it, but honestly, any lightning device will do - AVOID Bluetooth, because there's a slight input lag! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I know they can't run fullscreen. Try to remove the drivers with DDU and reinstall them. 

Also, if you're experiencing this issue also with flat screen games, it's probably software related. Or maybe issues with the SLI sync. I would try with one single card first, and if the problem persists I'd try a format and reinstall from scratches  good luck!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok it's defo not the GPU nor the CPU. I think you should be troubleshooting the usual,iI.e. drivers updates, cover any reflecting surface, etc...

With those specs you shouldn't have a single issue! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your specs? SLI in VR is almost useless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those damn belters ruining everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> his username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the companies appreciate the english-speaking workforce readily available + the existing pool of language talents Dublin/Ireland attracted. 

It is seriously the best contender. We'll see! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok - so you're postulating that those energy bursts might be aliens talking to themselves! That's fascinating and of course, my anthropocentrism didn't allow me to see that at first glance. Thanks for pointing this out.

Still, the communication over vast distance between two distinct races is a big hurdle to establish common grounds :( 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But then, if we're talking about aliens, we need to establish basic communication to understand each other - which would probably start from math, to then discuss physics. How can you do that if there's a ~20 year gap in every communication?

I'm seriously asking, because I haven't solved this problem yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 13:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. But we're talking communication here. Of course, another race might experience time at a much slower pace than ourselves, thus allowing for "real-time" communication which would seem super slow to us. 

(side note: their internet must suck)

Without a reliable, fast-enough communication method, establishing basic comprehension is very, very, very hard. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh yes - I thought we were talking about aliens! :) 

In the case of our race, we'd probably use English or whatever common language we'll choose, and then at this point some sort of lightspeed communication for small packages is good - but again in my opinion, long distances+huge data = physical shipment wins (with current technology) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am still not convinced that it would be useful in this scenario - I mean, we would first need to establish some sort of Rosetta Stone to understand each other, and doing this with 20+ years delay... :( 

On the other hand, if you need a "repository" for all the knowledge of your people to be preserved from extinction, physical copies is the way to go!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Communication would be useless unless it happens on a FTL level. What good can you do if it takes you 20 years just to send and receive a message?

So unless communication on a quantum level is possible (there's been a small glimmer of hope for using quantum entanglement to that avail), any other communication mean is kinda useless. If it's just to say "hello", the easiest would be to send small transmitting probes to the closest star systems with habitable planets, and so on, expanding outwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I didn't see it here and thought kind to share: Half-Life 2 VR mod with full tracked controllers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per title. A great team of devs is working on a full mod for HL2 which will work in VR - not just a VR mode, but full room-scale support* and tracked controllers*!!

Here's an article with a teaser trailer: https://uploadvr.com/half-life-2s-vr-mod-looks-amazing-new-trailer/

I'm so hyped! :)


(roomscale = when you can move in your physical space and your movement is reflected 1:1 in VR)

(tracked controllers = two controllers that allow you to move and use your hands in VR i.e. Vive wands for HTC Vive and Touch for Oculus Rift) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rock on dude, it looks great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell me it's not an April's fool.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to lie down on the roof with the helicopter. like, the whole level. 

but it is defo super polished! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go for it! I bought it and enjoyed it, and wished there was more content! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 13:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well... it is. A well done wave shooter, and the gun feel is great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 09:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the 'hug the floor' simulator? ;)

Humour aside - is defo polished and nice, but: 

A) it's another wave shooter
B) pricey for the amount of content, even for a VR game
C) kinda unbalanced - there's no real strategy to be applied when enemy waves are thick but to lie down. 

At least that's my 2 cents, others might feel different about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no. 

First, real manufacturing issues show themselves in the first few months of use. Anything happening after 6+ months is usually not really related to manufacturing. 

In Europe, as consumers we have two years warranty - but the second year only applies to the issues as stated above, which are very difficult to prove after such a long time. So it's kind of a moot point. 

What I did is: home content insurance for electronic devices. If anything I got on the list gets stolen on broken, I can have the full value back. 

It's great peace of mind for ten bucks per month. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, Elon Musk is working on making it possible right now - so 20 years might become 10.  

https://www.wired.com/2017/03/elon-musks-neural-lace-really-look-like/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commenting to save </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to the devs for the quick turnaround, I hope this solves some main issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you wholeheartedly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 09:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Chronos ever be on Steam?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
