<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2116</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 04:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't trust pretty boys. They generally have a lot of teeth beneath their smiles.

(Which is something I need to learn myself...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Bullroarer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 17:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hometown was small and godly.

Every Sunday we'd all gather at the big brick church and listen to Pastor James tell us we were lesser sinners compared to the outside world, but sinners all the same. We'd all dress in our best and then afterward gossip about those who didn't come under the guise of worrying about their spiritual path. Everyone went to church in our town, our heads bent in supplication.

I never fit in with the other boys. I was small and slender, and not very good at sports, especially the football my brothers excelled in. The first and last time I went hunting, I vomited at the sight of the sliced open doe and embarrassed my father. I hated when my older brothers would roughhouse, running to my room to draw instead.

It was easy to tell my father was disappointed.

I knew, intellectually, that there was a world outside the little town, but it was so hard to see past the thick, impenetrable forest that embraced us. Only a single road connected us to the outside, and I only had left the green cradle a handful of times. The world outside, said Pastor James, was drowning in its filth and sin.

Thus we were all shocked when someone new came to town.

Mrs. Henderson had died four months before, and her house was up for sale one day and the next it wasn't. My bedroom looked across both of our backyards and to the house. From my window seat, I peered out my curtains and saw people moving boxes into it. I clutched at the drapes, white-knuckled, as the stranger stepped out.

He was beautiful, a statue kissed to life, and his dark eyes glittered and his brown hair curled around his sharp jaw. His Oxford shirt was white, the sleeves rolled up his powerful forearms and the top buttons undone to show the top of his broad chest. He made a circuit around the backyard, a soft smile on his ruby lips, and I dropped my curtains closed. My heart was beating wildly, a flush upon my cheeks. I never felt so flustered, my stomach tying itself in knots.

"Luke!" my mother called, tapping on the door. "Let's meet our new neighbor!"

I got out of my window seat and straightened out my clothes. Meekly, I followed behind her as we went to greet our new neighbor. Mom was proud of being the first one to knock at his door. The stranger opened it, and close like this I could smell the rich scent of his cologne and see the shadow of stubble on his angular face. I had no words for the feelings coursing through my veins.

"Hello!" my mother giggled, heady as if the stranger's presence was intoxicating. "My name's Laura, and this my youngest, Luke. We wanted to welcome you to the neighborhood."

"I'm Alexander," he said, voice low and melodic like a fine red wine. His eyes slid from Mom to me, and it felt like I was being flayed open by his cool, assessing gaze. "It was lovely for you to come over."

My mother giggled again, making meaningless small talk with Alexander for a handful of minutes. I forced myself to look away from him for a moment, and instead focused on the thing hanging on the wall behind him.

The skull of a bull, bleached white by the sun, and the dark shadows of its eye sockets were boring into me. I could barely breathe, could barely hear my mother invite Alexander to dinner and him accept. I snapped out of it when my mother bid him goodbye, and I followed behind her back home.

That night, sleepless, I looked out of my window to see the lights of Alexander's home were alight and the man himself coming out carrying a lantern. Its orange light jostled with each step and highlighted the tight, defined lines of his bare torso. I watched him walk without hesitation into the dark expanse of trees and, terrified for reasons I could not explain, I raced underneath my covers to hide for the rest of the night.

---

I helped my mother clean the house while my father watched sports. Pastor James said alcohol was the Devil's drink, so Dad drank Coca-Cola instead of beer.

Mom laid out roast beef and potatoes on our fancy platters, placing them on our nice white table cloth. My parents sat on either end of the table, and Alexander sat across from me; he wore a burgundy sweater, his hair neatly combed. He smiled at me like we shared a secret, and I looked down at my plate.

"Thanks to our Lord Jesus for this bounty," Dad intoned. "Thank You for our good health and prosperity, and for our new friend and neighbor. Amen."

"Amen," we murmured in response, and dug in.

"What brings you to our little town, Alexander?" Dad asked.

"I've been all over the world, from Greece to India," Alexander replied. "I've seen all kinds of things. I just wanted something a little more...quiet."

"That's wonderful!" Mom said. "This is a great place to raise children."

"Mhm," Alexander hummed. "Do you have many children?"

"Three sons," Dad said. "Johnny is at University of Oregon and Mark's at Michigan State. Both are on their football team's starting lines."

"How wonderful," Alexander said. "Are you a football player too, Luke? Where do you plan on going to college?"

"Oh, Luke's more of an artist than a sports guy," Dad said. "He's going to take a gap year after graduation to figure out what he really wants to do."

I remember my mother and father telling me they weren't going to waste money on a "useless degree" and I had to earn the money for art school myself. My cheeks burned.

"We all have our talents," Alexander said. "We all have our places in the world."

"Luke's won awards for his drawings!" Mom said. "He'll show you after dinner."

I was scarlet. "They aren't...they aren't that good."

"I'm sure they're better than you think," Alexander said. The conversation was steered towards more pleasant climes.

After dinner, Mom showed Alexander the art hung in the hallway  little still lives of the forest, the church, some fruits. Childish things. Embarrassing. I slipped into the kitchen to get a drink of water.

The forest ran against the side of the house, and the kitchen sink window looked out into it. The moon was shrouded in black that night, so only the house casted ghostly light on to the woods. The trees moved strangely to me, branches twitching like clutching hands. Beyond the curtains of green needles, I swore I saw something tall and white move among them. I stared, unable to look away, as the white grew closer and closer

"Luke."

I jumped, startled, and Alexander said apologetically, "I didn't mean to scare you."

"It's fine," I said. "I just...I'm fine."

Alexander smiled, closed mouth and piercing. He moved like a tiger in the grass, reaching up to tuck a lock of my honey blond hair behind my ear. My mouth parted, tongue sticky. "You're a talented artist. It's a shame you'll waste away here."

"What?" I murmured. Alexander's hand dropped to my shoulder, grip firm.

"Do you think you'll go to school, after your gap year?" Alexander asked me, voice barely a breath. "Do you think your brothers would come to this place again, to take care of your parents when they are old and frail?"

In the living room, I could hear my parents laughing as if they were drunk. Alexander cupped my face, tilting my head up to stare upon him, and I trembled.

"You shouldn't be contained to banal still life in a dying town," he told me. "You should be part of the world. Capture it with both hands."

I looked down, lashes brushing against my cheeks, and couldn't think of a single word to say. Alexander released me, and I sagged.

"Just think about it, Luke," Alexander spoke to me, and left. I sunk to my knees on the kitchen floor. My parents were still laughing, loud and demented. The forest shuddered.

---

On Sunday, we all went to church.

My family sat in the third row of pews, and Alexander sat opposite of us. He smiled at me before being drawn into a conversation with Pastor James's beautiful wife. My mother always thought her lipstick was too garish for church.

Pastor James came up to the front of the church, and the congregation settled down. He looked red and angry, different from his usual stern calm. And his sermon was different, too  instead of talking of godly communities and being good Christians, he spoke of the corruption of the flesh. He railed against pornography, homosexuality, sex  things he rarely spoke of before.

His voice rose higher and higher, and the congregation began to scream along with him, joining together into a roaring drone. People were standing, stomping and crying in ways I've never seen before. I sat, shocked still, and tried to make sense of what was happening around me.

"Shed off earthly desire, earthly attachment," Pastor James called out. "Burn all the vanities and idols of man!"

I turned my head, and beside me stood Alexander, deathly calm and his hand outstretched. I took it, and he tugged me out of the church. I stumbled out into the freezing air and saw that it was night  which meant it must have been twelve hours since morning service began. Alexander placed his hand on my throat.

"How clean is this air?" Alexander asked me. "How freeing it is, to be outside? Follow me and I will show you true worship."

His hand gripped mine, and he took me past the town into the tall pillars of trees. Colors blurred together, the wind-blown pine trees singing out mourning dirges. Before me, Alexander changed  his hair grew long and wild, his clothes melting into long purple robes, ivy growing up about his feet. He drew me deeper and deeper into the trees until we broke into a clearing.

Up in the sky, the round moon was silver and naked. There was a flat gray stone in the middle of the tall grass, and on it stood a gleaming white bull more docile than a lamb. I fell to my knees in supplication, forehead to the ground in awe of what I saw.

"No more kneeling," Alexander commanded. "Don't you want to be free of this place?"

I looked up at Alexander. He was crowned by the moon, and ivy grew in his long hair.

"Yes," I murmured, and then, loud and ecstatic I cried, "*Yes!*"

"Then rise and show me!" Alexander yelled.

I stood and stripped myself naked, stumbling towards the white bull. I place my hand flat on its nose, and the steam of its breath rose into the air. Alexander gripped on of its horns and tilted its head back, dragging a glittering knife across its jugular. The warm blood drenched me, and when it poured into my mouth, it tasted like wine.

I laughed in ecstasy and Alexander gripped my chin, hot breath fanning across my face. I looked at him, eyes half-lidded and mouth panting.

"Let yourself be liberated," he told me.

I stumbled out into the town from the forest, and in front of the church a bonfire was roaring. The congregation was throwing vanities and idols into it under the direction of Pastor James. When I stepped into the flickering light, Pastor James pointed at me.

"A witch!" he accused. "Look at him who signed his soul to the Devil! Look at him who brings only ruin and damnation!"

Alexander rested his hands on my hips, and I raised a steady arm at Pastor James, my eyes fixed upon him. He started coughing and hacking, bloody phlegm coming up from his throat, and the congregation froze as he fell to the Earth, red foam oozing out his mouth as he choked to death.

"I will be free from this place," I commanded. "I will be free from these people."

One by one, the congregation threw themselves into the fire, not making a single noise as they burned to death. Alexander held me as we watched. My father was last, and he smiled beatifically as he stepped into the flames.

Alexander pressed his plush lips to my ear, hands slicking across the blood on my skin, and whispered, "I have many things to show you."

I tilted my head back against his shoulder, shaking with all my eagerness to *see.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 07:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://thesubject2116.tumblr.com/

Because someone is URL parking on subject2116.tumblr.com, but I never use my blog so maybe I'm just as guilty.

I want to write surrealist horror in honor of a very...odd year, but I can't think of a good idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know :( I use them on special occasions, like that night, just because I love how they smell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I'm the lucky one for finding someone that really understands me! We're just so compatible on every level! 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess! It's all for my husband's research, though. He's developing new ways to profile unknown killers by using a mix of psychological and neurological techniques, but I don't really understand beyond that. Sometimes it's hard keeping up with someone that smart! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 18:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband's been doing this for longer than we've been together! Since his graduate school days, I believe, and it's only been 37. He just really understands how they think and operate, and he's so very clever. Plus, he also tracks down people like hitmen and violent gangsters. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hybristophilia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 06:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a serial killer in my city.

He came into the houses of men and tortured them before slicing their slender throats. He preferred his victims slight, blond, and lonely, coming for them in the night. The radio told me this as I brushed my pale hair before bed, the host's voice bouncing through my cavernous house.

My husband was off at a convention for psychologists and neurologists, leaving me alone in our beautiful house in our quiet neighborhood. I stood in front of my bathroom mirror, smoothing perfumed lotions across my white skin and rubbing balm across my red lips  even if he wasn't there, I wanted to be beautiful for him. The radio was telling single men to buy security systems and guns to protect themselves from the "Blond Killer."

I padded downstairs, draped in a deep blue robe, and closed the curtains on the tall windows. The bright flood lights stretched across the manicured lawn, swallowed up by the fog rolling across the city. In it danced strange shadows, and I closed the blinds not to see them. I armed the security system and went back upstairs, turning off the lights as I went.

In my bedroom, my robe slid off and pooled to the floor. Under the covers, I sent a text to my husband - *love you, miss you* - and fell asleep after his response  *love you too, beautiful.*

I awoke to a hand on my throat.

"Wake up, bitch," the Blond Killer hissed. I gasped, tugged out of my bed by my hair and shoved to the floor. "Where's the fucking basement?"

I stood up on shaking legs, and he pressed a knife to my throat. The murderer and I went down to the basement, the only light strange foggy twilight coming from the cracks in the drapes and turning into pure darkness as we descended the stairs.

My husband's domain was the partially unfinished basement with its cold concrete floors and harsh halogen lights. He did so much of his research down here. The Blond Killer stopped when he saw the big metal slab in the center of the basement and grinned.

"Your owner's already introduced you to my games, huh?" he hissed in my ear. "Heard those rich fuckers are real kinky  I bet you know how to do all sorts of things for money."

I was silent, staring forward at the hanging plastic curtains that divided the basement. The Blond Killer pushed me against the metal surgery table, pelvis banging against it, and my hand slipped under. This wasn't the first time I tangoed.

I painted a gun at his shocked face. My own was perfectly blank.

"Drop the knife."

He did.

"Back up and turn around."

He did.

"You're too sloppy picking your victims," I said, walking him to the plastic curtains. "A slave to your passions. Easy to manipulate."

The plastic curtains parted to show a row of wire dog cages, chained to the wall and water bottles attached to them. He cried out, but I forced him inside and locked the door with a padlock. The key went around my neck, slipping under my sleep shirt.

"My husband studies serial killers," I told him softly. "He's going to love picking your brain."

He screamed obscenities at me as I left, turning off the lights as I went.

---

My husband came home from his conference two days later.

I greeted him at the door, taking off his jacket and tie, pressing a little kiss to his chin  my husband was tall, powerful hands stroking my hips.

"I got a welcome home present for you," I said. "It's in the basement."

He ravished my mouth in his joy. "You're perfect, my darling. What did I do to deserve you?"

I laughed, holding his hand as I brought him down to the basement. Upon being exposed to the light, the subject thrashed but it was weak from lack of food. My husband looked at it, calculating and cold.

"How wonderful," he said. "Nurse, please prepare a sedative for it."

I immediately went to work. He dressed in scrubs.

"We're going to see what makes you tick," my husband said. "Did you know a majority of serial killers experienced a traumatic brain injury in childhood? Was your frontal lobe damaged?"

"Fuck you," it swore. My husband just smiled.

"You'll tell me everything about yourself eventually," he said pleasantly. "They always do."

I gave the sedative to the subject, causing it to fall unconscious. My husband dragged it out of the cage and stripped it of its clothes; I gathered them and threw them into the incinerator. The subject was strapped down ot the metal table, and an IV was inserted. He administered the antidote for the sedative, and the subject came to slowly. When it realized it was trapped, it began to thrash.

"I'm going to get to the core of you," my husband said, matter-of-fact. "Once you have no more useful information, I'm going to crack open your skull and dissect your brain."

He gripped his chin.

"I'm going to see what makes you sick," he murmured, so low and rough it made me shiver.

We pulled up our surgical masks. I turned on the camera. He picked up a scalpel, disinfecting and gleaming.

"Subject thirty-seven, known as the Blond Killer," he said coolly. "Obsessed with torturing and killing blond men  evidence of repressed homosexuality, perhaps. Fortunately, I have a lovely blond assistant to help me understand his sexual psychosis."

I pressed myself against him with an excited whimper; he touched me sweetly as it watched.

"Let us begin with the barbiturate-amphetamine mix," he told me. "If that doesn't work, we'll move on to the drill." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 07:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting! I had a more Miguel Silverstre look in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 07:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've posted a bunch of stuff on this account, but my two most popular stories are [*The Anglerfish*](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4wqyto/the_anglerfish/) and [*How To Butcher Pigs.*](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/57ko1w/how_to_butcher_pigs/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 07:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Poppy Z Brite!!!!

There is a whole genre of horror called queer horror that deals with these themes. I write in it exclusively! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 06:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anne Rice is very important to me.

Seeing these openly queer characters who don't get murdered/killed was so vital in understanding myself and feeling good about it as a gay person. Sometimes her whole thing can be a lot, but I'll always be thankful for Anne Rice for having characters like Lestat and Louis.

(Also owe a lot to her pretty rich and petty vampires for expiring my stories' main monsters, so shout out.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 02:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd read poetry, actually. Lots of very interesting and flowery descriptive terms in there (how the *Iliad* describes dead bodies would put many a /r/nosleep author to shame!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
