<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1847</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was actual PMs within the Linkedin messaging interface.

I reached out to the guy and his linkedin account had indeed been compromised.

Just a heads-up that it isn't just automated phishing scams nowadays.  Good ol' fashion manual manipulation is at play here too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something fishy going on with Linkedin messages? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I got a PM on Linkedin from someone in my network.  It was worded just like some of the GoogleDoc exploits that went around a week or so ago.  

So I PM'ed the guy back and said "this smells fishy were you hacked?" and low an behold I got a response from him telling me "no, the link is good".  So I clicked it and it brings up a clear ripoff/phishing page.

Has anyone run into this?  The actual response from the contact threw me.  Did they maybe hack his Linkedin account and are manually sending these to his contact list or is there something more sophisticated going on here.

Pics of the PM conversation and the web page it linked to: http://imgur.com/a/pNSUD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing your story.

I'm sure Pastor Pat went through a lot of the feelings I am having now so it's nice to know that, even though he may have never know it, his kindness helped create a good person and put you on the right path.

Congrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK man wins Sexiest Beard in his first year entering the contest. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "hunting on acid"

Now that sounds like a safe trip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have kind of a "Weekend at Bernie's" vibe but sure, go for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt Damon, George Clooney, and Jon Stewart.  We're going fishing and bullshitting by the campfire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You get to arrange a weekend trip with three famous people that are the same sex as you. Who are the three people that you think would be cool to hang out with and what do you arrange to do for the weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should clarify that they were on welfare for 3 months when things got really bad but as soon as he had work and was able to stop it they got off.  That's what welfare is supposed to be for - short-term assistance.

But then I would point out what I wrote above is what he told me.  With everything that has happened now I find myself doubting anything that that he told me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't feel like I am being punished.  I'm just very, very disappointed and disillusioned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would tile the basin.

I didn't know how to do it and have done it twice now.  It really wasn't hard at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  I agree.

When I help people or do giveaways here I always check the requester's comment history.  No history or jerky history, no help.

I think my sin here was allowing myself to become emotionally invested in the young man and further to do anything in the physical world now just repulses me.  It is so much easier to not get involved emotionally when it's words on a screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can only hope that he wakes up and smells the coffee before he ends up in prison and his son ends up fatherless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I had already had several conversations with the sheriff when we first started helping the boy so that if anything came up with him the sheriff knew to call me so I could help try to resolve it.

I called him and told him that the boy wasn't working for me or being mentored by me any longer.  I didn't see fit to get the kid in any more trouble.  

I did take my license plate and also withheld his last paycheck until he returned by chainsaw and other tools.

When I called the sheriff he said it right - No good deed goes unpunished. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wiped right. Then swiped right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like helping others here but now I could really just use some advice and a "buck-up" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there.

I have frequented this sub for a while and enjoy helping out those that just need a little financial help, a laptop, or just something to make their life a little easier.

But I really could use some advice from the other "givers" here.

I've been very successful in life and, as my father taught me, I have always wanted to give back - or "pay it forward".  

That said, my job has caused me to emotionally detach from direct involvement with helping people.  I find it easier and less emotional to just help people without ever really getting to know them.  That way I have no expectations of whether they are or aren't a good person and whether or not I am being "scammed".  You just help someone and move on.

Well, I recently broke my golden rule and I'm paying for it emotionally.  My wife and I met a young man that had gotten himself into some legal troubles.  My gut said he was a good kid that just had been dealt a tough hand.  He was living with his girlfriend and their 4yo son in a shoddy trailer getting by on $200/wk.  He was too proud to take welfare and I respected that.

I hired him to work around our place doing yard and barn chores during the week and working with me on the weekend - so that I could have an extra pair of hands but more importantly so that I could teach him some handyman skills and maybe act as a good role model for him (he never had a father figure other than the one that tied him up and beat him as a kid).  

Everyone this kid knows has ended up in prison.  My wife and I got him a lawyer (we paid for it but had him pay it back through weekly deductions from his checks.  As a result he is out of direct danger but is on probation for the next year.  Any mess ups and he is going to jail for a couple of years.

So over the past 8 months we have gotten to know this kid.  It has been a challenge just trying to get through his young, know-it-all head - but we felt like we were making progress.

There were a few times that I caught him in lies - nothing serious but I made it clear to him that a man keeps his word and never lies.  And in the case where in the heat of the moment, out of fear, you lie - well you need to quickly correct that and, as my father drilled into us, "Accept the consequence of your actions".

Over the past holidays we gave him our old truck that was in superb condition.  We had a new one and didn't need it.  He had an unreliable car and with just one half-running car is fiance could not get a job.

Anyway, last weekend we found out that he had lied about getting the truck registration changed to his name.  He had shown me the "new plates" he got several months ago and I hadn't thought about it since.  Then my wife saw my old plates on the truck and took a picture.  I guess he realized he forgot to swap the plates before he came to work.  A few minutes later when I went to confront him the truck had different plates on it.  Rather than fess up he stuck to his lie and suddenly I realized that he wasn't just lying he was trying to continue with the deception.

I felt like I had no choice but to fire him.  Stupid me expected him to apologize and try to make it right but he went an entire different direction.  He left and began sending nasty, threatening text messages.  Then I realized that he had stolen several of my tools including a chainsaw.

Long story short - he just totally destroyed the relationship and in the process has made my wife and I question why we even put ourselves out there like that.  

The money we provided to help them is irrelevant to us.  The fact that people can be someone so different than what they portray has just shattered our confidence (again) in why we even try.

Have any of you had situations where the emotional damage of real-live relationships in assisting people caused you to take stock of why you help?

Have you found that just helping virtually protects your sanity and emotional well being?

This kid just has me in a really bad place.  I find myself still worrying about what will happen to his little boy but I also realize that we did everything we could... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] redditors old enough to remember Watergate - how did the country's response to the early days of that scandal differ from the current (potential) Russia/Trump scandal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y - The Last Man would make a fantastic Netflix series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Term limits on all elected positions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Owl says "who".

The mole says... well... "moley, moley, moley" (I think) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] redditors old enough to remember Watergate - were all Americans outraged or was it viewed through a partisan lens like the simmering (potential) scandals of the current administration? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I picture I took upside down between my legs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes it was only one coat using a foam roller.
 
It has held up wonderfully. I have a roller chair in my office and they rollaround quite often and I've had zero scuffs scrapes or anything else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. If you read the album notes I discuss the fact that I had no idea what I was doing and it required several mistakes and learnings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This absolutely put a smile on my face! 

My son is 22 and had a treehouse much 

When you're an old man you will look at that and remember the great times you had as a kid your treehouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I understand those criticisms.  

Like I said it bothered me at first when I approached the show as expecting a fully formed Iron Fist.  But when I changed mindsets and approached it as "this is like Matt Murdock just learning how to be Daredevil" it felt better.  Not great.  But better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  It's been long enough I think we will probably have to start back at the beginning with JJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to admit, I haven't watched Luke Cage yet.  And I haven't gotten back to the last 4 episodes of Jessica Jones.  We got distracted by Game of Thrones and just recently finished that, then got into 13 reasons why.  Now just getting back to the Marvel titles and Iron Fist just popped up first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah.  My wife got a bit confused last night (last episode).  I won't spoil it for you but there more of that "things change frickin' overnight" that really make you scratch your head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know I, as I'm sure you have, searched the internet high and low for my symptoms and possible causes.

I removed as many as I could - stress (stepping aside from my job), caffeine.  But never did I run across anything that indicated that magnesium was something I should look at.

Heck, back when the hand clinching started I of course started taking potassium - because that's what everyone always says causes cramping.

Anyway, I really will be thinking of you.  I hope things go well for you.  

My best advice (even though I couldn't follow it) is just try to keep positive.  

I did an amazing amount of soul searching and estate planning.  That's about the only positive I have from the experience so far.  And until the doctors clear me 100% in three months I'll probably always keep a bit of concern going in the back of my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do "news" websites even proofread their stories anymore?

"The bill offers $138 billion over 10 years to help states pay for such programs. Experts say this is far too little; Larry Levitt of the Kaiser Foundation estimates it would take at least $25 billion a year."

Pretty sure that's supposed to be "8 billion over 10 years" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I see where you are coming from on the first part.  I questioned the same things.  It didn't feel like he started out as someone with extensive experience as "a warrior".  That felt odd. 

I think I got over these concerns as the show moved forward but granted - it was a weird start.

As for the brutality, I didn't think it was nearly as brutal as say DD is.  

Thanks for your thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Appropriate](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kp-R1o753pM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how mine came out although it is an office as opposed to a garage.

http://imgur.com/a/U9EY2
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay. I finally finished Iron Fist last night. Why has there been so much hate on this show? [US] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 53yo comic nerd but I can't say I ever read an Iron Fist comic or had any special interest in the character. I'm sure I read a few of is appearances in other comics over the years but that's about it.

I went into this show with no preconceived notions other than lowered expectations from reading various online reviews that said it was the worst Marvel show on Netflix.

Was the show perfect? Far from it. But overall it was a pretty good series I thought. Finn Jones had the right physical look. I liked how they had little nods to the Iron Fist costume but didn't go there (yet). I liked some of the easter eggs and tie-ins to the other Defenders. I thought the fights got better as the series went along - not nearly as well choreographed as DD, but reasonable.

My biggest complaints would be that some of the acting was a little weak/hammy (Looking at you Harold!). The Hand was really "downgraded" I thought and portrayed as nothing more than junior martial arts students. That can be explained away though simply as they are being recruited as the local "soldiers" - not the real Ninja warriors that The Hand are.

I also had a problem with Danny's seeming lack of ability to control his emotions. After 15 years of becoming a living weapon - a warrior - he sure seemed to break down in tears a lot and/or lose his temper. But again, I excused this by the end of the series as character development. He left before he learned how to truly be the Iron Fist. He has the power but has yet to learn how to harness it and his emotions. So as a first tale of Danny coming into his own I thought it worked well.

If you hated the show I would really like to hear what specifically about the show you felt didn't work and rates it as the worst of the Marvel shows on Netflix.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay. I finally finished Iron Fist last night. Why has there been so much hate on this show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for checking up on me.  I really appreciate it.

While this response will probably never be viewed by anyone but you I feel it's worth leaving here in case someone in my same situation happens upon it.  Maybe it will give them some encouragement and ideas on how to move forward.

So, in brief the answer is yes -- sort of.  The jury is out but it feels like we have the cause.

So first, after I posted this original query things got much worse - in symptoms, potential diagnosis, and most importantly mentally.

My symptoms progressed and expanded.  My right eye began "pulsing" and twitching.  I began having back spasms that became so painful I was barely getting a few hours of sleep a night.

My weight plummeted to 152.  I am a very muscular "stocky" guy.  I haven't seen 152 since my mid-20's.  My strength just evaporated.

Then the migraines started.  My god.  I have never had a migraine.  It was just crushing.  When one would hit I would simply want to die.  It would generally end in pain so bad that I would start vomiting.  My migraines increased to where I was having them literally daily.

I began having episodes of what could best be described as "panic attacks".  I would just randomly start crying wildly.  Now the logic in my brain said "why are you crying?" but I couldn't stop.  My wife wrote it off to me having a mortality crisis or just the fear of the unknown.  But I can tell you that wasn't it.  It was just something in side of me would suddenly feel like every emotion at once was crushing in on me.

After MRIs and cat-scans at the neurologist I was seeing they ruled out the first wave of things - brain tumor, MS, and a few others.  They told me that I needed to be referred to the Emory Institute for Brain Disease, specifically to a specialist in "degenerative neuro-muscular disease".  Now just the name alone scared the shit out of me - and only made my anxiety worse.

Then the wait.  The neurologist at Emory that I was referred to is well known and respected.  My appointment was set 2 months away.  So, yeah... the wait.  

I had to stop driving entirely.  I am the CEO of a large software company.  I couldn't travel anymore which was a big part of my job.  So I went to my board and asked to step down.  They were very understanding but wouldn't let me do that.  We just shifted some duties until we could know more.  And we elevated the president to Co-CEO allowing me to just focus on internal business and work from home.

I finally got in to see him.  They scheduled a variety of additional tests.  He said he had some "suspicions" but didn't want to say anything until after he reviewed the test results.  These included a different type of MRI, some that I can't remember the names of, and a nerve conduction test.

They put me on sumatriptan, nortriptyline, and an anti-nausea drug.  These seemed to help.  My migraines slowed to one every 2-3 days.  My tremors reduced substantially.  Smaller and the violent leg kicks stopped almost entirely.

On my return visit I got the good news that my tests were clean for the things he was leaning toward.  So he prescribed one more thing.  Magnesium.  MAGNESIUM.

Now if you are like me, I've never thought once about magnesium as it relates to human health.  Google it and you will be surprised. 
 Right there were all of my symptoms listed associated with magnesium deficiency.  It is available over the counter so I bought it and started taking it.  And almost immediately my migraines stopped.  My tremors, that were already light, stopped all together.  My back tremors, hand tremors, leg kicks, eye twitches, and hand cramps - everything!

I'm sleeping again.  My weight is back up to 170.  I'm still weak but getting stronger by the day.

So I guess the moral of the story is the medical profession is really an art more than a science.  We as laymen just assume that the day we get sick a doctor will know what is wrong and cure us.  The months of waiting and guessing become the worst aspect.

And in the end, after you fear the worst, and prepare for the worst - it might just be something as simple as magnesium.  FUCKING MAGNESIUM! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No question - Dewey Cox said it best

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-eIdXnxgcHU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I don't remember this asshole getting charged with anything](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qgce06Yw2ro) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, well how are you going to handle that wait for GotG 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I went to college, like many students, I had no idea what I wanted to do for a career.

I was on probation after the first year with a 1.75GPA.

I got that pulled up to a 2.5 by the end of my junior year.

I finally had to apply myself senior year and got straight A's in closing out a BA in Economics and then proceed to take one more semester and summer classes in programming.

I graduated with a 2.8 or so but on my resume I showed "Cumulative GPA: 2.8" and "Senior Year GPA: 3.7" and highlighted in interviews that this demonstrated that I had grown up.

Seemed to have worked.  I got a job with a F500 in the IT department.

Today, I'm 53 and CEO of the third software company that I have founded.  I've also been President of one public company and Division CEO of another.

Morale of the story is don't let your unfocused "party years" hold you back.  Tell the story the way you want people to understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The wrong dog died" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  

My best to you and yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treasure Island!  And they had the cartoon segment with the donkey that if you pull its tail it spins like a tornado and knocks out the bad guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Banana Splits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, got the nein.  Have NO IDEA what OP is thinking here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 53yo father.  I watched the series with my wife and our 13yo son.

I can understand some of the "triggering" talk because it is a very disturbing and haunting show.  But what no one is saying is the important part.

Teenagers, who by definition are in a very awkward and emotional phase of life, SHOULD NOT WATCH THIS SHOW ALONE.  Where are the parents?

We found the show opened great lines of conversation with our son.  If it is used as a family learning and discussion tool it is wonderful.

But as a troubled teenager, watching this show alone, I could see where this would not result in anything good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I invest the million in a basket of quality stocks.  

Never touch the principal but all gains are mine. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL I'm not a mammal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pretty cool idea.  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. I've been tagged.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People.

Everyone wants something from you.  Everyone has a motive.

If you make your money a bit later in life you already have your friends and so basically you just shut down that part of your life and don't attempt to make new friends.

I feel sorry for those that get rich young before they realize how crappy most people are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about bahia but I'm sure bermuda would work just as well.

I do like some of the other ideas people have had - like moss or thyme.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it helps I have a couple hundred acres of land - about 100 are wooded.  There are four stands of hardwoods and there are *very few of this type of tree and only found in one of the stands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Georgia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will only have a few options so I'll have to give it some thought.

I just checked the code and the fact that the entire space is one room  it meets code.

Probably the one area I will need to think through is the Bat Cave room - where I might need/want to add an escape hatch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I smelled the wedge and it smells like what I'm familiar with for oak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to be the consensus.  Thanks.

White oak was what I thought it was but the red center made me think maybe I was mistaken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, because only one room will be the Bat Cave.

I guess I could go with Wayne Manor.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is only one large room.

The front of the lodge will have the front door ("the hobbit door").  Above the front door will be the loft which will have windows that you could exit in an emergency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  I wanted to get them cut back in winter when they say is the best time to cut trees for log houses.  Just finally got to it now.

I won't be installing them until Nov/Dec so they will have about 6 months to dry.

Of course if I screw up (which is highly likely) and the pine logs fail to stay straight I'll be cutting some more and trying to get them somewhat dry before winter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The roof is closed - the model had a removable ceiling so you could see inside.

I'm going to stop calling it a hobbit house (even though that is my wife's pet name for it) and call it a "beaver lodge" because that is the feeling I'm going for.  It will be lots and lots of wood.

The front will have a hobbit door but that's about it.

The house is underground only to the roof - so the walls are underground.  The roof has a main beam and two "ribs" off of that - so six triangle roof sections in total. 

My plan is once I get the superstructure in place I will attach purlins across between each beam/rib to the next.

I'm hoping to go with solar shingles but if they aren't available commercially by the time I need them I'll probably shift gears and just finish the roof in tin first and then cover it with regular solar panels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no thorns on this tree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are no thorns on this tree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Georgia.  I didn't smell it.  What would locust smell like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly (note - supposedly) depending on internal stressors in the log once cut it can bow.

Now I'm not really buying it.  It seems that any bowing of board lumber - sure - that makes sense.  When it was milled the internal structure of the rings are compromised and you would expect you might get bowing, cupping, etc.

But a tree that is growing straight on level land it would seem there would not be any internal stress built up in the tree.  Leaving the internal structure untouched it doesn't make sense to me that the tree would "warp".

Good news is - I'm open for learning.  So if the ones I've cut start bowing during the drying process I'll just rethink things, cuts some more, and try again.

Re: debarking - how do you go about this?  I bought a curved draw shave (I think that's what it's called).  I also bought a curved hand planer.  I was leaning against debarking assuming it will all fall off as the tree dries.  I know it does that with pine.  Do you know if oak bark will fall off in the drying process as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cinderblock makes a ton of sense.  

My only concern is that I heard you need to turn them ever week or so.  To do that if I have them on another log perpendicular I should be able to role them pretty easy.  Do you rotate yours or was I mislead on that been a requirement?

As for the splitting I assume you are using your logs for milling.  In my case I cut the logs 5-10' longer than needed and I will be cutting them to size so some cracking on the ends would be fine I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this help?

http://imgur.com/a/lDuDC

I wish I had grabbed some leaves.  I'll try to go back out tonight and do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip.  I'll make sure I do that in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you strip the bark? Doesn't if fall off as the log dries?

I know with Pine does but haven't done Oak before.

What is the purpose of the wax?

I do know that I need to get them elevated off the ground.  I am planning to use some other crappy logs that I have cut with a 2x6 of yellow wood between the two.  I heard that would discourage pests from traveling up to the good log.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those interested, I added a few pictures the my "hobbit house" album. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This weekend was for finding and cutting the trees that will be the main beam and ribs of the superstructure.

Oh, and I *really* need to stop calling this a hobbit house before I get too far along or people are going to be disappointed when it isn't a true earthen hobbit house.  Beaver Lodge just feels more accurate for what I'm envisioning.

http://imgur.com/a/kXOQm

So after looking at the pictures anyone with advice or experience drying large logs please chime in.   

I'm assuming since they were straight standing and grown on flat land - they should not bow during drying since they will not have their internal structure compromised.  Can anyone confirm that for me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bark looks like white oak from pictures I've checked but the inside makes me think this is red oak.  Help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me identify this oak tree I cut down? I am pretty sure it is red oak but would appreciate confirmation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> side by side.  One on each side of the spine.

I'm fused from C2-T1 so I get stiff in the upper back between the shoulderblades.  And of course I have the lower back problems everyone gets as they get older.

So I start by laying down on the floor with a pillow under my head.  I put one ball in each hand and "insert" them about even with my shoulder blades - one on each side.

Start them rolling slowly down your spine by pushing with your feet.  Then when you find a spot that needs some more attention you can rock back and forth with your feet to work the spot.

When you get to your buttocks you can simply grab the balls and put them back at the starting point and repeat.

I usually go down my spine two or three times and then I put the balls on each hip - not the small of the back - but down on the top of the buttocks right below the hip bone.  This is where the sciatic nerve runs.  Just resting on it there relieves the pain and I get ongoing relief for the rest of the night generally.

Hope that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I start up by my shoulder blades and then I lift my hips and slowly push with my feet.   The balls slowly roll down my back.  

I also like to put them right on above the buttocks when my sciatic nerve is bothering me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta build the little boy's muscles. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  That looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  Awesome.  Did not know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/I/61%2Bu23kzHoL._SY355_.jpg

What do you call it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly they both have passed away in the past year but they had a great lives for dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't but it is a good point.

Our whole property would not be very wheelchair friendly but most of my builds are elderly friendly as my wife and I still have both our parents and they are all getting up there in years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  I hadn't thought of snow.  Definitely would be pain to have a walk like this up north. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  Yeah.  I'm that guy.

Thanks.  Glad you liked the project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That does not sound fun.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, keep thinking that way!  :)

My motto is "just start".  If I waited for my projects to be fully formed in my mind and fully researched I would have a million excuses that would keep me from ever doing it.

I just jump in.  Make mistakes and adjust as I go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the edit because this one had me scratching my head.  LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.

And that was exactly the thought we use on all projects.  Go first with something that will be easy to change if you don't like it.

If you go with something permanent like grout you are stuck with it for life.

Better to try and fail and have a do-over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.  We literally did nothing but plant it, keep it watered, and weed it that first year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback.  We really only have the little Argentinian ants (not sure if that's the right name - that's what they call them here) that are a pain.  They don't bite but they get into EVERYTHING

Luckily we don't have any fire ants up by the house - just out in the pastures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think we have it hear in GA.  Hope not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> zero turn mower when the rest of the yard is getting mowed.

As you probably can see from the pictures there isn't much "lawn" exactly yet but we're getting there now that I'm not driving over everything all the time with my skidsteer and excavator.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son recognizes me from that phrase too. :)

When I need him for a chore I go in the house and yell "where's my conscripted laborer?"

He loves having me as a father I'm sure.  

My oldest son gave him great advice.  If Dad ever asks you if you want to do a chore and get paid for it immediately say "Yes" otherwise he'll leave and come back in 5 minutes and tell you that you are doing the chore anyway and you aren't getting paid.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South Texas?  Does anything grow in South Texas? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow!  Thanks.  I have never heard of this vine.  Where do you live?

Looks frightening: https://www.google.com/search?q=Trumpet+Vine oq=Trumpet+Vine aqs=chrome..69i57 sourceid=chrome ie=UTF-8#q=Trumpet+Vine+rash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!  I probably mentioned it in my natural swim pond post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand corrected.  You are correct after a quick google check.

Thanks for the information.  Always happy to learn something new.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Zoysia is not a creeper so it stays put pretty well.

EDIT: apparently zoysia is a creeper type grass but I have not noticed any feelers.  Maybe that's because the stone is nice and hot here in GA and without any soil or water it just stays put. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm...  Well the pallets are right about a cube yard.  The medium flagstone is on average 1.5" so each layer would cover 9 square feet x 24 (36" / 1.5) = 216 square feet.  Ish.

Hope that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I appreciate the concern.  I really do.

What I am building here is not for everyone.  I love DIY projects and over time when you build things they require maintenance.

Right now while I am still relatively young (53) and have my health I enjoy the building part.

Once everything is built out I'll enjoy the "maintenance mode" when I can't do as much physically.  

That said, I am currently building large stables for my wife and once those are done we are going to start searching for a live-in barn manager and groundskeeper that can help me with ongoing maintenance around the farm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I haven't noticed that so far.  I do want to see if I can get it all to "compact" more like it does in the areas where we walk the most but generally no I haven't seen anyone trip at all yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  I had to give the Devil something in return.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate the honest feedback.  To each his own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I know of but what the hell is Trumpet Vine?  I've never heard of that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  Feel free to come for a visit.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had 4 neck fusions - fused from C2 to T1.  Knee replacement.  Hip replacement in the next few years - so yeah - I can relate to ya.

The jacuzzi is nice for that massage feeling but I find that if I take a nice steam shower and then stretch on the floor with two tennis balls on my back I get much more relief than I ever did with a jacuzzi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will rock and wobble.  They will be above the level of your lawn.

But effectively no reason if that's how you want it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are more fun than should be legally allowed.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sigh  So I've been told by reddit more than a few times now.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go.  Everything you ever wanted to know about why Bamboo is the devil:

https://www.reddit.com/r/DIY/comments/63751i/sure_i_could_have_bought_a_custom_inground/?utm_content=comments utm_medium=user utm_source=reddit utm_name=frontpage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not.  zoysia is a very tightly packed small bladed grass used on golf course greens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It keeps me out of trouble!

I'm starting to put some projects over on /r/DIYinprogress since mine are long and ongoing and you can only post finished projects here.

My two big ones in progress now are a Hobbit House and a cabin on our lake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you forgot a few variety of poisonous snakes. :)

But screw you FL - at least we don't have gators!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You speak the truth there.  We have whole fields of blackberry bushes.  

While it is fun eating them once or twice a year the rest of the time you have to attack them with the bushhog but they just come back stronger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relationship goals!  

I hope you find it.  Just make sure you look in all places.

My wife missed me for a long time because she wasn't looking down.  She's six foot and I'm 5'7" if a stretch really good in the morning.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it's hard to see in the picture but where you walk the "wear" is really the grass clinging lower to the ground.  It kind of compacts and gets much more like you see it on a golf course green.

I have thought about using a weed eater on it and try into to cut it back even further on the ones we don't really walk on much and see if that evens it out more.

If not, I guess I could get my happy laborer to walk around on all of it every day.  He loves helping on my projects.  Not.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smells great.  Those things grow like crazy!

My wife likes to cut them back and puts the cuttings in a vase in the kitchen.  Makes the kitchen smell great and I steal from the stalks when I'm cooking.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Nector of the Gods](http://cdn.liquor.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/08/Mount-Gay-Extra-Old.jpg)

Barbados sugar cane rum.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  too many other places to pee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out my comment reply about moss.  

I provided a link to a company that sells moss for use on walkways like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  I like tags but sometimes I'll have one come up on a comment and I can't for the live of me remember why I tagged somebody with a weird name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  Did my wife put you up to that comment?  :)

The yard is already seeded with Bermuda but I HATE Bermuda (as much as some people hate Bamboo) so we are discussing do a full kill on it and seeding the whole thing with zoysia.

But man Zoysia seed is expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct, I am in GA.  And yes if someone tries this up north they will most likely need to deal with more sub base.

We get a lot of DIY bonuses living in the south - not heaving.  No snow load.  Pretty sweet.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why thank you!  I'm glad you liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is that?

My dogs don't seem to give one care at all about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you can't please all the people all the time. :)

My wife and I have pretty eccentric tastes I guess based on some of the feedback I have gotten on some of my other projects.

But in the end it's our house.  We are the ones that have to live in it and enjoy it.  It's nice to get to the point in life where you don't have to worry about keeping things neutral for resale value.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I understand.

I've moved to simply using my steam shower for relaxing sore and tired muscles.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pond guy present and accounted for!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL.  Yep.  Thanks for noticing the crazy guy.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure.   Here you go (with a view to the natural swim pond I built in the background that another commenter noticed). :)

http://imgur.com/a/OP46J </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some does. :)

https://stepables.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what?  I thought Bamboo was the devil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  Yep that was me.  :)

I wondered if anyone would recognize that in the background. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do make some moss that probably would work for you . 

If you are interested: https://stepables.com/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we use a zero-turn mower over it while mowing the rest of the yard.  

For the really tight spots like up by the corner to the house we hit it with a weedeater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great insights for those "inheriting" one of these!  Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 53.  Talk to me in 8 years.

We have had hot tubs since we got married 20 years ago but have just finally reached the age where we usually have a drink together in the evening, watch a little netflix with our little guy and hit the bed.

Here's hoping you'll still be a spring chicken when you get here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but why do you say that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry that you really (really) didn't like this project.

Not your style.  Get it.  Best to you and yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  I had to go see what picture 13 was.  I guess you don't like the grass part of this project. LOL

No problem.  To each his own.  It came out exactly as my wife wanted it so I'm happy with it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creating a flagstone and zoysia grass patio or walkway. Note: this project takes patience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GET OFF MY LAWN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to explain to my 13yo how cassette tapes worked after watching 13 Reasons Why together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can only hope... but there are people out there that actually believe this stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are doctors performing surgeries drunk today?  Are teachers teaching while drunk today?  Are firefighters fighting fires while drunk today?

Does everyone drink alcohol all the time now because it is legal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an underrated comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had it professionally done on my last two DIY projects.

I was considering doing it myself for my current one but after watching it done professionally and then watching the DIY tutorials on Youtube I have decided it would be just too much of a pain and mess with not enough savings.

This is one I will leave to the pros. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> National company.  But thanks for the details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's happened to me twice now.

In 2010 I took my oldest son (16 at the time) Washington for the Stewart/Cobert  Rally to Restore Sanity and/or Fear.  Everyone was encouraged to dress up and make funny signs.  We painted ourselves blue with pond dye and went as Na'vi from Avatar with messages on our shirts.

A couple of years ago someone posted a link to a slideshow from that rally.  I was going through the slideshow remembering a lot of the crowd shots when what shows up - but a picture of my son and me.  Was so random it made me laugh.

The other is more recent.  I was asked to do the spokesman part for a web commercial that our company did.  I knew it would be used in email campaigns but didn't expect it to be used in Google Ads.  

One day I was reading an article about SpaceX and about halfway through the article my ugly mug showed up on the page.  At first I was confused.  Then just horrified.  Eventually I started seeing the damn thing just about everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chug Boat.

Everyone picks a character from Love Boat.  

Every time your character comes on screen you have to drink.

When the whole ship is shown it's social - everybody drinks.

In the opening credits alone everyone drinks about 10 times.

The worst part is when they show the names of the stories for the episode.  If your character's name is in the story name you are screwed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
