<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3591</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks really great, now can I have some chips and ranchera salsa to go along?
Also, your rice grains are super long.  What type of rice is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> turkey is under appreciated.  Yours looks really yummy!  It looks like there's skin on the top, and the stuffing coming right out, how did you go about stuffing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the reverse sear.  I like to take my meat out and put it on a plate/platter and salt and pepper both sides, cover with saran wrap and let sit on the counter for at least a couple hours.  This allows the salt to extract water, become a solution and re-absorb into the meat through osmosis.  Gives a nice salty flavor.  Then I go into the oven for a bit till it's gray, and then final sear in the pan.  You should look into a pan sauce.  I'm not very good at those though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> beef ribs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I put Montreal steak seasoning on some beef ribs (they almost look like spare ribs they're not very long the way they were cut) and loaded them in a dutch oven on top of 1/8th sections of onions.  Put them in the oven @ 275 freedom degrees with aluminum foil helping to seal the lid.  Going to let it go for about 3 hours and then finish with Sweet Baby Rays' bbq sauce.  Does that sound good?  Any suggestions (especially on finishing, no grill available)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck, in upstate NY they bake pies and put them out on custom stands/boxes along with any produce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is because they get the cream from the style plant because they can't use cream from cows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I notice the slaw in the top left corner of the plate under the pico, that's what my local serves also, very good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there potato or something else like it in there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I think there's some translation problem.  What I mean is that it should be saucy-er.  More sauce. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like it saucier, but have an upvote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you do that?  Can't the poors just buy more money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had that happen to me at the 1994 Belgian GP.  Schumi won, but was DQ'd for excessive skid plate wear.  Found out the next day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't those things filled with the cartilage end of the rib bone?  Yuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/minnesota maybe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks super good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that sucks. Our shop probably needs a cat, but they probably wouldn't let us adopt one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got some weird parts, would you like to see my weird parts
/parts guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When life gives you lemons, spark one up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the end of the gif, you can see the spare timing belt.  For use in an emergency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like I'm at hannuma bay snorkel again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great, I'm thinking the oven is a bit low temp or the cook should've topped this pizza (held near the top of the dome). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I'm assuming lasagna noodles.  Why not just top it with mashed potato and call it smart cottage pie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am havening a hard time realizing why your newer post has a picture of a relay that you describe as a fuse when you want a temperature switch.  FFS, I could have been watching hockey a whole lot more tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking that's from a snow tractor.  That alternator looks familiar also.  Kassbohrer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear all of this new emissions stuff on vehicles is not working.  Just imagine how much energy it took to make that thing versus how much it saved.  We had a problem with a computer controlled Caterpillar wheel loader this year and spend a metric-crapload on parts and finally had to get a service call from the dealer to fix it because we didn't have the software to diagnose it correctly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of our Italian off road tractors use one of these for battery protection:  http://www.cooperindustries.com/content/public/en/bussmann/transportation/products/circuit_protection/fuses/marine_rated_batteryfuses.html Not easy to find at Napa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ford fleet, we go through those like chicklets.  Base number is 7212, but they sell them at Napa now.  Maybe F81Z-7212-A, I dunno.  Get the 7L378 bushings too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of enchilada?  Chicken maybe.  Looks really great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taco Bell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> deep fried cheese curds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you trying to signal something?  I'm pretty sure the edge of the knife should be facing the other way, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a full Japanese breakfast then?  I'd try the Nato and then probably love it although it looks disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had French Dip yesterday at a pretty fancy place for lunch with fries.  They were the worst fries ever.  The sandwich was pretty good, but the roll was pretty lame, and it really wasn't very big for the price.  YOURS LOOKS BETTER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, probably 14" would be good.  Could you detail a little more on the preparations to make it food grade? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That beef doesn't look good at all.  Come on UK, it's not supposed to be sausage! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty good, although that piece of chicken in the center is burnt to hell.  Hopefully it's just the sauce that got burnt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How stoned were they when they created this item? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you do a veg side like that with the courgettes, asparagus and carrot?  Like what sort of sauce and then preparation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems strange.  How do you stirfry a crab while it's in the shell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you say below you used flour.  Those are breaded wings.  Typically Buffalo wings are fried without any seasoning, flour, breading, just wings.  Then they are tossed with the Frank's and butter mixture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think you could go thinner on the steel, or is 1/4 the way to go.  Seems like it is pretty heavy for only 12".  I'd like mine bigger, but that means it would be a lot heavier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Cheese IS COLD! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, start by removing the pit from the avocado, remove the flesh from the skin, then you've got to slice the avocado.  Then add the avocado to a bacon cheeseburger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, it seems to keep for a long time.  Maybe it's like those fish in the tenaja that come to life when it rains in the desert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of our beasts used to have the OM926LA with a cannister filter. You learn to get the right socket and not too many ooga doogas if you don't want to break the cap and the machine is down for 4 days waiting for parts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bean dip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I just did a GIS on safe eyeballs.  Hork! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the whole time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, make sure to get the 1 year protection from Assurant for $6.49 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could be my old one.  Was the left front fender and suspension as well as the left door messed up?  Mine was 1986 w/70,000 miles or so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Bonito Michoacan just north of West Flamingo on Decatur.  Home made tortillas, guac, really good margaritas and the rest of the food. Go there for lunch, it can be loud at night with a band playing. http://www.bonitomichoacan.com/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tracks ate your shock absorber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what chicken breast milk would taste like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Florentine steak is from a wood fired oven, yes?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if doing thin burgers the grillmometer should be at least 350F.  Usually more like 450F.  For really thick burgers, you should have two zones, one hot and a safe zone so they don't get really burnt up on the outside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it depends on how thick they are.  If they are thin, you can do them on high.  However, if they're frozen that would be bad on the grill.  If you are doing them big and thick, you're going to want to slow the process to get the inside cooked to an acceptable temp.  You should probably employ a thermometer.

edit: my father would flip the burger when the red juice from the inside came to the top for a regular sized (1/4lb) burger.  Thermometer suggestion is only for thick burgers, so you can tell where the inside is at.  Toppings:  Do you have a can of New Mexico green chile?  Pepper jack cheese?  Pickles?  Tomato? Saute'd mushroom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks really great.  Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked at the menu for Chuy's and I'm really sure that I'll stick with my local places even though they are opening a new Chuy's 96 miles from me.  this looks good, and I up-voted but really if I'm paying for a dinner/lunch that's not enough food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at least it's not stuffed rarebit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2015/09/08/man-ticketed-for-broken-windshield-while-trying-to-fix-it/71884244/#
http://www.redstate.com/leon_h_wolf/2015/09/08/man-gets-ticketed-broken-windshield-pulling-windshield-repair-shop/
http://addictinginfo.org/2015/09/10/ticket-crazy-cop-issues-colorado-man-a-ticket-for-broken-windshield-in-parking-lot-of-repair-shop-video/
http://www.rawstory.com/2015/09/colorado-man-ticketed-for-broken-windshield-in-parking-lot-of-auto-glass-repair-shop-definitely-a-bummer/
http://boingboing.net/2015/09/14/man-trying-to-fix-broken-winds.html
http://www.azcentral.com/story/news/investigations/2015/09/09/broken-windshield-adams-county-auto-glass-shop/71977122/
http://www.dailykos.com/story/2015/9/8/1419535/-Police-ticket-man-for-broken-windshield-in-front-of-shop-where-he-was-having-it-repaired
Should I keep going? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fixed the MAF sensor in my 4.3l Blazer a number of years ago and went from 19mpg to 14.  I runs like a raped ape though since then.   I'm not sure why.  So, I'm actually pretty happy.  The new MAF was from Amazon and genuine Delco.  Seriously, before that I thought the trans was going out again and it wouldn't hold 30 mph on the way up a mountain pass where the speed limit was 55. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.breitbart.com/big-government/2015/09/08/denver-man-ticketed-for-broken-windshield-in-auto-repair-parking-lot/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why even repair an evap line?  I don't care that gasoline evaporates.
edit: I mean, the windows are at least cracked when I'm smoking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like there's so many little leaks it's blowing the rain off of the pavement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks pretty cool.  I got to use some plastic and rubber strap wrench set I bought a number of years ago yesterday and it worked like a charm on propane fittings, no spark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there was a thread a few months ago where the cop was hanging out near the windshield replacement shop and ticketing cars that had appointments for windshield replacement as they arrived with broken windshields. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's because front page commentors are off on a tangent and breaking the rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, I thought it was mashed potato because it looked so large. Ice cream would be good also though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's OP's spin, cuz it has SPINach! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Aspen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, this is what I was going to say.  The Hawaiian loco moco is gravy over burger pattie over rice with pasta salad.  A fried egg on top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's unusual, I have seen un-battered and un-wrapped relleno but not presented wide open like that on beans.  Where did you get this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I was seeing a fried egg on the bottom also.  But that's just the bun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking more about the other ones.  The ones the front doesn't fall off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the CCCC burger protein style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, this is an (I'm not sure) 2014 Ski-Doo Skandic Wide Trac with 550 fan motor. It burned to the ground along with all of the person's equipment attached last night. It's amazing such a large machine can fit in a boggan afterwards, everything that wasn't metal or Kevlar (in the track) is gone. Right here they are looking at how the starter motor gear is still engaged to the drive clutch which probably cause the starter to catch fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This one is rolling onto the scrap metal pile, not into the shop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there are a lot of these ships going around the world all the time and very seldom does this happen.  I just don't want people thinking that tankers aren't safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's not very typical.  I'd like to make that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commer made lots of interesting vehicles.  good pics on the wikipedia site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pizza on english muffin or bagel if you have a toaster oven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That roast looks like a standing rib roast (prime rib). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> coq au vin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks pretty great to me. A bit of slaw and potato with a nice gravy and some beef. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the thumb nail on the left is way taller than any of my nails, including my toes, and I can see a bit of the "whatever it's called" underneath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, you've got stick on nails.  WTF?  Also, that food looks pretty great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> upvoted, but not presented properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like baby back ribs. I think I'll try those next time because those little cartilage parts at the end of the St Louis cut freak me out a bit. Also, this looks great and I don't mind the sauce at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People say that if you have to pre-face your comment with something like "I hate to comment about...." you shouldn't comment. So, I'm going to take that advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a 2lb bag of frozen cooked shrimp and de-frosted some for a shrimp cocktail.  Fine.  Then I took a bite of one without sauce and it tasted of ...  nothing.  No taste at all.  That was scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No rubber, rubber's right out.  Uhhmmm, they've got to have a steering wheel and minimum amount of crew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a fun video.  Little George giggling all the way up the hill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he means the plastic wiring conduit that is slit all the way down so you can slip the wires inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, no cardboard then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just saw an advert for "whole grain popcorn" what unnecessary product descriptions have you seen? [misc/discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, If I ever start a restaurant it will be a pork tenderloin restaurant. It will be like in-n-out in that we only serve pork tenderloin and fries and malted milk shakes. (I know in-n-out only serves shakes, mine will be malted) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a good place nearby for new york type pies and slices (Spinelli's), but otherwise it's Domino's.  I wish we had a Papa John's nearby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had something similar yesterday, grande breakfast burrito with potato, egg, sausage, green chile sauce, cheese, peppers and onion. It's got to be at least 1lb, I didn't weigh it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of pentagram cut. They are satanists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> with a taco inside </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to try both, very good looking pizza OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at first I was like "where's the aparagus", then I read the comments and was "oh, garlic of the wood". And then I got a woody, good job OP's wife! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That burger knocked on my door and introduced itself. Also, what's the holy trinity? I know the trinity from Louisiana, but I wouldn't put it on a burger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having stromboli feelings about this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that looks so good. TBH, I'd rather have them separately though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been to the Ren fest in MN and CO, but I missed them.  Must go back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That piece of chicken looks perfect. I'd also really enjoy the casserole and slaw! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 17:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I slice up turkey kielbasa and fry it a bit, then add that to the cooked mac-n-cheese.  It's healthy because it's turkey obvs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 16:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like it go back and have the goat. It should taste mostly like beef, but different. Then pat yourself on the back, you're adventurous! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
