<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4900</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a centipede. I guarantee you there will be more shoes to drop, I can just guarantee it. Theres just too much information that we dont have that will be coming out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John McCain on Comey firing: There will be more shoes to drop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The diplomat is Sergey Lavrov, who was believed to be in charge of the US Election Hack for Russia in the Steele Dossier.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing that should truly scare everyone is that if the Steele dossier is accurate...the leverage the Russians have on Trump now just exponentially increased.

Even the smallest leak of corroborating information would bring down the Trump family empire.

You have to think at this point, what wouldn't Trump do in order to protect himself and his entire family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graham is nothing but talk. All Graham wants to do is set himself up with an alibi when the ship goes down. 

He's going to cast himself as opposing Trump...while not actually doing anything of substance to oppose Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The diplomat is Sergey Lavrov, the guy Christopher Steele believed to be in charge of the US Election Hack for Russia...

They literally don't even care about hiding it now. Trump absolutely thinks he's untouchable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop giving this turd headlines. He's just playing "hard to get" and trying to play both sides. 

He hasn't actually DONE anything meaningful. He's just trying to remind Trump that he wants in on the action but he doesn't come cheap.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most accurate summary so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
