<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8214</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> COULD BITCOIN BECOME THE BEST PERFORMING CURRENCY IN 2017? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon 'probably copied us' on Echo Show, startup CEO says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump fires FBI Director Comey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Safe Dividend Stocks to Watch in May 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 5 Biggest Jaw-Droppers at the 2017 MTV Movie   TV Awards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren Buffett: I was wrong on Google and 'too dumb' to appreciate Amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMZN Stock: Will There Be an Amazon Stock Split in 2017? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock/amazon-stock-split/

**Calling for an AMZN Stock Split in 2017**
Fifty, just 50 bucks! As of May Day 2017, thats how short Jeff Bezos is from beating Bill Gates to become the worlds richest man.
Confused? Well, Amazon.com, Inc. (NASDAQ:AMZN) stock has to advance by roughly $50.00 to cross the $1,000 mark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 325 Kilograms Lighter, Egyptian Woman Leaves India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tony Parker leaves Spurs' win in fourth quarter with injured leg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA And Google Both Have Amazing Employees, But Their Organizational Speeds Are Very Different </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk's SpaceX to send the first of its 4425 super-fast internet satellites into space in 2019 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> eBay cancels auction of Aaron Hernandez SUV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On World Press Freedom Day, student shares her opinion on why a free press matters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Burry Predicts an Imminent Stock Market Crash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.lombardiletter.com/michael-burry-stock-market-crash/10895/

**Michael Burry Predictions for 2017**

Michael Burrys predictions for 2017 are rather unpleasant. Unfortunately, they may also be right, because world events appear to be heading in exactly the direction Burry expects. Burry, who runs Scion Asset Management, LLC, says we can soon expect a global financial meltdown and World War 3.

Michael Burrys prediction for a stock market crash shouldnt surprise anyone. Burry is the physician turned hedge fund manager who managed to make millions for himself and his clients when most people were losing their shirts in 2008. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GDP Report Shows US Economy Off to Slow Start in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana Stock Predictions 2018: What to Expect from Weed Stocks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 NFL Draft: Chiefs, Texans spend big on quarterbacks and more Round 1 takeaways </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Measles outbreak prompts vaccination message from Kandiyohi County health officials </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Won't Have Any New Spacesuits For Years - And The Old Ones Are Running Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elton John Cancels Concerts After Potentially Deadly Infection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Defense Stocks for 2017: Is This Right Time to Invest Under Trump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CEO of LafargeHolcim, which has Whitehall plant, resigns after Syria deals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The iPhone 8 may be very hard to get until 2018 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General Electric shares rise 1% after earnings beat Street's expectations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELON MUSK IS SERIOUSLY STARTING A TELEPATHY COMPANY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aaron Hernandez Wiki: Cause of Death, Wife, Net Worth,   Facts to Know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horizons (HMMJ) ETF: Worlds First Marijuana ETF Is Worth a Second Look </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump eyes cap on charitable deductions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Things You Must Know Before the Market Opens Wednesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.thestreet.com/story/14089685/1/5-things-you-must-know-before-the-market-opens-wednesday.html
1. -- U.S. stock futures were rising Wednesday after earnings from Morgan Stanley (MS)  topped analysts' forecasts.

The S P 500 fell 0.29% on Tuesday, the Dow Jones Industrial Average dropped 0.55%, and the Nasdaq fell 0.12%, after first-quarter earnings from Goldman Sachs (GS) came up short, and Johnson   Johnson's  (JNJ)  revenue missed forecasts.

European stocks traded mixed on Wednesday with shares in London off slightly. Gains were held down by the two-day advance of the pound, which has risen against a weaker U.S. dollar after U.K. Prime Minister Theresa called for an early national election in order to shore up her domestic political support as she prepares to begin negotiations with officials in Brussels over the country's exit from the European Union. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starbucks joins 'unicorn food' craze with new drink </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snap's Evan Spiegel Is Right Though, Snapchat Is An App For Rich People, Not India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 8 Could Shake Up AAPL Stock Forecast in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock/iphone-8-shake-aapl-stock-forecast-2017/
**How iPhone 8 News Elevates AAPL Stock**
The truism holds that there is no faster way to cause mass hysteria among techies than a press releaseor widespread rumorabout the next iteration of the iPhone. And that excitement has only increased with every scintilla of the next-generation iPhone 8 news.
With the Apple stock price hitting all-time highs on the back of rumors regarding the next smartphone, especially its augmented reality (AR) technology, alongside the 10th anniversary of the original iPhone launch, you have what may prove to be Apple Inc.s (NASDAQ:AAPL) biggest event in years. Analysts are busy revising up their AAPL stock forecast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diabetes is on the rise in America's kids and experts don't know why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's Economy Grows 6.9%, but Warning Signs Persist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blackberry shares up 17% on $814.9M arbitration award </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galaxy S8 Vs Galaxy S6: Should You Upgrade? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Things You Must Know Before the Market Opens Thursday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.thestreet.com/story/14073951/1/5-things-you-must-know-before-the-market-opens-thursday.html

If you'd like to receive the free "5 Things" newsletter, please register here.
 
Here are five things you must know for Thursday, April 6:
1. -- U.S. stock futures were lower Thursday following a sudden turn down in Wednesday's trading after the Federal Reserve committed to further monetary tightening in 2017. Investors also were nervously anticipating the first meeting between Donald Trump and Chinese leader Xi Jinping.

The S P 500 declined 0.31%, the Dow Jones Industrial Average fell 0.20%, and the Nasdaq fell 0.58%. Stocks had rallied earlier Wednesday following very strong U.S. private payroll numbers from ADP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bezos is selling $1 billion of Amazon stock a year to fund rocket venture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reality Check: European Parliament's 'red lines' on Brexit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Profit from Canadian Marijuana Stocks While Staying in the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pensacola's first medical weed shop to open </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #Finance #Makemoney </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Internets Most Famous Pregnant Giraffe Still Hasnt Given Birth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharna Burgess Boyfriend 2017: Who is the DWTS Contestant Dating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, But I read the article all are important questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FOREX-Euro hits two-week low as inflation data lags expectations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonald's to switch to fresh beef in its Quarter Pounders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Questions You Need to Ask Before Investing in Marijuana Stocks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Today Status:**
OPEN :218.0
DAY RANGE: 215.7 - 223.7
VOLUME: 123,127,000
PREVIOUS CLOSE: 217.2
52WK RANGE: 178.0 - 475.2
1 YR RETURN: 3.74%
YTD RETURN: -22.50%
EARNINGS PER SHARE (JPY) (TTM): -197.0
MARKET CAP (B JPY): 929.730
SHARES OUTSTANDING (B): 4.238
PRICE/SALES (TTM): 0.18 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why do investors clamor for dividends? Why do market commentators write lectures decrying share buybacks? Because sometimes the stock price goes down after the buyback, and then they get all confused.

Assume, in the wake of purchasing in 5% of its shares at $40, Hewlett-Packard sees its shares fall to $16. It beyond any doubt looks as though H-P has squandered $24 on each share it purchased. Be that as it may, dumbfounding as this appears, there is no waste from the buyback. In the event that the organization had paid a $2 profit rather, then the shares would have fallen considerably more- - to $15.20. What you're taking a gander at is not squander but rather just a PC business that isn't doing admirably. 

Presently, about those charges. Individuals contributing through assessment conceded retirement records ought to be apathetic regarding whether they gather a 5% money profit or offer back 5% of shares. Individuals contributing through assessable records, however, ought to mind a ton. They're vastly improved off with buybacks. 

In the event that you gather $2,000 in a profit, the entire $2,000 is assessable. On the off chance that you gather $2,000 by offering offers, you pay assess just to the degree the stock has had a keep running up since you got it. On the off chance that you got into Apple at $410 and offer back 5 offers when it's at $400, your $2,000 payout is sans scot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Man: Homecoming' Trailer Screens Early at CinemaCon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WWE RAW RESULTS: WINNERS, GRADES, REACTION AND HIGHLIGHTS FROM MARCH 27 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> List of Top Tech Stocks in April 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 12:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Airlines Seeks China Southern Tie-Up as Traffic Booms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global Tensions Could Trigger World War 3 in 2018 or Even 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple says CIA's arsenal of iPhone and Mac exploits is outdated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Toll of London Attack Is Global for an Assailant Born in Britain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FDA Links Breast Implants To Deaths From Rare Type Of Cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 12:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> April The Giraffe Is Moody, Goat Gives Birth At Animal Adventure Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 10:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sharna Burgess, Bonner Bolton Are Both "Speechless" About the Reaction to Their Dancing With the Stars Chemistry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amgen Stock: The One Best Biotech Stock Play for 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. stocks looked set to open higher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-stocks-idUSKBN16S19H
French centrist Emmanuel Macron's performance in a television debate raised expectations that he would win the presidential election over the far-right's Marine Le Pen, boosting sentiment across Europe, with shares edging up toward 15-month highs.

Global investors have been worried about increasing protectionism, following the Brexit vote and President Donald Trump's election. Last week, the G20 leaders dropped a pledge to keep global trade free and open.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI Is Investigating Trump's Russia Ties, Comey Confirms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New NASA radar technique finds lost lunar spacecraft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Zuckerberg and Priscilla Chan are expecting another baby girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 04:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Soros Has Paid for His Opinions on Donald Trump and His Performance as President </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 17:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon Stock to Gain from Amazon Alexa, Google Assistant Face-Off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gabourey Sidibe on her dramatic weight loss: 'I did it so I can walk around comfortably in heels' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ADIDAS STOCK IS CRUSHING NIKE AND UNDER ARMOUR AND ITS NOT EVEN CLOSE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stocks close mostly lower after oil plunges 5.4%; ADP report crushes estimates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 12:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cramer: Teslas charts show a bumpy road ahead while Ford, GM race forward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.cnbc.com/2017/03/07/cramer-teslas-charts-show-a-bumpy-road-ahead-while-ford-gm-race-forward.html

Ford, GM race around Tesla's bumpy road	Ford, GM race around Tesla's bumpy road  
11 Hours Ago | 01:41
Shares of Tesla have been hammered in the past few weeks, prompting Jim Cramer to turn to the charts to investigate if it could impact the rest of the automobile industry.

To gain further insight on what the charts predict, Cramer spoke with technician Bob Moreno who runs RightViewTrading.com and is a colleague of Cramer's at RealMoney.com.

Moreno's research found that the era of Tesla outperformance is likely coming to an end, while Ford and General Motors could be ready to break out above key levels.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) Could Hit the $1-Trillion Mark Soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock/apple-inc-hit-1-trillion/
There Is No Looking Back for AAPL Stock
Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) stock touched an all-time high of $140.28 last Thursday and is the top gainer in the Dow Jones Index this year. Apple stock has gained more than 20% in the year to date with no slowing down in sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Klay Thompsons Girlfriend in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bezos Aims Rocket Maker's Ferocity at Tourism to Cut Space Costs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple responds to CIA iPhone exploits uncovered in new WikiLeaks data dump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top Stock Picks for the Week of March 6th </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.zacks.com/stock/news/251798/top-stock-picks-for-the-week-of-march-6th
Primerica, Inc. (PRI - Free Report)	, provides financial products and services, such as life insurance, and is a Zacks ranked #2, Buy. With Value and VGM scores of B, this company has an average four quarter positive earnings sursprise of 5.61%. Its one year gain of 93.7% is considerably higher than the Zacks Life Insurance Industrys rally of 29.7%. A good play on rising interest rates. 

GOL Linhas Aereas Inteligentes (GOL - Free Report)	, is a Brazilian discount airline. A Zacks ranked #1, Strong Buy, stock, this company is benefitting from a positive turn in the regional economy it services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kawhi Leonard grabbed the NBA MVP race in 7 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue Origin releases details of its monster orbital rocket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 16:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General Motors pulls back from European auto market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana Stocks: There Is No Stopping CARA Stock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Trumps Military Spending Surge Be the First Salvo of WW3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 16:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Health Organization releases list of antibiotic-resistant 'priority pathogens' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Crash in AMD Stock Could Be an Opportunity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High-Tech Condom Ring Coming Out To Measure Boink Performance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA Spacecraft Avoids Collision with Martian Moon Phobos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oscars Stage Manager Says Accountants 'Froze' After Wrong Winner for Best Picture was Announced </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTube's cord-cutting bundle really skinny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $AMZN Warren Buffett on Amazon: 'I don't have a good answer' on why I didn't buy it long ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Are the Best Technology Stocks for Long Term Investors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.profitconfidential.com/stocks/best-technology-stocks-long-term-investors/

There are very few long-term investors left on the market. Most people just want to get rich overnight. They arent willing to play the long game, sacrifice, or realize that wealth takes time.
But, for the more patient of our readers, I have compiled a list of the best technology stocks for long term investors. Its not a comprehensive list, but its got some gems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Apple The Best Dividend Growth Stock In The Market? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ezra Edelman Wiki: Everything to Know About the Oscar Winner for Best Documentary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oscars 2017: 'Moonlight' Wins Best Picture After 'La La Land' Mistakenly Announced as Winner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 14:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drug OD Deaths Have Nearly Tripled Since 1999: CDC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Top Cybersecurity Stocks for 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 15:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Swings to Loss in 4Q, Says Model 3 on Target </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discovery of 7 Earth-Size Exoplanets a 'Giant Leap' Forward in Alien-Life Hunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadian Marijuana Stocks Poised to Ramp Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMD Ryzen 7 Lifts Advanced Micro Devices Stock, Hits Intel Stock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Much Is the U.S. National Debt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA to Unveil New Exoplanet Discovery Tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Most Cheap Kenyan Female Celebrities. No 5 is the most scandulous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peta Murgatroyd and Maks Chmerkovskiy Announce Return to 'DWTS' After the Birth of Their Baby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EARNINGS Walmart Draws Digital Bead On Amazon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 13:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alibaba Pictures Stock Slumps 3.5% On Word Of Latest Loss.Alibaba Group, led by billionaire Jack Ma, made a big push into the entertainment industry in 2014 just ahead of its world-record IPO at the New York Stock Exchange.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple WWDC 2017 Could Push Apple Stock to New Highs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock/apple-wwdc-2017-push-apple-stock-new-highs/
**Why WWDC 2017 Is Significant for Apple Stock**
Apple Inc. (NASDAQ:AAPL) stock has come a long way since the WWDC 2016 event held in San Francisco. Apple WWDC 2017 is especially significant for AAPL stock as investors are contemplating how Apple Inc. may transform itself into more of a services company to maintain its position as the most valuable company in the world. Apple stock made another record closing at $135.72 on Friday and is up more than 17% year-to-date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George Soros Stock Market Predictions for 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.lombardiletter.com/george-soros-stock-market-predictions/7502/
If you want to get a good idea of where the stock market is going in 2017, it might be a good idea to see what the smart money is doing. In this case, its George Soros, the founder of the $4.5-billion Soros Fund Management LLC and the 23rd wealthiest person in the world. What is George Soros predicting for 2017?

Soros has a comprehensive understanding of the U.S. and global markets, and the U.S. economic outlook for 2017. Soros famously made $1.0 billion in a single day, back in 1992 when he bet against the British pound. So we know hes not afraid to make a big bet on something hes sure of, even if the prevailing wisdom suggests otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economist Marc Faber Warns Investors to Go Long on Gold, Silver, and Platinum in 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After data breaches, Verizon knocks $350M off Yahoo sale, now valued at $4.48B </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://techcrunch.com/2017/02/21/verizon-knocks-350m-off-yahoo-sale-after-data-breaches-now-valued-at-4-48b/
After the disclosure of two massive data breaches last year, today Yahoo and Verizon finally confirmed new terms for the sale of Yahoo to Verizon: Verizon will pay $350 million less than originally planned, working out to a price of $4.48 billion to acquire Yahoo.

The two have also agreed to share legal and regulatory liabilities after the massive data breach at Yahoo, which affected some 1.5 billion users across two hacks, one covering 500 million users revealed in September 2016, and another covering 1 billion users disclosed in December 2016. TechCrunch has also confirmed that any further Yahoo liability going forward will be assumed by Altaba, the newly branded holding company that will oversee the Yahoo stake in Alibaba after the sale of the rest of the assets to Verizon.

The deal is now expected to close in Q2 2016, the two companies said. Verizon also owns AOL, which owns TechCrunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Close to Trump Is Too Close for Boeing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 14:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
