<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2315</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sweet and cute. I hope she reconsiders and gives you another chance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohmagawd  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's so gorgeous. That skin is so smooth, that body is svelte! Scha-wing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I DIED  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, Riz is so beautiful and adorable. I want to snuggle him forever  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But now I'm unable to stop doing the right thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this! These stories either slipped my mind completely or I simply wasn't paying attention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've looked them up right on their website. There used to be one woman who seems to be of South Asian ancestry, but she's no longer reading for them. 

And I'm not sure if they're volunteers or if they're paid (I would imagine they get compensation now due to the shows success), but I think that's irrelevant to my question. 

I've heard David make an announcement at the beginning of a show that they get lots of interest from people wanting to read for them but that they aren't looking for new voice actors. I find it hard to believe that zero people of color have reached out with interest in joining their ranks. So if they have discovered their actors solely through a voluntary process, the basis for your response simply doesn't make sense. 

As a mixed-black queer woman, I'm fully aware that there's no such thing as "sounding" a race, ethnicity, sexual preference, or even a gender/sex etc. But it would be cool to hear some accents that aren't white British or white Irish or white Canadian or white American. It would be cool to hear African accents, Asian Accents. It would even be cool to hear stories read by black and brown American folx with certain vernaculars that some might say are stereotypical as people who use certain vernaculars do exist and as a person who grew up in and around it, the "hood" has some scary happenings/stories. It would be cool to hear an extremely effeminate male voice actor read for them. It would be cool to hear a gender-ambiguous voice. It would be cool to hear stories by and about POC and LGBTQIA folx and the things that only we experience. 

And for every one listener that would stop listening due to their inability to relate to anything that isn't white and hetero, I know the show would gain two more listeners who would be stoked on the representation. 

I also want to note that I don't think anyone who controls anything on the show is at all racist or intentionally excluding anyone, but I do think they simply aren't fully cognizant of how important representation is, especially when you're getting as big as NoSleep is getting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really offended, per say. Just curious is all. 

If Eurocentricity and heteronormativity offended me, I would spend my life in a state of offense. I like the straights and the whites! Many of friends and family members are straight and white. I adore the voice actor roster and the stories NoSleep picks. It would just be cool to have some variation. 

And I actually just wrote my first story. As my writing gets better, I plan to submit directly to the podcast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This has been asked before, I think, but got removed before I saw the responses: Why isn't there any POC and LGBTQIA representation on the show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Los Bastardos: Bastard #1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to believe me when I tell you that I never meant to murder anyone. But he kept trying to put is filthy hands up my shirt! I repeatedly told the bastard "NO!" Like so many before him, he persisted. As I sat there nearly giving up my protest out of fear that, if I didn't, the situation might quickly turn more violent and deadly dangerous... it was as if every hurt, every bruise, every assault, every ignored "no," every removal of rights and autonomy and agency ever inflicted on any woman suddenly became my own. 

I could feel the rage in my being reaching critical mass and something inside me broke wide open. 

As bastard #1 roughly pawed at my breasts and drunkenly drooled all over my neck, I felt around in my nightstand for the Montblanc Bonheur Fountain Pen my aunt had gifted to me last Eid. I'm quite sure he thought I was searching for a condom for his undoubtedly minuscule dick. "Got it!" I thought to myself as I gently removed the pen's cap. Then, with all the force I could muster from my 5'2" frame, I jabbed the Montblanc directly into what I hoped was his jugular. I pushed it in deep, twisted it around a bit, and swiftly pulled it back out. If the massive spurts of blood emitting from his neck were any indication, I had successfully found that precious vein. 

He looked at me with wide-eyed puzzlement, I stared directly back at him with wide-smile amusement. 

"You stabbed me, you stupid bitch!" were his last words before collapsing. I watched as he continued to bleed, slower now, onto my floor. I listened to his breaths becoming fainter and fainter. I headed to the kitchen to borrow my carnivorous roommate's meat cleaver and returned to my room, where he was lying on the floor, unfortunately still gasping for oxygen.

I stood over him, stared at him, then sat down on his chest with the meat cleaver in my right hand. With my left, I poked and prodded and stuck my fingers into the gaping hole I made just ten minutes before.

I took stock of the situation in which I found myself and began slicing into the flesh and bones of his neck until his head was completely detached from his pathetic body. His eyes were still wide open and his face still bore the signs of sheer terror. 

Sitting atop his lifeless (and now headless) body, I never felt more invigorated. And the release of the kill was absolutely magnificent, I tell you! Every fear, every hurt... all things fell away. I held the power.

I was almost giddy with euphoria until I realized I still had work to do on behalf of bastard #1's mistakes. Ugh. Even in death, men are writhing disappoints. I mean, he didn't even have the decency to bleed out on a blanket or something. Nope, right onto my gleaming, pristine pre-war hardwood. The bastard. 

"You've made such a fucking mess!" I shouted at his corpse as I set about cleaning up after him. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Jerk, Baby Boy, Mean Girls  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you're funnin' or trollin', but this is not a fact. They are not pink lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That so many people repeat the same scientific fact within only several minutes of one another. I don't think many people are reading other people's posts. It's like the same 20 or so things are said over and over again. Wow. Blowin' my mind, man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we talking a silicone dong? Because I tried to google it and I'm getting nothing haha. Please, further enlighten us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I replayed that part several times to make sure I wasn't buggin. I think it says "Oh, by the way, Big Red says hi." Throughly creeped me out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean when leaving Islam? Or leaving Saudi?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I must add that many western women often struggle for years to get a man to even propose. Whereas in majority Islamic countries and in Islam in general, marriage is easy to come by. So if a woman badly wants marriage and family, the western way of dating around often endlessly would seem like a miserable time to women who are brought up knowing that they will easily get married and obtain that family life quickly. 

But again, noooot worth it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an ex-Muslim revert, I'd say the only thing I loved about my brief time as a Muslim vs my life before and after is not having to fucking work! That is one area where Muslim women who are married to men who earn a decent living have it made. There's literally no expectation for a woman to work even if her husband is broke and jobless, he must find a way to support her. I mean, even housework and cooking aren't required of Muslim women (unless poor or from a culture where that's expected.) But Saudi women, for example, who are at least Middle class... most have full-time maids (and nannies if they have youngsters) and full-time drivers and really aren't expected to do much other than pop out babies, maybe cook, and shop (which is why there are so many malls here). This is true for all of the GCCs. 

Yeah, that part is enviable. But it's ultimately not worth the immense restrictions on women and on one's humanity in general.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the kind of Hadith that started my initial turn away from Islam. Like what in the actual fuck does this have to do with anything?! It's just so nonsensical!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
