<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4091</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides he is no stranger to these matters. Take his "tatsulok" for example. It was written years ago and its remained relevant to the current state of the country. Perhaps even more relevant now that ever.

OP try listening to the song </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please do ask about this. One of the reasons why i like him so much is how he tried to address these issues. He's ine of the few opm artists who genuinely cares about the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should get a feeder!

Ive only ever seen a hummingbird once. My mom grows a lot of flowers and we often get beesitors. One time this hummingbird visited her garden while me and my cousins were playing by the porch. I told my cousins and all of us stopped playing just to watch that magnificent creature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insta cooked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WAIT! They're airing it already!? Gyejalauwlwjbwha fuck exams im binging this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive been running too for the past couple of months in preparation for my military PFT. Here's 2 things that greatly changed my running.

1. Inhaling through the nose and and exhale through my mouth

2. Finding the correct music that matches my rhythm. For the first 6 weeks ive been listening really upbeat songs; mostly hiphop and while my speed had been improving, it always feels difficult to reach my goal(run 3mi in sub-18minutes). Then i listened to gorillaz' clint eastwood. Suddenly after 3mi was comfortable to run. To which i extended my distance to 5mi.

Hopefully you'll find your rhythm as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot. Im guessing you used a cron? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/creepy would love this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fucking awesome! I love glitch art that happens naturally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why hello there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHEN DOES IT END!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im glad you used a gif instead. I have a huge crush on her and what i noticed is, on pics, she doesnt look as pretty as she does on vids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And her voice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting it to get sexual for some reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't be surprised if this was winsor   newton.  Im envious of your blending skills! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful. Almost looks digital when not zoomed in </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would like to try it as well. Have you had any experience with desktop pen tablets before? ie wacom? I want to know how much different is it to use compared to wacom.

James jean uses ipad pro and pen with procreate and the pieces he creates are marvelous! Then again, it IS james jean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool concept </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvoted. Kek </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back when vector art was still a thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here i am.... rock you like a hurricane </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do this too. Often times it's delayed especially if it's a drawing/painting. One of them took six months but still. I only do it tho if i know i can deliver, it'll take months but i'll deliver.

Sometimes I intentionally let them forget it first. Truth is tho, i dont think they really forget. Just tired of bringing it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you thank you. I only have tumblr and ig but i havent really posted in a long time. I should tho as i have a lot of unpublished works. Im currently reworking an old work; kinda creepy as well. I think you'll like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandpa was my bestfriend when i was a kid. Whenever my grandma would go on a trip to visit our relatives, i would stay with my grandpa and he would tell me stories during his time in the military. I look up to him so much. He passed away when i was 14 but he's one of the reasons why i'm joining the military. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww man. I wish but she's thousand miles away. Don't wanna put anyone through LDR again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It was very hard at first.

 my favorite is the bit of purple/magenta on the shoulder


I'm glad someone appreciate that bit :)

Edit: idk how to format on mobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I've been practicing. Hopefully ill get it right someday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!

I knoww. I hope they get renewed for season 4. Seriously, the succeeding arc is what i was looking forward to the most.

To think bryan fuller finally broke the 2-seasons curse only to get cancelled again atfter season 3. What even? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The stag is very symbolic. The thing i like about it the most is how it transitioned to hannibal wendigo. Gave me goosebumps as it was both awesome and creepy at the same time. It's amazing how they portrayed the psychology of the characters(or at least Will and Hannibal) using magickal symbols. 

As for the human totem.. aggh! it's definitely one of my top 3 favourites along with the mushroom garden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbf, i do a lot of ps but i dont see what youre getting at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank mr skeltal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm posting it for the third time, i know. I should have posted it here first.

Coquilles is my favourite episode from the series when it comes to the aethetics. I think the cinematography is brilliant.


Question: What's your favourite sculpture/installation in the series? What is your design?


Also, I hope it gets renewed soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Coquilles" [x-post from r/Art] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My thoughts about season 3 is clouded by the prospect of season 4. I treated it as a primer since the things that are supposed to happen next would be my favourite in the series. God fucking damn it why isnt it renewed yet!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aagh that was fucking brilliant! Makes you wanna think, "what would be my design?"

I mean.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made her hair a little bit too big. I'm usually pretty strict with the face but with the hair, i just let loose. It's fun.


My main goal was to try and achieve a somewhat oilpaint-like texture using colour pencils(esp for the skin). :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knooww. It was so haunting. I had a different plan for the drawing but i diverted to this. The human sculptures/installations on the entire serieas are amazing but this stuck to me the most. Human totem pole comes second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
