<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1236</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing CSGO in Full HD seems just so wierd to me, I tried but had to switch back to 4:3 scaled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The old launcher was basic, beatiful, fast and well designed. found everything I needed in seconds. The new client is overdone, overdesigned and not practical. The animations are very clunky, chats fucking horrible. There was no need for a new client whatsoever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Pie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not going to music school 8 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would probably study more (In 8th grade). I am 16 currently and had to study hard in 9th grade order to get accepted into my desired gymnasium (10th-12th grade). If I studied harder the year before, this year would have been easier.   
As I mentioned, still go accepted though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure in Islamic countries it won't be accepted for 25 years atleast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disease...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mis neid "cringe'iks" muudab?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repeat please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paljud multifilmid nagu nt Shrek, Garfield, Rio jne on Eesti keeles paremad (minu arvates), tihtilugu lhevad nitlejate hled karakteritega kvasti paremini kokku. kki tahab Pilliboy18 pojale kvaliteeti nidata? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2012 he thought this wasn't a goal: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Snsouq5Qiy0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best parts:  
2:44
4:30  
8:50  
11:35  
13:07   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 2011, Estonia vs Ireland, Kassai was the head referee. From that day on, he is the most well known referee in Estonia. Love his calls! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I've learned while visiting the sub for a year: Elections and referendums are all rigged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> likonnad tallinnas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 12:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tervist!
Ega keegi ei oska nimetada mnda poodi Tallinnas, kus vib leida tumelillasid, rohelisi, punaseid jms natukene vrvilisemaid likondi Tallinnas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 23:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Communism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I jusr want to cover the  guitar, with lyrics however </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Help regarding recording a guitar track, specifically how can I sort of eliminate it from the song (so I don't have to use bad backing tracks w/o vocals) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello folks!
My guitar teacher let me borrow his processor, a Avid Eleven Rack if curious and I'm loving it and thinking about doing a cover. I don't need help with recording, mixing or stuff like that, rather than the song I want to cover.
How can I cover a song without downloading a crappy backing track without lyrics? I would love the lyrics to be there, I was thinking that fuck it, just gonna record over the song, it feels wierd however. The song I'm talking about is Gojira - From The Sky. Is there any way to sort of eliminate the guitar track completely from the original song or sort of volume it down in order to let me guitar be the dominant one.
Probably a stupid question, I hope to recieve an answer however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Help recording a cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [SONG] A possibly instrumental song. Vocaroo included </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://vocaroo.com/i/s1U24WWHN6nR

randomly popped into my head last night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 23:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea what a 3,14 day is, however, it is the mother tongue day in estonia though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 vids  year tho lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 06:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He can play every stringed instrument literally :d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 20:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unnecessary flight removal... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I think the teaching wasn't the main purpose of the video :d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the best profiles I've ever seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] [Rob Scallon's, not mine] Rob Scallon teaching Slap Guitar, while abusing his 8 string </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wC9QTHv2eQ4

pretty rad imo, can't believe how he talks at the same time he does this shit :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 23:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haircut reminds of John Wick buddy, nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 22:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Estonian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 20:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A country, whose people really want to get us regonized as a nordic country, which I, for some reason don't understand :d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't drink legally (and buy alchohol) until your 18, but that being said, most kids start drinking from grade 7, which is where the 13 year olds turn 14. Smoking starts from there also :d </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2,5 Year Growth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not from the US, where I live you can get what we call a "milk-license" (little kids drink milk so we call it a baby's license). When you are 16, you can apply for a license that allows you to drive as long as there is another driver with a full license (who has had it for 2 years)
I will do the milky ones, so the full ones at 18 will not be that much of a hustle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is machine casting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the way, bottle cap for scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This amount of hair collected on my comb within a week. I'm 15 with thin, about 30 cm long hair. Have I reached my hair growth limit, since I highyly doubt I'm balding. (Sorry, I really like my hair and now am a bit paranoid) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 17:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was the most fitting one I found where i could expect a reply from ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't watch the prices at first, anyways, I would suggest maison, look unique*r* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both look cool imo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folks, where could I order ear studs like this https://imgur.com/sFnDiBX online internationally that aren't made from cheap shit and don't cause infections etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chat filter forced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started noticing how after 2 years since I disabled chat censoring it suddenly shows ***** quite often, are they forcing it now to make the game for kindergarten kids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 21:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atlantis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you explain me what she said in the video? Why is this one kansas and this one not Arkansas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A metal song with all guitar pitch notes course (vocaroo included) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://vocaroo.com/i/s1PEsNuG0eTI
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/fuckswithducks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will research it first i guess, i think that not showing battery precentage is also a retarded change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The OxygenOS that came to OnePlus 2 a few weeks ago is missing some features or I suddenly have to enable them in some ultra advanced settings place? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It used to be that when I pulled the notification bar down and then held my finger on the data button, instead of triggering it's main function it showed the data cap. Now the shit leads to settings, it used to be that when you held your finger on Wifi, you would get a little window of available networks, not leads to Wifi settings. Did they remove these features? In order to check my data cap, I ought to go to settings now eh.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 23:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think you will be making any videos similar to your stuff earlier like "This isn't yellow", "What does a shadow weigh" etc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every person's health is their own deal, obesity should be illegal too? All obese people into gas chambers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Eliminating smoking is a sensible limitation for the net benefit of everyone, including smokers.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 16:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you think every smoker wants to quit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 21:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Id rank snax above him for sure though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seems to be a consistent yet hella boring player, like I don't remember any "sick", "flash" or "Huge" play by him, although I can recall many of other players, even like from byali. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never understood this subreddit's hype to device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 20:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Achievementwise astralis was bad compared to SK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot. Weed is expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 14:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found it on the net, had a laugh myself :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 13:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Visa requirement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Estonla, a alcohol tax is coming up which leads tons of more people into Valka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the chain, everything leads to Russia =D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feissis on grupp ,,Jah, see on vegan." Seal 10 000 liiget vms, vid liituda </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a propsal of a bus service going straight from the Tallinn port to Alko1000 in Valka, Latvia. I believe it hasn't been nor approved or decilined yet, but I might not be happening still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alcohol Chain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 12:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> device second? achievements do count too buddy, astralis wasnt that successful this year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] A song called "Still" singer, the music video was where he was laying down in a car park showed british trains etc (he also had telecaster shaped guitar in his hand sometimes in the video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 15:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for the artist of a song called "still". He was a english pop musician, the video was with him lying down the car park and sometimes had a telecaster in his hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 23:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone heard anything about Phant0mlord? Did dude like get a fake id and went to live on Madagascar or smth? He has been playing League though http://na.op.gg/summoner/userName=phantoml0rd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 17:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> virtus.pro had always been some kind of a shit up until they updated the site and got the url, virtuspro.org was their site before they got their wanted domain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/9M4BSlM.png

Any1 know where to buy a hat looking like that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/9M4BSlM.png

Any1 know where to buy a hat looking like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Where to buy a hat like this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 00:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I filter matches and press Go nothing happens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 22:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Interval album is great, I love every song in it, however finding the right tabs to certain seems to be a hard task for me. Fucking Plini is awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION][RECOMMENDATION] Any 6 string progressive metal song for learning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 23:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hi fellas,  
i would love to learn a progressive metal song which is played on a 6 string guitar. I've found some great songs I would love to, unfortunately most of them are on 7 or 8 strings.  
Would be great that the song you recommend stays under 4 minutes.

thanks fellas

EDIT: would be awesome if your recommendations were something in the lines of Animals as leaders or scale the summit etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I highly doubt Estonians number, i can probably think of like 15. I'm guessing that the number really doesn't go over 60-70. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 00:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age became sex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 21:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. 0 dmg is trynd goal is to only push, never do any damage to enemies the whole game (damage dealt to champs: 0). It is an advanced form of disrespect as the video author said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 11:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, not my first language </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 11:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said it about tryn, not singed, used ,,this" in a wrong place. Replace it with ,,it's" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 11:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said it about tryn, not singed, used this in a wrong place. Replace it with it's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 11:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No shit dude, i even said that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 01:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said it about 0 dmg tryn, not singed420 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 00:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Losing a diamond, years old account, it is a lot tougher to get over it than to get over 1 ruined game lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 00:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get over that 1 ruined game... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said that 0 dmg trynd is the same thing as Singed420's proxy games. Tbh I can't understand what you exactly replied to me, pacifist tryndamere is unacceptable as I said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen Singed420 do that tbh, not helping the fellas who gank him.  



This video is bullshit, i know, I understand everybody concern, but I think some people are insane with their judgements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ofcourse, there's a difference in having a bad game and inting, your absolutely right on that. But he doesn't int every game, he might have double digit deaths some games, but he actually tries most of the games, some less, some more.  
  
This shit ofcourse was inting, and this shit ain't acceptable BUT doesn't deserve an instant perma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Video. Game. You. Can. Get. Fucking. Over. 1. Loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zero Damage Tryndamere is an entirely different thing. This is downright trolling, inting, refusing to communicate/teamwork etc. This shit deserves a perma IF, you play it without your 5 premade who plays for fun and agree on that shit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other day, there was a twitch clip about jared giving qtpie's sick galio a kill - standing still since he was caught off guard. You think he deserves a perma? Even though he's definitely popularized the game, played it since fucking release, has a lot of skins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fed some when I was lvl 5-15 (or near that mark). I should be death sentenced, even though I haven't inted for years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This fid flair guys says the he trolls all of his games. He has number of deaths every game, some games have more because we all have bad games. Find me a person who hasnt been like 2/13 once in his fucking playtime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, it is a video game holy shit. 2 ints shouldn't be a permaban either. It's not like those 2 30-40 minute games are gonna ruin your rank forever, your gonna derank to bronze 5, your family leaves you, you will get to be homeless etc.     

It's a video game that exists in a fucking virtual platform.   
I agree there's a limit, I would give several weeks of banhammer to 2 int's too, but fucking perma? I'm sure that you have inted in your playing time, whether it was 4 years ago or 5 or who knows when. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He finished Diamond 1 I believe. Dude got Diamond 1, he obviously does something right lol. Some people literally here are fucking insane about punishments. I agree that int'ing isn't something to do, but you don't have to get fucking permad for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude got Diamond 1, he obviously does something right lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> applying your logic to real life: don't show the turning signal, life improsonment, throwing 1 candy paper on the ground death sentence? Dude got Diamond 1, he obviously does something right lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 22:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reddit police LOL int 1 game, gotta get fucking permaban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in csgo it's car at B </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are wondering who the dude at the beginning is, defuzah was a editor since 1.6, probably Estonian's like 2nd best or something similar to that. Recently, at 18/19 years old, he and his friends crashed into a tree going atleast 140km/h. All dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wallbanging in D2 Noob corner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 12:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Zool or whoever makes the maps CSCO'ified, could you please make the noob corner in dd2 wallbangable? atleast with awp. Also, the wooden boxes are abit thick :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 00:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did his parents say anything after his suicide? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely not the highest in smoking cigs underage. You haven't seen Europe. Most teen americans think of smoking as something hella taboo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old Town is what Reval (now Tallinn, capital of Estonia now, which has expanded outside the walls) was back in the Middle Ages. It is the main tourist attraction in Tallinn, there are flats there and people live there. There's also hotels there. Mostly it is covered by cafe's. Old Town is basically the heart of Tallinn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's the cozy album ;\)](http://meeldib.postimees.ee/2016/12/boredpanda-avaldas-fotograaf-kaupo-kalda-imelise-ulevaate-tallinna-kaunist-vanalinnast-mis-oleks-otsekui-keskaegsest-muinasjutust-valja-astunud-2/#_)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A very cozy ally in Old Town, Tallinn (album in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 15:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> StatTrak pedometer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gojira - Magma live footage anywhere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sup folks,
basically im trying to find a live version of Gojiras "Magma". I see Silvera, Shooting Star, Stranded live version on youtube a lot, but with the help of google intensive 30 minute long search I somehow haven't managed to find it, I'm guessing they haven't played it live.

Maybe some of you know  a live version of it, would love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't shoot through th egap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/sneakers startpack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 21:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about Lord Timepieces (The cheap watches) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problem with Oneplus 2 and USB file transfers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heyo!

I got a Oneplus 2 for 4 months now and I needed to get some pics and videos to my pc. Well, when I connectit to my pc, 80% of the pics and videos are not in DCIM folder, nor anywhere else. In order to get them I had to import all the images and videos.
  
I've never had this happen to any other android phone I have used and it really pisses me off.   
To clarify, my device is unrooted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today's american youngsters seem to be so spoiled about weed, they always know the strain, the thc %, look so nice and purple, or albino. Most of the world you go and buy "weed", 0 clue about what strain it is, %is etc, but it still gets you nice and high. It was probably same pre 2000's in the US, not so sure about it though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 20:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SOLVED YEA! IT was cause of the layer of plastic I removed from the pedal earlier below the motherboard, the switch didnt quite reach it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 19:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does not, the switch feels too easy to do anything. No clicks whatsoever go down.
Here's a gif, maybe it's cause I removed the layer of plastic fro, the motherboard, when i got it.
https://gfycat.com/GlitteringDefensiveCoral </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/BPpCmzF.jpg Inside, fresh battery, 9 Volts. It heats up when I plug the input output things in etc. With adapter just to the pedal, no, the Led wont turn on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly no, I might hit the music store where I bought it and test it there. Sadly I lost the check so if the pedal's broken I wont the money back :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't plug it to the wall, no extra 9V adapter, with cable snake the little amp goes off and so does the pedal. Too much to handle for that 1 adapter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Replaced the battery 2 minutes before doing this video, and as i said, i feel the pedal getting warmer on the sides
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GEAR] [HELP] Boss DS-1 not working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 17:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B88372KRtdR2ZnJ2cnZTc0hwWnM/view  

Here's a video of the problem. Battery in, input output cables into the amp and no sound what so ever. I can feel the pedal being warm when i touch it with my hands so it is getting power. It has worked before, not today though. When I push it hard, the amp makes some noise, similar to taking your cable out of your guitar when amp's on.  
What is this madness ;( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone else noticed that people dodge more often? Feels like 3 times more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I have both pickups selected and both knobs max, it makes sound. When I turn the upper one volume's down, the bridge one still makes sound. Vice versa it doesn't however </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GEAR] [HELP] Problem with pick-ups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 21:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ran into a little problem 5 minutes ago.
I have a Schecter Lady Luck, 2 humbucker pickups. Basically, If I have selected both and both pickup volmes are full, it makes sound. When I turn the bridge one down, there is absolutely no sound even though the upper one is still on max volume.
When I select the upper one only, it makes a sound though, and if both are selected and volume is up, by "punching" the upper pickup with my pick it makes a sound. Wierd shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 13:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seen it, don't know about the others but it didn't spark any kind of claustrophobic feeling for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 11:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, i still visit the sub even tho i have normal parents. However, i made this about the whining posts who think that parents must and gotta support everything they do etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching this movie as you commented since my friend recommended it to me last week. Great movie, im a bit mindfucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movies where the criminals win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I'd figure I would come here and I ask if you could recommend/tell me any movies where the criminals - let them be bank robbers, just robbers, drug lords, hitmen etc.

Here's a passage I took from a review of Heat since simple under 300 character questions are forbid it seems:  

Michael Mann's writing and direction elevate this material.

It's not just an action picture. Above all, the dialogue is complex enough to allow the characters to say what they're thinking: They are eloquent, insightful, fanciful, poetic when necessary. They're not trapped with cliches. Of the many imprisonments possible in our world, one of the worst must be to be inarticulate - to be unable to tell another person what you really feel. These characters can do that. Not that it saves them.  
Credit to Roger Ebert </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movies where the criminals win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movies where the criminals win? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 20:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/raisedbynarcissists starterpack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 14:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 21:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tallinna Ehituskoolis ning Poltehnikumis reaalselt mingi 90% teevad suitsu vi vapevad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite tunes, I have one request for you folks. Can  you find the lyrics to this song? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lee "Scratch" Perry - Bed Jammin' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one missing hearing champion quotes any time I click on champs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In Nazi germany, there was a children's educational book called ,,The Poisonous Mushroom", which taught to recognize jews - the poisonous mushrooms were jews and children had to recognize them (jewishvirtuallibrary.org) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 22:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way i can transform my torrents from bitTorrent to Qbittorrent? https://gyazo.com/eab49eb87d4d1c2e3ae3141b3145191f </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean like the list of torrents visible in the client. I'm so proud of my 40-50 torrents and I want to see them in Qbittorrent so I dont have to start fresh from the start ;( 
EDIT; im retard linked the img to the title https://gyazo.com/eab49eb87d4d1c2e3ae3141b3145191f </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way i can transform my torrents from bitTorrent to Qbittorrent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 22:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way i can transform my torrents from bitTorrent to Qbittorrent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean like the list of torrents visible in the client. I'm so proud of my 40-50 torrents and I want to see them in Qbittorrent so I dont have to start fresh from the start ;(
https://gyazo.com/d4939c5c50076d21b7d916c01f994c1a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 22:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lighters, from this year. Got about 50 from 10different countries atm! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 21:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 150 seconds for regular camps, what the fuck? From 50 or 60 seconds to 100 in S5 to 150 now? Rip farming junglers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people count 60ms lag? I have been playing with 70-80 ping for 3 years. Since 100 is where i count it laggy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where could I find a legit recipe for making LSD? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 13:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
