<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3285</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd do it but I'm currently writing the series "I'm Stuck in A Bio-Lab".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds really cool! You should do it before someone else takes it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on my 7th day. You got this man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a pathogen, more specifically a fungus, not a drug. I can't contact the CDC or any organization for that matter. The campus wifi has special blockers that only allow me to interact with Google search engine, and social media.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There'd be nothing else to do if I did get infected. However I can't contact the CDC, the wifi has some special software that sifts through phone usage. It restricts communications down to Google search engine social media only. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm Stuck in a Bio-Lab (Part One) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen guys, I dont have a lot of time. My phone is the only access I have to the outside world, and all it has is some shitty wifi connection. Im not sure if Im going to get out of here alive, and if I dont, you wont be around for much longer either. 

We designed a biological weapon, a disease thats growth sprawls all over your brain. Its fast acting, only taking 10-15 minutes to take over your mind. Once it does, it sends you into a hallucinogenic state. Your body starts convulsing into a constant state of horrific pain, it alters your brain chemistry to send you into a psychopathic state, your fight or flight responses kick in, making you attack all living creatures nearby. 

I hate my job, I wanted to design medicine. Ever since I was a little kid, I would play doctor with my mom and pretend to heal her of any diseases. I would give anything to be back there instead of the living Hell that entraps me. 

Big surprise, death found a way to prevail. Butt-fuck Benny, my lab assistant, somehow found his way onto my computer. I never told him the password, but I guess stupidity can work wonders. He wanted to see the disease for himself, so he unlocked the chamber remotely from my desktop. 

He got to see the disease alright, and so did the labs secretary when a screaming and convulsing Benny ripped her tongue straight out from between her teeth. It didnt take long for campus security to put Benny down, but they didnt know the dangers of what they encountered. 

The idiots shot Benny in the head, the worst thing you could do to a fungal infection. The spores spread into the air, infecting anyone in the 20 foot proximity. 

Meanwhile, I was at my desk, doing some paperwork when I got the email. I knew what was about to happen. I locked my door and stacked my chair and desk against it. The door and its hinges were made out of some titanium-steel alloy, but the feeling of security felt nice. I sat in the middle of the floor and waited for the screams to commence.

And they did.

It was like a symphony straight from Satans choir. Male and female voices joined each other in the perfect symbiosis of agony and wretched gasps for breath. I heard the pounding of fists and the tearing of flesh no more than a few feet outside my door. They were killing each other. 

While working in a factory of death, youd think Id be use to death quite literally being at my door. Youd be wrong. Those screams echo in my mind like a catchy 70s love song. The infected individuals outside screamed as though there soul was leaving their bodies. The screams sounded not so much like terror or fear, but a longing. A longing to die, something that wouldnt happen until a week later when the fungus devours the brain. 

Eventually the abrupt thuds of boney knuckles against flesh stopped, and all that was left was the unpunctuated, persistent groans and shrieks of pain. I sat there in the center of the floor praying to anyone that would listen that I would get out of here alive. 

That was yesterday.

My dreams were plagued by the undying screams of the tortured souls clawing at their skin in desperation to get the pain to stop. I wondered about them. Were their conscious minds still active? Were they aware of what they were doing? The pathogen was still under study, we only knew what it did to your body not your soul.

The screams and moans have begun to die down. The afflicted mustve moved on to another area. Thats when I heard it.

NO!!! PLEASE GOD NO!!! a womans voice shrieked from the room 30 feet across from mine.

I peeked through a small, portrait-sized window. I saw a mob of frenzied afflicted had managed to force their way into Doctor Shawanas office. Shawana was the only women in my division, and a cute one too. She had toned legs, a well-kept body, and beautiful wavy black hair. It was a shame to see the black hair practically being ripped from her scalp by a muscular infected security guard. She let out one final scream as she fell to the floor. Thuds landed on her body, scratches and cuts drained her of blood.

She was dead.

I fell upon my knees and vomited onto the floor. After about a minute there were no more fluids left in my body and I was doing nothing but dry heaving. The afflicted heard this and let out painful wretched screams. They charged my door and threw themselves at it. I could hear the crunching of their bones as they broke their limbs and skulls against the metal door. 

Those sounds didnt bother me so much, the noises that really got to me was the screams and footsteps from behind me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice, maybe? I've never had this problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent verse! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mother Wants to Force Her 3-Year-Old Son to Become A Faggot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am getting to the point where I don't want the west to be saved anymore. The best thing to pray for, at this point, is the rapture.

[Mother Wants to Force Her 3-Year-Old Son to Become A Faggot](http://www.conservativenews.com/article/2499/left-wing-feminists-freaks-out-when-her?utm_source=facebook utm_medium=social utm_content=062316-news utm_campaign=benshapiro) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad I could help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Views on Sin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't directly pertaining to NoFap but more on general sin. However I do think it would be beneficial to share my story to you all. 

Throughout my childhood and up to about 8th grade, I was slowly but surely falling away from my Catholic faith. I was going day to day chasing the next good feeling, whether it was masturbation, unhealthy foods, pornography, or spending hours a day not doing my homework and video gaming/watching TV. I was failing almost all my classes because I was too weak to deal with the stress and didn't care. All I cared about was pleasure, and that is all that defined me. Inevitably, I almost completely fell away from my Catholic faith, even going as far as to say that God hates me. I became severely depressed and plotted multiple ways to commit suicide, which I thought about and revised multiple times. 

My soul was completely drowned in sin. On top of that, I also suffered from sexual deviancy which I will not go into detail about. However, I came out of this wretched part of my life still a virgin and thank God for that everyday.

I woke up and realized that my depression was caused by my sin and my broken relationship with God. The more I strayed away from him, the more I hated myself. After months of recuperation, I have finally begun restoring my faith and improving my relationship with God. 

Now as a sophomore, I have cut out almost all of the sinful parts of my life, and I am eager to live with God as the main priority in my life and placing everything second to him, including myself and my temptations. Now that I am improving my faith, every sin hurts me greatly. It makes me feel like I'm returning to that state where I was living in perpetual sin. I thank God for it, because it provides me an incentive to work harder, but it is a very difficult process.

My advice to you is to place God first. Nothing comes before him. While suffering and pain in your life may be almost unbearable, he is the ultimate salvation. Trust in him, and he will lead you down the righteous path. I love you all, and thank you for reading. I truly hope my story provides some sort of inspiration for you, as it has for me. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Note To Prevent Relapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I typed this up on my phone to look at in order to prevent relapse. 

Satan is the one influencing your thoughts and emotions. He is manipulating your depression to make it seem like sin (masturbation) is the only way out, much like he did when Jesus was in the desert for 40 days. He made it seem like he (sin) was the only way to satisfaction. Notice how your emotions and desires drive you to be lustful, angry, and full of despair; all of which are three of the seven deadly sins. God will lead you through this, he wants you to get to Heaven and accept him. He loves you like a parent loves their child. Much like a parent, he wants nothing but success for his child. Ignore the emotions, ignore the temptations of Satan. Place yourself in God's hands. He will take care of you. 

I hope this helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was swamped with emotions and stress from a lack of PMO. I need to find a way to better manage my emotions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Relapsed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My goal was 2 weeks and I almost made it to 24 days. I have that to be proud of. My next goal is 60 days (with no relapse at/past it)! Wish me luck! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll get there man. Thanks so much for the advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I've just never felt this way before. Thank you though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 23 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Is Wrong With Me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NoFap is making me incredibly depressed. I've lost all motivation and just want to cry. I still have a sexual urge, a strong one actually, so I'm not flat-lining. I don't know what's wrong with me, but I honestly just want to relapse to get this feeling to end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here! I would put on a mask of confidence and act as though I was. In all reality, I hated myself. That's not the case anymore. I know my worth. I know how much influence I can have. NoFap has helped me so much.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. I was hiding parts of myself through masturbation. Now that I no longer do, they've been revealed to me. I've had them all along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
