<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9832</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nice nail Polish, red is a little dated."

The man took a sip of his coffee, and set it on his desk.

"I get bored and I do it for fun I guess."

"Did anyone follow you?" 

"No," Timothy said quietly. The man standing behind the desk stood up, adjusted his tie and walked over to the window.

"Did you bring the money?" The man asked buttoning up his jacket. "Yes or no?"

"I want to know what they are first."

The man turned and laughed, "You're going to waste my time like that? Come here to my fuckin office? Sit in the fuckin chair. And think what I have to sell to is fuckin cheap? Do you know who I am?"

Timothy nodded his head. 

"Good. You better. This is why I have a name that is hard to find but people want. This is why you're in that chair. It's because I man of quality. So." The man cracked his knuckles, pulled out a cigarette and lite it, "So the nightmares, they bad?" 

Timothy nodded his head. Gripping the chair.

"How old are you?"

"I'm twelve."

The man crossed his arms. 

"Someone hurt you?"

"No."

"Car accident?"

"No."

"Dad beat you?"

"No."

"Uncle touch you?"

"No."

"What are the nightmares."

"I don't want to say."

"Timothy, What are they."

"Sir-"

"Mr. Benetti, you talk to me with some respect." What are the nightmares." The man took a step forward.

"I don't want to talk about it."

"I don't give a fuck if you want to talk about it. What are the nightmares, Timothy. I need to know."

The man walked over and leaned down looking into Timothy's eyes. Outside the window a sound of a helicopter thudded in the distance. 

"Timothy." The man looked into one eye, and another. Then said through this teeth, "I need you tell me, if I'm going to help you. What are the nightmares."

"I just want her to stop."

"Who's her?"

"I don't know."

"What do you mean you don't know."

"I don't know!"

"You know it's a her!" 

"It's because of her screams!" Timothy crumbled in the chair, crying into his hands, "It's because of her screams."

The man stood up, he turned. He walked passed his desk and to the window. He stared out to the city that was making its way home under sheets of orange light coming from the last light of the sun. 

"Do hear them when you're awake?" The man asked, turned around to see Timothy standing on the chair. 

His eyes closed. And his hands balled into little fist. 

The man crossed his arms. 

"Is she here?"

Timothy whispered yes then looked to the corner of the room. 

"When did you start seeing her while you're awake?"

Timothy said a few weeks. 

The man sniffed. 

"Why don't you get off the chair, and go wait outside. Give me a second to, "The man looked to the corner of the room. Nothing but shadows. 

"Alright go outside. Have a seat in the waiting room. Give me a second to go through what I have. You come back in, and we take care of this little issue. What do you say, champ?"

Timothy nodded his head and gave a half smile. 

The man slowly watched Timothy leave has he slowly inched over to his phone. Picked it up. And dialed it. 


In the lobby the phone rang reverberating it's sharp chimes through the hallway where a boy exited an elevator and took a seat next to a stack of magazines.

"Hello, thank you for calling psychology offices of--"

A voice from the phone cut her off.

"Nicole," The voice said. "I want you to stay looking forward and smiling. I want you to after this phone call to hang up and and say you're going to the bathroom. And I want you to meet me down the street at their shitty coffee joint you like so much. We have a real big problem. You see that little boy, don't nod your head, keep looking forward. That's a Crossover. We need to fix that immediately, little fucking bitch tried to get a the good dreams from me. Alright. Just be quick. I'll see you there."

The phone clicked. 

Nicole kept her smile on her face. Looking forward. Then to the boy who sat smiling staring at Nicole. 

"Hi." The boy said, smiling. "I'm Timothy."

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Los Angeles. I walk every where. White, Black, Asian, Indian, everyone, even homeless smile like this. I never understood why this is being duct taped to white people. It's a half-assed smile.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you assume everyone knows what you know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's insane! You know what else is crazy! People like to make things up for fake Internet points! And sometimes the way they illustrate their stories looks like fiction! It's so crazy!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the "Why?" Unless he has NEVER seen this person before ever in his life, then that makes sense. That seems more natural, but if you see this person a couple times a week for a couple months, you damn well know what's going on.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds fake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can still be all you can be on a couch. Let it hold you during your high and enjoy the day away..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy 4/20! Please for the love of God, Stoners, Brothers, Sisters those who are sleeping and those so high right now they're scared of being awake. Don't make us look stupid today! Let's celebrate this amazing thing and not use it as a reason for the media to make us look stupid. Use your head. Don't get so baked to the point you want to race all the cars that look like Zebras or go scream at the top of your lungs Allahu akbar in a crowded mall just so you and your friends can giggle at all the white people sprinting towards an exit. "Haha! The fat ones just give up and lay on their backs!" So do something safe and fun! Rememeber, you only get ONE April 20th, 2017! Hell, who am I to tell you what to do or what you can yell in public places. Get out there! Be all you can be! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It bothers me. I'm developing a relationship with these guys. And every freaking mission, same gun, same clothes, I'm like "Guys, can we at least color coordinate one time."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much more evidence do we need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rock climbing. Compare that with the tempo, the style, the gameplay, the mood, and especially the NEED OF TERRAIN TO ACCOMMODATE AND SATISFY SUCH A DESIRE. It makes no sense! "He's over by the container--" "Hold on guys, you know what. I need to relax. I know there's cartel, but damn, I'm just really stressed out. And you know what? Some of these mountains could really use a good climbing..." Yes, I'm excited! Chalk up my hands cuz I'm ready for the vacation package DLC that features rock climbing, extreme hiking, and people watching. 10/10 can't wait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knew the say yes rule.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey fucking love this game. I'm protecting it from stupid ideas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh so you're fourteen.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is ridiculous. If you played the game you can walk up pretty much any mountain, so why do you need to "Rock climb" it. AND TONS of the buildings are maybe three floors? Four maybe? Is that what you want to do? Scale down three entire floors?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How in the fuck would that work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Holes In My Father. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 01:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get high before I do stand up. I produce laughs still, so does this count?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 07:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe that way is better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 14:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Alright, Now Let's here for a first timer here tonight--"

"Boooo!" 

"Hey, hey, hey first timers derserve a chance, okay? Alright. Let's give hand to Mr. Jeffery James! Come on Jeffery James!"

Crowd boos, some clap, The host exits off stage and slowly a boney tall man comes up to the mic, staring into the bright lights and speaks with a unreal confidence. 

"Hey folks, Name's Jeffery! Great to be here, man people get on my NERVES. I'll tell ya. Today, this guy, swear to god, was chewing gum so loud, with his mouth open like cattle, does that ever happen to you? Where you wish you had a hammer so you can just smash every fucking tooth out of his head, onto the ground, then curb stomp his skull until it because oatmeal under your shoes, then chase his crying kids and then smash them with the hammer and have sex in the gashes you leave from the blunt force trama? Anyone? Nobody?"

The crowd says nothing, some hang with their jaws open. Jeffery takes this as a bad sign, tries a older joke. 

"Well, speaking of kids. You ever notice how the scream? Always screaming, Doesn't matter where they are playground, backyard, you know where they scream the loudest,  the microwave. Don't you hate it, it takes ten minutes to shove the kid in there, you get the door shut, start jerking trying to concentate staring into the microwave but it's damn near impossible because your listening to this siren scream, "Help! Help! Mommy! Daddy!" - Man o man, don't you hate when this happens? I mean it's a hate or love it..." 

The crowd jaws keep dropping. Jeffery takes this as his first two jokes bombed. Well, third one should totally get them. 

"Okay, well this one time, Funny story, I cut off my own penis and fed it to my mother, don't worry, she was chained to the bed, I mean she wasn't going far I cut off her arms and legs, BUT she was chained. I stood right over her with a kniffe, and then slowly, started to cut my penis off, and man the LOOK ON HER FACE when it came off! Oh my god..you guys had to be there..." 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've rolled cars hundreds of times. You'd think they wouldn't let me drive anymore because sometimes we go through five or six cars in an hour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let the A.I squad dudes drive once in awhile. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kinda bummed that in the game, if I place a way point, I can't climb into the passanger seat and let one of my computer team mates drive there so I can relax and enjoy this lush, amazing landscape. Any idea if they could ever apply this change? I don't mind driving, but like I'm always the one driving. It's just not fair. This game is huge, and I'm playing on NO HUD or fast travel on the high difficult level.  So it be nice to take turns, I mean I do pretty much everything. I kill most of the dudes. I do all the talking. I find the cars. I call in the helicopter. All they have to do is find a shot when I need it. Can we please pass around some of the responsibility? 

(On a serious note I think that would be a cool thing to put into the game. Place a way point, jump into the passanger seat, and let one of your AI squad dudes drive while enjoy this wonderful computer generated world.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably a sign you're watching horrible movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would a person do if they believe in a flat earth but won a trip around the world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's appreciating that fact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I love about this is he KNOWS EXACTLY how he looks coming in there raising his burger in the air, so the surprise is so much more unexpected and satisfying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 04:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 10:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She must have sisters or something. That was experience right there. It was so fucking smooth and by the hair all in one motion. She knows how to fight girls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 11:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That flashcard is a sign how dedicated you are to being alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuuuckk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish it was less forward. 

"**Service me, human.**" 

This is what I don't understand. I come here everyday, every day, there's hundreds of these droids, they keep and manage themselves, right?

"**Service me, human. Give it to me.**"

I just want to buy my damn sandwich and leave. But I go towards the door and this thing comes rolling at me. 

"**Human, Service me, give it to me.**" 

I see how it grabs at me. Trying to touch me in places. All my places. What is it about this robot that wants me. I have to deal with this shit with people, and now technology is trying to put it's dick in me?

"**Human, service me, give it to me. Give it to me.**" 

I had enough, so last week I looked right into his dimming red eyes that said battery low and go, "You should be shut down you stupid, horrible machine! Every day you try to touch my places, you broken toaster with wheels! I hope when you get shut down forever!"

It's been a week since that metal monster try to touch my places. Maybe it finally got the message.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Internet working or is it becoming more and more of a problem for humanity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Internet working? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 03:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would the lawyers know about this channel and them decide to charge what they want to charge because they know Ethan would get funding for it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Godfather of cliches" is a cliche. Close!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he was creative enough be could just work his ideas through fiction so people can empathize more with his point of view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For him it's a start, and it's good to see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 20:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll remember this dude forever. First time I ever went to the comedy store this dude was working the door, super sweet dude, broke down how the store works and the open mic. Literally the first "nice" person I can say I met after two months here in Los Angeles. Now he's on the JRE. Good for him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant,this is a SMART fat joke, fuckin love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the notepad says. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 07:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, take a girl out to McDonald's for spaghetti. Fuckin brilliant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The doomsday clock is like a placebo pill for mankind, the more we believe in it, the more the effects seem real. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Killing time before the next American ushers you two boys into the next room?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course you have knives. How else is your parents going to stab you in the chest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiding your nails, which are probably as trashy as that piss stain on your sleeve, the two o clock shadow, and that cat turd you turned into a crayon and put it where an eyebrow used to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen seat cushions with better features.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 20:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never cried looking in the mirror before but now I can say I've seen somebody who has.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 00:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG it's that scene from The Perfect Storm. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 21:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because how will you get other people invested? Sure, you like plain and simple. But there's millions of people put there were this might actually help and so if it comes with a few bells and whistles, sure. Why not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 11:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those quotations are really generous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 11:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She probably holds dicks that tight too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clit is as fat as your face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 ever * </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did two motorcycles do a burn out on your forehead?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I sell cars because everyday when I look into the mirror I see one."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense, the only attention she seems to want is abuse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 00:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No she's not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 11:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Film yourself trying to do it! Then show us if it's hard or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy a house, tell them the circumstances, show them the twenty thousand I have that day and explain before I go spend it on weed and food for the homeless, that instead of monthly payments, ask if I can come and give them $15,000 a day ($5000 would go to basic spending: Food, travel, hookers, weed and food for the homeless.) Then when the house is payed, move and beg someone else to do the process all over again until I die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 01:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so glad I saw this before its deleted. What a moment of natural hindsight right at the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 10:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the same look every female that comes within two feet of you. You nailed it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 21:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "No, Daddy, no!!!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 03:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 23:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 20:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quit my job and survive on my work alone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 18:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone with a refrigerator  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 01:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited for when you get on Joe Rogan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is like when people warn you to not mess with people you don't know. That dude on the bike is that person. Breaking someone's windows and now they have to pay for it, that's messed up... But then again...maybe don't throw a water bottle at someone you don't know...?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 19:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With orphan elephants they reintroduce to the wild, do they, or is it even possible, to train them when they are faced with a situation such as poachers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 17:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like someone has a grudge and taking them out like tic tac toe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 10:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 19:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does a tsunami have to do with Donald Trump becoming president.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 18:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude he's sharing the experience. If you turned into a gif it would not feel the same. To be sitting at your TV and the looking out your window, then back to your TV, then the window, and maybe a little poo from the "Holy fuck. That's awesome." that escapes your mouth from experiencing such a thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 18:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aha! Debbie downer is here! Yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Alright... Alright... Keep it cool, human doing something with that glowing rectangle again.. Alright... Wait for it... NOW! HAHA HUMAN! YOU CANNOT STOP ME CUDDLING WITH YOU! HA NOW YOU MUST... must.. mu... Zzzzzz.."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you didn't even check. Or take a minute I guess to go "Hmm, I wonder if this came out weeks ago.. Hmm..." but I got cha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 03:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does a name of a channel have to do with how fresh their content is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 14:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Wait, before you put me into your face.. Have you considered eating asparagus?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Hike Through Joshua Tree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 11:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 00:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really happened  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milk Farm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 09:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ten days ago I stepped out of that machine. 

I felt the dirt in my toes. The heat from the sun and cool breeze against my tender skin. Goosebumps form as my chest takes in buckets of air. Sweet, sweet air. My eyes open.

I'm alive. I made it.

But made it where? That's a good question. See, when signed all the paperwork and before I stepped into that machine. I wasn't told where I would end up. It was apart of the agreement.

They said they would aim for the desert. Nobody knows anything about the future. They know the machine works. They can send me a few hundred years from the present. So they decided they would aim for the desert. It's sparse and away from society. I wouldn't cause any unnecessary distress. 

But downtown San Francisco is where I ended. There, naked, standing in front of hundreds of faces that just stared and stared. Like I was a shooting star...

It felt good, for a moment, it did.

It was all women, you see? I like my women ripe or seasoned. But not like this. Females of all ages. All shapes and sizes. Their jaws hung from their hinges and their eyes wide open. Taking all of me in. 

I wish it was me. What they were staring at. It was my treasure chest right in-between my legs, you see.

Currently, I hang with my face down. My arms and legs? Good question.  I woke up like this. Both of them gone. Not just an arm and a leg. Both arms. Both legs. Gone. Just little stumps now. I wish I had a chance to say goodbye. 

But I know why they did this. They took my legs so I wouldn't run away. And my arms to keep my hands from killing myself. 

I'm what you called "milked" daily.

Trust me. I tried. I tried telling them I could do it myself. How it's actually fun. All they had to do was supply pictures of Asian women and their feet and I was locked, loaded, and ready to unleash a tidal wave in any direction they pointed. This, of course, was before they put me under. And when I woke up to my new life.  

This is what happened. 

Apparently men are completely extinct. It's not clear to me why. There's just no men to take their seed and put into some pretty ladies tunnel of wonder and nine months later give birth to walking version of cancer.  

So. Me, having the wonderful balls I have, came to that point in time where balls have gone extinct. Gone. Finished. And my healthy, hearty coconuts we're looked at like rare precious metals.

Most of the days are like this. 

Morning comes and ice cold shower wakes me up. My eyes opened being greeted with the slab of concrete. My tears from the night before still haven't dried. I begin to shiver uncontrollably. They do this on purpose, you see. Man seed flourishes in cold weather.

The first thing I see other than the concrete just a few feet away from me is shoes. Nice, black dress shoes. 

"Morning, David." A voice says from above me. A pen is scribbling on a clipboard. She lowers herself down and wraps a cold hand around my cock. Inspecting it.

"It's good to go," she says. 

There's this canister in her hands. She shakes it like a spray can. I can see the shadow. The bottle with a thick nozzle shaped like a baseball bat.  She then places petroleum jelly down by her feet, taking a scoop of it with her fingers, rubbing it along and around the head of the nozzle. Then with her hand wrapped around my cock she slowly inserts the nozzle into the head of my penis. I can feel the edges drag as she pushes it deeper. I grunt in pain. I squeeze my eyes shut and imagine I'm back home with Martha. Sitting by her side with her hand entangled in mine, watching our daughters play hide and go seek in the front yard. "Watch me, Papa," my little one giggles running from one side of the yard to the other, "Watch me, Papa! Watch me!"

The pain rips me back to reality, and I scream. 

I think the jelly is just a placebo. Because I feel every centimeter, I feel every centimeter dig its way through. Then the lady presses a button. It beeps. This not only cue the nozzle to release, but also more screaming.

The lady pulls out. And she leaves. Coming back only ten minutes later and my dick is so hard I could fuck myself a tunnel through Mount Everest.  

"Good, good," she says, and she pats my ass.

For the next ten hours they will work in shifts. She will tug at my dick like it's a utter. Tugging and tugging. And because of that shit they blasted into my pee-hole. I cum buckets. Literally. 

See, my balls have swollen so much they have a brace so if my balls were to experience any kind of free fall. My sack doesn't rip and I don't die in agony. 

So I cum my first bucket. By the way, this isn't like cumming on a pair of nice tits, or in an eager open mouth. My dick feels like it has it's own mouth. It's own stomach. And when I bust, my balls purge themselves of their contents. My balls cramp, which opens the door for clustering contractions. Fifteen minutes or so the old hag tugs and tugs at me. Like a finger clasped over the head of a hose, I spurt into the metal bucket. 

Then the old bitch slaps me on the ass again. Tells me, "I'll be back in another hour. Don't you go anywhere." The door shuts. And she's gone. 

This time, she comes back with someone who's brand new. Who's training. A trainee.

They want to make sure to maximize my loads, right? Make sure they can take all they can. So there's these experiments. Make sure they maximize their profits. And lucky me, I get to be the first to have them experienced. So now not only do I have this old ladies hand wrapped around my flesh rocket. The girl they got training today is rubbing jelly on what looks like a traffic cone with knobs all around and over. 

The trainee places the head of the traffic cone against my asshole. Before this, they attach a breathing apparatus that attaches itself through a serious of tubes to a canister labeled Alkyl nitrites. The old lady explains to the trainee, "It's like forcing a kid to go to school, there's lost of screaming and resistance, so it helps his body relax. And we heat the tip, here, see? And then it's knife through butter."

I feel the heat and then the trainees body weight, and she presses. Until all that was outside is now in. Then the vibrating starts.  

And I wince, and I cry a bit. It hurts. I can feel it hit my stomach. The old lady and the trainee move in unison. Hold lady tugs at me, while the trainee pistons in and out. Every five minutes or so they stop to take a break. 

"Make sure you use your shoulders, push with your shoulders," The old lady says, pointing to the trainee shoulders, "In a couple of weeks he'll be lose enough we won't even have to use the jelly. But you can still hurt yourself, you know? Safety first."

It starts again. My balls purge themselves into the bucket. The old lady slaps me on the ass and says she'll see me in another hour. 

Then again. And again. And again. 

They even have a taste testing.

I can see the bucket through my watery eyes. My pearl greatness rocks back and forth. A door opens and shoes walk in. They take the bucket and place it a few feet from me. And with small spoons the ladies take small samples like they're dining with fine caviar. 

"Oh, this is delicious," one says. 

"This will bring so many wonderful boys and girls." Says another. 

"Here, try it on a biscuit."

Then they leave. And I wait another hour. And it starts again. 

Not all is bad. Mum always told me to look for the positive in things.

And now I have company.  

A day ago someone came looking for me from the past.

And now he hangs a few feet from me. His sobbing keeps me up at night. But what I go through is like skipping through a field of daisies and candy canes compared to him. 

Is his name Michael? Or Greg? Maybe Davis? I don't remember. I remember his voice. He broke down what my body would feel when I entered the machine. What the trip might be like (even though I don't remember.) He's a nice guy. It hurts to hear him cry like this.  

Every day we wake up together. I can hear him yell: "No! No! What are you doing! Stop it! Stop it! Just tell me what I need to do and I can change this! I can go back to the past and change this! Tell me what men did wrong! Tell me what happened to them! And I can fix this! I can go back and fix this!"

They just laugh. Then, they take a metal pipe and place it over a growing fire. When it glows amber, they take the pipe and places it on the edge of his penis. Which one of the ladies explain to the other, "This is something new, but it should help the process go much faster, you see number one over there?" She points to me, "He takes about fifteen to twenty minutes to milk. And then we need to give his body an hour to recover." She shows the trainee the glowing hot pipe. "This will cauterize his urethra. This will make for a smooth exit. So it pours instead of spurts of them." And then she shoves the metal rod into his penis. They have to cover his mouth so they can speak. 

"See? We do this for a couple days, and then by Friday it will take him only minutes to empty. The less friction, the better." 

Should I feel proud? No, not really. They're not coming in here and milking Arnold Schwarzenegger, you know? It's just some bloke who works at a petrel station and waits tables on the weekend. I signed up for this "experiment" because rent was past due and I needed the money. And now I wish I was suffering under my own roof. Not knowing that millions of my babies will be born from my seed.

This isn't going to go on forever. Maybe a few years? Just enough of me to keep humanity going. After that I don't know what they'll do with me. I just hope it's quick. 

Ten days so far, and it's not getting any better. Millions of my children will be born. And little do they know their father hangs daily being tugged at by an old woman, listening to the sound of my tears hit the concrete.

I'm reminded of a quote as I hang here waiting for the next session.

"Behind every beautiful thing, there's some kind of pain."

Was there something beautiful about my situation? 

I wager death will find me way before I find out. 

Until then, I wait for an answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 11:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like a soccer mom that just hatched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 11:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the brail on your forehead because the only people that would agree to touch you are blind?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 19:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It be funny if it was just dudes finding pictures on the internet just to troll this dude into thinking he's photoshopping real stupid people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 20:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Death by Stephen King. There's something really raw about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 03:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds almost real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Display </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to turn it off. I like the game. Just turn it off and I'll love it. Uncertainty makes the game have more suspense and tension to amplify the unexpected. ( Unless the game crashing was supposed to help with the element of surprise please let me know.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 08:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the transition goes smoother than your complexion. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 08:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her dad was a pig, you can see it in her nose.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 11:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think looking in the mirror can say so much more than anyone here could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 11:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the elephant like a metaphor for what we would see if you had a wide angle lens?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 11:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step 1 - Be a terrible writer and desperate for material

Step 2 - Let strangers roast you and take the best jokes 

Step 3 -... Profit?

Step 4- Jokes bomb, you go home, and stay in bed for the rest of your life because that's the closest you'll ever get to your dreams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 11:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It be nice if your mom got you in frame more
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 11:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With those man hands you could make a few bucks at your local gay glory hole , hell, let them see your face too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parents: "Is it a boy or a girl, doctor?"

Doctor: "Uh.."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 13:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your dick and that controller is the only thing you're going to ever touch with your hand(s)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 09:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting likes on social media can translate into material you can work out on stage if you know the difference between how something sounds when you say it, vs how it comes off to the reader when they read it. And if you've been doing your writing, taking a good idea that so many people liked via social media, shouldn't be that hard to rewrite so it can work as well on stage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 04:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to let things die. Let it go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jaws, Ursula, and the dude who just got his wisdom teeth pulled should get out of radio and maybe go try out at your local zoo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 15:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard that still to this day, doctors don't know if it's a boy or a girl.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 15:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a burn victim I'm happy to see you're making quite the recovery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 15:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to tell your mom to hold the camera a little more steady, the caveman wearing his boyfriends nighty is out of focus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
