<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2574</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [i ate] biscuits and gravy and peach tea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's the summer soon! so it won't be on much

(also there's enough insulation that the plants themselves don't get that warm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha oops  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure!  tbh, I really love the ikea ottoman as a way to prop up my feet, so I'm tempted to just leave it there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not gonna lie, i've been eying the wireless astros for this reason, haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] pot of japanese curry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finished living room! I actually kind of like how cozy it feels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] beef short rib and brisket soup with zucchini noodles and veggies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've only had it for a few days, but it's nice so far! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, it's the sven  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably won't be able to hang the tv, but i like the idea of a plant stand in the corner and a picture between windows  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe a clock on the wall between the windows? it just feels little empty there  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> good point, i might just stick with a plant in the corner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also thinking about getting a bar cart to put between the windows, or maybe a chair/lounge chair  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finished buying furniture for new living room, what should i do about plants and the walls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a new jacket and loving it! Roland Sands Ronin in Waxed Cotton 

https://i.imgur.com/Cn9g8Mv.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This review thread is worthless without actual links to the reviews, OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> imo, anything written by Simon R Green (Nightside, Deathstalker) is very violent without being grimdark  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [i ate] a spicy chicken breakfast biscuit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 06:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think book Avasarala would hate doing it, but would still do it if she convinced herself it was necessary.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/nLdR472.png

Here goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brief summary: 

Most of the loss was in this past year.  Exercise has been pretty standard push/pull/legs routine with a stricter focus on diet.  Nothing that unusual -- just old fashioned hard work and time.  Progress has been slow but steady.  

I had a wedding a couple weeks ago, and realized that the only suit I owned was the one I wore in the before photo, in 2013.  It is (obviously) way too large for me now, so I decided to splurge and a new one that fit me.  

It feels so nice to be able to dress sharp and also look the part.  I used to loathe going to any kind of fancy or formal event, but now I'm finding myself looking forward to going to more.

A couple more photos!

This was in 2011 I think: https://i.imgur.com/5FukFn1.jpg

And this was me trying on the new suit at the store a few weeks ago (they tailored the sleeves to be longer, don't worry): https://imgur.com/a/zu5oa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M/34/6'0 [240lbs  169lbs = 71lbs] (4 years) Suit progress. Most of the weight was in the past 1 year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 05:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 14:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares about appearing "cheap"? It's just business. You're trying to pay the least you can, he's trying to get the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that he realizes you're comfortable tho, he's going to sit on your head instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what were their final interval temps?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so too, but taking the Wii U as an example, there were a number of games that didn't support gamepad only play, and required display to a TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, that's why upgrade is in quotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I figured -- is this worth fixing or do most off the rack suits with some minor tailoring exhibit this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SuitSupply finished their suggested alterations -- thoughts on fit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 06:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Album: https://imgur.com/a/9wEk0


And why not, here's a before/after pic from a few years ago in my old suit:

Old: https://i.imgur.com/5FukFn1.jpg

New: https://i.imgur.com/5PoYfR6.jpg

My thoughts:

They adjusted the sleeve length, and I think it looks better now. The sleeves on the white shirt I'm wearing is a little long, so that might be contributing to it feeling like there's too much cuff. 

There's kind of weird wrinkling in the sleeves. Is it due to a sleeve pitch issue? Or maybe my dress shirt sleeves are too loose and showing through?  The wrinkling felt less pronounced in the store with their sample shirt. 

Overall fit feels nice and comfortable to me, and given I only wear a suit a few times a year for events, I might just live with the quirks. Or maybe it's major enough to warrant taking back for more adjustments. 

Thoughts?

Prior post: https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/5s4vu3/after_losing_weight_got_my_first_suit_in_years/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice! i used Bedo's recently for a jacket alteration and they were lovely to deal with  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why do you want it to be American made?

Maybe he wants to support a business that makes things in the U.S.? I think he's perfectly aware it's not going to be the most bang for buck, but people have diff priorities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually looks like an blue wax cotton version of Beltaff's turner jacket: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=66ZB27pR4c0

Customized with additional zippers over the top pockets, and the belt removed.

Belstaff is known for their slanted top left pocket, which you can see here https://i.reddituploads.com/f53df90a5eaf49109f2b54d04fd6b167?fit=max h=1536 w=1536 s=b36a2061f85f9180de0d3df0d4fd67b0 

You can also see the belt on the jacket in this shot: http://cinemavine.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/john-wick-chapter-2-movie-images-stills-common.jpg

I don't see a wax version of the turnet jacket in their store, but perhaps it was custom made for the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually looks like an blue wax cotton version of Beltaff's turner jacket: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=66ZB27pR4c0

Customized with additional zippers over the top pockets, and the belt removed.

Belstaff is known for their slanted top left pocket, which you can see here https://i.reddituploads.com/f53df90a5eaf49109f2b54d04fd6b167?fit=max h=1536 w=1536 s=b36a2061f85f9180de0d3df0d4fd67b0 

You can also see the belt on the jacket in this shot: http://cinemavine.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/john-wick-chapter-2-movie-images-stills-common.jpg

For something similar, there's also the Belstaff Brooklands jacket in navy blue: http://the-cafe-racer.com/belstaff-mojave-brooklands-wax-jacket-navy-blue#.WKE0FxIrLKI

Tho it's def more cropped than the one Cassian wore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 13:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly true.  Here's a good explainer: http://www.seriouseats.com/2015/07/the-food-lab-complete-guide-to-sous-vide-chicken-breast.html#safe

(and also a good recipe!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 07:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to set strict limits.  Pick the amount of weight you want to gain, and then once you get that point, start cutting.  That way, it never feels like you're out of control </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (photo before i cut the chicken into strips to go into lunch boxes) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sous vide has totally changed my meal prep approach. 8 chicken breasts for 2 unattended hours followed by 10 minutes total searing time for super juicy tumeric chicken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> tumeric chicken breast - 142F for 2.5 hours and then quickly seared </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 06:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 06:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I mentioned in the OP they are lengthening the sleeves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 05:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Witcher novels  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 01:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we stop by the Crow's nest? 

Dummy that's how you get fat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playing countless hours of FFXV changes your fashion sense, and you too will want to be part of Noctis' band of merry leather men </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 23:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing A LOT of Final Fantasy 15 recently and it's possible that I have gone full video game because I actually kind of dig this jacket I grabbed recently:

https://imgur.com/a/fMahI

But also I'm willing to acknowledge 80 hours of the game has addled my brain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For reference, the SuitSupply I was at charged me $28 for the proposed jacket alterations  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I... didn't actually get presented with that option and didn't realize S/R/L versions existed. I'm to make myself a note to ask about it when I go back in to the SuitSupply store to confirm the fitting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 6'0! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good idea!  

Haha, I went into the store wearing jeans and a tshirt + jacket, so the white dress shirt and the shoes are both just ones the store had lying around for folks to use while trying on suits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

It's the typical story: I watched what I ate a lot closer, and tried to exercise regularly.  Eating better was probably 80% of it though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 06:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they lengthen the end.  The guy said 3/4" or so wouldn't throw off the proportions too much, but I guess we'll see! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 05:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read online that they aren't so much wide as normal -- and that skinny lapels are supposedly going out of style.  Anyway, YMMV but I kind of dig the look/contrast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

The pant leg was cuffed to the length they'll hem it to, which is probably why it looks fine.  The shoe was a placeholder shoe they had in the store. I'm probably going to be looking for shoes separately later 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha yes, a camera strap. 

also, they'll lengthen the sleeves  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, i said in the OP they are lengthening it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After losing weight, got my first suit in years from SuitSupply. Thoughts on fit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First: **They said they'll lengthen the sleeves a bit since there's too much cuff (iirc the salesperson said ~3/4 of an inch) and hem the pants.**  Reason being: according to the salesperson, the size 38R suit fit my shoulders and chest better (with sleeves that are too short) vs the 40R that had decent sleeves but a looser fit. 

Also, it's actually a dark navy blue and not black.  The specific model is the Lazio suit

Fit pic: https://imgur.com/a/zu5oa

(For giggles, old suit pic from 10 years ago: https://imgur.com/a/mRPqq )

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I hang jackets/coats by the loop inside the collar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 00:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of my coats and jackets have a small loop inside the collar.  I've seen it called a locker loop in some places. 

Is it safe to hang using this loop? Or will it deform or stretch the item? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:41:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're worried, a bottle of lexol leather cleaner + conditioner is like $10 on Amazon. It's possible the jacket was stored at the warehouse in poor conditions, or that its just been sitting around a lot.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 05:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO Allsaints is overpriced at full MSRP, but if you catch one of their fairly frequent sales, the jackets aren't bad.  Give a sale price of $300-600 depending on the piece, IMO most folks have issues with their designs, which tend to be trendy or busy.

I actually think some of the Allsaints jackets look nice, and if nothing else, they are one of the more accessible brands for a lot of people in terms of physically judging if they're comfortable pulling off a perfecto style jacket. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes when I can't sleep or need to relax, I like to drink whiskey and cook. So now you know why at just past midnight, I have food for a week </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] turkey and tomato stew, roasted chicken breast, blackened brussels sprouts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 19:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody call the scale police </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 23:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice job! Your shoulders and arms are looking really great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] sous vide five spice pork shoulder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't work all day from it, but I like it as a temp morning desk before I head out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morning workspace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 06:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 00:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not widely known, but I have a soft spot for the Ivory series by Doris Egan: https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/884583.The_Gate_of_Ivory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 23:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look for suede or nubuck jackets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 08:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually like heavy bass in my workout phones, haha.  When I'm grunting and breathing hard and sweating, sound clarity and balance is the last thing on my mind and I just want a strong heavy beat to psych me up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's... not interactive.  You are literally passing fzf a list of every single line of text in every single file :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fzf actually can't do it.  fzf doesn't not reinitiate the search based on terms -- it can only filter a list of items.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, the interactive mode is something I've always wished fzf had.  This looks awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used Kenji's seriouseats sous vide chicken salad recipe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I followed Kenji's chicken salad recipe for the most part, tho I added more celery since I like the crunch. 

and yeah, i dumped the sous vide bags straight into an ice bath  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, just that I was out of the house for that long. One thing I tend to like about sous vide is the relatively large window it gives me to do other things without worrying about having to take it out at a precise time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cause i was out running errands for 2 hours haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chicken salad! Breasts at 150 for 2 hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short week for me, so 3 containers of chicken salad and, uh, salad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 05:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] meat and greens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 00:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 18:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an old shell cordovan wallet I've been using for a couple years that I love: 

https://imgur.com/a/qJ9Jn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far into it are you? I'm in season 5 right now and  IMO it's about as bad as the usual now in terms of breaking the law to catch the bad guy :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] i think i made my cheeseburgers too large </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 14:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO flank steak is normally thin enough that I go directly to the searing stage. Giving it a good sear cooks the insides to basically what I want  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beef brisket and tendon soup with a soft boiled egg [OC] [604x604] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 19:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might like this then: http://imgur.com/lFfeBNA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 17:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the texture! More firm than shreddable, but that was the intent. 

I loosely followed https://www.chefsteps.com/activities/char-siu-tender-cantonese-style-barbecued-pork </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] beef brisket and tendon soup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five spice pork shoulder (145 for 10 hours) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 06:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Nobuo Uematsu Composed FF7's "One-Winged Angel" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 17:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoa, i don't have shures but I have a JVC fx850 that uses shure style connectors. this should work with those, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you moving from? Chances are your current clothing will be perfectly fine, assuming you have stuff for California's weather. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 16:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> comfortable underwear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 15:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't know if you can pull of a leather jacket, or you just want to dip your toes into that style of jacket, IMO faux leather is perfectly fine and maybe even preferable.

Once you know a little more about what kind of leathers work for your normal wear and what doesn't, then it makes sense to buy something more expensive  and permanent.

Faux leather isn't going to like shred the moment you wear it either.  It'll last plenty long enough for you to get a feel for the style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 19:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New year, new (used) Belstaff leather bomber

https://imgur.com/a/5h2Np </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] pig trotters in pork bone stock and yam noodles with a soft boiled egg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's the rowley in medium  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 08:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I echo the buy on sale comment.  For example, they just had a 20% store wide sale  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Saints had a sale on this jacket and also an additional 20% off, which meant the total was around $331, which I think is not bad for a brand that's normally a little overpriced: 

https://imgur.com/a/Oj8p2

Taking it out for a spin for the first time today with just a basic long sleeve shirt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 19:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick repost from yesterday:

Belstaff has a sale right now on their Maxford jacket:

https://www.belstaff.com/sale/mens-sale/jackets/maxford-blouson-jacket-pale-military/71020401L81B0225-PaleMilitary.html

It's normally $1600 but marked down to $700.

Assuming fit is good, worth or not worth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 01:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Belstaff has a sale right now on their Maxford jacket:

https://www.belstaff.com/sale/mens-sale/jackets/maxford-blouson-jacket-pale-military/71020401L81B0225-PaleMilitary.html

It's normally $1600 but marked down to $700. Now, 700 is still well within Schott, etc territory. But I've found Belstaff's jackets to fit me much better. 

So with all that said, how do y'all feel about it for $700?  Obv not cheap, but doesn't feel ridiculously overpriced like it is for $1600.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it was around ~300  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 20:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW, I have the K7XX and at normal listening levels, unless the office is completely silent, the sound leakage isn't too bad when mingled into background conversation, typing, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grabbed this Belstaff leather bomber off ebay: 

https://imgur.com/a/EZs1x

Belstaff is not great at keeping old models on their website -- or at least I couldn't find any info about this bomber. 

I think it's the "Let Leather Bomber". Anyone happen to know the year it was made?

If it helps date, the tag still says Made In Italy and "Belstaff Gold Label".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 19:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grabbed this Belstaff leather bomber off ebay recently:

https://imgur.com/a/EZs1x

I like the fit, tho not 100% about the length yet. But overall I'm pretty happy with the jacket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wearing Under Armor boxer jocks for ~2 years now, and they've been amazing:

https://www.amazon.com/dp/B019Z2WPT2

Comfy and durable.  After buying 2, I ended up getting 12 more in assorted colors, and have been rotating through them every wash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I've found my go to keto friendly snack for when I want to nibble on something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 07:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 21:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just a thin sweater over a t shirt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 21:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i got it one up (40r) but mostly because the 38r was too small  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think so! i like the bottom two  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 19:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grabbed this camel coat yesterday:

https://imgur.com/a/pcsq6

Thoughts? Color is a little darker than some others I've seen, but I think I like it. 

How do the shoulders look? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 18:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grabbed this camel coat yesterday:

https://imgur.com/a/pcsq6

Thoughts? Color is a little darker than some others I've seen, but I think I like it. 

How do the shoulders look? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 21:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was trying this leather jacket on at All Saints: 

https://imgur.com/a/2OGM4

Thoughts? It is a small. The medium fits but is a little lose in the sleeves.  I like the small sleeves, but armpits are ever so slightly tight.  

 But I've read that leather will stretch, so maybe that's okay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 20:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying out this camel coat from JCrew:

https://imgur.com/a/Bjq2q

This is a 38R. I really love the color but the shoulders are a little tight. But the 40R feels too loose. Thoughts? I don't suppose cashmere/wool stretches at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 23:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Just a small nitpick but you'll be looking at that text A LOT.

That's exactly why I'm happy it's a normal font. I find many of the stylized fonts hard to read for extended periods of time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, it's a pretty dark green, the lighting didn't help  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 21:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This jacket was on sale at Nordstrom for half off:

https://imgur.com/a/fwDCm

Olive green g star raw denim jacket  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 23:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never owned or tried white pants before. 

Thoughts? Is the black sweater + white pants too much of a contrast?

https://imgur.com/a/jLkO7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a brooks brothers small i found at nordstrom rack  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dress shirt fit/style check (normally wear size medium, trying out small) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I normally wear medium dress shirts, but they've started to feel a bit big in the shoulders and chest. I grabbed a couple size small dress shirts + a new pair of pants last week.

Thoughts about the fit/style of the shirts or the pants?

Shirts feel like they fit fine, but are a bit tight when I raise my arms above my shoulders. Is that normal?

Fabric around buttons on chest don't stretch when I'm standing normally, but do start tightening slightly if I push my chest out.

http://imgur.com/a/oYX9k

(For reference, I'm 6'0, 175) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I normally wear medium dress shirts, but they've started to feel a bit big in the shoulders and chest.  I grabbed a couple size small dress shirts + a new pair of pants last week.

Thoughts? Shirts feel okay, but do feel tight when I raise my arms above my shoulders.

(For reference, I'm 6'0, 175)

http://imgur.com/a/oYX9k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 08:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only advice is that you need to take another photo with better lighting. Right now you're not much more than a silhouette.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 05:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh hey, I watch Reforged too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The clothing looks fine to my eye -- but the gold watch pushes it to douchebag level.  Avoid matching those accessories, maybe tone it down with the jackets/polos, and it's just your standard shirt + chino combo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO, the shoulder looks too big and the sleeves look a little long.  Combined with the longer length, it does make you look short to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 04:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to your team first. This is your biggest client. You want your team to succeed.  Maybe the guy arranging the trip has met the client in the past and working from that base.  Maybe not.

But, especially since you're new, I'd avoid potentially upstaging the rest of your team in front of an important client. No one wins in that scenario. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 07:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! IIRC it was a pixel art poster of something, I forget what, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 07:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asian genes means I will immediately look incredibly old the minute I hit 40 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 07:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing too out of the ordinary! Mostly keeping to a calorie deficit. Cooking for myself has helped a lot, as it's much easier to control what's actually going into the food.

Exercise wise, I'm doing a P/P/L routine with a rest day in between each 3-day stretch.  I'm probably going to crank it up a notch soon, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 07:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any protagonist from any book written by Simon R Green. If you want strict hero, maybe check out his Secret History books 

(The Nightside novels are my fave tho) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M/33/6'0 [240  170 = 70lbs] (~1.5 years) I found a jawline! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO Simon R Green's Deathstalker books are some of the most fun examples of the kind of thing you might be looking for  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leather jacket fit check </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 06:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted a while back with a jacket I grabbed to see if I could work the overall look: https://www.reddit.com/r/malefashionadvice/comments/516qna/first_time_trying_out_a_leather_jacket_style/

(Old album: http://imgur.com/a/Tjur4)

Since then, I've worn the jacket pretty consistently, and think it looks great. But it's still faux leather, and I figure it won't last.  It's also not very warm and kinda thin.  To that end, I've been looking around for a real leather jacket that I can wear longer term.

I happened to be in Nordstrom Rack the other day, and found this piece for ~$500, from an original price of $950 (it's Coach, which I know is considered overpriced, but I figured it might not be bad for $500).  

But that's still a buncha dollars so I wanted to get opinions on the fit:

New jacket album: http://imgur.com/a/5dLqR

I have 90 days to return it, so I've got plenty of time to mull over the purchase!

My thoughts: I like the fit through the shoulders, but feel like it might be a little short and the sleeves a little loose. 

I'm also still waffling between a straight black color, and trying to look for a lighter brown.  I like the dark brown! But think maybe black would be usable with more stuff.

Also, if anyone also has suggestions for real life stores to check out, that'd be great (specifically, I'm in the DC/MD/VA area).  I'm wary of just ordering jackets online (at least for my first!) without trying them, especially given how much they cost.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 18:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I have paid federal income tax every year since 1944, when I was 13. (Though, being a slow starter, I owed only $7 in tax that year.) I have copies of all 72 of my returns and none uses a carryforward."

and

 Buffett said he made $2.86 billion in charitable contributions for the year and did not take more than $2.85 billion of it as deductions.

Two things:

1. This is an incredibly epic micdrop on Buffett's part

2. Buffet donated TWO BILLION to charities in one year alone.  While Trump claimed nearly a billion in losses and took advantage, Buffett donated over double that amount to charities </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. regulators accuse Palantir of bias against Asians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 23:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean yes, this is why we have made Race a protected class, and why we have Equal Housing laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 06:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump also conveniently forgot his own practices of purposefully not renting to blacks.  Yup, never been worse off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 06:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was giving The Donald the benefit of the doubt that even he can't be that dumb.  But maybe that was stretching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 03:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We're going to rebuild our inner cities because our African-American communities are absolutely in the worst shape that they've ever been in before. Ever, ever, ever

Oh, it could be worse.  They could be refused apartment rentals because they were black by white racists whose names rhyme with Dump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 23:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the shirt has a bit of a tail in the front and back -- i've read that shirts like that shouldn't be untucked, but maybe as long as it's not like super long, it's fine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 23:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> none that i've noticed, though there's still a bit of fat remaining in the torso so we'll see! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 21:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost a bunch of weight recently, and have been meaning to pick up new shirts and jeans. Grabbed this shirt and jean yesterday: 

https://imgur.com/a/fOjr0

I used to wear L shirts and 36/30 jeans.  The new pair is a M slim shirt and 31/30 jeans. 

I'm not sure if the jeans are *too* tight though, and i'm being overambitious in my downsizing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 05:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 00:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually what I ran into as well with Ivy. Functionally, I was happy, but I run emacs full screen on an ultrawide 34" and not being to have it constrained to a single window was a deal breaker on that screen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
