<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject250</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 1 1/4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a rare man myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing the same thing now that my finals are over. 

Gig Em  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your tips on cooking the perfect steak? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before we start going down the *sous-vide* rabbit hole, I do not have access to anything of that sort.  I do have: one porterhouse steak, and a skillet that I plan on getting very hot. I don't cook steak often, I usually let some place that knows what they're doing cook my beef, but I'm curious as to what y'all recommend! 
Any tips regarding anything from basic cooking method to resting times will be appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, are we not doing phrasing anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a GT?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max price for shrimp where I'm at, 100 miles from the gulf coast, is never more than $15 lb for cooked shrimp seafood markets just like this. Raw, I get fresh, never frozen, gulf shrimp for $5-$10 per lb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I make-a the naked a pasta*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, my friend. On spring break I once accidentally smoked ONE bowl of weed with some friends that had accidentally gotten mixed with weed. 
We assumed it was sand, since we were on the beach for break, little did we know that it a bag of coke in our safe managed to spill onto a loose nug or two.
Desperate as we were to smoke what little weed was left, we hit the "sandy weed" and the smoke was different. Immediately started feeling euphoric and not coked out, more spacey and an experienced something completely unique. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not inclined to believe a high schooler who still calls weed "kush." Sorry kid, cocaine is way too pricy for some dealer to be just giving it to his clients without telling them or charging them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than waking up to vomit-covered pillows and sheets.  Which I definitely haven't done ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way to tell without a pic of the product.

The likelihood of someone taking the time to lace their product to make it "stronger" in any way without up-charging is extremely low.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Redbone Coonhound that I rescued, and his personality / needs sounds like they align with yours perfectly. Hounds are easy going, and loyal as can be. They don't require absurd amounts of exercise, but enjoy the outdoors and are happy to accompany you on a jog or trail hike. I would suggest considering that since you sound like you want a low maintenance dog that is easy to train, a GSD might not be as good of a fit as a hound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
