<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1922</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> German soldier held over anti-migrant 'assassination plot' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [r/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/6826et/go_back_to_your_country_egyptian_student_killed/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [r/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/67v3zi/a_german_solider_who_falsely_registered_as_a/)

[r/worldnews](https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews/comments/67usuq/german_lieutenant_arrested_for_alleged_xenophobic/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [r/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/66yiy0/mysterious_death_of_new_york_judge_was_initially/?st=j1tyuxuz sh=7e682d23) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious death of New York judge was initially called a suicide. Now, police think it's suspicious </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were suggesting that this could a false flag by a Muslim, that's why i responded.
There have already been a total of [33 incidents](http://edition.cnn.com/2017/03/20/us/mosques-targeted-2017-trnd/index.html) counted this year, where mosques were targets of threats, vandalism or arson. 4 Mosques burned in 2017:

January 7, the Islamic Center of Lake Travis, in Austin, Texas

January 14, the Islamic Center of Eastside, in Bellevue, Washington

January 27,  Islamic Center of Victoria, in Texas.

February 24, Daarus Salaam Mosque, near Tampa, Florida.

3 of the 4 incidents have already been confirmed as arson attacks, 1 of them is still being investigated. [This man was sentenced this year for setting a fire before](http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/florida-man-sets-mosque-on-fire-lectures-muslims-at-his-sentencing/article/2614078) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They caught the guy. http://www.cnn.com/2017/03/27/us/colorado-mosque-vandalism/

Not everything is a false flag. False flags are rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ibn Ali Miller, being a part of his community </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was recorded on a surveillance camera. They already have evidence for it. What they are waiting for is to confirm the motive behind the attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that's a total of [33 incidents](http://edition.cnn.com/2017/03/20/us/mosques-targeted-2017-trnd/index.html) counted this year, where mosques were targets of threats, vandalism or arson. 4 Mosques burned in 2017:

January 7, the Islamic Center of Lake Travis, in Austin, Texas

January 14, the Islamic Center of Eastside, in Bellevue, Washington

January 27,  Islamic Center of Victoria, in Texas.

February 24, Daarus Salaam Mosque, near Tampa, Florida.

3 of the 4 incidents have already been confirmed as arson attacks, 1 of them is still being investigated. [This man was sentenced this year for setting a fire before](http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/florida-man-sets-mosque-on-fire-lectures-muslims-at-his-sentencing/article/2614078) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have a lot of strange beliefs. For example, near the end of his life Mirza Ghulam Ahmad claimed that there might be more messiahs coming after him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 22:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [r/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/5xid8j/sikh_man_in_kent_south_of_seattle_says_he_was/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 Mosques burned in 2017:

January 7, the Islamic Center of Lake Travis, in Austin, Texas

January 14, the Islamic Center of Eastside, in Bellevue, Washington

January 27,  Islamic Center of Victoria, in Texas.

February 24, Daarus Salaam Mosque, near Tampa, Florida.

3 of the 4 incidents have already been confirmed as arson attacks, 1 of them is still being investigated.

[This man was sentenced this year for setting a fire before](http://www.washingtonexaminer.com/florida-man-sets-mosque-on-fire-lectures-muslims-at-his-sentencing/article/2614078) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 04:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secret Muslim confirmed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly there are many people who think like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can there really be such a thing as a "Muslim bakery"? The video was spread around online like it was some religiously-oriented bakeries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You just proved his point by your comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 00:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mosques need to invest in security cameras before it's too late. This is the 3rd arson attack i've heard of this year in USA.

[/r/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/5vybqh/tampa_mosque_fire_was_arson_mayor_confirms/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [r/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/5vs663/suspect_in_olathe_shooting_allegedly_told/)

[/r/EnoughTrumpSpam](https://www.reddit.com/r/EnoughTrumpSpam/comments/5vt5py/economically_anxious_old_white_male_executes_two/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tennessee Man who went on right-wing online forums and plotted NY mosque attack wont face terror charges due to loophole which targets foreign terrorism. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you end up in all those countries? Can you name some of the  impoverished countries that you found no issues with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 17:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of those countries have Muslims as well. How did you end up in all those countries? Can you name specific impoverished countries that you found no issues with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 06:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but I've been in impoverished countries with no Muslims and I haven't had the same issues.

What countries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize, good call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taqiyya: "taqiyya according to Shia doctrine,  is permissible in situations where there is overwhelming danger of loss of life or property and where no danger to religion would occur thereby". -Wikipedia

Taqiyya was used during the time of persecution where you were killed if you followed a religion that was not allowed in the land. This does not apply here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 03:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to hear that. I can't defend the actions of every Muslim community. Islam doesn't tell us to harm or take advantage of people just because they aren't Muslim. Muslims have a higher percentage of violent extremists today, but that has more to do with the political    social context the Muslims are in today. There is also a strong correlation with poverty and certain crimes. Even looking back 25 years ago, it wasn't this bad in several Muslim countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 01:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worshiping other than the Creator (idolatry) is considered one of the worst things a person can do in Islam. Idolatry is also considered the greatest sin in Judaism.  This doesn't mean you have to hate people of other religions. In fact, the speaker gave [a recent talk in a Church with Dr. James White](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=updtj99Fp80), where he discusses subjects such as monotheism and jihad more in-depth (better than a out of context audio clip). He has openly talked about Islam with people of other faiths many times. Muslims like Yasir Qadhi get along quite well with Christians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes. But men and women will pray separately, often in separate rooms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a Shia cleric. If i remember correctly, the Orlando attacker was Sunni and had some communication with Isis before the attack. I'm pretty sure the attacker wasn't attending a Shia mosque.  Also, the Shia cleric was mentioning capital punishment that was applied historically in certain Muslim lands for the sin of sodomy. I have yet to find a single Muslim group in America that is openly enforcing capital punishment or demanding capital punishment to be done to gay Americans.

 That's simply not true, from what we know of Orlando and San Bernardino.

It's inconclusive whether anyone from the San Bernardino shooter's family knew beforehand of the attack. The wife of Orlando shooter knew he was going to do something a few hours before. Check the Boston bombers or several other attackers. It's rare for the family to know about it, if anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 22:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  In his sermon/lecture in the YouTube audio below, Qadhi begins by calling Christians shirk for being polythesists who believe in the Triune God (three persons in one God), instead of Islams monotheist god Allah.

Muslims believe in strict monotheism. Worshiping other deities is not allowed in Islam.  Obviously that would mean Muslims therefore believe other religions that encourage polytheism to be wrong. I'm not sure why you think this is so surprising. Muslims don't worship other than the Abrahamic God; what Muslims however reject is the concept of Trinity. Can Muslims still live with Christians and other religious groups in peace? Absolutely yes.

 Qadhi declares that the prophet Mohammad  and by extension all Muslims  has been commanded to do jihad.

Yasir Qadhi clarified and said "*This audio clip is a shoddy cut-and-paste job from a lengthy theological series (around 15 hours of audio) I gave many years ago, discussing the reality of the Islamic concept of shirk (associating partners with Allh). The series had absolutely nothing to do with politics or jihad. Rather, some theological statements from that lecture have been taped together and made to look political. The audio recording as it stands is a complete distortion. Someone literally took sentences from different parts of that series and constructed a very menacing sounding paragraph in my voice. As such, that paragraph in the audio clip is a complete fabrication.[ ] I am a Muslim theologian and teach (and preach) the theology of Islam, but I have never called for violence against any group or religion*".   

It's important to watch the full speech, not a segment of few seconds.  [Here's a uncut lecture  of Yasir Qadhi explicitly condemning terrorism.](https://youtu.be/3y8i3hVtUYw?t=1m55s) He also explains some factors that lead to such groups and how to combat against them.

[Another lecture, talks about his beliefs regarding Jihad, monotheism, etc INSIDE A CHURCH](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=updtj99Fp80).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 20:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  https://www.google.ca/amp/www.breitbart.com/big-government/2015/07/19/the-mosques-behind-jihad-attacks-in-america/amp/?client=safari

A terrorist used to visit a mosque before he committed a violent act, and that's the proof that the mosque supported his action? [This](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=60CkEmXSYXw) is one of the "evil" Imams in Boston your article linked to. Pamela Geller of Breitbart is a known Islamophobe, the type of person who would make claims in 2008 like Obama making a pact with Muslims to institute sharia in America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Muslim here. I've been to several mosques, attended various Islamic programs here in America.  Mosques in America don't radicalize young people, the few individuals who do end up becoming terrorists are often loners, young ~20 year old men who are sometimes influenced by online foreign recruiters if anything. Even their own families don't know about their extremist views until it's too late.  The thought that some mosques are secretly plotting, grooming or even sympathizing with terrorists just doesn't happen, at least not in this country.

[YouTube Channel of the Muslim group that rejected the grant.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SwDim_lJLHg) They aren't as extreme as you might think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 17:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should keep posting this in any news subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Summary:

 Local business owner, Mike Hager flies to Iraq to bring his mother back home to the US for medical treatment. But under President Trump's ban on immigration, he was forced to leave his family behind.  Hager said he didn't expect it to be a problem for the family to travel since they all had green cards and had lived in the United States for 20 years.  

 "I was just shocked. I had to put my mom back on the wheelchair and take her back and call the ambulance and she was very very upset. She knew right there if we send her back to the hospital she's going to pass away - she's not going to make it," Hager said.

[Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r2ErY92A_ng) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Aboubaker Thabti (44):**
Born in Tunisia, Mr Thabti is reported to have moved to Quebec a decade ago and worked in a pharmacy. He was married with two young children, his brother said "He's so kind; everyone loves him - everyone."

**Azzedine Soufiane (57) :**
Born in Morocco and settled in Quebec three decades ago. He ran a grocery store in the suburb of Sainte-Foy. Mr Soufiane had helped many newcomers in Quebec City. "When I arrived here eight years ago, [his shop] was the first place I learned about and pretty much all of Quebec's Muslims did their groceries there," Mr Elabed told Canadian media.


**Khaled Belkacemi (60)**: 
Mr Belkacemi studied chemical engineering in his native Algeria before moving to Canada in the 1980s. He taught food at Quebec's Laval University and was married to a fellow professor there. 
He is described as "an extraordinary person" who was "always smiling" and "an outstanding teacher who loved his graduate students". He has 3 children.

**Abdelkrim Hassane (41):**
Studied information technology in Algeria before emigrating. A colleague said Mr Hassane had lived in Paris and Montreal before settling in Quebec City.
Mr Hassane worked in IT for the Quebec government. The colleague, Abderrezak Redouane, said he was "a very peaceful, sensitive man". He had three children.

**Brothers Mamadou Tanou Barry (42) and Ibrahima Barry (39):**  Both were born in Guinea in West Africa. They are described as IT workers. Mamadou Tanou was a father of two and was reportedly sending money home to Guinea. "Tanou lost his father three years ago, so it became his responsibility to support not only his family here but also his family in Africa. Now that's all been cut," a family friend told the Globe and Mail. Ibrahima worked for the province's health-insurance agency and had four children.

[source](http://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-38807775) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victims Of The Quebec Attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 14:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Told you so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 00:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't subscribe to r/The_Donald, majority of redditors were being fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do we have to hide in mosques? The only problem i see  is when they try to encourage or provoke Muslims to attack in order to trap them. But i don't see this happening here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we should work together with law enforcement. Now more than ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't anything new.  US has been responsible for the deaths of many civilians before, including when Obama was president.  It's now time to criticize Trump and help put an end to terrorism. Non-Muslims need to know that this is happening and this is what leads to further conflicts.

[/politics](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5r11he/donald_trumps_first_us_military_raid_kills_30/)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump's first US military raid kills several civilians, including 10 women and children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [/politics: Donald Trump's first US military raid 'kills 30 civilians, including 10 women and children](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5r11he/donald_trumps_first_us_military_raid_kills_30/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give him attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 04:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mt5l1_Xj2Jo

It would have been nice if that showed typical average Muslims. Instead it seemed to select Muslims who could make the show more controversial and atypical. Several progressive Muslims, a super strict literal Salafi type and a couple others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 03:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that Muslims do Not do that. Sure, there will always be a handful of cases, but the idea that Muslims collectively are oppressing their daughters, forcing them into slaveery is just not true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 23:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about the transgender issue, but everyone can convert to Islam and become Muslim. You can ask and seek counsel from an Imam on what to do for such issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 22:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [There is already one in Michigan,](http://www.halaltacosgardencity.com/) and a few other places like it. But maybe with more demand and increased popularity, we can get several Halal Taco stands coming soon to America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Professional Boxer, Anthony Joshua visits Mosque. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslims Are the VICTIMS of Between 82 and 97% of Terrorism-Related Fatalities: US Government | Global Research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BOOK: Who Speaks For Islam?: What a Billion Muslims Really Think </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coming Soon to America... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 04:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here is the article](https://www.victoriaadvocate.com/news/2017/jan/28/breaking-fire-consumes-victoria-islamic-center/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [/politics](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5qof3z/hours_after_trump_signs_muslim_ban_texas_mosque/)

[/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/5qo3km/texas_mosque_burned/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article doesn't say it was because of bigotry. The people are being fair and waiting for evidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 21:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mosques really need to invest in security cameras. We also should keep track of the number of mosques attacked and report it. Don't respond emotionally or start speculating, but do something useful about it.

[/politics](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5qof3z/hours_after_trump_signs_muslim_ban_texas_mosque/)

[/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/5qo3km/texas_mosque_burned/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's quite ironic considering what Trump just did a few hours ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 14:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/5qf4lk/man_kicked_jfk_airport_worker_wearing_hijab/)

[/politics](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5qgpyl/trump_fan_charged_with_hate_crimes_over_jfk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISIS was on the verge of defeat; Al-Qaeda stopped attacking the West. Trump's rhetoric and his policies help these groups gain recruits.  

And you can't nuke your enemies in modern warfare, it doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 03:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly enough, the original design for the Statue of Liberty was based off a Arab woman. http://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/statue-liberty-was-originally-muslim-woman-180957377/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 02:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Discussion in r/politics](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5pzr7r/donald_trump_to_sign_orders_restricting_refugee/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 23:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sadly a common feeling among converts. [Discussion about it](https://youtu.be/kHJ9nlQV-QQ?t=42m10s). How many converts do you know in person, and do you get along with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Is making fun of toddlers immoral?](https://i.redd.it/6rtylcf2ohby.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Would bad people make fun of toddlers?](https://i.redd.it/6rtylcf2ohby.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 05:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Now they are using children](https://www.reddit.com/r/The_Donald/comments/5pm11w/what_my_husband_and_i_do_in_bed_is_our_business/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 19 Dead Over 48 Hours as Tornadoes Wreak Havoc in the South </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 05:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 04:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the purpose of that sub? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who else could he have elected that supported LGBT rights? Also, lgbt issues aren't that important in comparison to other issues, so why elect someone for their position on LGBT alone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 02:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has spoken favorably of LGBT community several times now. How much do you want to bet that he won't make gay marriage illegal? At most, there is a slight chance he might let the states decide on gay marriage.  It's not like he is going to go out of his way to make it acceptable to bully or treat gay people unfairly. Sure, some people around him might be against gay marriage, but he is not against it. Some among the LGBT community WANT to feel like they are discriminated against and they can't handle the fact that Trump has repeatedly been liberal on these issues. Remind Me! 4 years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calm down, it's just a website redesign since we have a new president.  A few other pages were down too.  

And i don't get why people are afraid about this, among Republicans, Trump is one of the most liberal candidates when it comes to LGBT issues  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 20:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many signatures have we already gotten? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/5nz8m1/man_arrested_after_overnight_fire_at_bellevue/

[It may have been a mentally disturbed person](http://kuow.org/post/mosque-burns-bellevue-police-book-suspect) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Troopers is terrible though.  There's not much you can do to me meow, can you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why did they attack Hillary for the same reason? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 16:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't he answer the question on privacy in his ama? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sugar is now replaced by the cheaper high fructose corn syrup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple threads of the same story are often banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 20:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Censorship is the issue. This sub shuts down every post where the attacker isn't a white racist. 

Are you kidding? Look at every other post in this sub.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  We seem to treat everything else the same way.  If a skinny bulimic girl thinks she is fat, we wouldn't entertain her delusion and assume she is fat. If a person thinks they are really a cat in a human body, we still treat them as human.  But for transgendered people we seem to make an exception.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Less than 1% of Muslim world belong to extremist groups. Extremism in the Muslim world has been common in the last 10 years, but before this period it was not common. Muslim countries were rarely in the top 10 before year 2000.  [Source](https://www.start.umd.edu/gtd/globe/index.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 04:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a whole different issue. 100% of Muslims think alcohol and pork is bad, but that doesn't mean Muslims can't get along with people who consume those things. Adultery is another thing that Muslims are against, but is commonplace today in UK and other Western countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 04:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except it's completely inaccurate. That comment is basically a  r/AsABlackMan comment. Why would Muslims not acknowledge the problem when Muslims are by far the most common victims of terrorist attacks? Muslim communities consistently acknowledge and condemn terrorist attacks and extremist groups: 

http://kurzman.unc.edu/islamic-statements-against-terrorism/

http://www.globalresearch.ca/muslims-are-the-victims-of-between-82-and-97-of-terrorism-related-fatalities-us-government/5516565

[Hundreds of Calgary Muslims protest ISIS violence in Iraq](http://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/calgary/hundreds-of-calgary-muslims-protest-isis-violence-in-iraq-1.2683589)

[Hundreds of Muslims Join Pro-Christian, Anti-ISIS Rally in Baghdad](http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Peace/2014/07/22/Hundreds-of-Muslims-Join-Pro-Christian-Anti-ISIS-Rally-in-Baghdad)

[300 protest against ISIS in Auckland](http://www.nzherald.co.nz/nz/news/article.cfm?c_id=1 objectid=11313327)


[Global Protests Against ISIS Attack on Christians](http://rudaw.net/english/world/020820141) 

Protests are happening left and right. Muslims actively acknowledge the problem. They just aren't being heard.

TL:DR: [The demand that more Muslims must condemn ISIS is ridiculous](http://liberalconspiracy.org/2014/08/21/the-demand-that-more-muslims-must-condemn-isis-is-racist-and-rubbish/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 21:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you think posting this video is helping anyone? Even if you find the article, you should think about if it could benefit people for seeing the article before deciding to post it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is being spread around Facebook right now, but no context is given. We don't know if she was attacked because of wearing a hijab or because she's Muslim, and there is nothing in the video that would suggest that she was attacked for that reason anyway. If we have proof that she was attacked for her beliefs and we have this video, then we can show people about this Islamophobic incident and maybe do something positive about it. Otherwise i don't see what's the point of spreading this video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 20:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mosques need to invest in cameras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Then people start demanding video showing proof this happens if we take it down.

Video proof of what? This video just shows a man attacking a woman. We aren't told the context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 16:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consciousness isn't something physical like the rest of your body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 05:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I agree with op, but you have no idea what happens after death either.  You have yet to experience it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 02:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't experiencing gender dysphoria. He was born a biological male; the operations performed on him afterward were simply not enough to change his biological sex.  This study along with others  shows that gender identity is almost entirely based on nature and is almost exclusively predetermined before the birth of the baby.   This proves my point on why we should keep gender to refer to biological sex.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 23:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't judge him, the guy is just reviewing the experience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it probably didn't happen. 3 weeks detention for getting kneed in the face, yeah ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The case of  David Reimer if anything is in favor of my argument. He was a biological male who was referred to as a girl/woman, raised in a society which refers to biological males as men/boys. They didn't simply get his gender wrong, they got his biological sex wrong.  This is another reason why we should keep gender to refer to biological sex and not assume gender identity to be learned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 20:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you denying that people experience species dysphoria?  There are many other psychological phenomenon i could have brought up. And i've come across the studies about brain structure of transgendered people before. If i remember correctly, it was basically some brain similarities among transgendered people which was very flimsy evidence anyway. And this isn't hard science, since psychological phenomenon can't objectively be measured. This is why we will never have an   objective way to determine gender based on measuring brain structure.  But you bring up another interesting point. When transgendered people refer to themselves as a gender different to their biological sex, and more to how they feel or more closer to the gender role they associate in society (as another commenter also pointed out) then they are just reinforcing gender stereotypes.  Are transgendered people in favor of reinforcing stereotypes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 18:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Gender identity is why a transgender person is a transgender person. They identify with a gender that is different from the one they were assigned at birth. Regardless of how they were raised, regardless of how they might individually perform or not-perform their gender or how they might conform or not-conform to either socially constructed gender role, they still identify with a specific gender.

By doing this, aren't transgendered people then just helping maintain gender stereotypes? And i still don't see your point is. What's the big deal if people are misgendered then? Perhaps you can give me another example, because i still don't get the significance of what you're saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 17:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is only hard-science behind biological sex, which is why we use it to designate living things as male and female. There can be no hard measurable science behind social constructs, such as gender (using the definition of gender defined above).  Gender dysphoria is one of many psychological phenomenon. There is also such a thing as species dysphoria, but that of course doesn't make the person experiencing to be a different species, and it doesn't mean we should start referring to people as different species. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying it's imaginary. But if it's just a social construct and has no basis in biology, then there is no objective standard for right and wrong here.

   If you're a dude but for some reason for your entire life everyone has referred to you as a girl and woman, this wouldn't be very fun for you.

Your example doesn't work. If i was born a biological male and was referred to as a girl or woman my entire life, then i would be perfectly fine with it because that's the social construct i'm growing up with. I would feel exactly the same way as i do today where a person is referred to as a boy or a man if their biological sex is male. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If gender is just a social construct, it's perfectly valid for the law to recognize gender to be synonymous with your biological sex.   And you only have to search so far on the internet to come across  many transgendered people who are offended if they are misgendered outside of law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A significant number of transgendered people make at least some form of physical change if they want to be addressed as a different gender to that of their biological sex. But even if that's the case, if it's just a social construct, why did it even matter if people got misgendered?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 13:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gender is entirely based on sex.  Why do transgendered people physically change their body (sex change and hormone therapy) if it's simply a social construct? Why is it a problem if people are misgendered? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 20:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in America and spent time in UK. Muslims in America are commonly lower-middle class citizens, pay their taxes, follow the laws and tolerate people of different faiths and lifestyles (of course, there will always be a few exceptions). I lived in NYC most of my life; the city is very diverse and every ethnic group brings a bit of their own culture and own lifestyle when they come to this country and i don't see how any of this is a problem as long as they follow the laws. That's what makes the city beautiful.  To me, these immigrants have assimilated and integrated just fine. The crimes people often associate with migrants (like rape and theft) are just crimes more commonly done by people living in poverty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victim Forgives Woman Who Smashed Beer Mug In Her Face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 00:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 13:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snopes is a fact-checking website. Even if you disagree with it, you can just check the sources. Or you could have ignored the entire article and read the rest of the points i mentioned and Google what i said for yourself.

And why trust Eva Bartlett? I already pointed out how she says misleading things.  The Syrian government only allows independent journalists who spew their propaganda to go there, or else they will kick them out. https://www.cpj.org/2016/12/swedish-journalist-expelled-from-syria.php.  Because if you haven't realized yet, there is war propaganda being used to tell people that Assad is beating all the evil people and "liberating" the innocent people of Syria (who were actually supporting him all along).  I could show you an independent journalist who visited the rebel side who reports of Bashar's crimes. Would you accept that? probably not.

There are many Syrian people who have left and spoke out against Bashar, there are also family members of Syrians living in other countries who have spoken out. There are also several people who were on Bashar's forces but the deserted the army because they didn't want to kill innocent people. You can read all these accounts and more online.

Kim Jong Un also won with 100% of the vote, That doesn't mean it was a fair election. It takes common-sense to realize that you cannot have a fair election when there is a civil war going on, and you only count votes from particular regions that support Assad that the government has control over.

 You need to cite your source for the claim that "much of the country hated him".

Google it for yourself. If i cite any source, you'll likely just reject that too. I mean you rejected a fact-checking website, so i don't know what you accept.  There were mass protests against Assad in 2011-2012. One protest in particular, in April 2011 in Homs had ~100,000 people.  Many of Bashar's followers are Alawites (religion), and they were the minority in Syria. Most of those who opposed Bashar were Sunni Muslims and they made up [almost 75% of Syria.](http://www.state.gov/j/drl/rls/irf/2006/71432.htm)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 02:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The name of the journalist is Eva Bartlett and [she was refuted by snopes.](http://www.snopes.com/syrian-war-victims-are-being-recycled-and-al-quds-hospital-was-never-bombed/) She's a pro-Assad journalist and was speaking in that video at a pro-Syrian government event.  She is also a contributor at RT, a news site funded by the Russian government. She makes a number of mistakes including her claim of Al-Quds Hospital never being bombed. She also misleadingly states that Assad won democratically. Assad has been president for 16 years straight.  In 2000, Bashar won with 99.7% of the votes. He was the only candidate and Political opposition to the president was not allowed. The 2014 Syrian election could only be held in areas that were pro-Assad due to civil war. Rebel-held areas as well as Kurdish areas and others were deprived of the vote. 88.7% of the people able to vote in 2014 voted for Assad. The second-place finisher was a puppet opposition that fell apart right after the election. You can't really expect to have a fair election in middle of a civil war anyway. Contrary to what you might, much of the country hated him. There were large protests against him during 2011 which Bashar responded to very harshly eventually leading to a civil war.  A common point of criticism Assad/Putin  supporters like her make is that supporting the rebels is supporting terrorists. This is a really weak point because anyone who fights against the Syrian state is a terrorist by definition. No one is calling Bashar and Putin as 'terrorists' because they are state leaders, despite all the deaths they are responsible for. Yes, there is an al-qaeda presence as well, but there are various other groups.  For many of the rebel fighters, this is their first war that they are participating in.  Nearly half million have died, millions more have migrated and [Aleppo right now is under siege.](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/10/22/world/middleeast/syria-aleppo-un.html) These are facts, that some pro-Assad/Putin supporters act like is not even happening.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted the same message, because people keep spamming the same Eva Bartlett clip. We even had the same video about her in r/politicalvideos just 2 days ago. I've seen this clip posted about 10 different times on reddit in the last few days. And you don't have to like Snopes, she has already been refuted many times before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 19:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sources? Snopes is a fact-checking website. You don't have to like Snopes, it still provides the sources for you to check or you can just google for yourself to verify the information. The fact is that she is pro-Assad as she admitted herself, and she was speaking at a pro-Syrian government event in the clip that was posted. She is also a contributor at RT news. I already explained how misleading it is to claim that Bashar won democratically, and how she was wrong about [al-quds hospital not being bombed](http://eaworldview.com/2016/10/syria-feature-russian-bombing-aleppo-al-quds-hospital/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 18:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The name of the journalist is Eva Bartlett and [she was refuted by snopes.](http://www.snopes.com/syrian-war-victims-are-being-recycled-and-al-quds-hospital-was-never-bombed/) She's a pro-Assad journalist and was speaking in that video at a pro-Syrian government event.  She is also a contributor at RT, a news site funded by the Russian government. She makes a number of mistakes including her claim of Al-Quds Hospital never being bombed. She also misleadingly states that Assad won democratically. The 2014 Syrian election could only be held in areas that were pro-Assad due to civil war. Rebel-held areas as well as Kurdish areas and others were deprived of the vote. 88.7% of the people able to vote in 2014 voted for Assad. The second-place finisher was a puppet opposition that fell apart right after the election. You can't really expect to have a fair election in middle of a civil war anyway.  A common point of criticism Assad/Putin  supporters like her make is that supporting the rebels is supporting terrorists. This is a really weak point because anyone who fights against the Syrian state is a terrorist by definition. No one is calling Bashar and Putin as 'terrorists' because they are state leaders, despite all the deaths they are responsible for. Yes, there is an al-qaeda presence as well, but there are various other groups.  For many of the rebel fighters, this is their first war that they are participating in.  Nearly half million have died, millions more have migrated and [Aleppo right now is under siege.](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/10/22/world/middleeast/syria-aleppo-un.html) These are facts, that some pro-Assad/Putin supporters act like is not even happening.

edit: And how many times do we have to keep posting the same video? We had the same video in r/politicalvideos just 2 days ago and i've seen this clip posted about 10 different times on reddit in the last couple of days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 16:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aha! So Hillary did pay you before the Election was over! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 16:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was also  against the revolution at first. But now we are wayy beyond that point. If many of the rebels don't fight now, they will be killed along with many civilians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 07:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was reading [this article recently](http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/aleppo-conflict-syria-war-latest-five-things-you-can-do-to-help-a7472681.html). It depends where you live, you would have to check to see if you can help refugees in your local area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 07:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i don't know what the solution is either, and it all depends on what sources you trust.  If you think American news is bad, take a look at RT news on the Syrian civil war. They aren't just biased, they have a clear agenda where Putin   Assad cannot be blamed for the war despite the deaths of hundreds of thousands. And it makes sense since to Russia to show only one side of the war since they are more involved in this war than any Western country. 

Just want to point out, that woman doesn't represent Canada's view. She's speaking at a pro-Syrian government event. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 07:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The name of the journalist is Eva Bartlett.  [She was refuted by snopes.](http://www.snopes.com/syrian-war-victims-are-being-recycled-and-al-quds-hospital-was-never-bombed/) She's a pro-Assad journalist and was speaking in that video at a pro-Syrian government event.  She is also a contributor at RT, a news site funded by the Russian government. She makes a number of mistakes including her claim of Al Quds Hospital never being bombed. She also misleadingly states that Assad won democratically. The 2014 Syrian election was only held in areas under government control. Rebel-held areas as well as Kurdish areas and others were deprived of the vote. 88.7% of the people able to vote in 2014 voted for Assad. The second-place finisher was a puppet opposition that fell apart right after the election. 

A common point of criticism Assad supporters make is that supporting the rebels is supporting terrorists. This is a really weak point because anyone who fights against the Syrian state can be considered a terrorist by definition. No one is calling Bashar and Putin as 'terrorists' because they are state leaders. Yes, there is an al-qaeda presence as well, but there are various other groups and al-qaeda was never a monolithic group like Isis.  For many of the rebel fighters, this is their first war that they are participating in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 07:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The name of the journalist is Eva Bartlett.  [She was refuted by snopes.](http://www.snopes.com/syrian-war-victims-are-being-recycled-and-al-quds-hospital-was-never-bombed/) She's a pro-Assad journalist and was speaking in that video at a pro-Syrian government event.  She is also a contributor at RT, a news site funded by the Russian government. She makes a number of mistakes including her claim of Al Quds Hospital never being bombed. She also misleadingly states that Assad won democratically. The 2014 Syrian election was only held in areas under government control. Rebel-held areas as well as Kurdish areas and others were deprived of the vote. 88.7% of the people able to vote in 2014 voted for Assad. The second-place finisher was a puppet opposition that fell apart right after the election.  Nearly half a million people have already died, and millions have migrated. As of right now, civilians are dying as Aleppo is being taken over. These are facts. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 03:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be too late to help the people in Allepo, but we can still help the global refugee movement and donate to relief efforts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
